[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.2.2012.322
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: Game of Thrones S06E01
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 衣柜
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 衣柜
Script Updated By: 衣柜
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 720
PlayResY: 404
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Titles,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles_L,Microsoft YaHei,24,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Character_L,Microsoft YaHei,28,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,4,10,10,10,1
Style: Character_B,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Author,Microsoft YaHei,16,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,1,10,10,10,1
Style: QR code - BG,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000019FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,400,400,0,0,1,0,0,5,0,0,0,1
Style: QR code - code,Arial,20,&H00000000,&H000019FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,200,200,0,0,1,0,0,5,0,0,0,1
Style: Titles - 1,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,5,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles - 2,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles - 3 -,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H0001031B,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000429,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Subtitle,Microsoft YaHei,26,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.40,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\bord0\shad0\fscx89\fscy89\p1\move(298,257,298,257,120,1400)}m -11 -35 l -11 39 l 63 39 l 63 -35{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.40,Titles - 2,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\move(340,280,340,280,300,1400)\p1\fscx40\fscy40}m -86 -116 b -89 -117 -89 -117 -95 -119 l -97 -115 l -85 -105 l -116 -102 b -116 -100 -116 -98 -116 -97 l -108 -91 l -96 -91 l -116 -63 l -105 -69 l -96 -47 l -74 -63 l -77 -69 l -91 -63 l -91 -77 l -88 -80 l -66 -49 l -46 -63 l -58 -66 l -66 -74 l -49 -80 l -60 -91 l -74 -83 l -80 -91 l -77 -94 l -46 -94 l -52 -108 l -71 -105 b -69 -107 -67 -110 -66 -113 m -31 -119.875 l -33 -119 b -34 -113 -36 -107 -38 -102 l -46 -97 b -42 -93 -38 -89 -35 -85 l -44 -63 b -41 -64 -38 -65 -35 -66 l -35 -52 l -33 -47 l -27 -55 l -27 -69 l -21 -63 l -21 -69 l -19 -72 l -27 -88 l -21 -94 l -21 -99 l -27 -102 l -27 -102 l -30 -116 m -21 -113 l -21 -105 l -21 -99 l -21 -94 l -19 -85 l -19 -66 l -21 -49 l -19 -47 l -7 -52 l 26 -52 l 18 -66 l -7 -63 l -5 -69 l 6 -69 l 18 -69 l 20 -99 l -7 -94 l -7 -83 l 6 -85 l 6 -80 l -7 -77 l -7 -94 l -10 -99 l 23 -102 l 18 -116 l -10 -110 l -19 -116 m -105 -38 l -116 -41 l -110 -13 l -102 -19 l -102 -30 l -63 -33 l -55 -19 l -46 -41 l -49 -44 m -88 -33 l -91 -24 l -99 -24 l -105 -16 l -102 -13 l -85 -16 l -85 -10 l -94 -8 l -85 -16 l -102 -13 l -108 1 l -88 1 l -88 4 l -116 6 l -116 9 l -110 15 l -88 15 l -85 26 l -77 23 l -74 15 l -52 15 l -49 15 l -52 4 l -74 6 l -71 1 l -55 -2 l -60 -13 l -74 -10 l -74 -13 l -55 -16 l -63 -24 l -74 -24 l -80 -33 m -46 -41 l -38 -2 l -41 23 l -38 26 l 1 20 l 15 26 l 18 23 l 18 -8 l 20 -41 l 20 -44 l -24 -38 l -35 -41 l -35 -30 l -13 -30 l -19 -21 l -33 -19 l -33 -13 l -21 -13 l -33 6 l -33 15 l -13 -5 l -13 1 l -21 6 l -13 12 l -2 9 l -2 -8 l 9 -10 l 12 -19 l 1 -21 l -2 -27 l 9 -33 l 6 -16 l 6 -10 l 9 12 l -2 9 l -30 12 l -30 12 l -27 -2 l -27 -2 l -30 -16 l -27 -21 l -35 -41 m -126 -127 l -130 -130 l -129 38 l 34 37 l 35 -135 l -130 -131 l -127 -127 l 30 -129 l 31 32 l -124 34
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.40,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(386,224.2)\fad(1000,500)\b0\fs18\bord1} 最专业冰火字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.40,Titles - 1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(384,165.2)\fad(1000,500)}\N{\fs32.001\c&HFFFFFF&\b1}诚意奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.40,Titles - 1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(385,197.2)\fad(1000,500)\b000}专注GOT剧集{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.54,0:00:14.04,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(393.25,200.022)\fad(300,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}艾莉亚的缝衣针
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.09,0:00:16.04,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.875,313.122)\fad(500,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}美羽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.64,0:00:18.54,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(437.875,113.367)\fad(500,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}SaintHS
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.99,0:00:28.99,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(376.708,334.159)\fad(500,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}依依Eva
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.09,0:00:31.24,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(81.209,112.666)\fad(500,500)}校对{\fs24} {\b1}兮迩CeCe
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.64,0:00:33.64,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(438.417,107.016)\fad(500,500)}校对{\fs24} {\b1}北落师门
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.94,0:00:39.94,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(439.125,127.792)\fad(500,500)}后期{\fs24} {\b1}SerGawen@huiji.wiki
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.34,0:00:47.34,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(154,140.961)\fad(500,500)}监制{\fs24} {\b1}临冬城的狮子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.04,0:00:49.64,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(118.792,279.97)\fad(500,500)}监制{\fs24} {\b1}北落师门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.19,0:01:08.89,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(78.917,112.893)\fad(500,500)}策划{\fs24} {\b1}衣柜军团
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.14,0:01:18.14,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(120.792,141.05)\fad(500,500)}特别顾问{\fs24} {\b1}屈畅(ccxx)@史诗图书
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:23.70,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\t(\fscx150\fscy150,150)\p1\move(277,278,289,305,1,4381)}m -15 -18 l -15 -17 l -14 -16 l -13 -16 l -11 -15 l -6 -16 b -8 -15 -8 -15 -11 -13 l -14 -9 l -12 -9 l -10 -8 l -5 -9 b -4 -8 -2 -6 6 -7 l 7 -7 l 3 -8 l 1 -10 b 2 -14 5 -17 3 -19 l 2 -21 l 5 -21 l 3 -22 l 0 -23 l 0 -24 l 4 -26 l 8 -23 l 16 -21 b 20 -23 25 -24 28 -36 l 27 -35 b 26 -35 26 -35 22 -37 b 25 -34 25 -32 24 -32 l 17 -34 l 23 -30 b 22 -29 20 -27 19 -29 l 14 -33 b 15 -31 17 -29 16 -26 b 13 -25 11 -24 7 -27 l 11 -31 l 10 -36 b 10 -32 11 -32 8 -30 b 7 -30 5 -29 4 -29 b 3 -30 2 -31 0 -34 l 3 -28 l -1 -27 l -5 -30 l -7 -34 l -6 -30 l -3 -27 l -8 -28 l -15 -32 l -10 -27 l -6 -25 l -4 -25 l -7 -23 l -10 -21 l -3 -21 l -5 -20 l -7 -21 l -7 -22 l -8 -22 l -13 -19{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:23.70,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\pos(301.714,255.889)\fad(300,500)\frx360\t(20,200,\frx0)\fs25\b1}君临{\fs12\b0} King's Landing
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.35,0:00:27.77,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\move(420,300,420,280)\fs25\p1}m -17 -23 l -10 -8 l -19 -15 l -12 -1 l -24 -9 l -14 6 l -25 1 l -16 9 l -13 17 l -15 24 l 18 24 l 13 19 l 15 12 l 22 4 l 13 10 l 25 -3 l 20 0 l 14 3 l 17 -3 l 22 -11 l 13 -4 l 18 -21 l 13 -15 l 10 -13 l 11 -26 l 7 -16 l 7 -28 l 3 -16 l 0 -32 l -2 -15 l -6 -22 l -8 -28 l -8 -11{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.35,0:00:27.77,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(380,230,380,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}红堡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.35,0:00:27.77,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(425,250,425,235)\fad(300,500)\fs12\b0} Red Keep
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.05,0:00:38.24,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\pos(325,216)\clip(290,90,350,130)\t(0.1,3550,\clip(250,130,340,200))\p1\fscx95\fscy95}m -22 -17.5 l -16 -11.375 l -6 -3.125 l 0 -3.125 l -2 -7.25 l -1 -12.375 l 4 -12.375 l 5 -7.25 l 3 -3.125 l 10 -4.125 l 18 -11.375 l 22 -14.375 l 32 -22.625 l 33 -23.75 l 26 -15.5 l 18 -8.25 l 12 -1 l 7 7.25 l 7 15.5 l 9 22.625 l 15 33 l 16 36.125 l 25 51.5 l 24 52.5 l 13 38.125 l 10 34 l 3 25.75 l 0 25.75 l -17 53.625 l -18 51.5 l -16 47.375 l -9 32 l -8 27.875 l -4 14.375 l -5 6.125 l -8 2 l -16 -8.25 l -23 -16.5 l -28 -22.625{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.05,0:00:38.24,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(334.667,176.333)\fad(1000,1000)\frx25\fs28\b1\frz-22\t(0,1800,\frz-0)}临冬城{\fs12\b0}\NWinterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.63,0:01:26.10,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\move(388,290,408,290)\p1\fscx100\fscy100}m -27 -19 l -25 -22 l -12 -27 l -4 -7 l -2 -9 l -2 -14 l -4 -18 l -2 -17 l 0 -21 l 2 -17 l 5 -19 l 3 -14 l 3 -9 l 5 -8 l 12 -27 l 25 -23 l 27 -20 l 16 -16 l 12 1 l 5 4 l 5 5 l 10 0 l 13 5 l 7 9 l 10 14 l -8 14 l -6 9 l -11 5 l -9 0 l -3 5 l -3 4 l -12 2 l -16 -16{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.63,0:01:26.10,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(338,265)\fad(1250,1000)\frx50\t(1200,2500,\frx0)\fs28} {\b1}弥林\N{\fs12\b0}Meereen
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.86,0:01:05.54,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\pos(337.5,157.549)\fad(500,500)\fs12.746} 联合出品
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.86,0:01:05.54,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\fad(500,500)\fs24} 史诗图书 | 冰火中文维基 | 黑城堡奇幻微刊\N\N\N{\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.86,0:01:05.54,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\pos(337.5,212.563)\fad(500,500)\fs14.997} Epic Books         ASOIAF.huiji.wiki          Heichengbao\N{\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.54,0:01:20.54,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(486.25,119.545)\fad(500,500)} {\fs24\b1} 史诗图书 {\fs18\b0} 正统奇幻的圣殿
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.56,0:00:57.40,Titles,,0,30,200,,{\fad(100,50)\frx75\t(0,3500,\frx-0)\fs28} {\b1}绝境长城{\fs12\b0} the Wall
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.47,0:01:16.05,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\pos(430,320)\fs25\p1\fscx250\fscy250}m 0 -13 l -2 -14 l -4 -13 l -4 -11 l -3 -9 l -3 -9 l -5 -9 l -7 -7 l -7 -20 l -7 -16 l -7 -7 l -9 -5 l -9 -4 l -7 -5 l -7 10 l -7 1 l -7 -5 l -7 -5 l -5 -6 l -5 -1 l -7 2 l -6 3 l -7 6 l -8 10 l -7 10 l -5 5 l -3 3 l -1 3 l 1 5 l 3 10 l 4 10 l 2 3 l 3 2 l 1 -1 l 1 -6 l 1 -5 l 2 -1 l 4 1 l 6 -1 l 7 -6 l 6 -8 l 3 -9 l 2 -8 l 1 -9 l -1 -9 l -1 -9 l 0 -11{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.26,0:01:16.05,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\pos(392,255.559)\fs25\p1\fscx220\fscy220\frz-0\t(0,1000,\frz-18)}m -6 -5 l -5 -4 l -2 0 l -4 2 l -3 3 l -1 1 l 1 3 l 2 2 l 0 0 l 1 -1 l 0 -2 l -1 -1 l -6 -7{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.47,0:01:16.05,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(355,250,370,250)\fs28\b1}布拉佛斯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.47,0:01:16.05,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(365,260,355,260)\fad(100,1000)\fs12\b0} Braavos
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.09,0:01:41.48,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\pos(447.75,233.422)\p1\fscx80\fscy80}m -7 -20 l -7 -20 l -6 -23 l -8 -28 l -8 -31 l -6 -30 l -3 -27 l -2 -21 l 1 -24 l 0 -28 l 0 -32 l 1 -30 l 4 -28 l 4 -25 l 4 -22 l 6 -25 l 6 -28 l 8 -31 l 9 -27 l 10 -24 l 9 -20 l 12 -23 l 15 -29 l 16 -24 l 13 -18 l 17 -20 l 21 -25 l 21 -18 l 17 -14 l 21 -16 l 26 -19 l 25 -13 l 20 -9 l 25 -10 l 30 -12 l 27 -7 l 22 -5 l 27 -4 l 32 -6 l 29 -2 l 27 0 l 23 0 l 26 1 l 32 1 l 29 5 l 22 5 l 26 8 l 32 9 l 27 11 l 21 10 l 24 13 l 30 15 l 24 17 l 19 15 l 21 19 l 26 22 l 21 23 l 13 18 l 6 8 l 10 6 l 3 7 l 18 23 l 34 40 l 32 42 l 18 27 l 14 25 l 11 20 l 0 9 l -2 18 l 1 12 l 11 20 l 11 26 l 15 32 l 10 29 l 6 24 l 6 28 l 7 32 l 7 34 l 2 29 l 1 25 l -2 29 l 0 33 l -2 35 l -5 29 l -4 25 l -7 28 l -8 34 l -11 29 l -9 23 l -13 25 l -15 31 l -16 27 l -14 21 l -17 22 l -19 26 l -21 27 l -21 21 l -18 17 l -21 17 l -24 21 l -26 22 l -25 18 l -21 13 l -24 13 l -27 15 l -30 16 l -28 12 l -23 8 l -26 7 l -29 8 l -33 9 l -30 5 l -24 3 l -26 1 l -30 2 l -33 2 l -29 -2 l -24 -2 l -27 -5 l -30 -4 l -32 -6 l -28 -8 l -23 -8 l -24 -10 l -28 -11 l -31 -13 l -27 -13 l -25 -14 l -20 -12 l -22 -16 l -25 -16 l -27 -19 l -24 -19 l -20 -19 l -29 -29 l -34 -30 l -40 -43 l -41 -46 l -28 -36 l -27 -30 l -18 -20 l -21 -24 l -18 -23 l -12 -21 l -12 -18 l -11 -14 l -12 -3 b -13 2 -4 1 -3 -3 l -3 -4 l 4 -5 l 4 -4 b 0 0 17 1 12 -4 l 12 -4 b 12 -4 8 -5 3 -4 b 2 -3 -5 -6 -15 -2 l -11 -22 l -14 -25 l -14 -29 l -11 -26 l -8 -25
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.09,0:01:41.48,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(374,186.001)\fad(300,1000)\frx90\t(0,3500,\frx-0)\fs30} {\b1}多恩{\fs12\b0} Dorne
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.49,0:01:00.82,Titles,,0,0,100,,{\fs25\c&HC1DFED&} {\b0} 最专业的华语冰火资料站：        冰与火之歌{\b0\fs20}中文维基{\b0}\N\N{\fs20\c&HFFFFFF&}http://asoiaf.huiji.wiki
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.49,0:01:00.82,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(410,285)\fs25\c&HC1DFED&} {\b1\p1\fscx60\fscy60}m 31 -6 l -21 40 l 34 22 m 29 -8 l -3 -12 l -24 40{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.14,0:01:39.34,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(461,310)\fad(500,500)\fs14} {\c&HC1DFED&}根据长篇小说
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.14,0:01:39.34,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(552,334)\fad(500,500)} {\fs24}《{\b1}冰与火之歌{\b0}》{\fs14} 改编
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.14,0:01:39.34,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(627,358)\fad(500,500)} {\fs14} 原著 {\fs20} 乔治·R·R·马丁
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.36,0:01:49.67,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(350,294)\fad(300,500)\fs56.267\fn宋体\b1}权力的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.36,0:01:49.67,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(349,322)\fad(300,500)\c&HFFFFFF&\b1\fs22}衣柜字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.74,0:01:55.30,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(428,118.44)\fad(500,500)\p1}m -18.625 0 l -18.625 0 l 281.25 0 l 281.25 1.125 l -18.625 1.125{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.74,0:01:55.30,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\pos(231.125,202.841)\p1\fscx35\fscy35}m -86 -116 b -89 -117 -89 -117 -95 -119 l -97 -115 l -85 -105 l -116 -102 b -116 -100 -116 -98 -116 -97 l -108 -91 l -96 -91 l -116 -63 l -105 -69 l -96 -47 l -74 -63 l -77 -69 l -91 -63 l -91 -77 l -88 -80 l -66 -49 l -46 -63 l -58 -66 l -66 -74 l -49 -80 l -60 -91 l -74 -83 l -80 -91 l -77 -94 l -46 -94 l -52 -108 l -71 -105 b -69 -107 -67 -110 -66 -113 m -31 -119.875 l -33 -119 b -34 -113 -36 -107 -38 -102 l -46 -97 b -42 -93 -38 -89 -35 -85 l -44 -63 b -41 -64 -38 -65 -35 -66 l -35 -52 l -33 -47 l -27 -55 l -27 -69 l -21 -63 l -21 -69 l -19 -72 l -27 -88 l -21 -94 l -21 -99 l -27 -102 l -27 -102 l -30 -116 m -21 -113 l -21 -105 l -21 -99 l -21 -94 l -19 -85 l -19 -66 l -21 -49 l -19 -47 l -7 -52 l 26 -52 l 18 -66 l -7 -63 l -5 -69 l 6 -69 l 18 -69 l 20 -99 l -7 -94 l -7 -83 l 6 -85 l 6 -80 l -7 -77 l -7 -94 l -10 -99 l 23 -102 l 18 -116 l -10 -110 l -19 -116 m -105 -38 l -116 -41 l -110 -13 l -102 -19 l -102 -30 l -63 -33 l -55 -19 l -46 -41 l -49 -44 m -88 -33 l -91 -24 l -99 -24 l -105 -16 l -102 -13 l -85 -16 l -85 -10 l -94 -8 l -85 -16 l -102 -13 l -108 1 l -88 1 l -88 4 l -116 6 l -116 9 l -110 15 l -88 15 l -85 26 l -77 23 l -74 15 l -52 15 l -49 15 l -52 4 l -74 6 l -71 1 l -55 -2 l -60 -13 l -74 -10 l -74 -13 l -55 -16 l -63 -24 l -74 -24 l -80 -33 m -46 -41 l -38 -2 l -41 23 l -38 26 l 1 20 l 15 26 l 18 23 l 18 -8 l 20 -41 l 20 -44 l -24 -38 l -35 -41 l -35 -30 l -13 -30 l -19 -21 l -33 -19 l -33 -13 l -21 -13 l -33 6 l -33 15 l -13 -5 l -13 1 l -21 6 l -13 12 l -2 9 l -2 -8 l 9 -10 l 12 -19 l 1 -21 l -2 -27 l 9 -33 l 6 -16 l 6 -10 l 9 12 l -2 9 l -30 12 l -30 12 l -27 -2 l -27 -2 l -30 -16 l -27 -21 l -35 -41 m -126 -127 l -130 -130 l -129 38 l 34 37 l 35 -135 l -130 -131 l -127 -127 l 30 -129 l 31 32 l -124 34{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.74,0:01:55.30,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(293,112.813)\fad(500,500)\b1}协力制作
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.74,0:01:55.30,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(293,157.827)\fad(500,500)}史诗图书\N{\fs16}Epic Books
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.74,0:01:55.30,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(405.5,157.827)\fad(500,500)}冰火中文维基\N{\fs16}ASOIAF.HuiJi.WiKi
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.74,0:01:55.30,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(518,157.827)\fad(500,500)}黑城堡\N{\fs16}EPICASTLE
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.64,0:01:55.24,Titles_L,,260,0,163,,{\pos(310,300)\fad(500,500)\fs16\b0}第一集
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.64,0:01:55.24,Titles_L,,300,0,132,,{\pos(310,340)\fad(500,500)}红袍祭司\N{\fs16\b0}The Red Woman
Dialogue: 0,0:48:40.79,0:49:56.04,Titles,,0,0,20,,{\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(360,390)}衣柜字幕组出品
Dialogue: 0,0:48:40.79,0:49:56.04,Titles,,0,0,40,,{\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(357,372)}本集关键字：{\c&H5650F3\b0}梅丽珊卓   亚梭尔·亚亥  艾拉莉亚·沙德
Dialogue: 0,0:48:40.79,0:49:56.04,Titles,,0,0,335,,{\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(360,40)}剧情没看懂？ 典故不清楚？{\b0}\N维基新站网址：{\c&H00FF40}HTTP://AsoIaF.HuiJi.WiKi
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.54,0:02:41.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(498,262)\fad(300,500)}琼恩·雪诺
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.54,0:03:00.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(498,262)\fad(300,500)}白灵\N{\b0\fs12}雪诺的冰原狼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.54,0:03:04.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(385,262)\fad(300,500)}戴佛斯·席渥斯\N{\b0\fs12}“洋葱骑士”
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.54,0:03:46.34,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(453,206)\fad(300,500)\fs28}叛徒
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.54,0:03:51.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(489,184)\fad(300,500)}忧郁的艾迪\N{\b0\fs12}守夜人事务官
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.54,0:05:30.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(619,220)\fad(300,500)}梅丽珊卓\N{\b0\fs12}红袍祭司
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.54,0:06:36.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(613,247)\fad(300,500)}艾里沙·索恩\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.54,0:06:48.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(81,211)\fad(300,500)}奥利\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.84,0:09:48.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(581,248)\fad(300,500)}米兰达\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.04,0:09:55.04,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(388,200)\fad(300500)}拉姆斯·波顿\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.84,0:11:12.84,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(115,247)\fad(300500)}卢斯·波顿\N{\b0\fs12}北境守护
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.54,0:13:04.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(228,274)\fad(300,500)}珊莎·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.24,0:13:10.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(68,254)\fad(300,500)}“臭佬”\N{\b0\fs12}席恩·葛雷乔伊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.74,0:17:41.74,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(305,267)\fad(300,500)}塔斯的布蕾妮\N{\b0\fs12}“美人”
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.14,0:17:42.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(68,272)\fad(300,500)}波德瑞克·派恩\N{\b0\fs12}侍从
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.34,0:19:39.34,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(619,275)\fad(300,300)}瑟曦·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}太后
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.54,0:20:46.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(529,265)\fad(300,500)}詹姆·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.54,0:23:53.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(197,274)\fad(300,500)}玛格丽·提利尔\N{\b0\fs12}王后
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.54,0:24:14.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(388,304)\fad(300,500)}大麻雀\N{\b0\fs12}总主教
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.54,0:25:45.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(235,254)\fad(300,500)}艾拉莉亚·沙德\N{\b0\fs12}红毒蛇的情妇
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.54,0:25:45.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(516,254)\fad(300,500)}道朗·马泰尔\N{\b0\fs12}多恩亲王
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.54,0:26:34.04,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(63,312)\fad(300,500)}特蕾妮·沙德\N{\b0\fs12}“沙蛇”
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.54,0:28:09.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(457,312)\fad(300,500)}崔斯丹·马泰尔\N{\b0\fs12}道朗之子
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.54,0:26:34.04,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(457,279)\fad(300,500)}阿利欧·何塔\N{\b0\fs12}道朗的护卫队长
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.54,0:28:11.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(636,209)\fad(300,500)}娜梅莉亚·沙德\N{\b0\fs12}红毒蛇的私生女
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.54,0:28:11.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(247,154)\fad(300,500)}奥芭娅·沙德\N{\b0\fs12}红毒蛇的私生女
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.04,0:33:10.04,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(370,216)\fad(300500)}达里奥·纳哈里斯\N{\b0\fs12}\N丹妮莉丝的情人
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.54,0:29:11.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(85,296)\fad(300,500)}提利昂·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}“小恶魔”
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.54,0:29:11.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(423,296)\fad(300,500)}瓦里斯\N{\b0\fs12}“八爪蜘蛛”
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.54,0:32:59.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(438,214)\fad(300,500)}乔拉·莫尔蒙\N{\b0\fs12}“大熊”
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.54,0:41:49.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(475,184)\fad(300,500)}“无名之辈”\N{\b0\fs12}艾莉亚·史塔克
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.54,0:35:54.84,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(104,367)\fad(300,500)}丹妮莉丝·坦格利安\N{\b0\fs12}弥林的女王
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.54,0:37:51.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(508,241)\fad(300500)}摩洛卡奥\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.54,0:30:21.84,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(506,298)\bord0\frz-5\fry-30\fay-0.1\b0\c&000}弥莎就是伟主
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.54,0:30:21.84,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(506,236)\shad\bord0\frz20\fry-30\fay-0.1\b0\c&H3647E3&}杀死伟主
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.17,0:03:31.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,院子里面有动静\N{\fs16}It's coming from the courtyard.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.48,0:03:38.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是总司令大人！\N{\fs16}It's the Lord Commander!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.08,0:03:53.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,帮我把他抬进去\N{\fs16}Help me get him inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.92,0:04:51.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是索恩干的\N{\fs16}Thorne did this.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.34,0:04:58.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你有多少能信任的兄弟？\N{\fs16}How many of your brothers do you think you can trust?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.64,0:05:00.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,信任？\N{\fs16}Trust?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.48,0:05:04.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,都在这间屋子里了\N{\fs16}The men in this room.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.07,0:05:08.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,狼认识你吗？\N{\fs16}Does the wolf know you?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.77,0:05:10.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们需要一切帮助\N{\fs16}We need all the help we can get.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.28,0:05:19.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,戴佛斯爵士\N{\fs16}Ser Davos.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.62,0:06:03.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我在火焰中看到他了\N{\fs16}I saw him in the flames
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.13,0:06:06.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他在临冬城战斗\N{\fs16}fighting at Winterfell.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.25,0:06:12.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我解读不了火焰……\N{\fs16}I can't speak for the flames...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.34,0:06:16.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但他死了\N{\fs16}but he's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.32,0:06:38.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他是我们的总司令\N{\fs16}He was our Lord Commander.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.11,0:06:39.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,本来就不应该选他\N{\fs16}He never should have been!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.58,0:06:45.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们都知道为什么聚集在这里\N{\fs16}You all know why you're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.87,0:06:51.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,琼恩·雪诺死了\N{\fs16}Jon Snow is dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.54,0:06:52.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谁杀死他的？\N{\fs16}Who killed him?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.96,0:06:55.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是我\N{\fs16}I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.76,0:06:58.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有波文·马尔锡和奥赛尔·亚威克\N{\fs16}And Bowen Marsh and Othell Yarwyck
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.13,0:07:00.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,以及这座城堡里的其他军官\N{\fs16}and the other officers in this castle.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.55,0:07:02.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 凶手！ - 叛徒！\N{\fs16}- Murderers!  - Traitors!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.05,0:07:08.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们说对了！\N{\fs16}You're right!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.39,0:07:10.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们都是叛徒\N{\fs16}We've committed treason, all of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.73,0:07:13.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,琼恩·雪诺是我的总司令\N{\fs16}Jon Snow was my Lord Commander.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.98,0:07:16.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我对他没什么好感\N{\fs16}I had no love for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.73,0:07:19.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这也不是秘密了\N{\fs16}That was no secret.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.20,0:07:23.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我从未违抗过命令\N{\fs16}But I never once disobeyed an order.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.49,0:07:25.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,忠诚\N{\fs16}Loyalty is the foundation
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.04,0:07:28.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是守夜人的基石\N{\fs16}on which the Night's Watch is built.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.13,0:07:30.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,守夜人就是我的一切\N{\fs16}And the Watch means everything to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.58,0:07:32.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我献出了生命\N{\fs16}I have given my life,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.63,0:07:36.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们都向守夜人军团献出了自己的生命\N{\fs16}we have all given our lives to the Night's Watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.14,0:07:43.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,琼恩·雪诺准备毁了守夜人军团\N{\fs16}Jon Snow was going to destroy the Night's Watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.76,0:07:46.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他让野人通过我们的大门\N{\fs16}He let the wildlings through our gates
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.43,0:07:49.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,之前从来没有总司令这么干过\N{\fs16}as no Lord Commander has ever done before.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.98,0:07:54.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,反倒把那些饱受他们摧残的土地\N{\fs16}He gave them the very land on which they reaved
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.85,0:07:58.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,给予了他们\N{\fs16}and raped and murdered.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.74,0:08:02.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,雪诺总司令做了他认为对的事情\N{\fs16}Lord Commander Snow did what he thought was right,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.03,0:08:05.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对此我不怀疑\N{\fs16}I've no doubt about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.08,0:08:10.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他认为对的事情可能会害死我们\N{\fs16}And what he thought was right would have been the end of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.34,0:08:13.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是他逼我们做出这个糟糕的决定\N{\fs16}He thrust a terrible choice upon us.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.71,0:08:16.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,于是我们杀了他\N{\fs16}And we made it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.55,0:08:30.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他知道我们没有去\N{\fs16}He'll have seen we didn't come.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.89,0:08:32.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,索恩这会儿应该已经宣布\N{\fs16}Thorne will have made it official by now.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.11,0:08:34.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,黑城堡是他的了\N{\fs16}Castle Black is his.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.64,0:08:37.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不在乎谁坐在那个位子上\N{\fs16}I don't care who's sitting at the high table.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.90,0:08:39.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,琼恩是我的朋友\N{\fs16}Jon was my friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.61,0:08:42.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而这些混蛋残杀了他\N{\fs16}And those fuckers butchered him.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.87,0:08:45.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们要有仇报仇\N{\fs16}Now we return the favor.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.40,0:08:46.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们人手不够\N{\fs16}We don't have the numbers.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.96,0:08:48.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 我们有冰原狼 - 不够\N{\fs16}- We have a direwolf. - It's not enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.99,0:08:50.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我认识雪诺总司令的时间不长\N{\fs16}I didn't know Lord Commander Snow for long,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.08,0:08:54.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我相信他不会让朋友们白白送命\N{\fs16}but I have to believe he wouldn't have wanted his friends to die for nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.38,0:08:58.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果你想活到明天 你就来错地方了\N{\fs16}If you were planning to see tomorrow, you picked the wrong room.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.00,0:09:01.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,今天我们都会死\N{\fs16}We all die today.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.30,0:09:03.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,要死 也拉着索恩垫背\N{\fs16}I say we do our best to take Thorne with us when we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.06,0:09:07.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们要去战斗 但不是送死\N{\fs16}We need to fight, but we don't need to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.56,0:09:09.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 只要有人帮我们- 谁会帮我们？\N{\fs16}- Not if we have help. - Who is gonna help us?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.06,0:09:13.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不是只有你们欠琼恩·雪诺一条命\N{\fs16}You're not the only ones who owe your lives to Jon Snow.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.66,0:09:23.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,把门闩上\N{\fs16}Bolt the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.44,0:09:25.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别让任何人进来\N{\fs16}Don't let anyone in.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.44,0:09:27.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会尽快回来\N{\fs16}I'll be back as soon as I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.54,0:09:40.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,初见她时 她年方十一\N{\fs16}She was 11 the first time I saw her.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.76,0:09:45.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,狗舍总管的女儿\N{\fs16}The kennelmaster's daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.85,0:09:49.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她闻起来和狗一个味儿\N{\fs16}She smelled of dog.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.10,0:09:56.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我比她大不了多少 但大家都已经很怕我了\N{\fs16}I wasn't much older, but everybody was already afraid of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.53,0:10:00.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你当然也怕\N{\fs16}You certainly were.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.98,0:10:07.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但米兰达却不怕\N{\fs16}Myranda wasn't, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.65,0:10:11.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我能对她做的事比那些猎狗能好多少？\N{\fs16}What could I do to her that those hounds couldn't?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.62,0:10:13.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她无畏无惧\N{\fs16}She was fearless.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.57,0:10:16.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没有她做不了的事\N{\fs16}There was nothing she wouldn't do.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.92,0:10:25.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你所受的痛苦将会千倍偿还\N{\fs16}Your pain will be paid for a thousand times over.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.76,0:10:31.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我真希望你能亲眼看到\N{\fs16}I wish you could be here to watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.93,0:10:39.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大人 要为她掘一座坟吗？\N{\fs16}Shall I have a grave dug for her, my lord?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.94,0:10:43.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还是让人为她堆起一座柴火堆？\N{\fs16}Or would you rather the men build a pyre?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.69,0:10:50.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,埋了 烧了？\N{\fs16}Buried, burned?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.11,0:10:52.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是好肉\N{\fs16}This is good meat.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.83,0:10:54.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,拿去喂狗\N{\fs16}Feed it to the hounds.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.28,0:10:59.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你对骑兵的指挥挺不错\N{\fs16}Your command of the cavalry was impressive.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.12,0:11:02.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,正得益你的指挥 伪王史坦尼斯·拜拉席恩死了\N{\fs16}Thanks to you, the false king Stannis Baratheon is dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.12,0:11:04.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你知道谁完成了致命一击吗\N{\fs16}Do you know who struck the killing blow?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.84,0:11:06.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 不知道- 可惜\N{\fs16}- No. - A shame.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.96,0:11:08.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我本可以嘉奖这个人\N{\fs16}I'd reward the man.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.96,0:11:12.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不管怎么说 这仍是一次伟大的胜利\N{\fs16}Still, a great victory.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.35,0:11:14.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你觉得自己是胜利者吗？\N{\fs16}Do you feel like a victor?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.47,0:11:21.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我跟王室作对\N{\fs16}I rebelled against the crown
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.48,0:11:23.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,安排了你和珊莎·史塔克的婚事\N{\fs16}to arrange your marriage to Sansa Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.64,0:11:26.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你觉得夜袭敌人的马车\N{\fs16}Do you think that burning wagons in the night
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.28,0:11:28.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,杀死疲劳 已经没多少人的拜拉席恩军队\N{\fs16}and mowing down tired, outnumbered Baratheons
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.62,0:11:31.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,和面对有备而来 供给充足的兰尼斯特军队是一回事吗？\N{\fs16}is the same as facing a prepared and provisioned Lannister army?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.07,0:11:36.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不是\N{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.29,0:11:39.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,清算之日早晚会到来\N{\fs16}A reckoning will come.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.13,0:11:41.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们需要北境的支持\N{\fs16}We need the North to face it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.83,0:11:43.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,整个北境\N{\fs16}The entire North.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.80,0:11:47.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没了珊莎·史塔克 他们不会支持我们\N{\fs16}They won't back us without Sansa Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.34,0:11:50.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为我们手上没有珊莎·史塔克\N{\fs16}We no longer have Sansa Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.84,0:11:53.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你和她玩你那些游戏\N{\fs16}You played your games with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.17,0:11:56.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你和铁群岛的继承人玩你那些游戏 现在他俩都跑了\N{\fs16}You played your games with the heir to the Iron Islands and now they're both gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.76,0:11:59.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我已经派人去追他们了 还派出了我最好的猎狗\N{\fs16}I have a team of men after them with some of my best hounds.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.76,0:12:01.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们走不远的\N{\fs16}They won't get far.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.40,0:12:03.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,听你这么说我很高兴\N{\fs16}I'm glad to hear it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.52,0:12:06.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没了珊莎 你就没法生出继承人了\N{\fs16}Without Sansa, you won't be able to produce an heir.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.90,0:12:09.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没了继承人 那……\N{\fs16}And without an heir, well...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.91,0:12:15.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,希望学士们是对的\N{\fs16}let's hope the maesters are right
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.25,0:12:17.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,希望瓦妲夫人确实怀了个男孩\N{\fs16}and Lady Walda's carrying a boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.55,0:12:39.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别停下\N{\fs16}We can't stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.24,0:12:59.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们得过去\N{\fs16}We have to cross here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.74,0:13:05.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 我不行 - 只有这样才能甩掉猎狗\N{\fs16}- I can't. - It's the only way to throw off the hounds.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.41,0:13:07.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,可太冷了 我不能 我过不去 我会死的\N{\fs16}But it's too cold. I can't. I won't make it. I'll die.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.08,0:13:10.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我见过他的猎狗是怎么对付人的\N{\fs16}I've seen what his hounds do to a person.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.67,0:13:12.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,冻死要比那好多了\N{\fs16}This way is better.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.87,0:13:47.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这边 来\N{\fs16}Over here. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.69,0:14:04.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,珊莎\N{\fs16}Sansa.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.44,0:14:07.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,珊莎\N{\fs16}Sansa.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.50,0:14:30.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让他们安生一点\N{\fs16}Tell them to settle down!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.38,0:14:31.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,呆在这儿 我去把他们引开\N{\fs16}Stay here. I'll lure them away.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.72,0:14:33.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果没有你我肯定逃不掉的\N{\fs16}No, I won't make it without you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.97,0:14:35.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不会的\N{\fs16}You will.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.75,0:14:38.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,往北边逃 一直向北\N{\fs16}Go north, only north.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.09,0:14:39.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,琼恩是黑城堡总司令\N{\fs16}Jon is Lord Commander at Castle Black.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.01,0:14:41.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他能帮你\N{\fs16}He'll help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.94,0:14:53.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那边有人么？\N{\fs16}See somebody, eh?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.52,0:14:56.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-他们在那里！ -抓住他们！\N{\fs16}- There they are! - Get them!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.19,0:15:02.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,波顿夫人在哪儿？\N{\fs16}Where is Lady Bolton?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.36,0:15:05.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-她死了 -你说谎\N{\fs16}- Dead. - Liar.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.17,0:15:08.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她从城墙上跳了下来 摔断了腿\N{\fs16}She broke her leg jumping from the ramparts.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.45,0:15:10.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我把她丢到雪地里自生自灭了\N{\fs16}I left her to die in the snow.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.54,0:15:17.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-它们闻到了什么! –过去看看\N{\fs16}Got something! Run!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.01,0:15:21.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,呼\N{\fs16}Hyah!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.47,0:15:31.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,停下 站住\N{\fs16}Resist. Stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.06,0:15:36.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,站住\N{\fs16}Stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.20,0:15:40.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我很期待拉姆斯这次会切你的什么部位\N{\fs16}I can't wait to see what parts Ramsay cuts off you this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.13,0:15:51.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,骑兵！去看看那是谁？\N{\fs16}Rider! Who is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.16,0:15:53.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是个臭婊子\N{\fs16}It's a bloody woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.98,0:17:03.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别 求你了\N{\fs16}No! Please!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.00,0:17:59.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,珊莎小姐 我将再次为你而战\N{\fs16}Lady Sansa, I offer my services once again.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.04,0:18:03.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会保护您的安全 听从您的指示\N{\fs16}I will shield your back and keep your counsel
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.29,0:18:05.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如有必要 我愿奉献我的生命\N{\fs16}and give my life for yours if need be.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.05,0:18:09.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,以新旧诸神之名 我郑重起誓\N{\fs16}I swear it by the old gods and the new.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.23,0:18:21.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我在此发誓\N{\fs16}And I vow...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.81,0:18:26.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你将永远在我的壁炉边占有一席之地\N{\fs16}that you shall always have a place by my hearth
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.37,0:18:28.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你将\N{\fs16}and...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.40,0:18:32.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,同桌喝酒 同餐吃肉\N{\fs16}Meat and mead at my table.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.24,0:18:34.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,和我同桌喝酒 同餐吃肉\N{\fs16}...meat and mead at my table.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.04,0:18:41.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我誓言永不让你的服务\N{\fs16}And I pledge to ask no service of you
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.58,0:18:44.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,蒙上不誉的污名\N{\fs16}that might bring you dishonor.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.17,0:18:47.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,以新旧诸神之名 我郑重起誓\N{\fs16}I swear it by the old gods and the new.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.81,0:18:50.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,起来吧\N{\fs16}Arise.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.64,0:19:39.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,陛下 我无意打扰您\N{\fs16}Your Grace, I'm sorry to disturb you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.19,0:19:41.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,港里停了一艘多恩来的船\N{\fs16}A ship from Dorne has sailed into the harbor.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.11,0:19:44.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,弥赛菈\N{\fs16}Myrcella.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.80,0:21:00.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还记得你见过的第一个死人是谁么?\N{\fs16}Do you remember the first time you saw a dead body?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.31,0:21:03.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们的母亲\N{\fs16}Mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.19,0:21:07.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我现在能够想起来的\N{\fs16}All I could think about when she died
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.03,0:21:10.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就是她死时的模样\N{\fs16}was what would happen to her now.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.82,0:21:16.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,日日夜夜过去\N{\fs16}Every day, every night,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.90,0:21:19.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,妈妈现在是什么样子呢?\N{\fs16}what does Mama look like now?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.63,0:21:23.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她的尸体开始浮肿了么?\N{\fs16}Has she started to bloat?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.41,0:21:27.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她的皮肤变黑了么?\N{\fs16}Has her skin turned black?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.42,0:21:32.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她的嘴唇褪去 露出牙齿了么?\N{\fs16}Have her lips peeled back from her teeth?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.06,0:21:39.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我想象着弥赛菈呆在孤零零的墓穴中\N{\fs16}I think about locking Myrcella in a crypt.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.76,0:21:44.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她美丽的小脸蛋开始腐烂\N{\fs16}I think about her beautiful little face starting to collapse.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.43,0:21:47.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,嘘 别这么想\N{\fs16}Shh, shh. Don't think about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.69,0:21:49.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没法儿不这么想\N{\fs16}I have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.44,0:21:53.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没法让她一个人受苦\N{\fs16}I have to. It's not right she has to suffer alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.66,0:21:56.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她并未受苦 她已经去了\N{\fs16}She's not suffering. She's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.99,0:21:59.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没有人能够再伤害她了\N{\fs16}No one can hurt her anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.45,0:22:03.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她那么善良\N{\fs16}She was good.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.59,0:22:07.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,从降生那天起 她就那么甜美可爱\N{\fs16}From her first breath, she was so sweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.29,0:22:11.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不知道这点她继承了谁\N{\fs16}I don't know where she came from.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.29,0:22:16.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她一点都不像我\N{\fs16}She was nothing like me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.38,0:22:18.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不冷漠刻薄 不心怀嫉妒 只有善良\N{\fs16}No meanness, no jealousy, just good.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.97,0:22:20.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\fs16}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.72,0:22:24.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我想 如果我能培养出如此善良\N{\fs16}I thought if I could make something so good,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.06,0:22:27.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如此天真的女孩\N{\fs16}so pure...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.98,0:22:32.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-可能这意味着我并不是个怪物-听着 听我说\N{\fs16}- maybe I'm not a monster. - Listen-- listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.06,0:22:35.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她是我的女儿 但我让她失望了\N{\fs16}She was my daughter and I failed her.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.70,0:22:38.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不 我知道她的死注定会发生\N{\fs16}No, I knew this would happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.32,0:22:40.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,多年以前 一位女巫告诉我\N{\fs16}The witch told me years ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.37,0:22:45.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她预言说我将有三个子女 但都将在我之前而死\N{\fs16}She promised me three children and she promised me they'd die.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.58,0:22:48.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,“以黄金为裹尸布”\N{\fs16}"And gold their shrouds."
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.30,0:22:49.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她跟我说的事情全都成真了\N{\fs16}Everything she said came true.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.91,0:22:51.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你无法违抗命运\N{\fs16}You couldn't have stopped it.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.80,0:22:53.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这些预言就是我的命运\N{\fs16}It's prophecy. It's fate.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.50,0:22:56.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-你别去相信它们就好-我怎能不信\N{\fs16}- You don't believe that. - Of course I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.59,0:22:59.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,父亲死的那天 你亲口对我说\N{\fs16}You told me yourself when Father died.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.84,0:23:01.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你说我们将永远在一起\N{\fs16}You said we had to stay together.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.84,0:23:05.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你说其他人想让我们分离 想把属于我们的东西夺走\N{\fs16}You said people would try to tear us apart, take what's ours.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.18,0:23:06.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这也是一个预言\N{\fs16}That was a prophecy, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.81,0:23:09.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没有在意你所说的 但一切都成了真\N{\fs16}I didn't listen to you and everything you said came true.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.18,0:23:11.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去他妈的命运和预言\N{\fs16}Fuck prophecy. Fuck fate.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.69,0:23:14.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去他妈的其他人\N{\fs16}Fuck everyone who isn't us.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.19,0:23:15.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只有我们彼此才是\N{\fs16}We're the only ones who matter,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.82,0:23:17.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这个世界上唯一值得关注的事情\N{\fs16}the only ones in this world.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.03,0:23:19.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所有他们从我们这里夺走的\N{\fs16}And everything they've taken from us,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.49,0:23:21.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们将讨回来更多\N{\fs16}we're going to take back and more.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.20,0:23:26.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们将夺回一切\N{\fs16}We're going to take everything there is.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.01,0:23:37.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,“七层地狱的周围都是圣人的灵魂\N{\fs16}"The Seven Hells brim with the souls of saintly men.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.93,0:23:40.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们痛苦地嚎叫 他们的罪孽深重\N{\fs16}They scream in agony and their shame is so great,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.88,0:23:42.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,无法感觉到下方的火焰\N{\fs16}they do not feel the flames,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.93,0:23:45.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果他们现在不再隐藏自己曾犯下的罪\N{\fs16}for now they see if not for a single sin
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.94,0:23:48.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们便可得救”\N{\fs16}they concealed, they were saved."
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.77,0:23:50.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我希望见我的弟弟\N{\fs16}I'd like to see my brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.77,0:23:53.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-你须忏悔 -求求你\N{\fs16}- Confess. - Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.14,0:23:55.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他现在究竟如何? 至少告诉我这个\N{\fs16}How is he? At least tell me that.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.23,0:23:56.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你须忏悔\N{\fs16}Confess.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.23,0:24:02.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是王后 我要求见我弟弟一面\N{\fs16}I am the queen and I demand to see my brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.82,0:24:04.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,罪人没有提要求的资格\N{\fs16}Sinners don't make demands.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.91,0:24:07.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们唯有忏悔\N{\fs16}They make confessions.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.41,0:24:13.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,乌尼亚修女\N{\fs16}Septa Unella.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.46,0:24:16.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们的另一个客人想要见你\N{\fs16}Our other guests need you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.51,0:24:29.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,来吧\N{\fs16}There.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.18,0:24:34.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,乌尼亚修女有时候会狂热过头\N{\fs16}Septa Unella can be overzealous at times.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.57,0:24:35.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会跟她说\N{\fs16}I'll speak with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.57,0:24:40.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您你能告诉我我弟弟现在是怎么个样子吗?\N{\fs16}My brother, can you tell me how he is?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.49,0:24:46.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,并不是洛拉斯爵士让我来的\N{\fs16}It isn't Ser Loras that brings me here.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.78,0:24:49.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的丈夫现在很想你\N{\fs16}Your husband misses you dearly.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.75,0:24:53.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,男人与女人之间的婚姻是神圣的\N{\fs16}The love between a man and wife is sacred.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.84,0:24:57.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是众神对凡人爱的证明\N{\fs16}It reflects the love the gods have for all of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.12,0:25:01.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但罪恶让我们远离了神圣之路\N{\fs16}But sin leads us away from the sacred.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.68,0:25:04.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,唯有忏悔能够洗除罪恶\N{\fs16}And only confession can purge sin.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.63,0:25:07.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没有可忏悔的\N{\fs16}I have nothing to confess.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.43,0:25:12.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所以你觉得你清白无辜?\N{\fs16}So you believe you are pure?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.14,0:25:13.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,完美无瑕?\N{\fs16}Perfect?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.06,0:25:16.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,全然与罪恶无涉?\N{\fs16}Wholly without sin?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.78,0:25:19.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们都是罪人\N{\fs16}None of us are.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.15,0:25:23.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你本应在出发之时就开始忏悔\N{\fs16}You have started down the path.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.40,0:25:27.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但现今你已走了无数歧路\N{\fs16}But you have many miles to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.50,0:25:44.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我总是嫉妒奥柏伦\N{\fs16}I always envied Oberyn.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.17,0:25:45.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他享受过生活\N{\fs16}He lived.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.01,0:25:47.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他真的享受过自己的生活\N{\fs16}He truly lived.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.67,0:25:49.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他曾航行到世界各地\N{\fs16}Sailed around the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.64,0:25:51.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,和各个国家的人打过架\N{\fs16}Fought men from every country.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.65,0:25:54.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,睡过世上最美的女人\N{\fs16}Lay with the most beautiful women alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.15,0:25:56.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-还有男人  -还有男人\N{\fs16}- And men. - And men.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.27,0:25:58.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他经历过所有事情\N{\fs16}He experienced everything
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.99,0:26:01.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而我却只能坐在多恩这里\N{\fs16}while I sat here in Dorne
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.94,0:26:06.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,尽我所能让人们活下去 吃饱饭\N{\fs16}trying my best to keep my people alive and well fed.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.99,0:26:08.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但这就是生活\N{\fs16}But that is life.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.28,0:26:12.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,每个人都扮演着不同的角色\N{\fs16}We each have our roles.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.53,0:26:17.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奥柏伦生来就是个冒险家\N{\fs16}Oberyn was born to be an adventurer.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.37,0:26:19.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而我则是为统治而生的\N{\fs16}And I was born to rule.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.37,0:26:21.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,诸神不是傻瓜\N{\fs16}The gods are not fools.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.21,0:26:24.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你会是个差劲的冒险家\N{\fs16}You would have been a lousy adventurer.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.21,0:26:26.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,至于奥柏伦 呃\N{\fs16}And Oberyn, pfft,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.76,0:26:28.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他会是个糟透了的统治者\N{\fs16}he would have been a terrible ruler.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.55,0:26:31.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的母亲非常出色 你知道吗\N{\fs16}Your mother is a brilliant woman, you know that?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.05,0:26:34.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,道朗亲王\N{\fs16}Prince Doran.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.23,0:26:48.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,弥赛菈公主\N{\fs16}The Princess Myrcella.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.92,0:27:09.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你上一次离开这个宫殿是什么时候？\N{\fs16}When was the last time you left this palace?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.42,0:27:11.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不了解你统治的人民\N{\fs16}You don't know your own people.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.89,0:27:15.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不知道他们有多厌恶你\N{\fs16}Their disgust for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.23,0:27:19.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,伊莉亚·马泰尔被奸杀 而你什么都没有做\N{\fs16}Elia Martell raped and murdered, and you did nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.18,0:27:23.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奥柏伦·马泰尔惨遭杀害 你却仍然按兵不动\N{\fs16}Oberyn Martell butchered, and you did nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:25.11,0:27:27.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不配做多恩人\N{\fs16}You're not a Dornishman.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.03,0:27:30.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不配做我们的亲王\N{\fs16}You're not our prince.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.99,0:27:35.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,崔斯丹 我的儿子……\N{\fs16}My son Trystane...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.08,0:27:40.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的儿子和你一样软弱\N{\fs16}Your son is weak just like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.44,0:27:44.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,多恩再也不会由软弱的人来统治了\N{\fs16}And weak men will never rule Dorne again.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.30,0:28:09.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我说了我不饿\N{\fs16}I told you I'm not hungry.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.92,0:28:12.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们不是来给你带东西吃的\N{\fs16}We're not here to feed you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.17,0:28:16.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们是来杀你的\N{\fs16}We're here to kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.39,0:28:19.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想让她来动手 还是我？\N{\fs16}You want her to do it or me?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.14,0:28:22.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们是一家人 我不想伤害你\N{\fs16}We are family. I don't want to hurt you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.90,0:28:25.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她 还是我？\N{\fs16}Her or me?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.10,0:28:31.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你\N{\fs16}You.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.27,0:28:33.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很好\N{\fs16}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.27,0:28:35.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,聪明的孩子\N{\fs16}Smart boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.29,0:28:54.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你真是个贪得无厌的婊子 你知道吗？\N{\fs16}You're a greedy bitch, you know that?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.27,0:29:05.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们没办法站在八百尺高的金字塔顶\N{\fs16}We're never going to fix what's wrong with this city
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.36,0:29:07.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,来解决下面的城市发生的问题\N{\fs16}from the top of an 800-foot pyramid.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:07.97,0:29:10.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不会有事的\N{\fs16}We'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.48,0:29:12.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们穿得和普通的商人一样\N{\fs16}We're dressed like common merchants.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.56,0:29:16.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,可你走路的方式像个有钱人\N{\fs16}You walk like a rich person.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.98,0:29:19.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你曾经用过很长时间来研究有钱人走路的方式吗？\N{\fs16}You've spent a lot of time studying the way rich people walk?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.04,0:29:24.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你走路的样子就好像这些铺路石都是你的私人财产一样\N{\fs16}You walk as though the paving stones were your personal property.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.16,0:29:27.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在我还是个小男孩的时候 就从你们这种人身上偷钱\N{\fs16}I used to steal from people like you when I was a boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.41,0:29:29.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,真庆幸你现在不是个小男孩了\N{\fs16}It's a good thing you're not a boy anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.13,0:29:33.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为你没有命根子\N{\fs16}Because you have no cock.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.39,0:29:46.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是给你孩子的\N{\fs16}For your baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.00,0:29:49.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让他吃点东西\N{\fs16}to eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.77,0:29:54.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她以为你要吃了她的孩子\N{\fs16}She thinks you want to eat her baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.10,0:29:56.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他的瓦雷利亚语说得太差了\N{\fs16}His Valyrian is terrible.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.34,0:29:59.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他只是想把这些钱给你\N{\fs16}He only wants to give you money,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.21,0:30:03.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这样 你的孩子就有东西吃了\N{\fs16}so your baby can eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.88,0:30:20.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-“弥莎”在瓦雷利亚语里是母亲的意思  -我知道“弥莎”是什么意思\N{\fs16}- Mhysa means mother in Valyrian.  - I know what mhysa means.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.46,0:30:22.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-这是谁写的？ -那可不好说\N{\fs16}- Who wrote it?   - Hard to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:22.43,0:30:25.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们的女王在弥林城里没有以前那么受欢迎了\N{\fs16}Our queen is not as popular in Meereen as she used to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.05,0:30:27.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,鹰身女妖之子？\N{\fs16}The Sons of the Harpy?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.89,0:30:29.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很有可能\N{\fs16}Very possibly.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.31,0:30:34.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,丹妮莉丝·坦格利安夺走了他们最宝贵的财产\N{\fs16}Daenerys Targaryen took away their most valuable property,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.39,0:30:38.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她一开始就告诉他们人是不能作为财产的\N{\fs16}told them human beings weren't even property to begin with.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.40,0:30:40.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你能想象他们为什么不高兴\N{\fs16}You can see why they're unhappy.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.70,0:30:42.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不过 当然\N{\fs16}Of course,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.07,0:30:45.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这也有可能是获得自由的人所写的\N{\fs16}it could also be the freed men.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.87,0:30:49.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,长夜漫漫 处处险恶\N{\fs16}For the night is dark and full of terrors.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.33,0:30:53.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,光之王将龙之母送到了你们面前\N{\fs16}The Lord of Light sent the Mother of Dragons to you,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.04,0:30:56.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而暗影的仆从赶走了她\N{\fs16}and those who love the darkness chased her away.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.05,0:31:00.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很多原本的奴隶觉得丹妮莉丝抛弃了他们\N{\fs16}Many of the former slaves feel that Daenerys has abandoned them.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.43,0:31:04.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她确实骑龙飞走了 至今也没有回来\N{\fs16}She did fly away on a dragon and not come back.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.81,0:31:06.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们该如何应对？\N{\fs16}How will you respond?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.64,0:31:12.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们是要绑紧双手 等待龙之母归来\N{\fs16}Will you wring your hands, while you wait for the Mother of Dragons to return?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.79,0:31:16.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还是要亲手接过她的火种？\N{\fs16}Or will you take up her flames yourselves?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.66,0:31:21.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如今丹妮莉丝女王无法在这里为你们而战 你们会为自己的救赎而战吗？\N{\fs16}Will you fight for your own salvation, now that Queen Daenerys is not here to fight for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.52,0:31:23.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这可是个问题\N{\fs16}It's a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.91,0:31:28.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,恐惧让弥林陷入了停滞\N{\fs16}Fear has brought Meereen  to a standstill.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.62,0:31:32.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不管你是谁 不管你到哪儿去\N{\fs16}Whoever you are, wherever you go,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.95,0:31:36.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这城市里总有人想杀你\N{\fs16}someone in this city wants to murder you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.21,0:31:39.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们没法对抗未知的敌人\N{\fs16}We can't fight an enemy we don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.84,0:31:42.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,鹰身女妖之子精心谋划了\N{\fs16}The Sons of the Harpy planned their attack
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.84,0:31:44.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那场竞技场中的袭击\N{\fs16}in the fighting pits very carefully,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.76,0:31:47.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这意味着有一个人在给他们发号施令\N{\fs16}which means they take orders from someone.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.52,0:31:49.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那你开始寻找这个人了吗？\N{\fs16}And have you started looking for that someone?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.73,0:31:52.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的小小鸟们已经起飞了\N{\fs16}My little birds have already taken wing.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.65,0:31:57.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很快他们就会回来 唱着关于戴金面具的人的歌\N{\fs16}Soon they'll return, singing songs of men in gold masks.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.19,0:32:35.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好吧 看来我们近期是没法驶回维斯特洛了\N{\fs16}Well, we won't be sailing  to Westeros anytime soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.92,0:32:59.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是山羊吗？\N{\fs16}Goat?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.92,0:33:01.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是只公绵羊\N{\fs16}Ram.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.59,0:33:03.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你觉得这是我们的朋友干的吗？\N{\fs16}You think our friend got him?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.89,0:33:07.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不知道这世上还有什么能融化掉绵羊的角\N{\fs16}Don't know anything else that can melt a ram's horn.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.73,0:33:11.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那就是说我们走对路了\N{\fs16}We're on the right path, then.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:12.07,0:33:15.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也许她就是厌烦了当女王\N{\fs16}Perhaps she's tired of being queen.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.27,0:33:17.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我觉得她不太喜欢这差使\N{\fs16}I don't think she likes it very much.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:17.44,0:33:19.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她还没傻到会喜欢当女王\N{\fs16}She's too smart to like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.74,0:33:21.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,搞不好她飞到别的地方去了\N{\fs16}Maybe she's flown somewhere else,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.61,0:33:23.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一个远离像咱俩这样的人的地方\N{\fs16}somewhere far away from men like us.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.69,0:33:26.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我曾游遍世界\N{\fs16}I've been all over the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.61,0:33:28.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,到哪儿都躲不开咱俩这样的人\N{\fs16}There's no escaping men like us.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.62,0:33:31.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也躲不开她 哈？\N{\fs16}There's no escaping her, eh?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.45,0:33:34.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,每次你都会回来的 为什么？\N{\fs16}You keep coming back. Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.71,0:33:36.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你知道为什么\N{\fs16}You know why.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.26,0:33:40.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这感觉难道不会很糟吗\N{\fs16}Isn't it frustrating
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.43,0:33:43.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,渴望着一个根本不想让你回来的人？\N{\fs16}wanting someone who doesn't want you back?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.93,0:33:45.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,当然很糟\N{\fs16}Of course it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.47,0:33:48.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是个浪漫的人 我很佩服\N{\fs16}You're a romantic. I admire that.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.14,0:33:50.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有时看到你我就会想\N{\fs16}Sometimes I look at you and I think,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.19,0:33:52.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,“这就是我变老了以后的样子”\N{\fs16}"So that's what I'll be like when I grow old."
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.64,0:33:54.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果你会变老的话\N{\fs16}If you grow old.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.39,0:33:55.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果我会变老的话\N{\fs16}If I grow old.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.78,0:33:57.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我希望我会\N{\fs16}I hope I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.03,0:33:59.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我想看看在她征服了世界之后\N{\fs16}I want to see what the world looks like
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.86,0:34:01.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,世界会是个什么样子\N{\fs16}when she's done conquering it.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.62,0:34:03.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我也想\N{\fs16}So do I.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.30,0:34:26.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哈 一支军队？\N{\fs16}Huh, an army?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.17,0:34:27.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不是部队\N{\fs16}Not an army.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.68,0:34:29.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是部落\N{\fs16}A horde.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.09,0:34:56.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,多斯拉克人？\N{\fs16}Dothraki?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.64,0:35:21.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们抓住了她\N{\fs16}They have her.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.50,0:36:13.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她可能见鬼了\N{\fs16}Maybe she saw a ghost.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.88,0:36:15.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我朋友的母亲见过鬼 然后头发都吓白了\N{\fs16}My friend's mother saw a ghost and her hair turned white.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.28,0:36:18.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,白人都怕晒太阳\N{\fs16}Pink people are afraid of the sun.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.98,0:36:21.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,阳光会烧坏他们的皮肤\N{\fs16}It burns their skin.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.64,0:36:24.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这个女的在太阳底下晒得太久 连头发都晒白了\N{\fs16}This one stands too long in the sun and her hair goes white.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.08,0:36:28.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你觉得她下面的毛也是白的吗？\N{\fs16}You think she's got white pussy hair too?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.51,0:36:30.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你睡过下面是白毛的女人吗？\N{\fs16}you ever been with a girl with white pussy hair?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.65,0:36:32.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,睡过 你奶奶\N{\fs16}Only when I was fucking your grandma.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.71,0:36:38.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会向摩洛卡奥请求 睡你一晚\N{\fs16}I'll ask Khal Moro for a night with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.29,0:36:40.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你觉得怎么样？\N{\fs16}What do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.43,0:36:45.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,眼睛真漂亮 可惜是个傻子\N{\fs16}Pretty eyes, but she's an idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.56,0:36:48.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她不用那么聪明  照样有人捅她屁眼\N{\fs16}She doesn't have to be smart to get fucked in the ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.23,0:36:54.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,完事儿后我喜欢聊聊天 否则我们不就跟公狗一个样\N{\fs16}I like to talk when I'm finished. Otherwise, we might as well be dogs
Dialogue: 0,0:37:27.02,0:37:28.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不要\N{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:44.06,0:37:46.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,献给你 我的卡奥\N{\fs16}For you, my Khal.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:46.35,0:37:49.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们在山里找到这个白发女人\N{\fs16}The white-haired girl we found in the hills.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.43,0:37:54.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,吾血之血 看看这嘴唇\N{\fs16}Look at those lips, blood of my blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:54.49,0:37:56.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,蓝眼睛的女人都是女巫\N{\fs16}Blue-eyed women are witches.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.00,0:37:58.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谁都知道\N{\fs16}It is known.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.40,0:38:04.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,趁她还没对您施咒 赶紧砍掉她的头\N{\fs16}Cut off her head, before she casts a spell on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.00,0:38:06.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就算我瞎了\N{\fs16}Even if I was blind,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.00,0:38:09.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只要听我的老婆们说\N{\fs16}I'd hear my wives say,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.00,0:38:12.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,“砍掉她的头”\N{\fs16}"Cut off her head"
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.80,0:38:15.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我就知道这个女人一定很美\N{\fs16}and I'd know this woman is beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.65,0:38:17.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,幸亏我没瞎\N{\fs16}I'm glad I'm not blind.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.90,0:38:21.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,才能第一次看到这么漂亮的光屁股女人\N{\fs16}Seeing a beautiful woman naked for the first time,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.16,0:38:22.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有比这更好的事儿吗？\N{\fs16}what is better than that?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.90,0:38:25.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,杀掉别的卡奥？\N{\fs16}Killing another Khal?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.96,0:38:28.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好吧 还有杀死别的卡奥\N{\fs16}Yes, killing another Khal.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.85,0:38:32.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,占领一座城市 然后把人抢来当奴隶\N{\fs16}Conquering a city and taking her people as slaves,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.29,0:38:35.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,把战利品带回维斯·多斯拉克\N{\fs16}and taking her idols back to Vaes Dothrak.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.22,0:38:37.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,驯服一匹野马\N{\fs16}Breaking a wild horse,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.04,0:38:39.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,逼它听从你的命令\N{\fs16}forcing it to submit to your will.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.94,0:38:46.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,第一次看这么漂亮的光屁股女人是人生的五件美事之一\N{\fs16}Seeing a beautiful woman naked for the first time is among the five best things in life.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.87,0:38:51.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别碰我\N{\fs16}Do not touch me.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.34,0:39:02.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是坦格利安家族的“风暴降生”\N{\fs16}I am Daenerys Stormborn of the House Targaryen,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.69,0:39:05.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,丹妮莉丝一世 不焚者\N{\fs16}the First of Her Name, the Unburnt,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.30,0:39:10.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,弥林女王  安达尔人 洛伊拿人和先民的女王\N{\fs16}Queen of Meereen, Queen of the Andals and the Rhoynar and the First Men
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.83,0:39:15.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大草原的卡丽熙  镣铐破除者 龙之母\N{\fs16}Khaleesi of the Great Grass Sea, Breaker of Chains and Mother of Dragons.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.24,0:39:37.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你还有第一百万个名字 无名氏\N{\fs16}You are nobody, the millionth of your name,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.54,0:39:39.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,空头女王\N{\fs16}Queen of Nothing,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.89,0:39:41.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,摩洛卡奥的奴隶\N{\fs16}slave of Khal Moro.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.70,0:39:43.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,今晚我会睡你\N{\fs16}Tonight I will lie with you,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.00,0:39:45.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果马神够仁慈\N{\fs16}and if the Great Stallion is kind,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.33,0:39:47.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你会为我生个儿子\N{\fs16}you will give me a son.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.51,0:39:50.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你听见了吗？\N{\fs16}Do you understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.62,0:39:54.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不会和你睡\N{\fs16}I will not lie with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.76,0:39:59.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也不会为你生子 不会为任何人生子\N{\fs16}And I will bear no children, for you, or anyone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.22,0:40:03.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,除非太阳西升东落\N{\fs16}Not until the sun rises in the west, and sets in the east.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:03.45,0:40:06.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我就说吧 她是个女巫\N{\fs16}I told you she was a witch.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.14,0:40:08.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,快砍掉她的头\N{\fs16}Cut off her head.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.38,0:40:12.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我喜欢她 有个性\N{\fs16}I like her. She has spirit.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:13.28,0:40:17.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是 拔尔勃卡奥之子卓戈卡奥的妻子\N{\fs16}I was wife to Khal Drogo, son of Khal Bharbo.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.33,0:40:23.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,卓戈卡奥已死\N{\fs16}Khal Drogo is dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.00,0:40:25.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\fs16}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.19,0:40:28.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我亲手烧了他的尸体\N{\fs16}I burnt his body.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.76,0:40:33.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,原谅我 我不知道\N{\fs16}Forgive me. I did not know.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.93,0:40:36.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,睡卡奥的遗孀是禁忌\N{\fs16}It is forbidden to lie with a Khal's widow.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.70,0:40:39.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没有人会动你一分一毫\N{\fs16}No one will touch you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.26,0:40:46.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我向你保证\N{\fs16}You have my word.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.41,0:40:52.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果你护送我回弥林\N{\fs16}If you will escort me back to Meereen,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.83,0:40:57.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会回赠你的卡拉萨一千匹马 以示感激\N{\fs16}I will see that your khalasar is given a thousand horses, as a sign of my gratitude.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:58.12,0:41:00.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,卡奥死后\N{\fs16}When a Khal dies,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.68,0:41:04.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,卡丽熙只有一个去处\N{\fs16}there is only one place for his khaleesi.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.09,0:41:08.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,维斯·多斯拉克 多希卡林的神殿\N{\fs16}Vaes Dothrak. The Temple of the Dosh Khaleen.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.42,0:41:13.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,与其他卡奥的遗孀在那里共度余生\N{\fs16}To live out her days with the widows of dead khals.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:13.94,0:41:16.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谁都知道\N{\fs16}It is known
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.12,0:41:55.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,凡事总有价格\N{\fs16}But there has to be a price to pay for everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.54,0:41:59.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我知道 但你和他说过吗？\N{\fs16}I know, but have you tried telling him that?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:06.52,0:42:09.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fs16}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:09.14,0:42:11.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在那个御林铁卫出事后 谁还会去哪儿啊？\N{\fs16}Who'd go there after what happened to that Kingsguard?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:11.81,0:42:13.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-可能是他自找的 -可能吧\N{\fs16}- Probably had it coming.  - Maybe so,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:13.61,0:42:15.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我不会冒险的\N{\fs16}but I'm not risking it.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.31,0:42:16.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-就是做不到 -好吧\N{\fs16}- Just can't do it. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:16.98,0:42:19.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,实话说 他活该\N{\fs16}Honesty as well. He gets it.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.95,0:42:25.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你在听吗 瞎女孩？\N{\fs16}Are you listening, blind girl?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.70,0:42:30.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,听见他们说话了吗？\N{\fs16}Do you hear them talking?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:30.41,0:42:33.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有人和你说话吗？\N{\fs16}Do any of them talk to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:33.21,0:42:34.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你听不见\N{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:35.75,0:42:37.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,真可怜\N{\fs16}So sad.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:44.00,0:42:46.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,起来打啊 瞎女孩\N{\fs16}Stand and fight, blind girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:48.51,0:42:49.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我看不见\N{\fs16}I can't see.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:50.06,0:42:52.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是你的问题 与我无关\N{\fs16}That's your problem, not mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.29,0:43:21.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,明天见\N{\fs16}See you tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:13.93,0:44:17.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,戴佛斯爵士 我们没有理由开打\N{\fs16}Ser Davos, we have no cause to fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:17.93,0:44:20.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们都是受封的骑士\N{\fs16}We are both anointed knights.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.15,0:44:23.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大家听见了吗？没什么可怕的\N{\fs16}Hear that, lads? Nothing to fear.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:23.82,0:44:25.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果在日落前投降\N{\fs16}I will grant amnesty to all brothers
Dialogue: 0,0:44:26.11,0:44:28.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我保证赦免所有兄弟\N{\fs16}who throw down their arms before nightfall.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:28.53,0:44:32.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,至于你 戴佛斯爵士 我会放你去南方\N{\fs16}And you, Ser Davos, I will  allow you to travel south
Dialogue: 0,0:44:32.28,0:44:35.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,以自由之身 骑着新马\N{\fs16}a free man with a fresh horse.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:36.62,0:44:38.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,和一些羊肉\N{\fs16}And some mutton.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:38.95,0:44:40.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我想要些羊肉\N{\fs16}I'd like some mutton.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:40.62,0:44:44.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-什么？ -我算不上猎人\N{\fs16}- What?  - I'm not much of a hunter.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:44.51,0:44:48.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果想活着南下 我需要带点吃的\N{\fs16}I'll need some food if I'm gonna make it south without starving.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:52.43,0:44:54.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们会给你吃的\N{\fs16}We'll give you food.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.27,0:44:57.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果你想的话 可以带走红袍祭司\N{\fs16}You can bring the Red Woman with you if you like.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:57.52,0:45:00.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,或者把她留给我们 随你\N{\fs16}Or you can leave her here with us, whichever you choose.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:01.06,0:45:05.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但是要在黄昏前投降 否则将兵戎相见\N{\fs16}But surrender by nightfall or this ends with blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:07.45,0:45:09.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谢谢你 艾里沙爵士\N{\fs16}Thank you, Ser Alliser.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:09.48,0:45:13.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们先自己讨论一下 然后给你个答复\N{\fs16}We'll discuss amongst ourselves and come back to you with an answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:28.22,0:45:32.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,兄弟们 我这辈子都在避免与这种人打交道\N{\fs16}Boys, I've been running from men like that all my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:33.01,0:45:36.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,根据我的经验来看 一旦我们打开这扇门——\N{\fs16}In my learned opinion, we open that door--
Dialogue: 0,0:45:36.26,0:45:37.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们会把我们杀个精光\N{\fs16}And they'll slaughter us all.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.84,0:45:40.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们想进来 就进来\N{\fs16}They want to come in, they're gonna come in.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:40.23,0:45:43.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-是的 我们不能让他们轻易得逞 -艾迪是我们唯一的机会\N{\fs16}- Aye, but we don't need to make it easy for them. - Edd is our only chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:43.85,0:45:47.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,忧郁的艾迪居然是我们最后的希望 这实在太他妈的惨了\N{\fs16}It's a sad fucking statement if  Dolorous Edd is our only chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:49.19,0:45:50.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这不还有红袍祭司嘛\N{\fs16}There's always the Red Woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:50.82,0:45:53.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一个红发女要怎么对付40个全副武装的守夜人？\N{\fs16}What's one redhead gonna do against 40 armed men?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:55.11,0:45:57.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你还没见识过她的本事 我见过\N{\fs16}You haven't seen her do what I've seen her do.

