[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.2.2012.322
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: Game of Thrones S06E06
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 衣柜
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 衣柜 / ReEdit by NetAdmin@TLF
Script Updated By: 衣柜
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 720
PlayResY: 404
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Titles,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles_L,Microsoft YaHei,24,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Character_L,Microsoft YaHei,28,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,4,10,10,10,1
Style: Character_B,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Author,Microsoft YaHei,16,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,1,10,10,10,1
Style: QR code - BG,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000019FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,400,400,0,0,1,0,0,5,0,0,0,1
Style: QR code - code,Arial,20,&H00000000,&H000019FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,200,200,0,0,1,0,0,5,0,0,0,1
Style: Titles - 1,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,5,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles - 2,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles - 3 -,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H0001031B,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000429,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Subtitle,Microsoft YaHei,26,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Subtitle - 复制,Microsoft YaHei,22,&H8CC1DFED,&H93FFFFFF,&HCF000000,&HE4000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,7,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.40,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(1000,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx89\fscy89\p1\move(298,257,298,257,120,1400)}m -11 -35 l -11 39 l 63 39 l 63 -35{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.40,Titles - 2,,0,0,0,,{\fad(1000,500)\move(340,280,340,280,300,1400)\p1\fscx40\fscy40}m -86 -116 b -89 -117 -89 -117 -95 -119 l -97 -115 l -85 -105 l -116 -102 b -116 -100 -116 -98 -116 -97 l -108 -91 l -96 -91 l -116 -63 l -105 -69 l -96 -47 l -74 -63 l -77 -69 l -91 -63 l -91 -77 l -88 -80 l -66 -49 l -46 -63 l -58 -66 l -66 -74 l -49 -80 l -60 -91 l -74 -83 l -80 -91 l -77 -94 l -46 -94 l -52 -108 l -71 -105 b -69 -107 -67 -110 -66 -113 m -31 -119.875 l -33 -119 b -34 -113 -36 -107 -38 -102 l -46 -97 b -42 -93 -38 -89 -35 -85 l -44 -63 b -41 -64 -38 -65 -35 -66 l -35 -52 l -33 -47 l -27 -55 l -27 -69 l -21 -63 l -21 -69 l -19 -72 l -27 -88 l -21 -94 l -21 -99 l -27 -102 l -27 -102 l -30 -116 m -21 -113 l -21 -105 l -21 -99 l -21 -94 l -19 -85 l -19 -66 l -21 -49 l -19 -47 l -7 -52 l 26 -52 l 18 -66 l -7 -63 l -5 -69 l 6 -69 l 18 -69 l 20 -99 l -7 -94 l -7 -83 l 6 -85 l 6 -80 l -7 -77 l -7 -94 l -10 -99 l 23 -102 l 18 -116 l -10 -110 l -19 -116 m -105 -38 l -116 -41 l -110 -13 l -102 -19 l -102 -30 l -63 -33 l -55 -19 l -46 -41 l -49 -44 m -88 -33 l -91 -24 l -99 -24 l -105 -16 l -102 -13 l -85 -16 l -85 -10 l -94 -8 l -85 -16 l -102 -13 l -108 1 l -88 1 l -88 4 l -116 6 l -116 9 l -110 15 l -88 15 l -85 26 l -77 23 l -74 15 l -52 15 l -49 15 l -52 4 l -74 6 l -71 1 l -55 -2 l -60 -13 l -74 -10 l -74 -13 l -55 -16 l -63 -24 l -74 -24 l -80 -33 m -46 -41 l -38 -2 l -41 23 l -38 26 l 1 20 l 15 26 l 18 23 l 18 -8 l 20 -41 l 20 -44 l -24 -38 l -35 -41 l -35 -30 l -13 -30 l -19 -21 l -33 -19 l -33 -13 l -21 -13 l -33 6 l -33 15 l -13 -5 l -13 1 l -21 6 l -13 12 l -2 9 l -2 -8 l 9 -10 l 12 -19 l 1 -21 l -2 -27 l 9 -33 l 6 -16 l 6 -10 l 9 12 l -2 9 l -30 12 l -30 12 l -27 -2 l -27 -2 l -30 -16 l -27 -21 l -35 -41 m -126 -127 l -130 -130 l -129 38 l 34 37 l 35 -135 l -130 -131 l -127 -127 l 30 -129 l 31 32 l -124 34
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.40,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(386,224.2)\fad(1000,500)\b0\fs18\bord1} 最专业冰火字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.40,Titles - 1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(384,165.2)\fad(1000,500)}\N{\fs20}{\fs32.001\c&HFFFFFF&\b1}诚意奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.40,Titles - 1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(385,197.2)\fad(1000,500)\b000}专注GOT剧集{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.34,0:00:22.14,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(103.25,320.022)\fad(300,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}牛德君
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.39,0:00:26.59,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(104.875,103.122)\fad(500,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}SaintHS
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.59,0:00:18.69,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(287.875,310.367)\fad(500,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}埃尔夫歪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.69,0:00:31.19,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(376.708,284.159)\fad(500,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}Noxumos
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.79,0:00:33.89,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(201.209,142.666)\fad(500,500)}校对{\fs24} {\b1}屈畅   赵琳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.29,0:00:40.19,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(458.417,130.016)\fad(500,500)}校对{\fs24} {\b1}北落师门   依依Eva
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.64,0:00:43.24,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(109.125,137.792)\fad(500,500)}后期{\fs24} {\b1}SerGawen@huiji.wiki
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.14,0:00:51.64,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(454,150.961)\fad(500,500)}监制{\fs24} {\b1}临冬城的狮子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.14,0:00:48.64,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(118.792,140.97)\fad(500,500)}监制{\fs24} {\b1}北落师门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.64,0:01:09.64,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(108.917,102.893)\fad(500,500)}策划{\fs24} {\b1}衣柜军团
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.64,0:01:18.74,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(410.792,311.05)\fad(500,500)}特别顾问{\fs24} {\b1}屈畅(ccxx)@史诗图书
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.40,0:00:23.80,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\t(\fscx150\fscy150,150)\p1\move(277,278,289,305,1,4381)}m -15 -18 l -15 -17 l -14 -16 l -13 -16 l -11 -15 l -6 -16 b -8 -15 -8 -15 -11 -13 l -14 -9 l -12 -9 l -10 -8 l -5 -9 b -4 -8 -2 -6 6 -7 l 7 -7 l 3 -8 l 1 -10 b 2 -14 5 -17 3 -19 l 2 -21 l 5 -21 l 3 -22 l 0 -23 l 0 -24 l 4 -26 l 8 -23 l 16 -21 b 20 -23 25 -24 28 -36 l 27 -35 b 26 -35 26 -35 22 -37 b 25 -34 25 -32 24 -32 l 17 -34 l 23 -30 b 22 -29 20 -27 19 -29 l 14 -33 b 15 -31 17 -29 16 -26 b 13 -25 11 -24 7 -27 l 11 -31 l 10 -36 b 10 -32 11 -32 8 -30 b 7 -30 5 -29 4 -29 b 3 -30 2 -31 0 -34 l 3 -28 l -1 -27 l -5 -30 l -7 -34 l -6 -30 l -3 -27 l -8 -28 l -15 -32 l -10 -27 l -6 -25 l -4 -25 l -7 -23 l -10 -21 l -3 -21 l -5 -20 l -7 -21 l -7 -22 l -8 -22 l -13 -19{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.40,0:00:23.80,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\pos(301.714,255.889)\fad(300,500)\frx360\t(20,200,\frx0)\fs25\b1}君临{\fs12\b0} King's Landing
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.45,0:00:27.87,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\move(420,300,420,280)\fs25\p1}m -17 -23 l -10 -8 l -19 -15 l -12 -1 l -24 -9 l -14 6 l -25 1 l -16 9 l -13 17 l -15 24 l 18 24 l 13 19 l 15 12 l 22 4 l 13 10 l 25 -3 l 20 0 l 14 3 l 17 -3 l 22 -11 l 13 -4 l 18 -21 l 13 -15 l 10 -13 l 11 -26 l 7 -16 l 7 -28 l 3 -16 l 0 -32 l -2 -15 l -6 -22 l -8 -28 l -8 -11{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.45,0:00:27.87,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(380,230,380,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}红堡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.14,0:01:11.14,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(380,230,480,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}布拉佛斯\N{\fs14\b0}Braavos
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.45,0:00:27.87,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(425,250,425,235)\fad(300,500)\fs12\b0} Red Keep
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.45,0:00:39.45,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(380,260,380,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}临冬城
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.45,0:00:39.45,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(380,265,)\fad(300,500)\fs12\b0}Winterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.73,0:01:38.73,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(338,265)\fad(1250,1000)\frx50\t(1200,2500,\frx0)\fs28} {\b1}弥林\N{\fs20}{\fs12\b0}Meereen
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.46,0:01:31.46,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\pos(337.5,157.549)\fad(500,500)\fs12.746} 联合出品
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.46,0:01:31.46,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\fad(500,500)\fs24} 史诗图书 | 冰火中文维基 | 黑城堡奇幻微刊\N{\fs20}\N{\fs20}\N{\fs20}{\fs12}\N{\fs20}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.46,0:01:31.46,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\pos(359.5,212.563)\fad(500,500)\fs14.997} Epic Books         ASOIAF.huiji.wiki        微信号：Heichengbao\N{\fs20}{\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.14,0:01:15.14,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(516.25,129.545)\fad(500,500)} {\fs24\b1} 史诗图书 {\fs18\b0} 正统奇幻的圣殿
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.14,0:00:57.14,Titles,,0,30,200,,{\fad(100,50)\frx75\t(0,3500,\frx-0)\fs28} {\b1}绝境长城{\fs12\b0} the Wall
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.57,0:01:26.36,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(355,250,370,250)\fs28\b1}维斯·多斯拉克
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.57,0:01:26.36,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(365,260,355,260)\fad(100,1000)\fs12\b0} Vaes Dothrak
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.44,0:01:00.42,Titles,,0,0,100,,{\fs25\c&HC1DFED&\fad(100,1000)} {\b0} 最专业的华语冰火资料站：        冰与火之歌{\b0\fs20}中文维基{\b0}\N{\fs20}\N{\fs20}{\fs20\fs20\c&HFFFFFF&}http://asoiaf.huiji.wiki
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.64,0:01:00.42,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,1000)\pos(410,285)\fs25\c&HC1DFED&} {\b1\p1\fscx60\fscy60}m 31 -6 l -21 40 l 34 22 m 29 -8 l -3 -12 l -24 40{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.42,0:01:03.94,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(186.25,319.545)\fad(500,500)} {\fs18\b1} 黑城堡奇幻微刊{\fs18\b0}（heichengbao）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.24,0:01:38.94,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(460.667,310)\fad(500,500)\fs14} {\c&HC1DFED&}根据长篇小说
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.24,0:01:38.94,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(552.333,334)\fad(500,500)} {\fs24}《{\b1}冰与火之歌{\b0}》{\fs14} 改编
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.24,0:01:38.94,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(587,357.667)\fad(500,500)} {\fs12} 原著 {\fs20} 乔治·R·R·马丁
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.46,0:01:49.77,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(350,294)\fad(300,500)\fs56.267\fn宋体\b1}权力的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.46,0:01:49.77,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(349,322)\fad(300,500)\c&HFFFFFF&\b1\fs22}衣柜字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.84,0:01:55.40,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(428,118.44)\fad(500,500)\p1}m -18.625 0 l -18.625 0 l 281.25 0 l 281.25 1.125 l -18.625 1.125{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.84,0:01:55.40,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(231.125,202.841)\p1\fscx35\fscy35}m -86 -116 b -89 -117 -89 -117 -95 -119 l -97 -115 l -85 -105 l -116 -102 b -116 -100 -116 -98 -116 -97 l -108 -91 l -96 -91 l -116 -63 l -105 -69 l -96 -47 l -74 -63 l -77 -69 l -91 -63 l -91 -77 l -88 -80 l -66 -49 l -46 -63 l -58 -66 l -66 -74 l -49 -80 l -60 -91 l -74 -83 l -80 -91 l -77 -94 l -46 -94 l -52 -108 l -71 -105 b -69 -107 -67 -110 -66 -113 m -31 -119.875 l -33 -119 b -34 -113 -36 -107 -38 -102 l -46 -97 b -42 -93 -38 -89 -35 -85 l -44 -63 b -41 -64 -38 -65 -35 -66 l -35 -52 l -33 -47 l -27 -55 l -27 -69 l -21 -63 l -21 -69 l -19 -72 l -27 -88 l -21 -94 l -21 -99 l -27 -102 l -27 -102 l -30 -116 m -21 -113 l -21 -105 l -21 -99 l -21 -94 l -19 -85 l -19 -66 l -21 -49 l -19 -47 l -7 -52 l 26 -52 l 18 -66 l -7 -63 l -5 -69 l 6 -69 l 18 -69 l 20 -99 l -7 -94 l -7 -83 l 6 -85 l 6 -80 l -7 -77 l -7 -94 l -10 -99 l 23 -102 l 18 -116 l -10 -110 l -19 -116 m -105 -38 l -116 -41 l -110 -13 l -102 -19 l -102 -30 l -63 -33 l -55 -19 l -46 -41 l -49 -44 m -88 -33 l -91 -24 l -99 -24 l -105 -16 l -102 -13 l -85 -16 l -85 -10 l -94 -8 l -85 -16 l -102 -13 l -108 1 l -88 1 l -88 4 l -116 6 l -116 9 l -110 15 l -88 15 l -85 26 l -77 23 l -74 15 l -52 15 l -49 15 l -52 4 l -74 6 l -71 1 l -55 -2 l -60 -13 l -74 -10 l -74 -13 l -55 -16 l -63 -24 l -74 -24 l -80 -33 m -46 -41 l -38 -2 l -41 23 l -38 26 l 1 20 l 15 26 l 18 23 l 18 -8 l 20 -41 l 20 -44 l -24 -38 l -35 -41 l -35 -30 l -13 -30 l -19 -21 l -33 -19 l -33 -13 l -21 -13 l -33 6 l -33 15 l -13 -5 l -13 1 l -21 6 l -13 12 l -2 9 l -2 -8 l 9 -10 l 12 -19 l 1 -21 l -2 -27 l 9 -33 l 6 -16 l 6 -10 l 9 12 l -2 9 l -30 12 l -30 12 l -27 -2 l -27 -2 l -30 -16 l -27 -21 l -35 -41 m -126 -127 l -130 -130 l -129 38 l 34 37 l 35 -135 l -130 -131 l -127 -127 l 30 -129 l 31 32 l -124 34{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.84,0:01:55.40,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(293,112.813)\fad(500,500)\b1}协力制作
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.84,0:01:55.40,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(293,157.827)\fad(500,500)}史诗图书\N{\fs16}Epic Books
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.84,0:01:55.40,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(405.5,157.827)\fad(500,500)}冰火中文维基\N{\fs16}ASOIAF.HuiJi.WiKi
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.84,0:01:55.40,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(518,157.827)\fad(500,500)}黑城堡\N{\fs16}EPICASTLE
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.74,0:01:55.34,Titles_L,,260,0,163,,{\pos(310,300)\fad(500,500)\fs16\b0}第六集
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.74,0:01:55.34,Titles_L,,300,0,132,,{\pos(310,340)\fad(500,500)}吾血之血\N{\fs16\b0}Blood of My Blood
Dialogue: 0,0:50:07.14,0:51:21.14,Titles,,0,0,20,,{\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(360,390)}衣柜字幕组出品
Dialogue: 0,0:50:07.14,0:51:21.89,Titles,,0,0,40,,{\be1\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(357,372)}本集关键字：{\c&H5650F3\b0}班扬·史塔克   艾德慕·徒利   碎心
Dialogue: 0,0:50:07.14,0:51:21.14,Titles,,0,0,335,,{\pos(360,40)\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(360,40)}剧情没看懂？ 典故不清楚？{\b0}\N维基新站网址：{\c&H00FF40}HTTP://AsoIaF.HuiJi.WiKi
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.14,0:02:21.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(128,312)}梅拉·黎德\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.17,0:02:16.64,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(628,262)}布兰·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.14,0:06:06.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(288,182)}山姆威尔·塔利\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.14,0:06:11.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(114,232)}吉莉\N{\b0\fs12}野人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.14,0:08:27.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(401,271)}梅丽莎·佛罗伦\N{\b0\fs12}山姆的母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.14,0:08:49.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(58,227)}塔拉·塔利\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.14,0:10:32.64,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(539,246)}托曼·拜拉席恩一世\N{\b0\fs12}国王
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.14,0:14:57.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(148,215)}蓝道·塔利\N{\b0\fs12}角陵伯爵
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.14,0:24:15.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(159,202)}艾莉亚·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.14,0:34:31.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(208,215)}奥莲娜·雷德温\N{\b0\fs12}荆棘女王
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.44,0:31:42.44,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(468,254)}贾昆·赫加尔\N{\b0\fs12}无面者
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.74,0:38:50.74,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(456,213)}凯冯·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}国王之手
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.34,0:35:41.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(434,243)}蓝赛尔·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}凯冯之子
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.14,0:41:45.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(335,164)}瑟曦·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}太后
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.14,0:10:35.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(461,217)}大麻雀\N{\b0\fs12}总主教
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.14,0:32:43.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(116,254)}梅斯·提利尔\N{\b0\fs12}高庭公爵
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.14,0:39:23.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(455,224)}瓦德·佛雷\N{\b0\fs12}孪河城侯爵
Dialogue: 0,0:41:27.14,0:41:29.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(314,219)}艾德慕·徒利\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:41.44,0:44:43.44,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(639,218)}班扬·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}前守夜人首席游骑兵
Dialogue: 0,0:46:16.14,0:46:18.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(448,253)}丹妮莉丝·坦格利安\N{\b0\fs12}“风暴降生”
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.14,0:32:40.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(362,236)}詹姆·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}御林铁卫
Dialogue: 0,0:46:23.14,0:46:25.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(233,202)}达里奥·纳哈里斯\N{\b0\fs12}雇佣兵
Dialogue: 0,0:48:43.14,0:48:45.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(495,326)}卓耿\N{\b0\fs12}丹妮的黑龙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.14,0:11:26.14,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(140,254)}玛格丽·提利尔\N{\b0\fs12}王后
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.83,0:02:51.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,伊里斯·坦格利安二世: 烧死他们！\N{\fs16}Burn them all!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.47,0:02:52.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,艾德·史塔克: 我妹妹在哪？\N{\fs16}Where's my sister?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.90,0:02:56.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,伊里斯·坦格利安二世: 烧死他们！\N{\fs16}Burn them all!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.24,0:03:28.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,动一下吧\N{\fs16}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.84,0:03:44.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,伊里斯·坦格利安二世: 烧了他们  都烧了！\N{\fs16}Burn them. Burn them all!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.92,0:04:00.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,伊里斯·坦格利安二世: 烧死他们！\N{\fs16}Burn them all!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.70,0:04:11.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,梅拉\N{\fs16}Meera.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.63,0:04:13.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们发现我们了\N{\fs16}They found us.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.84,0:04:23.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对不起\N{\fs16}I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.94,0:05:29.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,跟我来  快点\N{\fs16}Come with me, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.38,0:05:36.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,尸鬼们可不休息\N{\fs16}The dead don't rest.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.54,0:06:04.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,都是绿色的呀\N{\fs16}It's so green.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.35,0:06:06.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,啊 确实\N{\fs16}Oh, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.11,0:06:07.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,等你到了河间地的南边\N{\fs16}Once you get south of the Riverlands,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.02,0:06:10.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就会看到更多不同种类的树木\N{\fs16}very different sorts of trees start to take over.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.02,0:06:14.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,枫树 榆树 山毛榉 杨树\N{\fs16}Maple, elm, beech, poplar.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.29,0:06:20.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有奇怪的柳树\N{\fs16}The odd willow.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.29,0:06:22.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有 夏天快结束了\N{\fs16}And of course now that summer's over,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.86,0:06:25.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,秋色渐浓\N{\fs16}you'll start seeing the autumn colors coming in.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.14,0:06:32.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不过这里的绿色还是比别处更多\N{\fs16}Still, you'll find more green here than anywhere else.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.27,0:06:35.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你紧张了 你一紧张就话痨\N{\fs16}You're nervous. You're a nervous talker.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.75,0:06:43.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一紧张就闭着嘴也不会好到哪去\N{\fs16}That's not any better being a nervous mute.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.81,0:06:45.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我从没想到过我还会回到这\N{\fs16}I didn't think I'd ever come back here
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.82,0:06:50.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我父亲已经逼我放弃了爵位和继承权\N{\fs16}after my father made me renounce my title and inheritance
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.16,0:06:52.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,呃 还威胁我 不那么做的话就杀了我\N{\fs16}and, well, threaten to kill me if I didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.16,0:06:56.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那时我就是个不受欢迎的人\N{\fs16}A person just doesn't feel welcome at that point.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.60,0:07:01.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我也压根没想到会把这小家伙介绍给我的家人\N{\fs16}And I certainly didn't expect to be introducing him to my family.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.30,0:07:05.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那么你应该知道怎样跟他们说\N{\fs16}So you know what to tell them.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.87,0:07:07.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就说小山姆是你的孩子\N{\fs16}That Little Sam is your baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.84,0:07:09.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对  这很重要\N{\fs16}Yes, now that's very important.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.51,0:07:13.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果他认同小山姆是他的孙子 那他就会接受你\N{\fs16}If he thinks that Little Sam is his grandchild, he'll take you in.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.08,0:07:17.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他会有人教导 识字读书\N{\fs16}He'll get an education. He'll learn to read.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.59,0:07:20.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你也可以帮着教他 对吧？\N{\fs16}And you can help teach him. Huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.59,0:07:23.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你都给你家人说了我的哪些情况？\N{\fs16}What did you tell your family about me?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.99,0:07:29.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我告诉他们我在北境遇到了你\N{\fs16}I told them I met you in the North.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.50,0:07:31.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,说了有多北么？\N{\fs16}Did you tell them how far north?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.47,0:07:34.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,呃 信里面写不下那么多\N{\fs16}Well, it wasn't a very large piece of parchment.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.67,0:07:36.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你没告诉他们我真正的家乡？\N{\fs16}You didn't tell them where I'm really from?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.44,0:07:38.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没说我是个野人？\N{\fs16}You didn't tell them I'm a wildling?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.34,0:07:40.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,问题是……\N{\fs16}The thing is...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.54,0:07:42.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我父亲不喜欢野人\N{\fs16}my father doesn't like wildlings.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.98,0:07:47.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他希望我能够像男人一样"去杀掉混蛋野人"\N{\fs16}He hoped I'd make a man of myself by "killing some bloody wildlings,"
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.45,0:07:51.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所以这是一个尽可能要避免的话题\N{\fs16}so it's probably a good subject to avoid if at all possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.99,0:07:56.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我……觉得我们到了\N{\fs16}I... think we're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.75,0:08:27.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,山姆\N{\fs16}Sam.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.06,0:08:29.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哦 山姆\N{\fs16}Oh, Sam.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.46,0:08:31.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,噢 你好 母亲\N{\fs16}Oh, hello, Mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.29,0:08:36.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我以为再也见不到你了\N{\fs16}I never thought I'd see you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.36,0:08:38.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你看起来很棒\N{\fs16}You look wonderful.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.87,0:08:43.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,塔拉？\N{\fs16}Talla?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.30,0:08:46.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,天呐 真是女大十八变\N{\fs16}Gods, you're a woman now.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.17,0:08:48.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,父亲说我必须嫁给西蒙·佛索威\N{\fs16}Father says I have to marry Symun Fossoway.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.74,0:08:51.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 他牙齿是黄色的……  - 够了 塔拉\N{\fs16}- He has yellow teeth... - That's enough, Talla.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.58,0:08:58.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对了 母亲 这是吉莉\N{\fs16}Oh... Mother, this is Gilly.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.42,0:09:02.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,噢 天呐\N{\fs16}Oh, my.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.79,0:09:04.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你真可爱\N{\fs16}You are lovely.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.86,0:09:09.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很荣幸能见到您 塔利夫人\N{\fs16}I am happy to know you, Lady Tarly.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.70,0:09:15.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哦  还有这个小家伙\N{\fs16}Oh, and this,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.67,0:09:18.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是我们的儿子 山姆威尔\N{\fs16}this is our son Samwell.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.91,0:09:26.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你好啊 小家伙\N{\fs16}Hello, little one.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.21,0:09:29.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是我 你的奶奶\N{\fs16}It's me, your grandmother.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.35,0:09:32.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我能抱抱他么？\N{\fs16}May I hold him?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.36,0:09:34.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,当然可以\N{\fs16}Yes, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.79,0:09:43.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你好奇心很强 我看得出来\N{\fs16}You have a curious mind, I can tell.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.33,0:09:46.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你会像你爸爸一样博览群书\N{\fs16}You'll be a scholar like your father.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.43,0:09:49.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,父亲在哪？\N{\fs16}Where is Father?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.79,0:09:50.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,狄肯呢？\N{\fs16}And Dickon?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.84,0:09:52.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们去打猎了\N{\fs16}They're on a hunt.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.77,0:09:55.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们会回来跟我们一起吃晚饭\N{\fs16}They'll join us for dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.01,0:09:59.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,进来吧 这么远的路\N{\fs16}Come inside. Such a journey.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.45,0:10:01.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们肯定累坏了\N{\fs16}You must be exhausted.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.25,0:10:04.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,来 长途旅行之后都会想洗澡\N{\fs16}Come, you'll be wanting a bath after all that travel.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.72,0:10:06.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,噢 还有出席晚餐的衣服\N{\fs16}Oh, and a dress for dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.92,0:10:08.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你可以穿我的\N{\fs16}You can wear one of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.69,0:10:10.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你……你喜欢什么颜色？\N{\fs16}What's... what's your color?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.62,0:10:12.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,深蓝还是银色？\N{\fs16}Midnight blue or silver?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.09,0:10:15.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大概是银色？ 来\N{\fs16}Silver, maybe. Come.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.30,0:10:17.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果你需要的话 可以选一个我的卧室\N{\fs16}You can choose one of my bedrooms if you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.67,0:10:29.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没有别的办法了么？\N{\fs16}Is there no other way?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.31,0:10:30.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你很怕她出事？\N{\fs16}You're afraid for her?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.98,0:10:33.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我当然怕她出事！\N{\fs16}Of course I'm afraid for her!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.32,0:10:39.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是因为好像这样做太危险\N{\fs16}It just seems very dangerous.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.02,0:10:42.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她会被全程保护\N{\fs16}She'll be protected the entire way.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.56,0:10:45.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,教团武装对那些\N{\fs16}The Faith Militant are very stern
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.23,0:10:47.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,越界的人非常严厉\N{\fs16}with those who overstep their bounds.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.66,0:10:53.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而且玛格丽王后和你母亲不同\N{\fs16}And Queen Margaery isn't your mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.33,0:10:56.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我觉得诸神可能会引导人们\N{\fs16}I suspect the gods will predispose the common people
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.37,0:10:58.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对她礼貌以待\N{\fs16}to gentleness on her behalf.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.01,0:11:01.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她确实对他们敞开了真心\N{\fs16}She's truly opened her heart to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.58,0:11:05.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她一直都致力于帮助那些贫穷和不幸的人们\N{\fs16}She's always been very devoted to the poor and the unfortunate.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.45,0:11:08.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而且她现在也笃信诸神\N{\fs16}And now she's devoted to the gods as well.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.48,0:11:12.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您想见见她么？\N{\fs16}Would you like to see her?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.57,0:11:35.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们伤害你了吗？\N{\fs16}Have they hurt you?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.91,0:11:37.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有没有虐待你？\N{\fs16}Have they mistreated you?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.41,0:11:40.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 没有 陛下   - 我想你\N{\fs16}- No, Your Grace. - I've missed you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.58,0:11:42.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,比你想得还要多\N{\fs16}More than you could know.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.38,0:11:44.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们很快就能再次相聚\N{\fs16}We'll be together again soon
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.65,0:11:47.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一切都会比之前更好\N{\fs16}and everything will be better than it was before.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.49,0:11:49.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,怎么能更好？\N{\fs16}Better how?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.52,0:11:50.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很快就是……\N{\fs16}Soon the...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.36,0:11:55.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,救赎之路\N{\fs16}walk of atonement.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.66,0:11:58.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他说了没有别的办法\N{\fs16}He says there's no other way.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.90,0:12:02.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你跟他谈过吗 跟大麻雀？\N{\fs16}Have you spoken to him at all, the High Sparrow?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.10,0:12:05.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的 有过几次\N{\fs16}Yes, a few times.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.57,0:12:06.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你呢？\N{\fs16}Have you?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.01,0:12:08.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的 我也有\N{\fs16}Yes, I have.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.61,0:12:11.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他也不完全就是我们认为的那样  是吧？\N{\fs16}He's not quite what we thought he was, is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.27,0:12:15.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你觉得我疯了\N{\fs16}You think I'm mad.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.65,0:12:17.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的话听起来很疯狂\N{\fs16}I sound mad.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.82,0:12:19.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不 不 你没有\N{\fs16}No. No, you don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.85,0:12:21.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你……你永远不会\N{\fs16}You... you could never.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.99,0:12:23.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你说得对 他不是\N{\fs16}You're right, he's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.76,0:12:25.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他更有……\N{\fs16}He's a lot more...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.56,0:12:27.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,正是如此\N{\fs16}He is.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.19,0:12:29.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他有些不一样的经历\N{\fs16}There's something about him.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.40,0:12:31.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他看这个世界的方式\N{\fs16}His way of looking at the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.83,0:12:39.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,承认真实的自我到底是什么确实不是一件简单的事情\N{\fs16}It's not an easy thing admitting to yourself what you really are.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.11,0:12:41.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这已经花了我好一阵子\N{\fs16}It's taken me a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.14,0:12:43.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他帮了我\N{\fs16}He's helped me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.28,0:12:45.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你在说什么？\N{\fs16}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.28,0:12:49.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是个好人 你一直都是好人\N{\fs16}You're a good person. You've always been a good person.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.81,0:12:52.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是我所知道的最好的人\N{\fs16}You're the best person I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.99,0:12:55.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我只是告诉他你对穷人的帮助\N{\fs16}I was just telling him about your devotion to the poor.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.09,0:12:57.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,啊  是的  我去过他们的住处\N{\fs16}Ah, yes, I visited their hovels
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.99,0:13:01.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,喂他们喝汤  确保别人看到我做过这些事情\N{\fs16}and I fed them soup and I made sure I was seen doing it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.83,0:13:06.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但是 我从来都没有给过他们真正需要的东西\N{\fs16}I never gave them what they really needed, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.30,0:13:10.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我想了很久 想到我给自己装扮上多么好看的伪装\N{\fs16}I've had lots of time to think about how good I was at seeming good.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.57,0:13:15.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我给自己讲的那些故事\N{\fs16}All those stories I told myself about who I was
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.28,0:13:17.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,关于我是谁 我为什么要做这些事\N{\fs16}and why I did the things I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.15,0:13:21.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那些故事里面有太多的谎言\N{\fs16}There were so many lies in those stories.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.62,0:13:25.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不懂\N{\fs16}I don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.42,0:13:27.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没事 真没什么\N{\fs16}It's all right. It really is.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.69,0:13:31.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,卸下伪装就像卸下负担\N{\fs16}It's such a relief to let go of those lies.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.23,0:13:38.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,洛拉斯怎么样？\N{\fs16}What about Loras?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.03,0:13:41.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我爱我弟弟\N{\fs16}I love my brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.74,0:13:45.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,永远都爱\N{\fs16}I will always love my brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.67,0:13:49.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他的灵魂纯洁而完美\N{\fs16}His soul is pure and perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.08,0:13:52.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他的罪抹不去那种纯净\N{\fs16}His sins don't erase that purity,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.68,0:13:54.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只是遮蔽了它\N{\fs16}they only obscure it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.82,0:13:59.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他只是需要 为他们赎罪\N{\fs16}He just needs... to atone for them.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.45,0:14:01.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们都是如此\N{\fs16}We all do.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.86,0:14:05.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,或早或晚 必有一劫\N{\fs16}Sooner or later, one way or another.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.39,0:14:09.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,诸神对我们都早有安排\N{\fs16}The gods have a plan for us all.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.78,0:14:27.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,穿着这个不好走路\N{\fs16}It's hard to walk in this.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.82,0:14:31.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,裙子好看\N{\fs16}It's beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.59,0:14:35.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你真好看\N{\fs16}You're beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.60,0:15:26.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这鹿肉 很好吃\N{\fs16}This venison, it's very tasty.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.57,0:15:29.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是今天猎到的吗？\N{\fs16}Is it from today's hunt?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.21,0:15:31.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,呃 不是\N{\fs16}Well, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.21,0:15:33.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,今天的我们还没处理好\N{\fs16}We haven't been able to cure that one yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.25,0:15:35.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是上周的\N{\fs16}This is last week's.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.23,0:15:38.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哦 当然 很抱歉\N{\fs16}Oh, of course. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.89,0:15:40.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们走了太久的路\N{\fs16}Long journey.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.95,0:15:43.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们从七十码外的地方\N{\fs16}Brought it down from 70 yards.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.56,0:15:45.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一箭中的\N{\fs16}One shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.76,0:15:48.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哦 那……那可真是够远的\N{\fs16}Oh, that's... that's a fair distance.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.59,0:15:51.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你在长城的时候经常打猎吗？\N{\fs16}So do you do much hunting up at the Wall?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.77,0:15:54.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哦 是啊 没错\N{\fs16}Oh, yes. Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.53,0:15:56.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我经常去\N{\fs16}A good amount.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.27,0:15:58.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在长城以北的地方\N{\fs16}North of the Wall,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.94,0:16:01.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不打猎就没得吃\N{\fs16}you don't hunt, you don't eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.74,0:16:04.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,猎物大多是鹿吧？也是麋鹿？\N{\fs16}Mostly deer or is it elk as well?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.11,0:16:08.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,主要是兔子\N{\fs16}Rabbits.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.42,0:16:10.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有些时候会打松鼠\N{\fs16}Sometimes squirrels.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.89,0:16:17.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我说的“我们”主要是指我和我朋友琼恩\N{\fs16}I say "we," it's my friend Jon mostly.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.79,0:16:19.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有时艾迪也会去\N{\fs16}Sometimes Edd.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.59,0:16:21.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哦 还有吉莉\N{\fs16}Oh, and Gilly.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.46,0:16:24.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她……她也是个相当棒的猎手\N{\fs16}She's... she's quite a good hunter as well.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.47,0:16:27.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女猎手\N{\fs16}Huntress.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.87,0:16:30.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我觉得在你的家乡这应该挺常见的\N{\fs16}I imagine it's common where you're from.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.17,0:16:33.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们遇到过最后壁炉城的安柏大人 对吧 蓝道\N{\fs16}We once met a man, Lord Umber from Last Hearth, wasn't it, Randyll,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.71,0:16:35.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他说他教自己所有的女儿打猎\N{\fs16}who said he taught all his daughters how to hunt.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.04,0:16:38.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你父亲教你打猎的？\N{\fs16}Your father taught you to hunt?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.65,0:16:40.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们的父亲可永远都不会这么做\N{\fs16}Our father would never teach us.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.58,0:16:44.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我猜没准他能从你父亲身上学点东西\N{\fs16}I think our father could learn a thing or two from your father.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.68,0:16:45.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,到此为止\N{\fs16}That's enough of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.46,0:16:51.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,山姆威尔 你还想再来点面包吗？\N{\fs16}Samwell, would you care for more bread?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.12,0:16:54.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哦 是的 要的 谢谢\N{\fs16}Oh, yes. Yes, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.19,0:16:55.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谢谢您 母亲\N{\fs16}Thank you, Mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.87,0:17:02.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你还嫌自己不够胖吗？\N{\fs16}Not fat enough already?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.95,0:17:16.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是奉总司令大人的命令来到南方的\N{\fs16}I travelled south under orders from the Lord Commander.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.88,0:17:19.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 他想让我…… - 我读了你的信\N{\fs16}- He wants me to... - I read your letter.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.95,0:17:22.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想要当学士\N{\fs16}You're to be a maester.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.02,0:17:24.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fs16}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.46,0:17:26.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一旦我拥有了自己的颈链\N{\fs16}And once I have my chain,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.33,0:17:28.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,便会回到黑城堡\N{\fs16}I'll return to Castle Black.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.93,0:17:32.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我以为守夜人会把你变成一个真男人\N{\fs16}I thought the Night's Watch might make a man of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.73,0:17:35.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,至少也该有点男人的模样\N{\fs16}Something resembling a man at least.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.34,0:17:40.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,结果你却依旧如此软弱 胖得不行\N{\fs16}You managed to stay soft and fat.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.78,0:17:45.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就知道一头扎进书堆\N{\fs16}Your nose buried in books.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.48,0:17:49.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一辈子都在阅读更优秀的人所取得的成就\N{\fs16}Spending your life reading about the achievements of better men.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.02,0:17:53.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我敢打赌你还是骑不上马 挥不动剑\N{\fs16}I'll wager you still can't sit a horse or wield a sword.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.59,0:17:56.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,蓝道 成为守夜人的学士是很高的荣誉\N{\fs16}Randyll, to be maester of the Night's Watch is a great honor.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.79,0:17:59.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他能挥剑\N{\fs16}He can wield a sword.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.49,0:18:02.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他曾杀死一个瑟恩人\N{\fs16}He killed a Thenn.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.40,0:18:05.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还杀死过一个异鬼\N{\fs16}He killed a white walker.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.32,0:18:09.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,根本没有异鬼这种东西\N{\fs16}There's no such thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.07,0:18:14.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在南下黑城堡的路上 我亲眼所见\N{\fs16}I saw it with my own eyes on our way down to Castle Black.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.54,0:18:18.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他把一柄匕首捅进了异鬼的心脏\N{\fs16}He drove a dagger into the walker's heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.28,0:18:21.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他不止一次冒着生命危险救我\N{\fs16}He risked his own life to save mine more than once.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.88,0:18:25.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他是一名战士 取得的成就是你们一辈子都得不到的\N{\fs16}He's a greater warrior than either of you will ever be.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.82,0:18:30.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你南下黑城堡的路上？\N{\fs16}Your way down to Castle Black?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.73,0:18:35.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他在哪儿杀死异鬼的？\N{\fs16}Where did he kill a white walker?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.40,0:18:40.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你从哪儿来？\N{\fs16}Where are you from?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.70,0:18:43.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是怎么遇到我儿子的？\N{\fs16}How'd you come to meet my son?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.55,0:18:47.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,守夜人去了我们的堡垒\N{\fs16}The Night's Watch came to our keep.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.96,0:18:49.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 哪儿的堡垒？ - 吉莉\N{\fs16}- Where? - Gilly.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.45,0:18:51.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 长城以北 - 长城以北？\N{\fs16}- North of the Wall. - North of the Wall?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.15,0:18:58.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是个野人\N{\fs16}You're a wildling.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.63,0:19:09.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,近几个世纪以来 七大王国都在抵抗这些野蛮人的入侵\N{\fs16}The Seven Kingdoms have waged war against these savages for centuries
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.90,0:19:14.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而我却在家里盛情款待他们中的一个\N{\fs16}and here I sit hosting one in my hall
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.96,0:19:16.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,真是多亏了我的好儿子\N{\fs16}thanks to my son.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.91,0:19:20.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,看见那把剑了吗？\N{\fs16}See that sword?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.31,0:19:26.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,它叫“碎心”\N{\fs16}It's called Heartsbane.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.31,0:19:30.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,已经在我们家族流传了五百多年\N{\fs16}It's been in our family for 500 years.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.12,0:19:32.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,它是瓦雷利亚钢剑\N{\fs16}It's Valyrian steel.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.29,0:19:34.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,全世界也没有几把留存了\N{\fs16}Only a handful of them left in the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.85,0:19:38.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在我死后 它理应由我的长子继承\N{\fs16}It's supposed to go to my firstborn son after I die.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.83,0:19:40.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,由他继承\N{\fs16}To him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.73,0:19:45.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但他永远也别想得到这把剑\N{\fs16}He will never wield that sword.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.23,0:19:49.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果他成为了角陵的塔利伯爵\N{\fs16}If he were to become Lord Tarly of Horn Hill,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.44,0:19:51.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那将会是这个家族的末日\N{\fs16}it would be the end of this house.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.41,0:19:57.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我见到你的时候以为你是个鼹鼠村的妓女\N{\fs16}I took you for a Mole's Town whore when I saw you
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.48,0:19:59.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,然后我接受了这个事实\N{\fs16}and I made my peace with that.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.15,0:20:00.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有什么人会爱上他？\N{\fs16}Who else would have him?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.82,0:20:04.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我真是高估了他\N{\fs16}But I overestimated him.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.02,0:20:07.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不\N{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.56,0:20:13.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一个野人婊子诱惑了我儿子\N{\fs16}It was a wildling whore that seduced my son.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.90,0:20:17.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你这是在报复我吗 小子？\N{\fs16}This you getting back at me, boy?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.08,0:20:24.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,把那东西带到我的餐桌上 让它和我共进晚餐？\N{\fs16}Bringing that to my table and making me dine with it?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.77,0:20:29.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你得到了自己一直想要的 对吗？\N{\fs16}And you got what you were after, didn't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.31,0:20:33.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一个私生子 一个血统不正的私生子\N{\fs16}A bastard. A half-breed bastard.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.68,0:20:36.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,作为你回家的邀请函\N{\fs16}Your invitation into our home.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.86,0:20:39.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,来吧 亲爱的 塔拉\N{\fs16}Come, my dear. Talla.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.59,0:20:42.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我吃不下去了\N{\fs16}I've lost my appetite.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.66,0:20:44.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他丢了我们家族的脸\N{\fs16}He dishonors us.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.12,0:20:46.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你丢了你自己的脸\N{\fs16}You dishonor yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.90,0:20:54.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你母亲心地善良 你不配做她的儿子\N{\fs16}Your mother's a fine woman. You're not worthy of her.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.07,0:21:01.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,为了让她开心 我会留下那野人 她可以在厨房打杂\N{\fs16}To please her, I'll take the wildling in. She can work in the kitchens.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.58,0:21:04.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的私生子也可以由我们抚养\N{\fs16}The bastard will be raised here.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.45,0:21:10.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但今晚会是你这辈子在角陵的最后一个晚上\N{\fs16}But this will be the last night you ever spend at Horn Hill.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.76,0:21:21.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我很抱歉让他这样对待你\N{\fs16}I'm sorry I let him treat you that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.06,0:21:25.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我害怕他会赶走你和小山姆\N{\fs16}I was afraid he'd turn you and Little Sam away.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.53,0:21:28.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我并不生你的气\N{\fs16}I'm not angry at you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.54,0:21:30.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让我生气的是那些可怕的人\N{\fs16}I'm angry that horrible people
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.67,0:21:33.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们那样对待好人却不受到任何惩罚\N{\fs16}can treat good people that way and get away with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.75,0:21:40.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你什么时候离开？\N{\fs16}When do you have to go?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.78,0:21:45.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,天一亮就得走\N{\fs16}First light.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.63,0:21:58.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,替我向他道别\N{\fs16}Say good-bye to him for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.37,0:22:09.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不是他所说的那样 山姆\N{\fs16}You're not what he thinks you are, Sam.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.58,0:22:12.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他并不了解你是什么样的人\N{\fs16}He doesn't know what you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.45,0:22:17.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,再见 吉莉\N{\fs16}Good-bye, Gilly.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.76,0:23:03.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 山姆？ - 我们该走了\N{\fs16}- Sam? - We're leaving.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.70,0:23:05.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 什么？ - 收拾好东西\N{\fs16}- What? - Get your things.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.63,0:23:08.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我什么东西也没有\N{\fs16}I don't have any things.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.77,0:23:11.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 你在干什么啊？ - 我们应该在一起\N{\fs16}- What are you doing? - We belong together.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.71,0:23:13.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们三个\N{\fs16}All of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.71,0:23:16.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你母亲和妹妹怎么办？\N{\fs16}What about your mother and sister?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.34,0:23:18.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哦 她们会理解的\N{\fs16}Oh, they'll understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.38,0:23:20.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我还穿着你妹妹的裙子呢\N{\fs16}Your sister's dress.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.15,0:23:22.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她不会介意的\N{\fs16}She won't mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.95,0:23:25.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,反正你穿着更好看\N{\fs16}Looks better on you anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.92,0:23:27.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,山姆\N{\fs16}Sam.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.99,0:23:30.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那是你父亲的剑\N{\fs16}That's your father's sword.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.16,0:23:32.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是我家族的剑\N{\fs16}It's my family's sword.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.00,0:23:38.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,山姆\N{\fs16}Sam.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.87,0:23:41.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他不会来找剑吗？\N{\fs16}Won't he come for it?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.00,0:23:45.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那就让他来啊\N{\fs16}He can bloody well try.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.64,0:23:51.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,狮子与玫瑰已合而为一\N{\fs16}The lion and the rose are one.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.71,0:23:53.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,为此我感谢天上的神祇\N{\fs16}I thank the gods above.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.85,0:23:56.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而你 我美丽动人的新娘\N{\fs16}And to you, my beauteous bride,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.45,0:23:58.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我宣誓我的爱至死不渝\N{\fs16}I pledge undying love.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.59,0:24:02.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,乔佛里国王万岁 玛格丽王后万岁\N{\fs16}Hail King Joffrey. Hail Queen Margaery.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.99,0:24:05.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我将向我的新后祝酒致敬\N{\fs16}I'll drink a toast to my new queen,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.73,0:24:08.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没有什么比这更加合情\N{\fs16}for there is no one fairer.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.16,0:24:12.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,亲爱的舅舅 你愿分享我的喜悦 做我的御用斟酒人吗？\N{\fs16}Dear Uncle, will you share my joy and be my royal cupbearer?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.47,0:24:15.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大口喝吧 我尊贵的国王\N{\fs16}Drink long and deep, my noble king,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.33,0:24:17.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,尽情享受这杯香甜佳酿\N{\fs16}from this cup of sweet wine.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.67,0:24:20.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这将是他人生的最后一口\N{\fs16}The last drink he shall ever take.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.31,0:24:22.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而我则会迎来美妙的复仇\N{\fs16}And vengeance shall be mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.16,0:24:36.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,毒药！\N{\fs16}Poison!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.16,0:24:37.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谋杀！\N{\fs16}Murder!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.02,0:24:40.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我无法喘息 我……我将死去\N{\fs16}I gasp. I... I die.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.86,0:24:45.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我无法站立\N{\fs16}I limp.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.47,0:24:48.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就是那人……\N{\fs16}And it was he...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.87,0:24:50.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他毒杀了我\N{\fs16}...that poisoned me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.90,0:24:53.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我邪恶的舅舅小恶魔\N{\fs16}My evil Uncle Imp.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.18,0:25:01.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,冷静下来 亲爱的\N{\fs16}Calm down, dear.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.99,0:25:07.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的初生子\N{\fs16}My firstborn son.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.05,0:25:10.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的小金狮\N{\fs16}My golden lion
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.56,0:25:13.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,被无礼 粗暴地害死\N{\fs16}foully, falsely slain.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.69,0:25:17.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我祈祷你能享有永久的宁静\N{\fs16}I pray you found a lasting peace
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.43,0:25:19.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,永不再陷入斗争与痛病\N{\fs16}free from strife and pain.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.07,0:25:24.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,残酷的诸神啊 听我诉说\N{\fs16}Hear my prayer, O cruel gods.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.44,0:25:26.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,请带走我来换取他的重生\N{\fs16}Take my life instead.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.37,0:25:30.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,若我心爱的孩子已经死去 哪怕一天我也难以支撑\N{\fs16}For I cannot face another day when my sweet boy is dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.34,0:25:33.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,灾祸啊\N{\fs16}Oh, woe.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.35,0:25:35.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不幸啊\N{\fs16}Oh, grief.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.82,0:25:40.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,最黑暗的日子啊 我的内心充满了悲伤\N{\fs16}Oh, darkest day, my heart is full of sorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.12,0:25:45.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所有的希望都已离去\N{\fs16}All hope is lost.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.33,0:25:48.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所有的欢乐都已消散\N{\fs16}All joy is gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.40,0:25:54.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,仿佛明日将不会降临这个世上\N{\fs16}And there is no tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.32,0:26:16.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,什么声音？什么味道？\N{\fs16}What is that I hear and smell?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.99,0:26:19.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我就要送那人踏上地狱之道\N{\fs16}Someone I'll soon send to hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.76,0:26:22.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们说泰温·兰尼斯特拉出的都是黄金\N{\fs16}It's time to see if truth they told
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.43,0:26:26.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是时候来看看他们是不是在骗人\N{\fs16}who said Tywin Lannister shits gold.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.30,0:26:30.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你这畜牲 你这畜牲\N{\fs16}You beast. You beast.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.37,0:26:35.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你杀了我妻 现在又将你父亲置于死地\N{\fs16}You killed my wife and now you've taken your father's life.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.31,0:26:38.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不曾有比你更恶毒的子女玷污过这片土地\N{\fs16}No worse child ever stained this land.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.18,0:26:40.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我诅咒我命名你的那日\N{\fs16}Curse the day I named you.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.06,0:26:53.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是我罪恶之极 现在我必须逃离\N{\fs16}My greatest crime. Now I must flee.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.86,0:26:56.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,到狭海彼岸之地\N{\fs16}Then sail across the Narrow Sea
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.76,0:27:00.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,将更多背叛送抵\N{\fs16}to do unto you more treachery.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.00,0:27:04.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,论可怕 寒冬怎与我相比！\N{\fs16}Don't fear winter. Fear me!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.74,0:27:10.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谢谢大家\N{\fs16}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.68,0:27:14.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女士们先生们 向您介绍比安卡\N{\fs16}Ladies and gentlemen, I give you Bianca,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.35,0:27:16.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,克拉伦佐\N{\fs16}Clarenzo.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.38,0:27:20.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,伯波诺\N{\fs16}I give you Bobono.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.12,0:27:22.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,卡梅洛\N{\fs16}I give you Camello.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.66,0:27:24.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,最后隆重介绍\N{\fs16}And last but not least,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:25.02,0:27:27.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,甜美的克连恩夫人\N{\fs16}sweet Lady Crane.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.50,0:27:41.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好好拍拍这衣服 把那些跳蚤甩下去 乖\N{\fs16}Give this a good beating. Shake those fleas out. That's a dear.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.08,0:27:44.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那些观众真是狗屁不懂\N{\fs16}That crowd was shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.62,0:27:50.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女孩\N{\fs16}Girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.72,0:27:53.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你回来做什么？\N{\fs16}What are you doing back here?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.15,0:27:54.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没什么\N{\fs16}Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.65,0:27:58.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那天观众里也有你\N{\fs16}I saw you the other day in the audience.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.12,0:28:01.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这愚蠢的戏你都看过几遍了？\N{\fs16}How many times have you seen this stupid play?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.00,0:28:04.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,三次\N{\fs16}Three times.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.13,0:28:05.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你付钱了么？\N{\fs16}Did you pay?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.79,0:28:08.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没有\N{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.60,0:28:13.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我记得演员去我们村庄时\N{\fs16}I remember when the players came to my village.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.01,0:28:16.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没有钱 于是我偷偷溜了进去\N{\fs16}I didn't have any money, so I snuck in.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.71,0:28:18.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就像你一样\N{\fs16}Just like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.98,0:28:21.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我看到上了妆的脸 戏服\N{\fs16}Saw the painted faces, the costumes,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.18,0:28:22.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,听了歌\N{\fs16}listened to the songs,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.85,0:28:26.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在年轻的恋人相拥而死时痛哭\N{\fs16}cried when the young lovers died in each other's arms.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.39,0:28:30.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,第二天 我离家加入了他们 从此再未回头\N{\fs16}I ran off and joined them the next day, never looked back.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.69,0:28:33.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你演得很精彩\N{\fs16}You're very good.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.19,0:28:34.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我最后那段独白像屎一样\N{\fs16}My final speech is shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.03,0:28:38.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但就像我经常说的 也是摸着良心说的\N{\fs16}But to be fair to myself, which I always like to be,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.40,0:28:40.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,剧本写得不好\N{\fs16}the writing's no good.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.73,0:28:42.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那就别按它来\N{\fs16}So change it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.34,0:28:47.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没有你的话 他们不过就是在放屁打嗝 打打闹闹\N{\fs16}It would all just be farting, belching, and slapping without you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.64,0:28:50.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想怎么改？\N{\fs16}How would you change it?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.18,0:28:59.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,王太后爱她的孩子 胜过一切\N{\fs16}The queen loves her son more than anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.49,0:29:02.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他被夺走生命 她却不及告别\N{\fs16}And he was taken from her before she could say good-bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.62,0:29:04.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她不会只是哭泣\N{\fs16}She wouldn't just cry.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.29,0:29:11.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她会满腔愤怒\N{\fs16}She would be angry.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.23,0:29:13.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她要杀死谋杀她儿子的人\N{\fs16}She would want to kill the person who did this to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.00,0:29:19.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你叫什么名字？\N{\fs16}What's your name?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.91,0:29:23.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,茉慈\N{\fs16}Mercy.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.11,0:29:25.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你有双会说话的眼睛 茉慈\N{\fs16}You have very expressive eyes, Mercy.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.99,0:29:28.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好看的眉毛\N{\fs16}Wonderful eyebrows.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.78,0:29:31.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你喜欢扮成其他人吗？\N{\fs16}Do you like pretending to be other people?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.52,0:29:36.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我得走了 我父亲在等我\N{\fs16}I have to go. My father's waiting for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.36,0:29:47.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,克连恩夫人 他们爱您\N{\fs16}Lady Crane, they loved you.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.20,0:29:49.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们真可爱 要不就是喝醉了\N{\fs16}They were sweet. Or drunk.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.60,0:29:52.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,醉醺醺的可爱\N{\fs16}Drunkenly sweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.24,0:29:53.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奈德死的时候没人笑\N{\fs16}No laugh for Ned's death.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.56,0:29:57.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这些人真是比动物还蠢\N{\fs16}These people are worse than animals.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.85,0:30:01.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但他们爱她 他们全都爱她\N{\fs16}But they loved her. They all love her.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.61,0:30:05.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是啊 你人兽通吃啊\N{\fs16}Yes, you are adored by people and animals alike.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.48,0:30:08.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我只是善用天赋 尽己所能\N{\fs16}I do what I can with what I'm given.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.12,0:30:10.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,用你的天赋？\N{\fs16}With what you're given?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.12,0:30:11.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,额 我在想……\N{\fs16}Well, I was thinking...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.06,0:30:13.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哦 现在我们都是思想家了 是么？\N{\fs16}Oh, we're all thinkers now, are we?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.66,0:30:16.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奶头里都是想法\N{\fs16}Full to the tits with ideas.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.56,0:30:19.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 我不是说……－你有个想法 我有个想法\N{\fs16}- I didn't mean... - You have ideas, I have ideas,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.97,0:30:21.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他也有个想法\N{\fs16}he has ideas.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.83,0:30:24.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,为什么我的想法比你们的更有价值？\N{\fs16}Why should my ideas have any more value than yours
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.64,0:30:27.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就因为我一辈子都在干这个\N{\fs16}simply because I've been doing this my whole life?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.04,0:30:30.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谁想来评判我的工作？\N{\fs16}Who is anyone to judge my work?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.34,0:30:33.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是我的专业 我知道我在做什么\N{\fs16}This is my profession. I know what I'm doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.21,0:30:35.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你没有权利拥有想法\N{\fs16}You have no right to an opinion.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.46,0:30:50.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,小心那个人\N{\fs16}Careful of that one.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.53,0:30:56.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她想要你死\N{\fs16}She wants you dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.88,0:31:37.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如何？\N{\fs16}And?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.54,0:31:39.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如我所料\N{\fs16}As I expected.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:41.48,0:31:43.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,可惜了\N{\fs16}A shame.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.32,0:31:45.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女孩很有天赋\N{\fs16}A girl had many gifts.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.32,0:31:50.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你答应我的\N{\fs16}You promised me.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.33,0:31:58.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别让她太受罪\N{\fs16}Don't let her suffer.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.78,0:32:52.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,全体立定！\N{\fs16}Company, halt!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.15,0:32:55.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大人\N{\fs16}My lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.85,0:32:57.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大人\N{\fs16}My lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.33,0:33:03.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,朋友们 是时候了\N{\fs16}My friends, the hour has come.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.20,0:33:06.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,疯狂已经占领了这座城市\N{\fs16}Madness has overtaken this city
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.03,0:33:11.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,置我的孩子于它的魔爪之下\N{\fs16}and grasped in its claws my children.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.74,0:33:14.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但现在我们必须将它赶走\N{\fs16}But now we must drive it back
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.01,0:33:18.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让它从哪来就回哪去\N{\fs16}under the rocks whence it came.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.18,0:33:22.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,疯狂已到尽头！\N{\fs16}Madness has had its day!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.88,0:33:28.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,齐步走！\N{\fs16}Forward, march!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.79,0:33:34.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,富贵抑或贫穷 高尚抑或平庸\N{\fs16}Rich or poor, noble or common,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.63,0:33:38.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一旦有罪 皆需赎罪\N{\fs16}if we sin, we must atone.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.37,0:33:42.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,提利尔家族的玛格丽\N{\fs16}Margaery of House Tyrell
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.97,0:33:45.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,以罪人之身至此\N{\fs16}came to us a sinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.11,0:33:50.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她在圣堂中面对诸神 撒了谎\N{\fs16}She stood before the gods in the holy sept and lied.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.54,0:33:53.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她对其弟犯下的罪行视若无睹\N{\fs16}She turned a blind eye to her brother's sins.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:53.68,0:33:56.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她令她的家族蒙羞\N{\fs16}She disgraced her house,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.35,0:33:59.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,令国王蒙羞 令自己蒙羞\N{\fs16}her king, and herself.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.22,0:34:33.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,全体立定！\N{\fs16}Company, halt!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.19,0:34:35.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,向前\N{\fs16}Face front!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.55,0:34:37.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,向左转！\N{\fs16}Turn!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.19,0:34:41.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,提利尔大人\N{\fs16}Lord Tyrell.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.06,0:34:44.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,詹姆爵士\N{\fs16}Ser Jaime.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.43,0:34:46.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,抱歉打断\N{\fs16}Sorry to interrupt.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.43,0:34:49.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们为玛格丽王后和洛拉斯·提利尔爵士而来\N{\fs16}We're here for Queen Margaery and Ser Loras Tyrell.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.24,0:34:52.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,把他们交出来 否则我们不客气\N{\fs16}Give them to us and we'll be on our way.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.60,0:34:56.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我无权把他们交给你们\N{\fs16}I don't have the authority to give them to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.81,0:34:59.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而你们也无权把他们带走\N{\fs16}And you don't have the authority to take them.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.75,0:35:01.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对啊\N{\fs16}That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.29,0:35:13.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,执矛！\N{\fs16}Lock spears!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.43,0:35:17.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我代表拜拉席恩家族的托曼一世国王\N{\fs16}I speak for King Tommen of House Baratheon, First of His Name.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.70,0:35:20.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,诸神并不认为他有权处理此事\N{\fs16}The gods don't recognize his authority in this matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.87,0:35:23.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你已经侮辱了一个大家族\N{\fs16}You've already insulted one great house.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.70,0:35:25.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不会再有第二个\N{\fs16}It won't happen twice.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.77,0:35:28.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,玛格丽·提利尔若走下这条街道\N{\fs16}Every last sparrow will die
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.11,0:35:30.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我就把所有麻雀都杀光\N{\fs16}before Margaery Tyrell walks down that street.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.68,0:35:33.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因侍奉诸神而死\N{\fs16}To die in the service of the gods
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.28,0:35:35.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们每个人都会倍感欣慰\N{\fs16}would please each and every one of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.58,0:35:37.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们渴望如此\N{\fs16}We yearn for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:46.96,0:35:49.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我们今天不必如此\N{\fs16}But there is no call for it today.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.33,0:35:55.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,今天不会有赎罪游街\N{\fs16}There will be no walk of atonement.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.72,0:36:13.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,列队！\N{\fs16}Order up.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.82,0:36:16.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,玛格丽王后已经赎罪\N{\fs16}Queen Margaery has already atoned for her sins
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.89,0:36:19.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她已将另一人\N{\fs16}by bringing another
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.99,0:36:22.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,带入七神的光芒之下\N{\fs16}into the true light of the Seven.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.09,0:36:55.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们一同宣布\N{\fs16}Together we announce
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.39,0:36:57.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,迎来一个崭新的和谐时代\N{\fs16}a new age of harmony.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.96,0:37:00.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,迎来王权和神权的\N{\fs16}A holy alliance
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.00,0:37:04.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,神圣同盟\N{\fs16}between the Crown and the Faith.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.69,0:37:23.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,托曼国王万岁 愿诸神保佑你 玛格丽王后\N{\fs16}Long live King Tommen and bless you, Queen Margaery!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.79,0:37:26.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,王权和神权\N{\fs16}The Crown and the Faith
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.29,0:37:30.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是这个世界的两大支柱\N{\fs16}are the twin pillars upon which the world rests.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.13,0:37:35.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们将一同恢复七国的荣耀\N{\fs16}Together we will restore the Seven Kingdoms to glory.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:54.20,0:37:55.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,怎么回事？\N{\fs16}What's happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.85,0:37:57.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们被耍了\N{\fs16}He's beaten us.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.96,0:37:59.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就是这么回事\N{\fs16}That's what's happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.71,0:38:17.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你跟教会作对 就是跟国王作对\N{\fs16}When you attack the Faith, you attack the Crown.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.81,0:38:20.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,任何跟国王作对的人\N{\fs16}Anyone who attacks the Crown is unfit
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.88,0:38:23.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,都不适合担任御林铁卫\N{\fs16}to serve as Lord Commander of the Kingsguard.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.58,0:38:27.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,从你出生之前我一直是御林铁卫\N{\fs16}I've been a member of the Kingsguard since before you were born.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.42,0:38:32.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不必如此 你不必做任何事\N{\fs16}You don't have to do this. You don't have to do anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.86,0:38:36.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我必须给诸神交代\N{\fs16}I have to answer to the gods.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.90,0:38:39.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,坐在上王位的人不用给教会任何交代\N{\fs16}Not when you're sitting in that chair.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.27,0:38:45.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,此事的决定没有回旋余地\N{\fs16}The Crown's decision on this matter is final.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.01,0:38:50.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那你要我脱光了游街吗？\N{\fs16}Will I be walking naked in the streets?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.04,0:38:53.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还是说我会在圣堂地牢里待上几个月\N{\fs16}Or will I spend a few months in the sept dungeons first
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.65,0:38:55.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,教教我什么叫诸神的仁慈？\N{\fs16}to teach me about the gods' mercy?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:59.99,0:39:04.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你已经忠诚地侍奉你的家族和国王很多年了\N{\fs16}You have served your house and your king faithfully for many years.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.39,0:39:06.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你将继续如此\N{\fs16}And you will continue to do so.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.39,0:39:10.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但不是在君临\N{\fs16}But not in this city.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.60,0:39:16.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你丢掉了它？\N{\fs16}You've lost it?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.70,0:39:20.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的 父亲\N{\fs16}Yes, Father.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:20.11,0:39:23.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那是座城堡 不是他妈的绵羊\N{\fs16}It's a castle, not a bloody sheep.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.14,0:39:26.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你还知道它在哪儿吧\N{\fs16}Presumably you still know where it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:26.41,0:39:28.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不是弄丢了奔流城\N{\fs16}You didn't lose Riverrun.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.11,0:39:30.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而是让黑鱼抢去了\N{\fs16}You let the Blackfish take it from you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:30.35,0:39:33.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他突袭我们 他比任何人都熟悉那座城堡\N{\fs16}He surprised us. He knows the castle better than anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.42,0:39:36.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,红色婚礼之后 你的确把黑鱼弄丢了\N{\fs16}You did lose the Blackfish after the Red Wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.89,0:39:39.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他就在这个大厅里 你却让他给跑了\N{\fs16}You had him right here in this hall and you let him leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.99,0:39:42.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我让你去抓住他 杀掉他\N{\fs16}Then when I told you to hunt him down and kill him,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.59,0:39:43.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你却连人影都没找到\N{\fs16}you couldn't find him.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.06,0:39:46.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这才叫弄丢了\N{\fs16}That's what it means to lose something.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.26,0:39:49.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如今他回来了 还抢去了奔流城\N{\fs16}Now he's come back and taken Riverrun.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.80,0:39:51.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不觉得应该怪咱们\N{\fs16}I don't think it's fair to blame us...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.07,0:39:55.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,三百年来 咱们一直在亲徒利家的靴子\N{\fs16}For 300 years we kissed Tully boots,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.44,0:39:59.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,向他们和他们那臭烘烘的鳟鱼旗子誓忠\N{\fs16}swore oaths to them and their stinking fish banners.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.45,0:40:01.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,再也不能这样了 奔流城是咱们的\N{\fs16}Not again. Riverrun is ours.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:01.78,0:40:04.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,给我抢回来！\N{\fs16}Take it back!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.22,0:40:05.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们人手不够\N{\fs16}We don't have the men.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.85,0:40:09.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,咱们的人手是那条死鱼的十倍\N{\fs16}We've got 10 times as many men as the damn Blackfish.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.29,0:40:12.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,梅利斯特家族叛变了 布莱伍德家族也是\N{\fs16}The Mallisters have risen against us. And the Blackwoods.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.42,0:40:15.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,无旗兄弟会在召集平民造反\N{\fs16}The Brotherhood Without Banners is rallying the commoners against us,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.73,0:40:17.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,袭击咱们的补给车队和营地\N{\fs16}raiding our supply trains and camps.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.76,0:40:20.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奔流城经得住一年的围攻\N{\fs16}Riverrun can withstand a siege for a year.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.50,0:40:24.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果你们只提得出借口 不如让她来管事\N{\fs16}If I want excuses, I'll put her in charge.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.34,0:40:26.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们在嘲笑咱们\N{\fs16}They're laughing at us.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.20,0:40:28.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,整个河间地\N{\fs16}All across the Riverlands
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.17,0:40:29.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,直到君临\N{\fs16}right down to King's Landing,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.01,0:40:31.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,都在嘲笑咱们\N{\fs16}they're laughing at us.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.74,0:40:34.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我睡觉的时候都听得见！\N{\fs16}I hear it in my sleep!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.38,0:40:37.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们真是不走运 我还没死呢\N{\fs16}I'm not dead yet, unfortunately for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.48,0:40:42.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在他们把自己的嘲笑吞回去噎死之前  我绝不咽气\N{\fs16}And I'll not leave this world until they all choke on that laughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.32,0:40:44.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,把城堡夺回来\N{\fs16}Take that castle back.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.32,0:40:48.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他不会投降的 父亲\N{\fs16}He'll never yield, Father.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.94,0:40:51.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哦 他会的\N{\fs16}Oh, he'll yield.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:55.93,0:40:58.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你把你那把刀拿给他看\N{\fs16}You'll show him the knife you used
Dialogue: 0,0:40:58.77,0:41:02.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那把刀杀了罗柏·史塔克的婊子肚子里的孩子\N{\fs16}to kill Robb Stark's child in his whore mother's belly,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.57,0:41:04.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你也把你的刀拿出来\N{\fs16}and you'll show him the knife you used
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.94,0:41:07.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那把割了他侄女喉咙的刀\N{\fs16}to open his niece's throat.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.18,0:41:09.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,然后你们给他提提醒\N{\fs16}And you'll remind him who it was
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.25,0:41:13.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,红色婚礼是为谁办的婚礼\N{\fs16}that got married at the Red Wedding in the first place.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:13.22,0:41:14.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是为他侄子\N{\fs16}His nephew.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.14,0:41:32.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,开心点 艾德慕大人\N{\fs16}Cheer up, Lord Edmure.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.87,0:41:34.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你要回家了\N{\fs16}You're going home.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.04,0:41:38.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我被派去对付黑鱼\N{\fs16}I'm being sent to deal with the Blackfish.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:38.64,0:41:41.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,瓦德·佛雷显然没法自己应付\N{\fs16}Apparently Walder Frey can't manage it on his own
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.61,0:41:43.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为他都四百岁了\N{\fs16}because he's 400 years old.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.52,0:41:46.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,给我一支军队去河间地\N{\fs16}Sent me with an army to the Riverlands
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.12,0:41:47.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,围城估计得持续几个月\N{\fs16}and a siege that could last months.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:48.09,0:41:50.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去外地带兵\N{\fs16}Better you're elsewhere at the head of an army
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.62,0:41:52.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,总比被抓进圣堂的地牢好\N{\fs16}than in the sept dungeons.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.30,0:41:55.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不会去河间地的\N{\fs16}I'm not going to the Riverlands.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:58.23,0:41:59.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那你想干嘛？\N{\fs16}What, then?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.57,0:42:03.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我要给波隆备下世人不敢想象的巨额酬金\N{\fs16}I'm going to give Bronn the largest bag of gold anyone's ever seen
Dialogue: 0,0:42:03.77,0:42:06.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让他召集最好的杀手\N{\fs16}and have him gather the best killers he knows.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:06.74,0:42:10.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,然后我带他们去大圣堂 砍掉大麻雀的头\N{\fs16}I'll take them to the sept and I'll remove the High Sparrow's head
Dialogue: 0,0:42:10.21,0:42:12.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,砍掉所有麻雀的头\N{\fs16}and every other sparrow head I can find.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.14,0:42:15.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-你不能这么做 -他抢走了咱们的儿子！他偷走了咱们的儿子！\N{\fs16}- You can't. - He has our son! He stole our son!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.81,0:42:17.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他在分裂咱们的家族\N{\fs16}He's torn our family apart.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:17.92,0:42:20.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们该如何处置那些分裂咱们的人？\N{\fs16}How should we treat people who tear us apart?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:20.35,0:42:24.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,绝不放过他们 不给他们任何慈悲\N{\fs16}We should treat them without mercy and we will.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:24.52,0:42:27.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但如果你杀了大麻雀 你不会活着离开圣堂的\N{\fs16}But if you kill the High Sparrow, you won't leave the sept alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.46,0:42:30.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而没有你 一切都毫无意义\N{\fs16}And without you, this is all for nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:30.60,0:42:33.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,立于军队之首 那是属于你的位置\N{\fs16}Stand at the head of our army where you belong,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:34.07,0:42:36.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也是父亲想要你在的位置\N{\fs16}where Father wanted you.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:36.47,0:42:38.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让我们的人看清楚 他们应该向谁效忠\N{\fs16}Show our men where their loyalties belong.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:38.94,0:42:40.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让他们看看兰尼斯特家族的样子\N{\fs16}Show them what Lannisters are,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.04,0:42:42.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,和我们处置敌人的手段\N{\fs16}what we do to our enemies.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:44.34,0:42:46.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,把那个愚蠢的小城堡夺回来\N{\fs16}And take that stupid little castle back
Dialogue: 0,0:42:46.68,0:42:48.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为它是我们的 因为你做得到\N{\fs16}because it's ours and because you can.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:48.98,0:42:52.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你马上要接受审判了 我得守着你\N{\fs16}You'll stand trial soon. I need to be here for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:53.01,0:42:56.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那会是一场比武审判\N{\fs16}It will be a trial by combat.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:56.45,0:42:58.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而我有魔山\N{\fs16}I have the Mountain.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:01.06,0:43:03.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们这些人 只能让我们更强大\N{\fs16}They've made us both stronger, all of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.10,0:43:07.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们不知道我们有多强大\N{\fs16}They have no idea how strong we are.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:07.69,0:43:09.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不知道等待他们的是什么下场\N{\fs16}No idea what we're going to do to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.15,0:43:22.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们一直在一起\N{\fs16}We've always been together.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:22.65,0:43:25.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也会永远在一起\N{\fs16}We'll always be together.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:25.32,0:43:27.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,全世界只有我俩\N{\fs16}We're the only two people in the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:47.71,0:43:49.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你为什么帮我们？\N{\fs16}Why did you help us?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.08,0:43:54.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,三眼乌鸦派我来的\N{\fs16}The Three-Eyed Raven sent for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:54.68,0:43:55.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,三眼乌鸦死了\N{\fs16}The Three-Eyed Raven's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:55.98,0:43:58.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如今他已获重生\N{\fs16}Now he lives again.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:10.73,0:44:13.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我上次见到你的时候 你还是个孩子\N{\fs16}When I last saw you, you were a boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:15.13,0:44:16.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,无所畏惧的孩子\N{\fs16}A fearless boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:16.80,0:44:19.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,最喜欢爬城墙 把他的母亲吓得不轻\N{\fs16}Loved to climb the castle walls, frighten his mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.79,0:44:22.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是谁？\N{\fs16}Who are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:40.07,0:44:41.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,班扬叔叔\N{\fs16}Uncle Benjen.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:43.06,0:44:44.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,琼恩最后一次来信说\N{\fs16}The last letter Jon wrote me
Dialogue: 0,0:44:44.60,0:44:46.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你在长城之外失踪了\N{\fs16}said you had been lost beyond the Wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:49.43,0:44:52.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我带领一队游骑兵深入北方\N{\fs16}I led a ranging party deep into the North
Dialogue: 0,0:44:52.10,0:44:54.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,寻找白鬼的踪迹\N{\fs16}to find white walkers.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.94,0:44:56.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,结果它们找到了我们\N{\fs16}They found us.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:56.64,0:45:00.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一个白鬼用冰剑捅了我的肚子\N{\fs16}A white walker stabbed me in the gut with a sword of ice.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:02.81,0:45:04.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,留下我等死\N{\fs16}Left me there to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:04.58,0:45:05.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,慢慢转化\N{\fs16}To turn.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:07.04,0:45:08.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,森林之子发现了我\N{\fs16}The Children found me.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:08.75,0:45:11.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,阻止了异鬼的魔法\N{\fs16}Stopped the walker's magic from taking hold.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:12.06,0:45:13.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,怎么阻止的？\N{\fs16}How?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:13.46,0:45:15.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,和他们当初造出异鬼的方法一样\N{\fs16}The same way they made the walkers in the first place.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:15.86,0:45:17.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你自己也看到了\N{\fs16}You saw it yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:19.00,0:45:21.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,龙晶\N{\fs16}Dragonglass.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:21.10,0:45:24.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一片龙晶刺入心脏\N{\fs16}A shard of dragonglass plunged into your heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:26.37,0:45:29.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,现在你成为了三眼乌鸦\N{\fs16}You are the Three-Eyed Raven now.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:29.21,0:45:32.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没时间去学 我什么都控制不了\N{\fs16}I didn't have time to learn. I can't control anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:35.18,0:45:37.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在夜王到来之前\N{\fs16}You must learn to control it
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.32,0:45:39.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你必须学会控制\N{\fs16}before the Night King comes.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:41.69,0:45:43.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,喝吧\N{\fs16}Drink.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:45.62,0:45:48.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他总会找到办法\N{\fs16}One way or another,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:48.79,0:45:51.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,攻入人类世界\N{\fs16}he will find his way to the world of men.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:51.60,0:45:54.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,当他到来时\N{\fs16}When he does,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:54.10,0:45:57.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你会在等候着他\N{\fs16}you will be there waiting for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:57.37,0:46:00.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你要做好准备\N{\fs16}And you will be ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:20.96,0:46:23.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一切还好吗？\N{\fs16}Everything all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:23.53,0:46:25.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,到弥林还要骑多少天？\N{\fs16}How many days' ride to Meereen?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:25.66,0:46:27.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,最快一周\N{\fs16}A week at best.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:27.60,0:46:31.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,把我的卡拉萨带回维斯特洛需要多少艘船？\N{\fs16}How many ships will I need to bring my khalasar to Westeros?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:31.10,0:46:33.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,多斯拉克人以及他们的马\N{\fs16}Dothraki and all their horses,
Dialogue: 0,0:46:33.30,0:46:35.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,无垢者 次子团……\N{\fs16}the Unsullied, the Second Sons...
Dialogue: 0,0:46:35.74,0:46:37.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,至少需要一千艘船\N{\fs16}a 1,000 ships easily.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:37.71,0:46:39.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-或许更多 -谁有那么多艘船？\N{\fs16}- Probably more. - And who has that many?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:39.95,0:46:41.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没人有\N{\fs16}Nobody.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:41.55,0:46:43.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只是暂时而已\N{\fs16}Nobody yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:45.65,0:46:49.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所以我们骑马回弥林 然后启航去维斯特洛\N{\fs16}So we ride for Meereen and after that we sail for Westeros.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:49.25,0:46:50.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,然后呢？\N{\fs16}And what then?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:50.86,0:46:53.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会把属于我的东西夺回来\N{\fs16}I take what is mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:53.73,0:46:56.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不适合坐在宫殿里的王位上\N{\fs16}You weren't made to sit on a chair in a palace.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:56.66,0:46:59.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那我适合做什么？\N{\fs16}What was I made for?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:59.10,0:47:02.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是个征服者 风暴降生的丹妮莉丝\N{\fs16}You're a conqueror, Daenerys Stormborn.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:11.94,0:47:13.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在这等着\N{\fs16}Wait here.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:49.63,0:47:51.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我去找她\N{\fs16}I'm going after her.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:51.23,0:47:52.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在这儿等我\N{\fs16}Wait for me here.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:47.80,0:48:51.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,从古至今 所有的卡奥都会选择三名血盟卫\N{\fs16}Every khal who ever lived chose three blood riders
Dialogue: 0,0:48:51.97,0:48:54.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,和他并肩作战 守护他\N{\fs16}to fight beside him and guard his way.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:55.18,0:48:57.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我不是卡奥\N{\fs16}But I am not a khal.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:58.80,0:49:00.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不会选择三名血盟卫\N{\fs16}I will not choose three blood riders.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:02.38,0:49:04.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们都是我的血盟卫\N{\fs16}I choose you all.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:07.54,0:49:09.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我对我的卡拉萨的期望\N{\fs16}I will ask more of you than any khal
Dialogue: 0,0:49:10.58,0:49:12.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也比其他任何卡奥更多！\N{\fs16}has ever asked of his khalassar!
Dialogue: 0,0:49:14.77,0:49:17.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们愿意和我一起骑着木马横渡黑色咸水吗？\N{\fs16}Will you ride the wooden horses across the black salt sea?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:19.98,0:49:23.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们愿意为我杀死穿铁衣服的敌人\N{\fs16}Will you kill my enemies in their iron suits
Dialogue: 0,0:49:24.53,0:49:26.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,并拆了他们的石头房子吗？\N{\fs16}and tear down their stone houses?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:29.28,0:49:32.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们愿意为我夺回七国吗？\N{\fs16}Will you give me the Seven Kingdoms,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:32.60,0:49:35.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那份卓戈卡奥曾在圣母山前\N{\fs16}the gift Khal Drogo promised me
Dialogue: 0,0:49:35.99,0:49:38.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,许诺给我的礼物？\N{\fs16}before the Mother of Mountains?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:41.21,0:49:43.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们会拥戴我\N{\fs16}Are you with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:46.45,0:49:47.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,从今天\N{\fs16}Now
Dialogue: 0,0:49:50.70,0:49:52.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,直到永远吗？\N{\fs16}and always?

