[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.2.2012.322
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: Game of Thrones S06E04
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 衣柜
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 衣柜
Script Updated By: 衣柜
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 720
PlayResY: 404
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Titles,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles_L,Microsoft YaHei,24,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Character_L,Microsoft YaHei,28,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,4,10,10,10,1
Style: Character_B,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Author,Microsoft YaHei,16,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,1,10,10,10,1
Style: QR code - BG,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000019FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,400,400,0,0,1,0,0,5,0,0,0,1
Style: QR code - code,Arial,20,&H00000000,&H000019FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,200,200,0,0,1,0,0,5,0,0,0,1
Style: Titles - 1,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,5,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles - 2,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles - 3 -,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H0001031B,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000429,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Subtitle,Microsoft YaHei,26,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.50,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(1000,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx89\fscy89\p1\move(298,257,298,257,120,1400)}m -11 -35 l -11 39 l 63 39 l 63 -35{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.50,Titles - 2,,0,0,0,,{\fad(1000,500)\move(340,280,340,280,300,1400)\p1\fscx40\fscy40}m -86 -116 b -89 -117 -89 -117 -95 -119 l -97 -115 l -85 -105 l -116 -102 b -116 -100 -116 -98 -116 -97 l -108 -91 l -96 -91 l -116 -63 l -105 -69 l -96 -47 l -74 -63 l -77 -69 l -91 -63 l -91 -77 l -88 -80 l -66 -49 l -46 -63 l -58 -66 l -66 -74 l -49 -80 l -60 -91 l -74 -83 l -80 -91 l -77 -94 l -46 -94 l -52 -108 l -71 -105 b -69 -107 -67 -110 -66 -113 m -31 -119.875 l -33 -119 b -34 -113 -36 -107 -38 -102 l -46 -97 b -42 -93 -38 -89 -35 -85 l -44 -63 b -41 -64 -38 -65 -35 -66 l -35 -52 l -33 -47 l -27 -55 l -27 -69 l -21 -63 l -21 -69 l -19 -72 l -27 -88 l -21 -94 l -21 -99 l -27 -102 l -27 -102 l -30 -116 m -21 -113 l -21 -105 l -21 -99 l -21 -94 l -19 -85 l -19 -66 l -21 -49 l -19 -47 l -7 -52 l 26 -52 l 18 -66 l -7 -63 l -5 -69 l 6 -69 l 18 -69 l 20 -99 l -7 -94 l -7 -83 l 6 -85 l 6 -80 l -7 -77 l -7 -94 l -10 -99 l 23 -102 l 18 -116 l -10 -110 l -19 -116 m -105 -38 l -116 -41 l -110 -13 l -102 -19 l -102 -30 l -63 -33 l -55 -19 l -46 -41 l -49 -44 m -88 -33 l -91 -24 l -99 -24 l -105 -16 l -102 -13 l -85 -16 l -85 -10 l -94 -8 l -85 -16 l -102 -13 l -108 1 l -88 1 l -88 4 l -116 6 l -116 9 l -110 15 l -88 15 l -85 26 l -77 23 l -74 15 l -52 15 l -49 15 l -52 4 l -74 6 l -71 1 l -55 -2 l -60 -13 l -74 -10 l -74 -13 l -55 -16 l -63 -24 l -74 -24 l -80 -33 m -46 -41 l -38 -2 l -41 23 l -38 26 l 1 20 l 15 26 l 18 23 l 18 -8 l 20 -41 l 20 -44 l -24 -38 l -35 -41 l -35 -30 l -13 -30 l -19 -21 l -33 -19 l -33 -13 l -21 -13 l -33 6 l -33 15 l -13 -5 l -13 1 l -21 6 l -13 12 l -2 9 l -2 -8 l 9 -10 l 12 -19 l 1 -21 l -2 -27 l 9 -33 l 6 -16 l 6 -10 l 9 12 l -2 9 l -30 12 l -30 12 l -27 -2 l -27 -2 l -30 -16 l -27 -21 l -35 -41 m -126 -127 l -130 -130 l -129 38 l 34 37 l 35 -135 l -130 -131 l -127 -127 l 30 -129 l 31 32 l -124 34
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.50,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(386,224.2)\fad(1000,500)\b0\fs18\bord1} 最专业冰火字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.50,Titles - 1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(384,165.2)\fad(1000,500)}\N{\fs20}{\fs32.001\c&HFFFFFF&\b1}诚意奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.50,Titles - 1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(385,197.2)\fad(1000,500)\b000}专注GOT剧集{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.20,0:00:14.00,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(393.25,100.022)\fad(300,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}兮迩CeCe
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.25,0:00:16.30,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.875,313.122)\fad(500,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}Noxumos
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.45,0:00:18.55,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(137.875,110.367)\fad(500,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}Joker
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.55,0:00:29.55,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(176.708,104.159)\fad(500,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}FreezeBlade
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.75,0:00:31.50,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(401.209,322.666)\fad(500,500)}校对{\fs24} {\b1}屈畅   赵琳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.15,0:00:36.60,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(458.417,100.016)\fad(500,500)}校对{\fs24} {\b1}拉拉兄控凯冯  北落师门
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.50,0:00:41.50,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(409.125,137.792)\fad(500,500)}后期{\fs24} {\b1}SerGawen@huiji.wiki
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.40,0:00:52.60,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(454,100.961)\fad(500,500)}监制{\fs24} {\b1}临冬城的狮子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.10,0:00:50.50,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(118.792,140.97)\fad(500,500)}监制{\fs24} {\b1}北落师门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.40,0:01:10.00,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(478.917,112.893)\fad(500,500)}策划{\fs24} {\b1}衣柜军团
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.50,0:01:18.60,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(120.792,281.05)\fad(500,500)}特别顾问{\fs24} {\b1}屈畅(ccxx)@史诗图书
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.26,0:00:23.66,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\t(\fscx150\fscy150,150)\p1\move(277,278,289,305,1,4381)}m -15 -18 l -15 -17 l -14 -16 l -13 -16 l -11 -15 l -6 -16 b -8 -15 -8 -15 -11 -13 l -14 -9 l -12 -9 l -10 -8 l -5 -9 b -4 -8 -2 -6 6 -7 l 7 -7 l 3 -8 l 1 -10 b 2 -14 5 -17 3 -19 l 2 -21 l 5 -21 l 3 -22 l 0 -23 l 0 -24 l 4 -26 l 8 -23 l 16 -21 b 20 -23 25 -24 28 -36 l 27 -35 b 26 -35 26 -35 22 -37 b 25 -34 25 -32 24 -32 l 17 -34 l 23 -30 b 22 -29 20 -27 19 -29 l 14 -33 b 15 -31 17 -29 16 -26 b 13 -25 11 -24 7 -27 l 11 -31 l 10 -36 b 10 -32 11 -32 8 -30 b 7 -30 5 -29 4 -29 b 3 -30 2 -31 0 -34 l 3 -28 l -1 -27 l -5 -30 l -7 -34 l -6 -30 l -3 -27 l -8 -28 l -15 -32 l -10 -27 l -6 -25 l -4 -25 l -7 -23 l -10 -21 l -3 -21 l -5 -20 l -7 -21 l -7 -22 l -8 -22 l -13 -19{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.26,0:00:23.66,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\pos(301.714,255.889)\fad(300,500)\frx360\t(20,200,\frx0)\fs25\b1}君临{\fs12\b0} King's Landing
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.31,0:00:27.73,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\move(420,300,420,280)\fs25\p1}m -17 -23 l -10 -8 l -19 -15 l -12 -1 l -24 -9 l -14 6 l -25 1 l -16 9 l -13 17 l -15 24 l 18 24 l 13 19 l 15 12 l 22 4 l 13 10 l 25 -3 l 20 0 l 14 3 l 17 -3 l 22 -11 l 13 -4 l 18 -21 l 13 -15 l 10 -13 l 11 -26 l 7 -16 l 7 -28 l 3 -16 l 0 -32 l -2 -15 l -6 -22 l -8 -28 l -8 -11{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.31,0:00:27.73,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(380,230,380,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}红堡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.31,0:00:27.73,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(425,250,425,235)\fad(300,500)\fs12\b0} Red Keep
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.31,0:00:35.31,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(380,260,380,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}派
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.50,0:00:35.31,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(405,260,405,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}克
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.70,0:00:35.31,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(430,260,430,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}城
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.31,0:00:35.31,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(460,260,460,240)\fad(300,500)\fs12\b0}Pyke
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.50,0:00:47.01,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(334.667,176.333)\fad(1000,1000)\frx25\fs28\b1\frz-22\t(0,1800,\frz-0)}临冬城{\fs12\b0}\N{\fs20}Winterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.59,0:01:36.59,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(338,265)\fad(1250,1000)\frx50\t(1200,2500,\frx0)\fs28} {\b1}弥林\N{\fs12\b0}Meereen
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.32,0:01:13.50,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\pos(337.5,157.549)\fad(500,500)\fs12.746} 联合出品
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.32,0:01:13.50,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\fad(500,500)\fs24} 史诗图书 | 冰火中文维基 | 黑城堡奇幻微刊\N{\fs20}\N{\fs20}\N{\fs12}\N{\fs20}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.32,0:01:13.50,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\pos(337.5,212.563)\fad(500,500)\fs14.997} Epic Books         ASOIAF.huiji.wiki          Heichengbao\N{\fs20}{\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.20,0:01:16.20,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(516.25,119.545)\fad(500,500)} {\fs24\b1} 史诗图书 {\fs18\b0} 正统奇幻的圣殿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.52,0:01:07.02,Titles,,0,30,200,,{\fad(100,50)\frx75\t(0,3500,\frx-0)\fs28} {\b1}绝境长城{\fs12\b0} the Wall
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.43,0:01:26.22,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(355,250,370,250)\fs28\b1}维斯·多斯拉克
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.43,0:01:26.22,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(365,260,355,260)\fad(100,1000)\fs12\b0} Vaes Dothrak
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.30,0:01:00.28,Titles,,0,0,100,,{\fs25\c&HC1DFED&\fad(100,1000)} {\b0} 最专业的华语冰火资料站：        冰与火之歌{\b0\fs20}中文维基{\b0}\N{\fs20}\N{\fs20}{\fs20\fs20\c&HFFFFFF&}http://asoiaf.huiji.wiki
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.50,0:01:00.28,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,1000)\pos(410,285)\fs25\c&HC1DFED&} {\b1\p1\fscx60\fscy60}m 31 -6 l -21 40 l 34 22 m 29 -8 l -3 -12 l -24 40{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.28,0:01:02.38,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(516.25,119.545)\fad(500,500)} {\fs24\b1} 技术支持 {\fs18\b0}灰机T.R.A.N.S.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.10,0:01:38.80,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(460.667,310)\fad(500,500)\fs14} {\c&HC1DFED&}根据长篇小说
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.10,0:01:38.80,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(552.333,334)\fad(500,500)} {\fs24}《{\b1}冰与火之歌{\b0}》{\fs14} 改编
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.10,0:01:38.80,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(587,357.667)\fad(500,500)} {\fs12} 原著 {\fs20} 乔治·R·R·马丁
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.32,0:01:49.63,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(350,294.067)\fad(300,500)\fs56.267\fn宋体\b1}权力的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.32,0:01:49.63,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(348.667,322)\fad(300,500)\c&HFFFFFF&\b1\fs22}衣柜字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(428,118.44)\fad(500,500)\p1}m -18.625 0 l -18.625 0 l 281.25 0 l 281.25 1.125 l -18.625 1.125{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(231.125,202.841)\p1\fscx35\fscy35}m -86 -116 b -89 -117 -89 -117 -95 -119 l -97 -115 l -85 -105 l -116 -102 b -116 -100 -116 -98 -116 -97 l -108 -91 l -96 -91 l -116 -63 l -105 -69 l -96 -47 l -74 -63 l -77 -69 l -91 -63 l -91 -77 l -88 -80 l -66 -49 l -46 -63 l -58 -66 l -66 -74 l -49 -80 l -60 -91 l -74 -83 l -80 -91 l -77 -94 l -46 -94 l -52 -108 l -71 -105 b -69 -107 -67 -110 -66 -113 m -31 -119.875 l -33 -119 b -34 -113 -36 -107 -38 -102 l -46 -97 b -42 -93 -38 -89 -35 -85 l -44 -63 b -41 -64 -38 -65 -35 -66 l -35 -52 l -33 -47 l -27 -55 l -27 -69 l -21 -63 l -21 -69 l -19 -72 l -27 -88 l -21 -94 l -21 -99 l -27 -102 l -27 -102 l -30 -116 m -21 -113 l -21 -105 l -21 -99 l -21 -94 l -19 -85 l -19 -66 l -21 -49 l -19 -47 l -7 -52 l 26 -52 l 18 -66 l -7 -63 l -5 -69 l 6 -69 l 18 -69 l 20 -99 l -7 -94 l -7 -83 l 6 -85 l 6 -80 l -7 -77 l -7 -94 l -10 -99 l 23 -102 l 18 -116 l -10 -110 l -19 -116 m -105 -38 l -116 -41 l -110 -13 l -102 -19 l -102 -30 l -63 -33 l -55 -19 l -46 -41 l -49 -44 m -88 -33 l -91 -24 l -99 -24 l -105 -16 l -102 -13 l -85 -16 l -85 -10 l -94 -8 l -85 -16 l -102 -13 l -108 1 l -88 1 l -88 4 l -116 6 l -116 9 l -110 15 l -88 15 l -85 26 l -77 23 l -74 15 l -52 15 l -49 15 l -52 4 l -74 6 l -71 1 l -55 -2 l -60 -13 l -74 -10 l -74 -13 l -55 -16 l -63 -24 l -74 -24 l -80 -33 m -46 -41 l -38 -2 l -41 23 l -38 26 l 1 20 l 15 26 l 18 23 l 18 -8 l 20 -41 l 20 -44 l -24 -38 l -35 -41 l -35 -30 l -13 -30 l -19 -21 l -33 -19 l -33 -13 l -21 -13 l -33 6 l -33 15 l -13 -5 l -13 1 l -21 6 l -13 12 l -2 9 l -2 -8 l 9 -10 l 12 -19 l 1 -21 l -2 -27 l 9 -33 l 6 -16 l 6 -10 l 9 12 l -2 9 l -30 12 l -30 12 l -27 -2 l -27 -2 l -30 -16 l -27 -21 l -35 -41 m -126 -127 l -130 -130 l -129 38 l 34 37 l 35 -135 l -130 -131 l -127 -127 l 30 -129 l 31 32 l -124 34{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(293,112.813)\fad(500,500)\b1}协力制作
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(293,157.827)\fad(500,500)}史诗图书\N{\fs16}Epic Books
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(405.5,157.827)\fad(500,500)}冰火中文维基\N{\fs16}ASOIAF.HuiJi.WiKi
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(518,157.827)\fad(500,500)}黑城堡\N{\fs16}EPICASTLE
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.60,0:01:55.20,Titles_L,,260,0,163,,{\pos(310,300)\fad(500,500)\fs16\b0}第四集
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.60,0:01:55.20,Titles_L,,300,0,132,,{\pos(310,340)\fad(500,500)}陌客之书\N{\fs16\b0}Book of the Stranger
Dialogue: 0,0:57:21.00,0:58:31.00,Titles,,0,0,20,,{\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(360,390)}衣柜字幕组出品
Dialogue: 0,0:57:21.75,0:58:31.75,Titles,,0,0,40,,{\be1\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(357,372)}本集关键字：{\c&H5650F3\b0}陌客之书
Dialogue: 0,0:57:21.00,0:58:31.00,Titles,,0,0,335,,{\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(360,40)}剧情没看懂？ 典故不清楚？{\b0}\N维基新站网址：{\c&H00FF40}HTTP://AsoIaF.HuiJi.WiKi
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.00,0:02:03.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(128,312)\fad(300,500)}长爪\N{\b0\fs12}瓦雷利亚钢剑
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.30,0:02:27.30,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(228,262)\fad(300,500)}琼恩·雪诺\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.50,0:02:15.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(116,254)\fad(300,500)}忧郁的艾迪\N{\b0\fs12}守夜人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.00,0:03:09.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(148,281)\fad(300,500)}珊莎·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.00,0:03:09.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(288,291)\fad(300,500)}塔斯的布蕾妮\N{\b0\fs12}“美人”
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.00,0:03:09.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(588,291)\fad(300,500)}波德瑞克·派恩\N{\b0\fs12}侍从
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.00,0:03:20.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(263,262)\fad(300,500)}托蒙德\N{\b0\fs12}野人头领
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.00,0:07:36.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(585,284)\fad(300,500)}梅丽珊卓\N{\b0\fs12}红衣祭司
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.00,0:07:36.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(157,279)\fad(300,500)}戴佛斯·席渥斯\N{\b0\fs12}洋葱骑士
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.00,0:09:08.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(257,312)\fad(300,500)}罗宾·艾林\N{\b0\fs12}鹰巢城公爵 谷地守护
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.00,0:09:23.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(236,269)\fad(300,500)}约恩·罗伊斯\N{\b0\fs12}“青铜”
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.00,0:09:37.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(367,272)\fad(300,500)}培提尔·贝里席\N{\b0\fs12}“小指头”
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.00,0:12:49.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(495,326)\fad(300,500)}提利昂·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}“小恶魔”
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.00,0:12:51.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(523,296)\fad(300,500)}瓦里斯\N{\b0\fs12}“八爪蜘蛛”
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.00,0:12:51.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(638,294)\fad(300,500)}灰虫子\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.00,0:12:51.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(224,287)\fad(300,500)}弥桑黛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.00,0:19:57.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(613,247)\fad(300,500)}达里奥·纳哈里斯\N{\b0\fs12}雇佣兵
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.00,0:20:40.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(620,262)\fad(300,500)}乔拉·莫尔蒙\N{\b0\fs12}“大熊”
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.00,0:25:37.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(109,211)\fad(300,500)}丹妮莉丝·坦格利安\N{\b0\fs12}弥林的女王
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.00,0:28:34.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(208,241)\fad(300,500)}玛格丽·提利尔\N{\b0\fs12}王后
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.40,0:29:01.40,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(488,304)\fad(300,500)}大麻雀\N{\b0\fs12}总主教
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.00,0:33:24.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(109,320)\fad(300,500)}洛拉斯·提利尔\N{\b0\fs12}百花骑士
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.00,0:34:56.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(581,298)\fad(300,500)}托曼·拜拉席恩一世\N{\b0\fs12}国王
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.00,0:34:56.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(108,281)\fad(300,500)}派席尔\N{\b0\fs12}大学士
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.00,0:34:35.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(497,274)\fad(300,500)}瑟曦·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}太后
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.00,0:37:53.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(128,274)\fad(300,500)}奥莲娜·雷德温\N{\b0\fs12}荆棘女王
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.00,0:37:53.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(540,227)\fad(300,500)}凯冯·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}国王之手
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.00,0:37:58.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(607,274)\fad(300,500)}詹姆·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}御林铁卫
Dialogue: 0,0:40:35.30,0:40:37.30,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(468,254)\fad(300,500)}席恩·葛雷乔伊\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:29.00,0:41:33.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(315,267)\fad(300,500)}亚拉·葛雷乔伊\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:56.00,0:43:58.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(188,250)\fad(300,500)}拉姆斯·波顿\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:03.00,0:44:05.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(428,242)\fad(300,500)}欧莎\N{\b0\fs12}野人
Dialogue: 0,0:50:51.00,0:50:53.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(500,216)\fad(300,500)}萨沃卡奥\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.88,0:02:20.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你要去哪？\N{\fs16}Where you gonna go?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.35,0:02:23.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,南方\N{\fs16}South.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.62,0:02:26.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去干什么？\N{\fs16}What are you gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.69,0:02:28.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,取暖\N{\fs16}Get warm.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.77,0:02:37.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我和你在艰难屯的时候\N{\fs16}I was with you at Hardhome.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.27,0:02:41.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们看到了外面有什么\N{\fs16}We saw what's out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.71,0:02:43.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们都知道他们往这来了\N{\fs16}We know it's coming here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.17,0:02:45.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你怎能在这时抛下我们？\N{\fs16}How can you leave us now?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.71,0:02:48.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我能做的我都做了 你知道的\N{\fs16}I did everything I could. You know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.31,0:02:51.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 你发过誓 - 是的 我把我的生命献给了守夜人\N{\fs16}- You swore a vow. - Aye, I pledged my life to the Night's Watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.88,0:02:53.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 我付出了我的生命 - “夜夜皆然”\N{\fs16}- I gave my life. - For all nights to come.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.75,0:02:56.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们杀了我 艾迪！我的兄弟们\N{\fs16}They killed me, Edd! My own brothers.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.29,0:02:58.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你还想让我留在这里？\N{\fs16}You want me to stay here after that?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.25,0:03:01.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有人来了！\N{\fs16}Riders approaching!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.89,0:03:03.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,打开大门！\N{\fs16}Open the gate!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.65,0:04:39.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,汤很好喝\N{\fs16}This is good soup.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.06,0:04:45.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你还记得老奶妈以前常做的腰花馅饼吗？\N{\fs16}Do you remember those kidney pies Old Nan used to make?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.26,0:04:47.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,加了豌豆和洋葱的？\N{\fs16}With the peas and onions?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.53,0:04:53.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们一开始就不该离开临冬城\N{\fs16}We never should have left Winterfell.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.57,0:04:56.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不希望回到我们离开的那天吗？\N{\fs16}Don't you wish we could go back to the day we left?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.31,0:05:02.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我真想对着我自己大喊“别去啊 白痴”\N{\fs16}I want to scream at myself, "Don't go, you idiot."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.11,0:05:04.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们怎么会知道？\N{\fs16}How could we know?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.28,0:05:08.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我花了很多时间回想当初我对你有多么混蛋\N{\fs16}I spent a lot of time thinking about what an ass I was to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.35,0:05:12.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我真希望我能改变一切\N{\fs16}I wish I could change everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.52,0:05:13.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们那时只是孩子\N{\fs16}We were children.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.76,0:05:15.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就承认吧 我很讨人厌\N{\fs16}I was awful, just admit it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.59,0:05:19.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你偶尔有些讨厌\N{\fs16}You were occasionally awful.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.06,0:05:21.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我肯定我是很无趣的\N{\fs16}I'm sure I can't have been great fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.97,0:05:24.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,总是在你们一起玩的时候缩在墙角闷闷不乐\N{\fs16}Always sulking in the corner while the rest of you played.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.83,0:05:26.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 你能原谅我吗？ - 没什么好原谅的\N{\fs16}- Can you forgive me? - There's nothing to forgive.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.77,0:05:28.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 原谅我 -好吧\N{\fs16}- Forgive me. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.87,0:05:30.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好吧 我原谅你\N{\fs16}All right, I forgive you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.19,0:05:50.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你觉得都几千年了\N{\fs16}You'd think after thousands of years,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.16,0:05:52.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,守夜人总该学会怎么酿出好酒吧\N{\fs16}the Night's Watch would have learned how to make a good ale.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.83,0:05:57.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你要去哪儿？\N{\fs16}Where will you go?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.20,0:06:01.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们要去哪儿？\N{\fs16}Where will we go?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.87,0:06:05.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,要是我不照看着你 父亲的在天之灵不会放过我的\N{\fs16}If I don't watch over you, Father's ghost will come back and murder me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.94,0:06:09.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们要去哪儿？\N{\fs16}Where will we go?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.68,0:06:12.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不能待在这了 在发生了这些事以后\N{\fs16}I can't stay here, not after what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.28,0:06:14.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们只有一个地方可以去\N{\fs16}There's only one place we can go.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.42,0:06:16.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,家\N{\fs16}Home.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.82,0:06:19.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们是该叫波顿打铺盖卷走人吗？\N{\fs16}Should we tell the Boltons to pack up and leave?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.96,0:06:21.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们会从他们手里夺回来的\N{\fs16}We'll take it back from them.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.69,0:06:26.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没有军队\N{\fs16}I don't have an army.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.75,0:06:28.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你救了多少野人？\N{\fs16}How many wildlings did you save?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.33,0:06:29.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们不是来这为我效命的\N{\fs16}They didn't come here to serve me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.03,0:06:32.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们的命是你给的\N{\fs16}They owe you their lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.40,0:06:35.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你觉得有卢斯·波顿继续做北境守护他们会安全吗？\N{\fs16}You think they'll be safe here if Roose Bolton remains Warden of the North?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.67,0:06:38.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 珊莎 -临冬城是我们的家\N{\fs16}- Sansa. - Winterfell is our home.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.14,0:06:41.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是我们的 也是艾莉亚 布兰和瑞肯的\N{\fs16}It's ours and Arya's and Bran's and Rickon's.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.74,0:06:43.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不管他们在哪 它都属于我们家族\N{\fs16}Wherever they are, it belongs to our family.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.98,0:06:45.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们必须为它而战\N{\fs16}We have to fight for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.42,0:06:47.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我已经厌倦战斗了\N{\fs16}I'm tired of fighting.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.45,0:06:52.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,自从离家我就一直在战斗\N{\fs16}It's all I've done since I left home.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.42,0:06:54.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我杀过守夜人的兄弟\N{\fs16}I've killed brothers of the Night's Watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.46,0:06:57.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我杀过野人 我杀过我敬仰的人\N{\fs16}I've killed wildlings. I've killed men that I admire.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.23,0:07:00.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我绞死了一个比布兰还小的男孩\N{\fs16}I hanged a boy younger than Bran.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.17,0:07:07.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我战斗过 却失败了\N{\fs16}I fought and I lost.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.34,0:07:14.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果我们不夺回北境 我们永远不会安全\N{\fs16}If we don't take back the North, we'll never be safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.65,0:07:18.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我需要你帮助我\N{\fs16}I want you to help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.25,0:07:22.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但如果有必要 我会亲自动手\N{\fs16}But I'll do it myself if I have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.92,0:07:28.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女士\N{\fs16}My lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.16,0:07:30.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,戴佛斯爵士\N{\fs16}Ser Davos.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.70,0:07:35.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你会留在黑城堡吗？\N{\fs16}Will you stay here at Castle Black?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.90,0:07:39.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会谨遵琼恩·雪诺的命令\N{\fs16}I will do as Jon Snow commands.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.74,0:07:41.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你现在效命琼恩·雪诺了？\N{\fs16}You serve Jon Snow now?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.87,0:07:44.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他是预言中的王子\N{\fs16}He's the prince that was promised.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.68,0:07:49.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,原谅我 女士 我还以为那是史坦尼斯\N{\fs16}Forgive me, my lady, I thought that was Stannis.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.39,0:08:01.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们那边发生了什么？\N{\fs16}What happened down there?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.79,0:08:06.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,打了场仗 史坦尼斯被打败了\N{\fs16}There was a battle. Stannis was defeated.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.80,0:08:10.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那席琳呢？\N{\fs16}And Shireen?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.03,0:08:12.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,公主怎么样了？\N{\fs16}What happened to the princess?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.67,0:08:15.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我看到了发生的事\N{\fs16}I saw what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.47,0:08:18.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我看到史坦尼斯的大军被击溃\N{\fs16}I saw Stannis' forces defeated in the field.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.41,0:08:20.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女士 我是戴佛斯·席渥斯爵士\N{\fs16}My lady, I'm Ser Davos Seaworth.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.41,0:08:22.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们见过\N{\fs16}We've met before.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.11,0:08:23.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我那时是蓝礼·拜拉席恩的御林铁卫\N{\fs16}I was Kingsguard to Renly Baratheon.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.95,0:08:28.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,直到蓝礼被血魔法暗杀而死\N{\fs16}Before Renly was assassinated with bloodmagic.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.32,0:08:30.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那已经过去了\N{\fs16}That's in the past now.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.46,0:08:34.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的 是过去了\N{\fs16}Yes, it's in the past.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.29,0:08:36.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,并不意味着我忘掉了\N{\fs16}It doesn't mean I forget.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.59,0:08:39.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,或原谅了\N{\fs16}Or forgive.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.80,0:08:43.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他承认了 你知道的\N{\fs16}He admitted it, you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.50,0:08:45.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谁？\N{\fs16}Who did?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.40,0:08:47.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,史坦尼斯\N{\fs16}Stannis.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.57,0:08:49.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就在我处决他之前\N{\fs16}Just before I executed him.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.52,0:09:37.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谷地守护者！\N{\fs16}The Defender of the Vale!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.79,0:09:39.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,培提尔叔叔！\N{\fs16}Uncle Petyr!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.33,0:09:47.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大人\N{\fs16}My lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.00,0:09:49.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,过来瞧\N{\fs16}Come and see.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.67,0:09:52.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我错过了你的命名日 来吧\N{\fs16}I missed your name day. Go on.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.86,0:09:56.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,猎鹰！\N{\fs16}A falcon!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.81,0:09:58.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是矛隼\N{\fs16}A gyrfalcon.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.27,0:09:59.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,最名贵最稀有的鸟\N{\fs16}The greatest and rarest of birds.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.84,0:10:02.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,贝里席 上次我见到你的时候\N{\fs16}Last time I saw you, Baelish,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.65,0:10:06.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你告诉我你要带着珊莎·史塔克回到五指半岛\N{\fs16}you told me you were taking Sansa Stark home with you to the Fingers.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.95,0:10:08.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是这样做了\N{\fs16}Indeed I was.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.32,0:10:10.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但是不久前我们收到报告\N{\fs16}And yet not long ago, we received reports
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.62,0:10:13.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,说她嫁给了临冬城的拉姆斯·波顿\N{\fs16}that she has been married to Ramsay Bolton in Winterfell.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.82,0:10:17.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去五指半岛的路上 我们遭到了一大批波顿军队的袭击\N{\fs16}On our way to the Fingers, we were set upon by a large force of Bolton men.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.49,0:10:20.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们似乎明确地知道我们何时出行\N{\fs16}Seemed to know exactly when we were traveling
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.10,0:10:22.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也明确地知道我们护送的是谁\N{\fs16}and exactly whom we were transporting.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.06,0:10:23.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你把我当白痴吗？\N{\fs16}Do you take me for a fool?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.87,0:10:26.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,告诉我 罗伊斯大人\N{\fs16}Tell me, Lord Royce,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.84,0:10:30.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有多少人知道我与珊莎·史塔克的出行计划？\N{\fs16}how many people knew of my travel plans with Sansa Stark?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.31,0:10:33.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我只把我的打算告诉过你\N{\fs16}I shared my intentions with you
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.71,0:10:35.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别无二人\N{\fs16}and no one else.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.94,0:10:39.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在别人家里诽谤别人\N{\fs16}Slander a man in his own home,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.82,0:10:42.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,接下来便是兵戎相见\N{\fs16}you might find yourself crossing swords with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.72,0:10:47.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的家属于谷地 而谷地主人就站在我们面前\N{\fs16}Your home is the Vale. The Lord of the Vale stands before us.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.46,0:10:50.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,主人说了算\N{\fs16}And only his judgment concerns me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.17,0:10:58.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们应该把他扔下月门吗？\N{\fs16}Shall we throw him through the Moon Door?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.41,0:11:07.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大人\N{\fs16}My lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.61,0:11:12.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大人 我一直对艾林家族尽诚竭节\N{\fs16}My lord, I have always been faithful to House Arryn.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.28,0:11:15.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,无论是对令尊 令堂 还是现在的您\N{\fs16}To your father, to your mother, and now to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.62,0:11:17.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你相信他吗 培提尔叔叔？\N{\fs16}Do you believe him, Uncle Petyr?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.16,0:11:29.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,罗伊斯大人竭力效忠谷地\N{\fs16}Lord Royce has served the Vale well.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.37,0:11:33.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,戎马多年 战绩彪炳\N{\fs16}He's enjoyed a distinguished military career.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.20,0:11:36.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果他的忠诚值得信任\N{\fs16}If we could trust his absolute loyalty,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.84,0:11:39.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那么在即将到来的征战中他仍是总司令的绝佳人选\N{\fs16}he would make a capable commander in the wars to come.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.01,0:11:46.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您大可相信我的绝对忠诚 大人\N{\fs16}You can trust my absolute loyalty, my lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.62,0:11:49.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我认为他值得一次机会 您觉得呢？\N{\fs16}I think he deserves one more chance. What do you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.39,0:11:58.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fs16}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.30,0:12:07.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我带来了好消息\N{\fs16}I bring good news.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.67,0:12:10.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我在北境的朋友告诉我珊莎·史塔克逃出了临冬城\N{\fs16}My friends in the North tell me Sansa has escaped Winterfell.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.34,0:12:12.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我估计她已经去往黑城堡了\N{\fs16}I expect she's headed to Castle Black
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.21,0:12:14.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她的哥哥在那里做总司令\N{\fs16}where her brother serves as Lord Commander.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.64,0:12:18.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但她在那不安全 波顿正在追捕她\N{\fs16}But she won't be safe there, not with the Boltons after her.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.88,0:12:22.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她是我表姐\N{\fs16}She's my cousin.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.52,0:12:26.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们应该帮助她\N{\fs16}We should help her.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.69,0:12:29.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的第一反应也是这个\N{\fs16}That was my instinct as well.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.46,0:12:31.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,公爵已经发话了\N{\fs16}Our lord has spoken.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.60,0:12:35.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,集合谷地的骑士\N{\fs16}Gather the Knights of the Vale.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.63,0:12:38.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,加入战争的时候到了\N{\fs16}The time has come to join the fray.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.91,0:12:45.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你把敌人请进了我们的城市？\N{\fs16}You invite the enemy into our city?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.14,0:12:46.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fs16}I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.91,0:12:49.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一位智者曾经告诉我\N{\fs16}As a clever man once told me,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.48,0:12:52.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,“需要握手言和的是敌人 而不是朋友”\N{\fs16}"We make peace with our enemies, not our friends."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.25,0:12:55.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不跟女王的敌人握手言和\N{\fs16}I don't make peace with the queen's enemies.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.32,0:12:56.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会杀死他们\N{\fs16}I kill the queen's enemies.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.52,0:12:57.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对 那是军事手段\N{\fs16}Yes, that's the military approach.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.09,0:12:59.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在弥林发挥了什么作用？\N{\fs16}And how has that worked here in Meereen?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.76,0:13:02.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我表达的是外交手段\N{\fs16}I represent the diplomatic approach.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.16,0:13:04.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女王试过与伟主们言和\N{\fs16}Our queen tried to make peace with the Masters
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.39,0:13:06.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们却想要杀她\N{\fs16}and they tried to murder her.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.46,0:13:09.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们谈判时留点神\N{\fs16}We enter these negotiations with open eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.50,0:13:12.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,相信我 我近期的奴隶经历\N{\fs16}Trust me. My own recent experience with slavery
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.90,0:13:14.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,已经告诉我这项制度有多可怕了\N{\fs16}has taught me the horrors of that institution.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.90,0:13:16.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您做了几天的奴隶呢？\N{\fs16}How many days were you a slave?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.88,0:13:18.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,长到够我知道了\N{\fs16}Long enough to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.47,0:13:21.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没有长到够你了解\N{\fs16}Not long enough to understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.02,0:13:31.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我用一个辉币买了这个侏儒\N{\fs16}I bought this dwarf for a single gold honor.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.69,0:13:33.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不知何故你竟飞黄腾达\N{\fs16}And somehow you've risen
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.86,0:13:36.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,都住到弥林的大金字塔顶来了\N{\fs16}to the top of the Great Pyramid of Meereen.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.86,0:13:38.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,真让人称奇不已\N{\fs16}It's most impressive.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.76,0:13:41.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,现在你还代替阿斯塔波的善主发言呢\N{\fs16}And now you speak for the Good Masters of Astapor.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.70,0:13:44.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,敬时来运转\N{\fs16}Here's to reversals of fortune.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.13,0:13:45.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们是来这觐见女王的\N{\fs16}We came here to meet the queen
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.80,0:13:48.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,结果 迎接我们的是侏儒和太监\N{\fs16}and instead we're greeted by a dwarf and a eunuch.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.30,0:13:52.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让我们摊开了说吧 好吗？说说你们想要什么\N{\fs16}Let's make this simple, shall we? Tell me what you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.21,0:13:55.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们想要你们离开奴隶湾\N{\fs16}We want you to leave Slaver's Bay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.24,0:13:58.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,带上你们的龙和雇佣兵 走人\N{\fs16}Take your dragons and your mercenaries and go.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.05,0:14:01.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,丹妮莉丝女王不会永远待在弥林的\N{\fs16}Queen Daenerys won't stay in Meereen forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.72,0:14:03.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她的目标在西方\N{\fs16}Her path takes her westward.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.59,0:14:05.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们上次见面的时候 我提出给她船只\N{\fs16}When we last met, I offered her ships
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.02,0:14:09.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这样她就可以回到属于她的维斯特洛 但她拒绝了\N{\fs16}so she could return to Westeros where she belongs. She refused them.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.99,0:14:12.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她拒绝了 是因为成千上万的\N{\fs16}She refused them because hundreds of thousands
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.19,0:14:14.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,男人女人和孩子还活在链铐之下\N{\fs16}of men, women, and children still lived in chains.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.26,0:14:16.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们自古以来就是如此\N{\fs16}As they have since the dawn of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.80,0:14:19.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 不再是了 - 你觉得你现在就是自由人了吗？\N{\fs16}- Not anymore. - You think you're a free man now?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.07,0:14:21.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你还是在遵令行事\N{\fs16}You still follow orders.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.00,0:14:24.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的主人有银发和奶子\N{\fs16}Just because your master has silver hair and tits
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.64,0:14:26.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,并不意味着她就不是奴隶主\N{\fs16}doesn't mean she's not a master.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.48,0:14:29.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,朋友 朋友 朋友 拜托\N{\fs16}Friends, friends, friends, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.01,0:14:34.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,世上总是有有钱有势的人和一无所有的人\N{\fs16}There have always been those with wealth and power and those with nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.65,0:14:37.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,世界的规则就是这样 我不是来改变世界规则的\N{\fs16}That is the way of the world. I'm not here to change the way of the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.75,0:14:40.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奴隶制就是我们世界的规则\N{\fs16}Slavery is the way of our world.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.32,0:14:43.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们不是非得用奴隶来赚钱\N{\fs16}You don't need slaves to make money.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.89,0:14:46.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,维斯特洛几百年来都没有奴隶\N{\fs16}There haven't been slaves in Westeros for hundreds of years
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.86,0:14:48.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我却比你们中任何一个都富有\N{\fs16}and I grew up richer than any of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.83,0:14:54.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不过 我们的女王却发现她错在\N{\fs16}But our queen recognizes that she erred
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.60,0:14:57.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只是废除奴隶制\N{\fs16}by abolishing slavery
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.34,0:15:00.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,却没有提供一个新的体系来取代它\N{\fs16}without providing a new system to replace it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.28,0:15:04.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所以这里是女王的提议\N{\fs16}So here is the queen's proposal.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.15,0:15:07.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奴隶制永不回到弥林\N{\fs16}Slavery will never return to Meereen,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.12,0:15:09.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但她会给奴隶湾的其他城市\N{\fs16}but she will give the other cities of Slaver's Bay
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.95,0:15:11.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一些时间来调整到新的秩序\N{\fs16}time to adjust to the new order.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.02,0:15:13.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,什么意思？\N{\fs16}What does that mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.42,0:15:16.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,废除奴隶制不必一夜完成\N{\fs16}Instead of abolishing slavery overnight,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.66,0:15:19.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,可以宽限到七年\N{\fs16}we will give you seven years to end the practice.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.50,0:15:26.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奴隶主将获得补偿\N{\fs16}Slaveholders will be compensated
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.44,0:15:29.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,价格公道\N{\fs16}for their losses, of course, at fair prices.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.27,0:15:31.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,作为交换 你们要停止\N{\fs16}In exchange, you will cut off
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.87,0:15:33.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对鹰身女妖之子的支持\N{\fs16}your support for the Sons of the Harpy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.71,0:15:35.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,鹰身女妖之子和我们无关\N{\fs16}We do not support the Sons of the Harpy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.34,0:15:38.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好吧 随意了 总之你们会停止支持\N{\fs16}Fine, fine, but you will cut it off all the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.58,0:15:42.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我希望你们接受 朋友们\N{\fs16}I do hope you accept, my friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.65,0:15:44.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们不会得到更好的条件了\N{\fs16}You will not receive a better offer.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.99,0:15:50.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让我们扬帆于自由之潮\N{\fs16}Let us sail on the tide of freedom
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.93,0:15:53.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而不是被它吞没\N{\fs16}instead of being drowned by it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.56,0:15:57.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我还给尊贵的客人们准备了点离别的礼物……\N{\fs16}And as a parting gift to our honored guests...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.61,0:16:08.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,给自由一个机会吧\N{\fs16}Give freedom a chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.51,0:16:11.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,它仍与从前一样甜美\N{\fs16}See if it doesn't taste every bit as good as what came before.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.53,0:16:24.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的朋友们！\N{\fs16}My friends!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.51,0:16:28.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大大的抱歉\N{\fs16}Large sorry...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.20,0:16:30.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让你们等了‘肥肠’久的时间\N{\fs16}...you wait so fat time.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.87,0:16:34.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,要不我来替你作翻译吧\N{\fs16}Perhaps I should translate for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.90,0:16:36.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们会说通用语\N{\fs16}We speak the Common Tongue.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.61,0:16:40.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 真棒 - 今天你和奴隶贩子们见了面\N{\fs16}- Excellent. - You met with the slavers today.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.18,0:16:41.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没错\N{\fs16}I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.68,0:16:43.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们的兄弟姐妹们在和这些渣滓抗争的路上前仆后继\N{\fs16}Our brothers and sisters died fighting this scum.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.78,0:16:46.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而你现在却邀请他们登堂入室 共饮美酒\N{\fs16}Now you invite them to our city and drink wine with them.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.62,0:16:53.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我想建筑这个大厅的目的\N{\fs16}I imagine this room was built
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.12,0:16:56.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是让统治者威慑被统治者\N{\fs16}so the rulers could intimidate the ruled.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.26,0:17:00.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我不是你们的统治者\N{\fs16}But I am not your ruler.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.13,0:17:02.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不是解放者\N{\fs16}I'm not the Breaker of Chains.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.53,0:17:04.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不是不焚者\N{\fs16}I'm not the Unburnt.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.80,0:17:09.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,更不是龙之母\N{\fs16}And I am certainly not the Mother of Dragons.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.10,0:17:11.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你在这里只是一个陌生人\N{\fs16}You are a stranger here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.24,0:17:14.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,凭什么代表弥林和我们的敌人进行谈判？\N{\fs16}So why do you represent Meereen in these talks with our enemies?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.28,0:17:17.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为我们的女王选择我作为她的顾问\N{\fs16}Because our queen chose me as her advisor.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.81,0:17:19.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,直到陛下旅途归来\N{\fs16}Until she returns from her travels...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.02,0:17:21.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她什么时候才能回来？\N{\fs16}When does she return?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.62,0:17:24.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很快 我向你们保证\N{\fs16}Soon. You have my word.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.15,0:17:27.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们不认识你 更不信任你 我们熟知的是灰虫子\N{\fs16}We don't know you. We don't trust you. We know Torgo Nudho.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.92,0:17:29.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们随他抗击伟主 我们信任他\N{\fs16}We fight with him against the Masters. We trust him.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.96,0:17:33.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这正是灰虫子参与谈判的原因\N{\fs16}And that is exactly why Grey Worm took part in these negotiations.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.90,0:17:37.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,作为无垢者军团的指挥官 他知道如何打败奴隶贩子\N{\fs16}As commander of the Unsullied, he knows how to defeat the slavers
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.63,0:17:39.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但他同样知道什么时候应该缔造和平\N{\fs16}and he knows when it is time to make peace.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.47,0:17:42.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你和那群奴隶贩子握手言和？\N{\fs16}You have made peace with the slavers?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.44,0:17:43.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们提出了条件\N{\fs16}We offered terms.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.77,0:17:45.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你呢？灰虫子\N{\fs16}And you, Grey Worm?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.97,0:17:47.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想和那群将我们从母亲的臂弯中夺走\N{\fs16}You want to drink wine with these men?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.99,0:17:52.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,像牲畜般竞标拍卖的人一起把酒言欢吗？\N{\fs16}The men who tore us from our mothers' arms and and sold us at auction like cattle?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.81,0:18:01.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是士兵 不是政客\N{\fs16}I am a soldier, not a politician.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.34,0:18:03.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但如果有机会缔结和平\N{\fs16}But if there is a chance for peace --
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.88,0:18:05.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,公正的和平\N{\fs16}a <i>just</i> peace --
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.41,0:18:07.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们应该把握住\N{\fs16}we should take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.08,0:18:09.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,弥桑黛\N{\fs16}Missandei,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.75,0:18:13.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你知道那些人的真面目 你怎能信任他们？\N{\fs16}you know what these men are. How can you trust them?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.26,0:18:17.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不信任他们 从未有过\N{\fs16}I do not trust them. I will never trust them.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.61,0:18:25.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但有位智者曾经说过\N{\fs16}But as a wise man once said,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.77,0:18:31.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,需要握手言和的是敌人 而不是朋友\N{\fs16}"We make peace with our enemies, not our friends. "
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.26,0:18:39.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 不要搬我出来圆你的谎话 - 那些人尊重你\N{\fs16}- Do not use me for your lies. - Those men respect you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.76,0:18:42.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们尊重我是因为他们对我知根知底\N{\fs16}They respect me because they know who I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.16,0:18:44.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 他们深知我的忠诚 - 我也一样\N{\fs16}- They know I am loyal. - As do I.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.27,0:18:46.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我对女王陛下忠诚 而不是对你\N{\fs16}I am loyal to my queen, not you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.64,0:18:48.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果你胆敢背叛她的事业 你就将是我之敌\N{\fs16}If you betray her work, you are my enemy.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.60,0:18:51.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没有背叛她的事业 我正试图挽救她的城市\N{\fs16}I am not betraying her work. I am trying to save her city.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.84,0:18:54.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你向奴隶主承诺他们可以保留奴隶制\N{\fs16}You promised the slavers they could keep slavery.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.38,0:18:55.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,短期之内\N{\fs16}For a short time.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.68,0:18:58.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,七年对奴隶来说可不是什么短期\N{\fs16}Seven years is not a short time for a slave.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.51,0:18:59.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你说得对\N{\fs16}You're right.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.08,0:19:02.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奴隶制可怖 应当即刻根除\N{\fs16}Slavery is a horror that should be ended at once.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.62,0:19:05.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,战争可怖 应当马上停止\N{\fs16}War is a horror that should be ended at once.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.25,0:19:06.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我没法两头兼顾\N{\fs16}I can't do both today.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.02,0:19:08.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不该信任那些人\N{\fs16}You are wrong to trust these men.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.56,0:19:11.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我信任的不是奴隶主 而是他们为自己打算的心思\N{\fs16}I don't trust the Masters. I trust their self-interest.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.09,0:19:13.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果他们确信与我合作对他们自己有利\N{\fs16}They're trustworthy if they're convinced
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.86,0:19:16.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那他们就可以被相信\N{\fs16}that working with me is in their self-interest.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.13,0:19:19.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不知道他们 你不了解他们\N{\fs16}You don't know them. You don't understand them.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.10,0:19:20.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们在他们眼里根本不是人\N{\fs16}We are not human in their eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.87,0:19:23.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,当他们看向我 看到的是一把武器\N{\fs16}They look at me and see a weapon.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.24,0:19:25.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,当他们看向她 看到的是一个娼妓\N{\fs16}They look at her and see a whore.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.34,0:19:28.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,当他们看向我 看到的是一个畸形的小怪兽\N{\fs16}They look at me and they see a misshapen little beast.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.21,0:19:30.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们的蔑视造就他们的弱点\N{\fs16}Their contempt is their weakness.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.35,0:19:33.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们会低估我们 而我们会利用这一点\N{\fs16}They'll underestimate us every time and we will use that to our advantage.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.12,0:19:37.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们不可能为你所用\N{\fs16}You will not use them.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.12,0:19:39.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们会利用你 这是他们的天性\N{\fs16}They will use you. That is what they do.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.68,0:20:02.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你还好吗？\N{\fs16}You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.68,0:20:05.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,何不坐下来喘口气呢？\N{\fs16}Why don't you sit and catch your breath?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.91,0:20:08.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我很好\N{\fs16}I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.08,0:20:11.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我觉得你骑不了龙\N{\fs16}I don't think you could ride the dragon.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.39,0:20:13.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,换做二十年前 也许可以\N{\fs16}20 years ago, maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.62,0:20:15.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 什么？ - 我们的女王\N{\fs16}- What? - Our queen.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.99,0:20:19.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别看她很娇小 你懂的 其实她很狂野\N{\fs16}She's wild, you know. Don't let her size fool you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.46,0:20:22.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我这么年轻都难以招架\N{\fs16}It's hard enough for me and I'm a young man.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.30,0:20:26.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你呢 我担心你的心脏受不了\N{\fs16}You, I don't think your heart could take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.57,0:20:32.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女王陛下选择了我一定让你非常不爽\N{\fs16}Must make you angry that our queen chose me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.34,0:20:35.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我很难过 过不了太久你就会辜负她\N{\fs16}Makes me sad. You'll disappoint her before long.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.58,0:20:38.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 她会忘了你 - 我们都好景不长\N{\fs16}- She'll move on. - We'll all disappoint her before long.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.11,0:20:40.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,现在我们需要彼此 当我们不再需要彼此的时候……\N{\fs16}We need each other right now. After we're done needing each other...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.05,0:20:44.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,喔 我可不想和你打 安达尔人乔拉\N{\fs16}Oh, I don't want to fight you, Jorah the Andal.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.59,0:20:46.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我能有什么好处？\N{\fs16}What do I have to gain?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.39,0:20:49.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果我赢了 我就成了干翻一个老家伙的草包\N{\fs16}If I win, I'm the shit who killed an old man.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.16,0:20:52.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,万一我输了 我就成了被一个老家伙干翻的草包\N{\fs16}If I lose, I'm the shit who was killed by an old man.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.06,0:20:57.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你小时候没受过多少管束 是吧？\N{\fs16}You didn't get much discipline as a child, did you?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.30,0:20:59.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一点没有\N{\fs16}None.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.18,0:21:07.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这条路直穿马门\N{\fs16}The road running through the Horse Gate,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.88,0:21:09.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们叫它众神大道\N{\fs16}they call that the godsway.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.78,0:21:12.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,东市 西市\N{\fs16}Eastern Market, Western Market.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.58,0:21:16.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,卓戈卡奥死后 她本该来到这里 加入那些遗孀\N{\fs16}When Khal Drogo died, she was supposed to come here and join the Dosh Khaleen
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.89,0:21:20.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,成为多希卡林的一员\N{\fs16}the widows of the dead khals.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.22,0:21:22.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那就是他们要带她去的地方\N{\fs16}That's where they would have taken her
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.26,0:21:25.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,多希卡林神庙\N{\fs16}the Temple of the Dosh Khaleen.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.57,0:21:35.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你在做什么？\N{\fs16}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.17,0:21:37.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这座马族圣城禁止携带武器出入\N{\fs16}It's forbidden to carry weapons in the sacred city.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.81,0:21:41.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,难道潜入城中偷走他们的卡丽熙就不禁止吗？\N{\fs16}Isn't it forbidden to sneak into their city and steal their khaleesi?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.31,0:21:43.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果他们发现了我们 而我们手无寸铁\N{\fs16}If they spot us and we're unarmed,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.28,0:21:45.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们就说我们是要去西市的商人\N{\fs16}we'll say we're traders heading for the Western Market.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.85,0:21:47.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但如果他们看到武器……\N{\fs16}But if they see weapons...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.58,0:21:49.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你这是在要求一条狗交出它的牙\N{\fs16}You're asking a dog to hand over his teeth.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.38,0:21:51.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,下面有十万人\N{\fs16}There's 100,000 of them down there.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.49,0:21:52.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们不能硬闯\N{\fs16}We can't fight our way out.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.09,0:21:55.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们等到天黑 然后找到她\N{\fs16}We wait till dark, and then we'll find her.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.83,0:22:08.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这把刀和我有很深的羁绊\N{\fs16}I'm very attached to this knife.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.65,0:22:22.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别担心 不会碰到你\N{\fs16}Don't worry. It didn't touch you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.75,0:22:25.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你知道这意味着什么？\N{\fs16}You know what happens?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.95,0:22:27.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我知道这意味着什么\N{\fs16}I know what happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.56,0:22:31.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我自己来吧\N{\fs16}I'll do it myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.76,0:23:06.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我应该投胎成一个多斯拉克人的\N{\fs16}I should have been born a Dothraki.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.13,0:23:37.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,走吧\N{\fs16}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.37,0:23:39.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,朋友们\N{\fs16}My friends...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.26,0:23:43.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们从西市来 在城里迷路了\N{\fs16}We wandered off from the Western Market and got lost.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.13,0:23:46.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您二位能告诉我们怎么回去吗？\N{\fs16}Could you show us the way back?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.32,0:23:47.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们卖的是什么？\N{\fs16}What do you sell?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.74,0:23:48.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,酒\N{\fs16}Wine.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.17,0:23:51.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,明天来我的货摊\N{\fs16}Come down to my stall tomorrow,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.17,0:23:55.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我一定奉上一桶青亭岛的佳酿\N{\fs16}I'll give you a cask of the Arbor's finest.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.93,0:24:02.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们不是商人\N{\fs16}You're not merchants.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.15,0:24:03.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去叫人来\N{\fs16}Get the others.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.77,0:24:57.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,告诉过你这把刀和我的羁绊很深的\N{\fs16}Told you, I'm very attached to this knife.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.27,0:25:00.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你还好吧？\N{\fs16}You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.88,0:25:03.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果他们发现一具被捅死的尸体\N{\fs16}If they find a body with a stab wound,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.15,0:25:05.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,全城的人都会出动搜查我们\N{\fs16}the whole city will be looking for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.57,0:25:38.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她们有些人认为多斯拉克人不该与外族通婚\N{\fs16}Some of them don't think Dothraki should breed with foreigners.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.59,0:25:43.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那群老蠢妇 她们从未察觉我们一直在稀释原始的血脉\N{\fs16}They are stupid old women. They don't realize that we have always diluted our blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.60,0:25:45.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这一个 是拉札人\N{\fs16}This one is Lhazareen.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.58,0:25:48.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她的卡奥放火烧掉她的村子后发现了躲在井底的她\N{\fs16}Her Khal found her hiding in a well after he burned her village.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.98,0:25:51.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你那时多大？\N{\fs16}How old were you?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.55,0:25:53.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,十二岁\N{\fs16}Twelve.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.93,0:25:58.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一年之后 她给她的卡奥诞下了一个女儿 当时他是怎样的欣喜若狂？\N{\fs16}A year later, she bore her Khal a daughter. How did he show his happiness?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.65,0:26:01.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他打断了我的肋骨\N{\fs16}He broke my ribs.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.52,0:26:07.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们不是这里的女王 但卡奥们倚仗我们的智慧\N{\fs16}We are not queens here, but the khals depend on us for our wisdom.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.74,0:26:09.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们的生活充满意义\N{\fs16}Our lives have meaning.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.85,0:26:12.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,比起多数人而言\N{\fs16}That is more than most have.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.83,0:26:18.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,卡奥们明晚在卡拉萨大会聚首时 我希望他们能让你与我们一起度过余生\N{\fs16}When the khals meet for the Khalar Vezhven tomorrow night, I hope they let you live out your days with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.03,0:26:22.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,其他的结果可就没那么舒服了\N{\fs16}The other possibilities are not so pleasant.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.18,0:26:25.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我去上厕所\N{\fs16}I need to make water.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.12,0:26:28.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不可能逃得出多斯拉克人的地盘\N{\fs16}You can't run from Dothraki
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.14,0:26:30.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你也清楚这一点\N{\fs16}You know this.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.82,0:26:33.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我从没想过逃离多斯拉克人\N{\fs16}I will never run from Dothraki
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.89,0:26:36.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去 给她带路\N{\fs16}Go, show her.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.15,0:26:39.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我需要呼吸点新鲜空气\N{\fs16}I needed fresh air.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.16,0:26:42.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,老女人太臭了\N{\fs16}The old women stink.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.20,0:26:43.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她们确实招人恶心\N{\fs16}They do stink.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.04,0:26:47.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的卡奥死时你一定非常年轻\N{\fs16}You must have been very young when your Khal died.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.54,0:26:48.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,十六岁\N{\fs16}Sixteen.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.54,0:26:52.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,可惜他没死得更早\N{\fs16}Too bad he didn't die sooner.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.57,0:26:56.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没错 真是可惜\N{\fs16}Yes, too bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.10,0:26:58.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你真的有三条龙吗？\N{\fs16}Is it true you have three dragons?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.78,0:27:04.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们会吐火吗？\N{\fs16}And they breathe fire?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.08,0:27:05.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,会\N{\fs16}They do.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.52,0:27:08.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想有朝一日亲眼看一看他们吗？\N{\fs16}Would you like to see them one day?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.38,0:27:10.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是一个多希卡林\N{\fs16}I am Dosh Khaleen.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.72,0:27:15.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我无法离开维斯·多斯拉克 直到我生命结束 化为火葬台上的一缕轻烟\N{\fs16}I can never leave Vaes Dothrak, until I rise as smoke from the pyre on the day I die.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.01,0:27:18.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 住手 不要伤害她 - 她会出卖我们\N{\fs16}- No, don't hurt her. - She'll give us away.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.28,0:27:20.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们现在得走了\N{\fs16}We have to go now.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.82,0:27:27.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们不可能从维斯·多斯拉克活着出去\N{\fs16}We will never get out of Vaes Dothrak alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.62,0:27:30.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们所能做的就是奋力一搏\N{\fs16}All we can do is try.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.12,0:27:32.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不\N{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.43,0:27:34.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们所能做的比那多得多\N{\fs16}We can do more than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.73,0:27:36.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而你们要助我一臂之力\N{\fs16}And you're going to help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.15,0:27:40.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,至于你……\N{\fs16}And you...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.74,0:27:42.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,请对我有信心 卡丽熙\N{\fs16}Have faith in me, Khaleesi.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.79,0:27:44.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不要背叛我\N{\fs16}Do not betray me.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.73,0:28:49.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果我现在让你离开 你会去哪里？\N{\fs16}If I were to let you leave right now, where would you go?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.36,0:28:52.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你会去找寻什么？\N{\fs16}What would you seek out?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.18,0:28:56.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会去见我的哥哥\N{\fs16}I'd go to my brother,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.78,0:28:58.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的丈夫 我的家人\N{\fs16}my husband, my family.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.35,0:29:02.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那是自然 但对你而言 这就意味着找寻金钱\N{\fs16}Of course, but for you, that means seeking out money,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.55,0:29:05.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,华服 权柄\N{\fs16}finery, power.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.52,0:29:09.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,找寻家人即是找寻罪恶\N{\fs16}Seeking out your family means seeking out sin.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.42,0:29:11.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我并不是诋毁你\N{\fs16}I'm not maligning you.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.43,0:29:14.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我也曾追寻那些东西\N{\fs16}I sought those things out, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.46,0:29:16.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,重视他们超过一切\N{\fs16}To the exclusion of all else.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.53,0:29:20.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我父亲是鞋匠\N{\fs16}My father was a cobbler.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.40,0:29:24.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他在我年轻时去世  我继承了他的店\N{\fs16}He died when I was young and I took over his shop.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.67,0:29:27.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他是个简单的人  做的鞋也很简便\N{\fs16}He was a simple man and he made simple shoes.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.28,0:29:30.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,可是我后来发现  我在制鞋上的功夫用的越多\N{\fs16}But I found that the more work I put into my shoes,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.78,0:29:31.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,卖的也就越好\N{\fs16}the more people wanted them.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.08,0:29:35.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,上好的皮革 装饰\N{\fs16}Fine leather, ornamentation,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.25,0:29:39.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,细节设计以及花费的时间\N{\fs16}detailing, and time.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.22,0:29:40.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,尤其是时间\N{\fs16}Time most of all.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.02,0:29:43.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,花去几十个钟头来制作一双鞋\N{\fs16}Dozens of hours spent on a single pair.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.73,0:29:45.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,品质需要时间\N{\fs16}Quality takes time.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.56,0:29:47.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,确实如此\N{\fs16}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.60,0:29:49.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我估计你一直都穿着某人花去一整年时间\N{\fs16}I imagine you've worn a year
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.76,0:29:52.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所制成的鞋\N{\fs16}of someone's life on your back.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.83,0:29:55.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,贵族喜欢用我的生命去呵护他们的脚\N{\fs16}The highborn liked to cover their feet with my time
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.27,0:29:58.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而且他们对此也给予丰厚的报酬\N{\fs16}and they paid well for the privilege.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.37,0:29:59.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我用他们给的钱\N{\fs16}I used their money
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.04,0:30:02.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去为自己购买机会 享受他们那种生活\N{\fs16}to buy a taste of their lives for myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.88,0:30:05.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,每当我沉溺于此\N{\fs16}Each time I indulged,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.11,0:30:09.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我都能感觉自己变得更好了\N{\fs16}I felt myself ascending to something better.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.32,0:30:11.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,后有某日汝穿过墓园\N{\fs16}And one day you walked through a graveyard
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.42,0:30:13.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,顿悟世事皆为浮云\N{\fs16}and realized it was all for nothing
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.22,0:30:15.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,乃下决心追逐正义\N{\fs16}and set out on the path to righteousness.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.86,0:30:18.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,陌客之书，第25节\N{\fs16}Book of the Stranger, verse 25.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.56,0:30:21.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你知道《七星圣经》？\N{\fs16}You know "The Seven-Pointed Star."
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.20,0:30:23.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,乌尼亚修女给我读过   她无时不刻不在读\N{\fs16}Septa Unella reads it to me. At me.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.97,0:30:27.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的  是的  她确实喜欢对人宣讲\N{\fs16}Yes, yes, she does enjoy reading at people.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.50,0:30:30.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你说的差不多\N{\fs16}You're close.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.04,0:30:34.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不过那不是墓园\N{\fs16}But it wasn't a graveyard.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.18,0:30:36.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而是一场盛宴\N{\fs16}It was a feast.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.11,0:30:38.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我买了好酒陈酿\N{\fs16}I bought old fine wine
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.48,0:30:40.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有很多年轻漂亮的女孩\N{\fs16}and young pretty girls
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.62,0:30:44.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,邀请朋友们前来 一起分享\N{\fs16}and invited my friends to come and share it all.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.42,0:30:47.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们分享美酒  分享女人\N{\fs16}We passed around the wine, passed around the women,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.92,0:30:50.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,陷入了恍惚状态\N{\fs16}and soon we fell into a stupor.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.96,0:30:56.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我在黎明前醒来\N{\fs16}I woke before dawn.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.83,0:30:59.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,几乎不能站直身\N{\fs16}I could barely stand.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.07,0:31:04.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,其他所有人都在长椅或者地上睡着\N{\fs16}Everyone else was asleep on the couches or on the floor,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.91,0:31:09.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,乱七八糟地睡在他们昂贵的衣服旁边\N{\fs16}lying in heaps next to their fine clothes.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.64,0:31:12.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们的身体一览无余\N{\fs16}The truth of their bodies laid bare.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.15,0:31:16.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我可以闻到他们\N{\fs16}I could smell them
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.08,0:31:20.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,透过熏香和香水\N{\fs16}beneath the incense and the perfume
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.52,0:31:24.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有美味佳肴已经开始变质的味道\N{\fs16}and the fine food that had already started to turn.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.36,0:31:29.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我非常清晰地看到了这一切\N{\fs16}And I saw it with perfect clarity.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.63,0:31:32.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我看到了我的罪\N{\fs16}I saw what my sins were.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.47,0:31:37.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我拥有的金子  我喝过的酒  我上过的女人\N{\fs16}The gold I had, the wine I drank, the women I used,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.44,0:31:41.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我为保住地位而做出的不懈努力\N{\fs16}my ceaseless struggle to maintain my position.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.31,0:31:48.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这都成了故事的一部分\N{\fs16}It was all part of a story.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.99,0:31:54.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一个我用来告诫自己“我是谁？”的故事\N{\fs16}A story I was telling myself about who I was.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.06,0:31:56.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一个在光明之下无所遁形的\N{\fs16}A collection of lies
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.72,0:31:58.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谎言的集合\N{\fs16}that would disappear in the light.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.79,0:32:02.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那些我曾避之唯恐不及的人\N{\fs16}The people I was trying to climb away from,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.80,0:32:04.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,街上的乞丐\N{\fs16}the beggars in the street,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.37,0:32:05.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,穷苦人\N{\fs16}the poor,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.00,0:32:09.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们比曾经的我更加接近真实\N{\fs16}they were closer to the truth than I ever was.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.87,0:32:12.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所以你做了什么？\N{\fs16}So what did you do?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.51,0:32:14.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我离开过去的生活 前去找寻他们\N{\fs16}I left to go and find them.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.48,0:32:18.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我甚至连鞋都没穿\N{\fs16}I didn't even put on my shoes.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.18,0:32:22.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我走出了门就再也没回去\N{\fs16}I walked out the door and never went back.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.82,0:32:29.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,来吧  我们去看看他\N{\fs16}Come, let's go and see him.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.99,0:32:33.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-谁？  -你哥哥\N{\fs16}- Who? - Your brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.38,0:32:50.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,洛拉斯\N{\fs16}Loras.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.08,0:32:59.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,洛拉斯\N{\fs16}Loras.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.04,0:33:19.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,听我说\N{\fs16}Listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.01,0:33:21.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你必须保持坚强\N{\fs16}You need to stay strong.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.31,0:33:27.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我根本坚强不了\N{\fs16}I can't stay strong.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:27.88,0:33:29.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我从没坚强过\N{\fs16}I never was strong.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.75,0:33:31.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你很坚强\N{\fs16}You are strong.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.62,0:33:33.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是我们家族的未来\N{\fs16}You are the future of our house,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.06,0:33:35.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们血脉的未来\N{\fs16}the future of our family.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.56,0:33:38.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我才不在乎那个\N{\fs16}I don't care about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.09,0:33:42.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你难道...你难道告诉他们那个了？\N{\fs16}Have you... have you told them that?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.46,0:33:43.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,告诉他们你不在乎？\N{\fs16}That you don't care?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.03,0:33:48.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我只想一切停下来\N{\fs16}I just want it to stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.44,0:33:52.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,帮帮我\N{\fs16}Help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.85,0:34:01.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们想让我帮你\N{\fs16}They want me to help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.98,0:34:05.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们想让我帮忙  把你逼疯\N{\fs16}They want me to help tear you down.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.82,0:34:08.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这就是为什么他让我来看你  我知道会是这样\N{\fs16}That's why he's letting me see you. I know it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:08.89,0:34:12.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果我们之中谁屈从于他们  他们就赢了\N{\fs16}And if either of us give in to what they want, then they win.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.66,0:34:14.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让他们赢吧\N{\fs16}Let them win.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.30,0:34:17.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只要让一切停止就行\N{\fs16}Just make it stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.87,0:34:20.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,求你了\N{\fs16}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.22,0:34:23.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fs16}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.14,0:34:31.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在当前的窘境下 如何避免灾难的降临\N{\fs16}And now, how to avert disaster with our current predicament.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.08,0:34:34.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这个大麻雀\N{\fs16}This High Sparrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.35,0:34:37.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,陛下  我应付过各种各样的狂信徒\N{\fs16}I have dealt with fanatics of every description, Your Grace.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.42,0:34:41.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不要激怒他们  这是最重要的事情\N{\fs16}Not setting them off, that's the most important thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.16,0:34:44.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你已经深陷内部和外部的敌人包围了\N{\fs16}You are beset with enemies both within and without.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.46,0:34:46.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你在这里做什么？\N{\fs16}What are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.86,0:34:52.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我就当前的窘境来给国王提供谏言\N{\fs16}I am advising the king on our current predicament.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.37,0:34:55.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-出去  -我可是御前重臣\N{\fs16}- Leave. - I am a member of the small council.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.84,0:34:57.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,陛下\N{\fs16}The king...
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.17,0:34:59.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是御前会议吗？\N{\fs16}Is this a small council meeting?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.91,0:35:01.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,显然不是\N{\fs16}Obviously not.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.28,0:35:04.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我来这是奉献我的智慧和支持\N{\fs16}I'm here to lend my wisdom and my support.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.48,0:35:07.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,感谢你的谏言  国师\N{\fs16}Thank you for your counsel, Grand Maester.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.82,0:35:09.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,今天就到此为止吧\N{\fs16}That will be all for now.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.82,0:35:11.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,陛下\N{\fs16}Your Grace.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.38,0:35:38.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,鉴于我错过了之前多次御前会议\N{\fs16}Since I've missed the past several small council meetings,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.01,0:35:41.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我想与你讨论几件事\N{\fs16}I wanted to speak to you about a few things.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.48,0:35:45.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我一直在思考大麻雀\N{\fs16}I've been thinking about the High Sparrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.89,0:35:48.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,彼此彼此 真不幸\N{\fs16}As have we all, unfortunately.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.66,0:35:51.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们和这样一个人打交道时必须小心\N{\fs16}We need to be careful in dealing with such a man.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.03,0:35:55.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,避免事态进一步升级\N{\fs16}To prevent things from escalating any further.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.60,0:35:59.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,避免与其敌对\N{\fs16}We have to be careful not to antagonize him.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.93,0:36:02.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他手上押着玛格丽  我们不能拿她冒险\N{\fs16}He has Margaery. We can't put her at risk.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.44,0:36:05.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-他很危险  -看着我\N{\fs16}- He's dangerous. - Look at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.27,0:36:07.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们对我做了什么？\N{\fs16}What did they do to me?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.21,0:36:09.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对国王的亲生母亲？\N{\fs16}To the king's own mother?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.72,0:36:16.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,算了\N{\fs16}It's all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.45,0:36:18.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,已经过去了  成了过去时\N{\fs16}It's done. It's in the past.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.99,0:36:21.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而且确实\N{\fs16}And of course
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.32,0:36:24.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,玛格丽的安全是第一位的\N{\fs16}Margaery's safety is paramount.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.39,0:36:29.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不喜欢玛格丽  对吧？\N{\fs16}You don't like Margaery, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.00,0:36:34.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我喜不喜欢她根本无关紧要\N{\fs16}Whether I like her or not is completely unimportant.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.57,0:36:38.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,玛格丽是王后\N{\fs16}Margaery is the queen.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.77,0:36:42.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,王后要有尊严  国王更须如此\N{\fs16}Queens must command respect. Kings even more so.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.98,0:36:45.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这不仅仅是为了他们  更是为了所有人\N{\fs16}Not just for their own sake, but for everyone's.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.75,0:36:51.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大麻雀对国王和王后没有尊重\N{\fs16}The High Sparrow has no respect for kings or queens.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.29,0:36:53.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对世上任何事情都没有尊重\N{\fs16}No respect for anything in this world.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.22,0:36:56.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他根本不在乎世上的一切存在\N{\fs16}He has no use for the things of this world.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.22,0:36:59.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他想将一切扳倒  然后用什么来取而代之？\N{\fs16}He wants to knock them down and replace them with what?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.96,0:37:02.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,用幻想\N{\fs16}With fantasies.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.16,0:37:04.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,用街上的乞丐\N{\fs16}With beggars in the street.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.27,0:37:05.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,用虚妄\N{\fs16}With nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.47,0:37:09.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,母亲……\N{\fs16}Mother...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.67,0:37:12.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有些事我想告诉您\N{\fs16}there's something I want to tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.78,0:37:16.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大麻雀告诉我的事\N{\fs16}Something the High Sparrow told me.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.88,0:37:20.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你和他谈过了？\N{\fs16}You've spoken with him?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.55,0:37:25.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我答应过他不会告诉任何人  如果他发现我……\N{\fs16}I promised him I wouldn't tell anyone. If he found out I told...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.09,0:37:28.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那就是他不会轻易饶恕的泄密行为了\N{\fs16}It would be a breach of confidence which he would not take lightly
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.99,0:37:31.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,瞧瞧他天天宣讲做人的真实\N{\fs16}given his constant prattling about the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.96,0:37:37.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是你的母亲\N{\fs16}I am your mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.43,0:37:40.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你永远可以信任我\N{\fs16}You can always trust me.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.48,0:37:51.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,根据国王陛下的命令 御前会议推迟举行\N{\fs16}The small council meeting has been postponed on the king's orders.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.98,0:37:54.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我还以为我们第一次会面时已经说得很清楚了\N{\fs16}I would have thought we were perfectly clear the first time.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:54.42,0:37:57.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-你在这里不受欢迎  -你说过你尊重我们的父亲\N{\fs16}- You're not welcome. - You once spoke of your respect for our father
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.58,0:38:00.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是因为他懂得和对手一起共事的重要性\N{\fs16}because he understood the necessity of working with one's rivals.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.42,0:38:05.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,亲爱的  你已经毫无尊严和权威可言\N{\fs16}My dear, you have been stripped of your dignity and authority,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.36,0:38:08.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,公开羞辱 然后软禁在红堡\N{\fs16}publically shamed, and confined to the Red Keep.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.46,0:38:10.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有什么共事的资本？\N{\fs16}What's left to work with?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.80,0:38:13.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,瑟曦是国王的母亲\N{\fs16}Cersei is the mother of the king.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.30,0:38:16.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,国王肯听她的意见 也信任她\N{\fs16}She has the king's ear and his trust.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.10,0:38:18.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,并且国王最近经常和大麻雀一起讨论\N{\fs16}And the king has been speaking regularly
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.14,0:38:21.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,玛格丽王后和洛拉斯爵士\N{\fs16}with the High Sparrow about Queen Margaery and Ser Loras.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.64,0:38:23.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大麻雀能够攫取权力\N{\fs16}The High Sparrow seized power
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.38,0:38:27.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,正因为看透了我们只会在内部争吵而不是将其夺回\N{\fs16}knowing full well we'd bicker amongst ourselves instead of seizing it back.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.25,0:38:29.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,下场如此  我们真不赖\N{\fs16}Here we are. Well done to us.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.15,0:38:31.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,现在七国的未来\N{\fs16}Now the future of the Seven Kingdoms
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.35,0:38:33.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,全操于他肮脏的农民之手\N{\fs16}rests in his dirty peasant hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.29,0:38:36.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,几天后  他将对我进行审判\N{\fs16}In a few days, he'll have a trial for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.16,0:38:39.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不过在此之前  玛格丽王后要先进行赎罪之旅\N{\fs16}But before that, Queen Margaery will make her walk of atonement.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.83,0:38:43.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的  玛格丽将要当着全城的善男信女的面\N{\fs16}Yes, Margaery will repent her sins
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.53,0:38:45.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,忏悔罪行\N{\fs16}before the good people of the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.60,0:38:48.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哦  不\N{\fs16}Oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.17,0:38:50.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这事不能发生\N{\fs16}That cannot happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.07,0:38:52.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不会发生\N{\fs16}That will not happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.97,0:38:54.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我同意\N{\fs16}I agree.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.28,0:39:00.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你有维斯特洛大陆第二多的军队\N{\fs16}You've got the second largest army in Westeros.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.28,0:39:01.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你将带他们进城\N{\fs16}You'll bring them into the city,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.82,0:39:04.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在玛格丽王后被羞辱之前阻止它发生\N{\fs16}stop Queen Margaery's humiliation before it starts,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.59,0:39:06.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,并将她带回王宫监护\N{\fs16}and take her back into Crown custody.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.09,0:39:10.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,为了王后的安全 国王已命我不要采取任何针对大麻雀\N{\fs16}The king has ordered me to take no action against the High Sparrow
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.93,0:39:14.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,或教团武装的行动\N{\fs16}or the Faith Militant out of fear for the queen's safety.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.13,0:39:15.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你无需行动\N{\fs16}You will take no action at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:16.06,0:39:18.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,当提利尔军队来的时候  你让开就是\N{\fs16}When the Tyrell armies come, you will stand down.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.70,0:39:22.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,国王的命令严格要求您不能让开吗？\N{\fs16}Are you expressly forbidden from standing down?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.47,0:39:25.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的  不过如果国王……\N{\fs16}No, but if the king should call...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.44,0:39:28.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,整个事件将在任何人要求你做任何事情之前结束\N{\fs16}The whole thing will be over before anyone can call on you to do anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.31,0:39:32.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那时大麻雀已被监禁 最好是死了\N{\fs16}When the High Sparrow is in custody or dead, preferably,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.55,0:39:35.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,玛格丽已回到托曼身边\N{\fs16}and Margaery's back at Tommen's side,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.18,0:39:37.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你觉得国王会对结果生气吗？\N{\fs16}do you think the king will be angry at the outcome?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.39,0:39:40.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你和我们一样讨厌这些狂信徒\N{\fs16}You hate these fanatics as much as we do.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.22,0:39:43.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你恨他们对你儿子的所作所为\N{\fs16}You hate what they've done to your son.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.59,0:39:45.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想要蓝塞尔回来吗？\N{\fs16}Do you want Lancel back?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.56,0:39:47.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还是说你已经彻底放弃他了？\N{\fs16}Or have you given him up for good?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.23,0:39:51.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我当然想要他回来\N{\fs16}Of course I want him back.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.87,0:39:56.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那就让开吧\N{\fs16}Then stand aside
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.57,0:39:59.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让那些将他从你身边夺走的人付出代价\N{\fs16}and let the people that took him from you be destroyed.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:03.34,0:40:05.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果一切没有按计划进行\N{\fs16}If it doesn't go as planned,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.25,0:40:07.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,麻雀们在城里有很多盟友\N{\fs16}the sparrows have many friends in this city.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.71,0:40:10.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,内战将会爆发   很多人会死\N{\fs16}We'll have civil war. Many will die.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.55,0:40:12.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,无论我们做什么都会有很多人死去\N{\fs16}Many will die no matter what we do.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.72,0:40:16.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们死好过咱们死\N{\fs16}Better them than us.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:12.91,0:41:15.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们说你回来了 我不信\N{\fs16}They told me you were home and I didn't believe it.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.35,0:41:20.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我说 “席恩·葛雷乔伊吗？”\N{\fs16}"Theon Greyjoy?" I said.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:20.19,0:41:22.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,“他死了”\N{\fs16}"He's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.62,0:41:24.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,“他死了很久了”\N{\fs16}He's been dead a long time."
Dialogue: 0,0:41:28.13,0:41:30.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他放你走的？\N{\fs16}He let you go?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.20,0:41:31.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我逃出来的\N{\fs16}I escaped.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:34.20,0:41:36.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我听不清\N{\fs16}I can't hear you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:36.14,0:41:37.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我逃出来的\N{\fs16}I escaped.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.14,0:41:41.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,看着我\N{\fs16}Look at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.58,0:41:51.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,看着我！\N{\fs16}Look at me!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.45,0:41:56.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好多人为了救你而死\N{\fs16}Men died trying to rescue you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.19,0:41:57.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们都是好人\N{\fs16}Good men.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:57.89,0:41:59.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的人\N{\fs16}My men.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:00.83,0:42:02.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对不起\N{\fs16}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:02.56,0:42:04.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你曾是我的弟弟\N{\fs16}You were my brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:04.70,0:42:07.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是个被宠坏了的混蛋 但你是我弟弟\N{\fs16}You were a spoiled little cunt, but you were my brother
Dialogue: 0,0:42:07.83,0:42:09.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我为你赌上了一切\N{\fs16}and I risked everything for you
Dialogue: 0,0:42:09.90,0:42:11.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你却背叛了我\N{\fs16}and you betrayed me.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:11.37,0:42:13.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我知道 我知道 我对不起你\N{\fs16}I know. I know and I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:13.64,0:42:14.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别说了\N{\fs16}Stop saying that.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:16.01,0:42:17.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他让我崩溃了\N{\fs16}He broke me.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:17.34,0:42:20.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他让我崩溃成了无数碎片\N{\fs16}He broke me into 1,000 pieces.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:20.15,0:42:21.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 我知道 -你不知道\N{\fs16}- I know. - You don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:21.62,0:42:24.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他送了一片给我们\N{\fs16}He sent us one of those pieces.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:24.22,0:42:26.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所以我才去救你\N{\fs16}That's why I came for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:32.23,0:42:34.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你为什么回来\N{\fs16}Why did you come here?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:34.23,0:42:35.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我还有什么地方可去？\N{\fs16}Where else could I go?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:35.93,0:42:39.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你听到父亲死了 就想回来争夺王位吗？\N{\fs16}You heard Father was dead and you thought you'd claim the crown?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:39.73,0:42:41.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不 不是的  入港之后我才知道他去世了\N{\fs16}No, no. I only heard he died after we docked.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.80,0:42:44.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,恰好在选王会之前回到派克岛？\N{\fs16}You happen to show up on Pyke right before the kingsmoot?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:44.81,0:42:46.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不知道这事\N{\fs16}I didn't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.28,0:42:52.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你觉得你搞了那些事情出来后\N{\fs16}You think any ironborn wants you to be king
Dialogue: 0,0:42:52.58,0:42:54.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还会有铁民想要拥戴你？\N{\fs16}after what you've done?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.48,0:42:56.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不想当国王\N{\fs16}I don't want to be king.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:56.55,0:42:59.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想要什么？\N{\fs16}What do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:59.89,0:43:01.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我应该听你的话 你是唯一一个……\N{\fs16}I should have listened to you. You're the only one...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:02.02,0:43:04.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,无所谓了 别哭了\N{\fs16}That doesn't matter anymore. Stop crying.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:04.46,0:43:06.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,看着我\N{\fs16}Look at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:07.22,0:43:09.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,告诉我你到底想要什么\N{\fs16}Tell me what you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.10,0:43:16.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你应该统治铁群岛\N{\fs16}You should rule the Iron Islands.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:18.04,0:43:20.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让我来帮你\N{\fs16}Let me help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:46.73,0:43:48.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们把你收拾得挺干净\N{\fs16}They've cleaned you up nicely.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:51.07,0:43:54.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你知道我是谁吗\N{\fs16}You know who I am?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:54.41,0:43:55.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一个老爷\N{\fs16}A lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:55.71,0:43:57.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fs16}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:57.74,0:44:00.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一个老爷\N{\fs16}A lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:00.41,0:44:02.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你见过我的家徽吗？\N{\fs16}You've seen my banners?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:03.68,0:44:05.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,剥皮人\N{\fs16}The flayed man.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:05.92,0:44:08.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你害怕吗？\N{\fs16}Does that worry you at all?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:08.86,0:44:10.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,剥皮后你会吃人吗？\N{\fs16}You eat them after?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:14.03,0:44:15.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不会\N{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:15.36,0:44:18.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我可是见过人吃人\N{\fs16}Then I've seen worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:42.52,0:44:44.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你服侍过史塔克家？\N{\fs16}You served the Starks?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:44.66,0:44:47.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的 他们用链子锁着我\N{\fs16}Aye. They put me in chains
Dialogue: 0,0:44:47.29,0:44:49.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,拿剑抵在我的喉咙上\N{\fs16}and put a sword at my throat,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:49.26,0:44:50.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所以我服侍他们\N{\fs16}so I served them.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:50.63,0:44:54.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,史塔克家族覆灭已久\N{\fs16}The Starks have been gone for a long time,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.10,0:44:56.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但你一直保护着瑞肯\N{\fs16}but you kept protecting Rickon.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:56.97,0:45:00.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,找得到合适的买家 他能卖个好价钱\N{\fs16}He'd fetch a good price to the right buyer.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:00.57,0:45:02.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我服侍他家族那么久\N{\fs16}I served his family a long time.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:02.44,0:45:04.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一点钱都没捞到\N{\fs16}Didn't get no wages.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:04.68,0:45:07.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,依我看 这是他们欠我的\N{\fs16}Way I see it, I'm owed.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:09.95,0:45:12.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,话虽如此\N{\fs16}Be that as it may,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:12.65,0:45:15.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,瑞肯再也不是你可以卖的了\N{\fs16}Rickon's not yours to sell anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:15.22,0:45:16.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他是我的了\N{\fs16}He's mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:16.99,0:45:20.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所以你现在还有什么用呢？\N{\fs16}So what use could I possibly have for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:22.43,0:45:24.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我可以给你你想要的\N{\fs16}I can give you what you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:24.87,0:45:27.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你真的知道我想要什么吗？\N{\fs16}And you're sure you know what that is?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:28.70,0:45:32.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,男人都想要一个东西\N{\fs16}Same thing men always want.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:32.31,0:45:36.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,男人想要的时候 就会先给她洗个澡\N{\fs16}And when they really want it, they give it a bath first.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:44.82,0:45:47.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你真会说话\N{\fs16}You're a good talker.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:49.36,0:45:51.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我喜欢\N{\fs16}I like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:58.80,0:46:02.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你比席恩·葛雷乔伊会说多了\N{\fs16}You're a much better talker than Theon Greyjoy.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:03.94,0:46:05.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是吗？\N{\fs16}That so?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:05.84,0:46:08.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让他开口说话真费劲\N{\fs16}I had to work hard to get him talking.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:08.24,0:46:10.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但他还是说了\N{\fs16}But he talked.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:10.84,0:46:12.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们都会说的\N{\fs16}They all do.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:12.61,0:46:15.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他什么都说了\N{\fs16}He told me everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:15.48,0:46:18.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,史塔克家男孩们的一切\N{\fs16}All about the Stark boys,
Dialogue: 0,0:46:18.42,0:46:20.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谁帮他们逃跑\N{\fs16}who helped them escape,
Dialogue: 0,0:46:20.75,0:46:22.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她是怎么帮的\N{\fs16}and how she did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:50.55,0:46:52.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,开门！\N{\fs16}Open the gate!
Dialogue: 0,0:47:39.53,0:47:41.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,吃的不好 抱歉\N{\fs16}Sorry about the food.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:41.74,0:47:43.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们可不以美食闻名\N{\fs16}It's not what we're known for.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:43.87,0:47:46.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没关系 你们有更重要的事\N{\fs16}That's all right. There are more important things.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:51.34,0:47:53.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的信 总司令大人\N{\fs16}A letter for you, Lord Commander.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:54.98,0:47:56.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我已经不是总司令了\N{\fs16}I'm not Lord Commander anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:16.84,0:48:19.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,叛徒及野种琼恩·雪诺\N{\fs16}"To the traitor and bastard Jon Snow.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:19.47,0:48:22.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你让数以千计的野人越过了绝境长城\N{\fs16}You allowed thousands of wildlings past the Wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:22.81,0:48:24.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你背叛了自己人\N{\fs16}You have betrayed your own kind.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:24.38,0:48:26.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你背叛了北境\N{\fs16}You have betrayed the North.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:26.35,0:48:29.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,临冬城是我的 野种 来看看吧\N{\fs16}Winterfell is mine, bastard. Come and see.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:31.08,0:48:33.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你弟弟瑞肯在我的地牢里\N{\fs16}Your brother Rickon is in my dungeon.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:41.83,0:48:43.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他的冰原狼的皮铺在我的地板上\N{\fs16}His direwolf's skin is on my floor.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:43.93,0:48:46.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,来看看吧 我要我的新娘\N{\fs16}Come and see. I want my bride back.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:46.37,0:48:50.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,交出她 野种 我便不找你或你的野人朋友们的麻烦\N{\fs16}Send her to me, bastard, and I will not trouble you or your wildling lovers.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:50.20,0:48:53.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如若不肯 我会向北进军 大肆屠戮\N{\fs16}Keep her from me and I will ride north and slaughter
Dialogue: 0,0:48:53.41,0:48:56.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所有在你庇护之下的野人 不管是男人 女人或小孩\N{\fs16}every wildling man, woman, and babe living under your protection.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:57.01,0:49:00.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会当着你的面活剥他们 我会……\N{\fs16}You will watch as I skin them living. You... "
Dialogue: 0,0:49:02.78,0:49:04.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,继续\N{\fs16}Go on.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:04.52,0:49:06.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,都是类似的话\N{\fs16}It's just more of the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:11.19,0:49:14.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让你眼睁睁地看着我的士兵轮奸你的妹妹\N{\fs16}"You will watch as my soldiers take turns raping your sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:16.30,0:49:17.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会让你眼睁睁的看着我的狗\N{\fs16}You will watch as my dogs
Dialogue: 0,0:49:17.70,0:49:20.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,吃了你狂野的幼弟\N{\fs16}devour your wild little brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:22.34,0:49:25.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,然后我会挖出你的眼睛 剩下的留给我的狗\N{\fs16}Then I will spoon your eyes from their sockets and let my dogs do the rest.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:26.07,0:49:30.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,来看看吧 拉姆斯·波顿 临冬城公爵和\N{\fs16}Come and see. Ramsay Bolton, Lord of Winterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:49:30.11,0:49:31.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,北境守护\N{\fs16}and Warden of the North."
Dialogue: 0,0:49:35.38,0:49:39.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,临冬城公爵和北境守护\N{\fs16}Lord of Winterfell and Warden of the North.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:39.42,0:49:42.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他父亲死了\N{\fs16}His father's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:42.42,0:49:43.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,拉姆斯杀了他\N{\fs16}Ramsay killed him.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:44.06,0:49:46.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 现在他手里还有瑞肯 - 我们不能确定\N{\fs16}- And now he has Rickon. - We don't know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:46.53,0:49:48.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不 可以确定\N{\fs16}Yes, we do.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:49.03,0:49:51.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他有多少兵？\N{\fs16}How many men does he have in his army?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:53.60,0:49:57.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他说起史坦尼斯的进攻时 提到有五千人\N{\fs16}I heard him say 5,000 once when he was talking about Stannis's attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:57.44,0:49:59.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你有多少人？\N{\fs16}How many do you have?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:59.91,0:50:02.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,能行军打仗的？\N{\fs16}That can march and fight?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:02.98,0:50:04.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,二千\N{\fs16}2,000.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:06.01,0:50:08.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,剩下的是小孩和老人\N{\fs16}The rest are children and old people.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:13.42,0:50:16.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是真正的北境守护之子\N{\fs16}You're the son of the last true Warden of the North.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:16.46,0:50:20.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,北境家族都很忠诚 只要你要求 他们会和你并肩战斗\N{\fs16}Northern families are loyal. They'll fight for you if you ask.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:22.23,0:50:26.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那个魔鬼抢走了我们的家 我们的弟弟\N{\fs16}A monster has taken our home and our brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:27.87,0:50:30.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们必须回到临冬城 把他们都抢回来\N{\fs16}We have to go back to Winterfell and save them both.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:42.86,0:50:45.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,圣城中禁止流血\N{\fs16}It is forbidden to spill blood in the sacred city.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:45.87,0:50:49.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也禁止携带武器\N{\fs16}It is forbidden to <i>carry weapons</i> in the sacred city.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:49.18,0:50:51.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所以我们不流血\N{\fs16}So we don't spill blood!
Dialogue: 0,0:50:51.14,0:50:53.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,嗯……也总不能一点血都不流吗\N{\fs16}Well... there's always a little blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:53.98,0:50:57.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有人用石头砸烂了他的头\N{\fs16}Someone crushed his head with a rock.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:57.28,0:50:59.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,阿戈属于我的卡拉萨\N{\fs16}Aggo belonged to my khalasar.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:59.67,0:51:01.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他很干的很好\N{\fs16}He served me well.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:01.49,0:51:03.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他被人用石头砸烂了头\N{\fs16}He got his head smashed in by a rock.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:04.00,0:51:05.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去他的阿戈\N{\fs16}Fuck Aggo.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:11.72,0:51:14.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,把卓戈的遗孀带上来\N{\fs16}Bring in Drogo's widow.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:36.72,0:51:40.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谁看得上她？她是个矮子\N{\fs16}Who cares about her? She's a midget.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:40.52,0:51:42.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我喜欢她\N{\fs16}I like her.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:42.34,0:51:44.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她比牛奶还惨白\N{\fs16}She's paler than milk.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:44.26,0:51:46.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我想尝尝卡丽熙是什么滋味\N{\fs16}I'd like to know what a khaleesi tastes like.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:46.80,0:51:47.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好啊\N{\fs16}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:47.97,0:51:49.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,尝尝我的小兄弟就知道了\N{\fs16}You can suck my dick.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:50.25,0:51:53.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她属于多希卡林\N{\fs16}She belongs with the Dosh Khaleen.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:53.26,0:51:55.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,渊凯的贤主大人们想要她\N{\fs16}The Wise Masters of Yunkai want her.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:55.75,0:51:58.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们想用一万匹马交换\N{\fs16}They're offering ten thousand horses in exchange.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:58.69,0:52:00.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哪个更值钱\N{\fs16}What's worth more,
Dialogue: 0,0:52:00.15,0:52:02.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一个粉嘟嘟的小女孩儿 还是一万匹马\N{\fs16}one pink little girl or ten thousand horses?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:02.82,0:52:06.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,操他贤主大人的香屁股\N{\fs16}Fuck the Wise Masters in their perfumed asses.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:06.25,0:52:08.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,要马我自己会抢\N{\fs16}I'll take their horses for myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:09.24,0:52:12.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们不想听听我的想法吗？\N{\fs16}Don't you want to know what I think?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:14.43,0:52:16.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想被卖了当奴隶？\N{\fs16}You'd rather be sold into slavery?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:17.21,0:52:20.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还是想给拉寇尝尝你的滋味\N{\fs16}Or maybe you'd like to show Rhalko here what you taste like?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:20.61,0:52:22.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不想\N{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:22.09,0:52:24.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哪个都不想\N{\fs16}I don't want either of those things.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:24.06,0:52:25.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想不想我们不在乎\N{\fs16}We don't care what you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:25.80,0:52:28.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是多希卡林神庙\N{\fs16}This is the Temple of the Dosh Khaleen.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:28.08,0:52:29.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这没你说话的份儿\N{\fs16}You have no voice here,
Dialogue: 0,0:52:29.69,0:52:31.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,除非你是多希卡林\N{\fs16}unless you are Dosh Khaleen.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:31.89,0:52:34.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但你不是 除非我们认定你是\N{\fs16}Which you are not, until we decide you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:34.64,0:52:38.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我知道我在哪 我来过这儿\N{\fs16}I know where I am. I have been here before.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:38.63,0:52:43.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,多希卡林在这儿预言我的孩子会成为骑着世界的骏马\N{\fs16}This is where the Dosh Khaleen pronounced my child the Stallion Who Mounts the World.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:43.46,0:52:45.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,然后呢？\N{\fs16}And what happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:45.46,0:52:47.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你像傻瓜一样 竟然相信一个巫魔女\N{\fs16}You trusted a sorceress, like a fool.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:48.00,0:52:51.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为你 你的孩子死了\N{\fs16}Your baby is dead because of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:51.72,0:52:54.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,卓戈卡奥也死了\N{\fs16}And so is Khal Drogo.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:55.75,0:52:59.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在这儿卓戈发誓要带着他的卡拉萨向西走到世界尽头\N{\fs16}This is where Drogo promised to take his khalasar west to where the world ends.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:59.97,0:53:03.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,骑着木马横渡黑色咸水 做出古往今来其他卡奥都从来没有做过的事\N{\fs16}To ride wooden horses across the Black Salt Sea as no khal has done before.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:03.81,0:53:09.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他发誓要杀死穿铁衣服的人 拆了他们的石头房子\N{\fs16}He promised to kill the men in their iron suits and tear down their stone houses.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:10.17,0:53:13.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他在圣母山前对我发誓\N{\fs16}He swore to me before the Mother of Mountains.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:13.71,0:53:15.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你竟然蠢到相信他\N{\fs16}And you were dumb enough to believe him.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:16.36,0:53:20.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,此时此地 伟大的卡奥们在讨论什么？\N{\fs16}And here, now, what great matters do the Great Khals discuss?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:20.30,0:53:22.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,抢劫哪个小村子\N{\fs16}Which little villages you'll raid,
Dialogue: 0,0:53:22.39,0:53:26.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,能骑多少个姑娘 该要求多少匹骏马作贡品\N{\fs16}how many girls you'll get to fuck, how many horses you'll demand in tribute.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:26.62,0:53:29.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们都是小人物\N{\fs16}You are small men.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:29.26,0:53:32.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们不配领导多斯拉克人\N{\fs16}None of you are fit to lead the Dothraki.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:34.54,0:53:37.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我配\N{\fs16}But I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:39.02,0:53:41.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而我也将领导\N{\fs16}So I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:50.78,0:53:52.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好\N{\fs16}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:52.70,0:53:55.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不用当多希卡林了\N{\fs16}No Dosh Khaleen for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:55.27,0:53:59.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们轮流上你\N{\fs16}Instead we'll take turns fucking you.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:59.04,0:54:03.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,然后让我们的血盟卫上你\N{\fs16}And then we'll let our bloodriders fuck you.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:04.99,0:54:08.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你要是还撑得住\N{\fs16}And if there's anything left of you,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:08.75,0:54:11.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,再给我们的马一个机会\N{\fs16}we'll give our horses a turn.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:14.67,0:54:17.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,疯婊子\N{\fs16}You crazy cunt.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:17.45,0:54:21.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你真以为我们会臣服于你？\N{\fs16}Did you really think we would serve you?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:27.38,0:54:29.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们不用臣服\N{\fs16}You're not going to serve.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:29.69,0:54:31.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们会死\N{\fs16}You're not going to die.

