[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.2.2012.322
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: Game of Thrones S06E02
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 衣柜
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 衣柜
Script Updated By: 衣柜
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 720
PlayResY: 404
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Titles,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles_L,Microsoft YaHei,24,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Character_L,Microsoft YaHei,28,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,4,10,10,10,1
Style: Character_B,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Author,Microsoft YaHei,16,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,1,10,10,10,1
Style: QR code - BG,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000019FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,400,400,0,0,1,0,0,5,0,0,0,1
Style: QR code - code,Arial,20,&H00000000,&H000019FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,200,200,0,0,1,0,0,5,0,0,0,1
Style: Titles - 1,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,5,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles - 2,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles - 3 -,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H0001031B,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000429,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Subtitle,Microsoft YaHei,26,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.96,0:00:11.50,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(1000,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx89\fscy89\p1\move(298,257,298,257,120,1400)}m -11 -35 l -11 39 l 63 39 l 63 -35{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.96,0:00:11.50,Titles - 2,,0,0,0,,{\fad(1000,500)\move(340,280,340,280,300,1400)\p1\fscx40\fscy40}m -86 -116 b -89 -117 -89 -117 -95 -119 l -97 -115 l -85 -105 l -116 -102 b -116 -100 -116 -98 -116 -97 l -108 -91 l -96 -91 l -116 -63 l -105 -69 l -96 -47 l -74 -63 l -77 -69 l -91 -63 l -91 -77 l -88 -80 l -66 -49 l -46 -63 l -58 -66 l -66 -74 l -49 -80 l -60 -91 l -74 -83 l -80 -91 l -77 -94 l -46 -94 l -52 -108 l -71 -105 b -69 -107 -67 -110 -66 -113 m -31 -119.875 l -33 -119 b -34 -113 -36 -107 -38 -102 l -46 -97 b -42 -93 -38 -89 -35 -85 l -44 -63 b -41 -64 -38 -65 -35 -66 l -35 -52 l -33 -47 l -27 -55 l -27 -69 l -21 -63 l -21 -69 l -19 -72 l -27 -88 l -21 -94 l -21 -99 l -27 -102 l -27 -102 l -30 -116 m -21 -113 l -21 -105 l -21 -99 l -21 -94 l -19 -85 l -19 -66 l -21 -49 l -19 -47 l -7 -52 l 26 -52 l 18 -66 l -7 -63 l -5 -69 l 6 -69 l 18 -69 l 20 -99 l -7 -94 l -7 -83 l 6 -85 l 6 -80 l -7 -77 l -7 -94 l -10 -99 l 23 -102 l 18 -116 l -10 -110 l -19 -116 m -105 -38 l -116 -41 l -110 -13 l -102 -19 l -102 -30 l -63 -33 l -55 -19 l -46 -41 l -49 -44 m -88 -33 l -91 -24 l -99 -24 l -105 -16 l -102 -13 l -85 -16 l -85 -10 l -94 -8 l -85 -16 l -102 -13 l -108 1 l -88 1 l -88 4 l -116 6 l -116 9 l -110 15 l -88 15 l -85 26 l -77 23 l -74 15 l -52 15 l -49 15 l -52 4 l -74 6 l -71 1 l -55 -2 l -60 -13 l -74 -10 l -74 -13 l -55 -16 l -63 -24 l -74 -24 l -80 -33 m -46 -41 l -38 -2 l -41 23 l -38 26 l 1 20 l 15 26 l 18 23 l 18 -8 l 20 -41 l 20 -44 l -24 -38 l -35 -41 l -35 -30 l -13 -30 l -19 -21 l -33 -19 l -33 -13 l -21 -13 l -33 6 l -33 15 l -13 -5 l -13 1 l -21 6 l -13 12 l -2 9 l -2 -8 l 9 -10 l 12 -19 l 1 -21 l -2 -27 l 9 -33 l 6 -16 l 6 -10 l 9 12 l -2 9 l -30 12 l -30 12 l -27 -2 l -27 -2 l -30 -16 l -27 -21 l -35 -41 m -126 -127 l -130 -130 l -129 38 l 34 37 l 35 -135 l -130 -131 l -127 -127 l 30 -129 l 31 32 l -124 34
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.96,0:00:11.50,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(386,224.2)\fad(1000,500)\b0\fs18\bord1} 最专业冰火字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.96,0:00:11.50,Titles - 1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(384,165.2)\fad(1000,500)}\N{\fs20}{\fs32.001\c&HFFFFFF&\b1}诚意奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.96,0:00:11.50,Titles - 1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(385,197.2)\fad(1000,500)\b000}专注GOT剧集{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.00,0:00:13.50,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(393.25,100.022)\fad(300,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}兮迩CeCe
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.05,0:00:16.00,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.875,313.122)\fad(500,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}拉拉兄控凯冯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.30,0:00:18.10,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(437.875,113.367)\fad(500,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}林顿
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.95,0:00:28.95,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(176.708,104.159)\fad(500,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}SerGawen
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.05,0:00:31.20,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(401.209,112.666)\fad(500,500)}校对{\fs24} {\b1}屈畅   赵琳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.60,0:00:35.30,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(158.417,137.016)\fad(500,500)}校对{\fs24} {\b1}守誓剑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.90,0:00:39.90,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(439.125,127.792)\fad(500,500)}后期{\fs24} {\b1}SerGawen@huiji.wiki
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.50,0:00:52.50,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(154,140.961)\fad(500,500)}监制{\fs24} {\b1}临冬城的狮子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.10,0:00:50.10,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(418.792,170.97)\fad(500,500)}监制{\fs24} {\b1}北落师门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.50,0:01:10.50,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(478.917,112.893)\fad(500,500)}策划{\fs24} {\b1}衣柜军团
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.10,0:01:18.10,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(120.792,141.05)\fad(500,500)}特别顾问{\fs24} {\b1}屈畅(ccxx)@史诗图书
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.26,0:00:23.66,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\t(\fscx150\fscy150,150)\p1\move(277,278,289,305,1,4381)}m -15 -18 l -15 -17 l -14 -16 l -13 -16 l -11 -15 l -6 -16 b -8 -15 -8 -15 -11 -13 l -14 -9 l -12 -9 l -10 -8 l -5 -9 b -4 -8 -2 -6 6 -7 l 7 -7 l 3 -8 l 1 -10 b 2 -14 5 -17 3 -19 l 2 -21 l 5 -21 l 3 -22 l 0 -23 l 0 -24 l 4 -26 l 8 -23 l 16 -21 b 20 -23 25 -24 28 -36 l 27 -35 b 26 -35 26 -35 22 -37 b 25 -34 25 -32 24 -32 l 17 -34 l 23 -30 b 22 -29 20 -27 19 -29 l 14 -33 b 15 -31 17 -29 16 -26 b 13 -25 11 -24 7 -27 l 11 -31 l 10 -36 b 10 -32 11 -32 8 -30 b 7 -30 5 -29 4 -29 b 3 -30 2 -31 0 -34 l 3 -28 l -1 -27 l -5 -30 l -7 -34 l -6 -30 l -3 -27 l -8 -28 l -15 -32 l -10 -27 l -6 -25 l -4 -25 l -7 -23 l -10 -21 l -3 -21 l -5 -20 l -7 -21 l -7 -22 l -8 -22 l -13 -19{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.26,0:00:23.66,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\pos(301.714,255.889)\fad(300,500)\frx360\t(20,200,\frx0)\fs25\b1}君临{\fs12\b0} King's Landing
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.31,0:00:27.73,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\move(420,300,420,280)\fs25\p1}m -17 -23 l -10 -8 l -19 -15 l -12 -1 l -24 -9 l -14 6 l -25 1 l -16 9 l -13 17 l -15 24 l 18 24 l 13 19 l 15 12 l 22 4 l 13 10 l 25 -3 l 20 0 l 14 3 l 17 -3 l 22 -11 l 13 -4 l 18 -21 l 13 -15 l 10 -13 l 11 -26 l 7 -16 l 7 -28 l 3 -16 l 0 -32 l -2 -15 l -6 -22 l -8 -28 l -8 -11{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.31,0:00:27.73,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(380,230,380,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}红堡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.31,0:00:27.73,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(425,250,425,235)\fad(300,500)\fs12\b0} Red Keep
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.31,0:00:35.31,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(380,260,380,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}派
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.50,0:00:35.31,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(405,260,405,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}克
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.70,0:00:35.31,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(430,260,430,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}城
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.31,0:00:35.31,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(460,260,460,240)\fad(300,500)\fs12\b0}Pyke
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.50,0:00:47.01,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(334.667,176.333)\fad(1000,1000)\frx25\fs28\b1\frz-22\t(0,1800,\frz-0)}临冬城\N{\fs12\b0}Winterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.59,0:01:39.59,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(338,265)\fad(1250,1000)\frx50\t(1200,2500,\frx0)\fs28} {\b1}弥林\N{\fs12\b0}Meereen
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.32,0:01:13.50,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\pos(337.5,157.549)\fad(500,500)\fs12.746} 联合出品
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.32,0:01:13.50,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\fad(500,500)\fs24} 史诗图书 | 冰火中文维基 | 黑城堡奇幻微刊\N{\fs20}\N{\fs20}\N{\fs20}{\fs12}\N{\fs20}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.32,0:01:13.50,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\pos(337.5,212.563)\fad(500,500)\fs14.997} Epic Books         ASOIAF.huiji.wiki          Heichengbao
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.50,0:01:16.00,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(516.25,119.545)\fad(500,500)} {\fs24\b1} 史诗图书 {\fs18\b0} 正统奇幻的圣殿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.52,0:01:07.02,Titles,,0,30,200,,{\fad(100,50)\frx75\t(0,3500,\frx-0)\fs28} {\b1}绝境长城{\fs12\b0} the Wall
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.43,0:01:26.22,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(355,250,370,250)\fs28\b1}布拉佛斯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.43,0:01:26.22,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(365,260,355,260)\fad(100,1000)\fs12\b0} Braavos
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.30,0:00:59.18,Titles,,0,0,100,,{\fs25\c&HC1DFED&\fad(100,1000)} {\b0} 最专业的华语冰火资料站：        冰与火之歌{\b0\fs20}中文维基{\b0}\N{\fs20}\N{\fs20\c&HFFFFFF&}http://asoiaf.huiji.wiki
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.50,0:00:59.18,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,1000)\pos(410,285)\fs25\c&HC1DFED&} {\b1\p1\fscx60\fscy60}m 31 -6 l -21 40 l 34 22 m 29 -8 l -3 -12 l -24 40{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.10,0:01:38.80,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(462,310)\fad(500,500)\fs14} {\c&HC1DFED&}根据长篇小说
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.10,0:01:38.80,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(552,334)\fad(500,500)} {\fs24}《{\b1}冰与火之歌{\b0}》{\fs14} 改编
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.10,0:01:38.80,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(625,358)\fad(500,500)} {\fs14} 原著 {\fs20} 乔治·R·R·马丁
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.32,0:01:49.63,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(350,294.067)\fad(300,500)\fs56.267\fn宋体\b1}权力的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.32,0:01:49.63,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(348.667,322)\fad(300,500)\c&HFFFFFF&\b1\fs22}衣柜字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(428,118.44)\fad(500,500)\p1}m -18.625 0 l -18.625 0 l 281.25 0 l 281.25 1.125 l -18.625 1.125{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\pos(231.125,202.841)\p1\fscx35\fscy35}m -86 -116 b -89 -117 -89 -117 -95 -119 l -97 -115 l -85 -105 l -116 -102 b -116 -100 -116 -98 -116 -97 l -108 -91 l -96 -91 l -116 -63 l -105 -69 l -96 -47 l -74 -63 l -77 -69 l -91 -63 l -91 -77 l -88 -80 l -66 -49 l -46 -63 l -58 -66 l -66 -74 l -49 -80 l -60 -91 l -74 -83 l -80 -91 l -77 -94 l -46 -94 l -52 -108 l -71 -105 b -69 -107 -67 -110 -66 -113 m -31 -119.875 l -33 -119 b -34 -113 -36 -107 -38 -102 l -46 -97 b -42 -93 -38 -89 -35 -85 l -44 -63 b -41 -64 -38 -65 -35 -66 l -35 -52 l -33 -47 l -27 -55 l -27 -69 l -21 -63 l -21 -69 l -19 -72 l -27 -88 l -21 -94 l -21 -99 l -27 -102 l -27 -102 l -30 -116 m -21 -113 l -21 -105 l -21 -99 l -21 -94 l -19 -85 l -19 -66 l -21 -49 l -19 -47 l -7 -52 l 26 -52 l 18 -66 l -7 -63 l -5 -69 l 6 -69 l 18 -69 l 20 -99 l -7 -94 l -7 -83 l 6 -85 l 6 -80 l -7 -77 l -7 -94 l -10 -99 l 23 -102 l 18 -116 l -10 -110 l -19 -116 m -105 -38 l -116 -41 l -110 -13 l -102 -19 l -102 -30 l -63 -33 l -55 -19 l -46 -41 l -49 -44 m -88 -33 l -91 -24 l -99 -24 l -105 -16 l -102 -13 l -85 -16 l -85 -10 l -94 -8 l -85 -16 l -102 -13 l -108 1 l -88 1 l -88 4 l -116 6 l -116 9 l -110 15 l -88 15 l -85 26 l -77 23 l -74 15 l -52 15 l -49 15 l -52 4 l -74 6 l -71 1 l -55 -2 l -60 -13 l -74 -10 l -74 -13 l -55 -16 l -63 -24 l -74 -24 l -80 -33 m -46 -41 l -38 -2 l -41 23 l -38 26 l 1 20 l 15 26 l 18 23 l 18 -8 l 20 -41 l 20 -44 l -24 -38 l -35 -41 l -35 -30 l -13 -30 l -19 -21 l -33 -19 l -33 -13 l -21 -13 l -33 6 l -33 15 l -13 -5 l -13 1 l -21 6 l -13 12 l -2 9 l -2 -8 l 9 -10 l 12 -19 l 1 -21 l -2 -27 l 9 -33 l 6 -16 l 6 -10 l 9 12 l -2 9 l -30 12 l -30 12 l -27 -2 l -27 -2 l -30 -16 l -27 -21 l -35 -41 m -126 -127 l -130 -130 l -129 38 l 34 37 l 35 -135 l -130 -131 l -127 -127 l 30 -129 l 31 32 l -124 34{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(293,112.813)\fad(500,500)\b1}协力制作
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(293,157.827)\fad(500,500)}史诗图书\N{\fs16}Epic Books
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(405.5,157.827)\fad(500,500)}冰火中文维基\N{\fs16}ASOIAF.HuiJi.WiKi
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(518,157.827)\fad(500,500)}黑城堡\N{\fs16}EPICASTLE
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.60,0:01:55.20,Titles_L,,260,0,163,,{\pos(310,300)\fad(500,500)\fs16\b0}第二集
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.60,0:01:55.20,Titles_L,,300,0,132,,{\pos(310,340)\fad(500,500)}家\N{\fs16\b0}Home
Dialogue: 0,0:52:23.75,0:53:23.00,Titles,,0,0,20,,{\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(360,390)}衣柜字幕组出品
Dialogue: 0,0:52:23.75,0:53:23.00,Titles,,0,0,40,,{\be1\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(357,372)}本集关键字：{\c&H5650F3\b0}旺旺 攸伦
Dialogue: 0,0:52:23.75,0:53:23.00,Titles,,0,0,335,,{\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(360,40)}剧情没看懂？ 典故不清楚？{\b0}\N维基新站网址：{\c&H00FF40}HTTP://AsoIaF.HuiJi.WiKi
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.50,0:02:19.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(589,284)\fad(300,500)}三眼乌鸦\N{\b0\fs12}先知
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.50,0:02:26.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(385,262)\fad(300,500)}布兰·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}先知
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.20,0:06:09.20,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(589,300)\fad(300,500)}梅拉·黎德\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.00,0:07:05.60,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(328,262)\fad(300,500)}叶子\N{\b0\fs12}森林之子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.00,0:07:46.90,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(513,247)\fad(300,500)}艾里沙·索恩\N{\b0\fs12}守夜人总教头
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.50,0:07:55.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(257,279)\fad(300,500)}戴佛斯·席渥斯\N{\b0\fs12}洋葱骑士
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.30,0:09:10.30,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(557,312)\fad(300,500)}“旺旺”\N{\b0\fs12}巨人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.70,0:09:22.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(63,312)\fad(300,500)}托蒙德\N{\b0\fs12}野人头领
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.50,0:10:04.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(516,254)\fad(300,500)}忧郁的艾迪\N{\b0\fs12}守夜人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.00,0:12:29.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(135,254)\fad(300,500)}劳勃·斯壮\N{\b0\fs12}御林铁卫
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.00,0:12:45.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(197,274)\fad(300,500)}瑟曦·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}太后
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.50,0:14:31.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(81,248)\fad(300,500)}拖曼·拜拉席恩一世\N{\b0\fs12}国王
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.80,0:14:36.80,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(647,274)\fad(300,500)}詹姆·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.50,0:16:32.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(428,284)\fad(300,500)}大麻雀\N{\b0\fs12}总主教
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.50,0:21:09.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(585,296)\fad(300,500)}提利昂·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}“小恶魔”
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.00,0:21:29.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(123,296)\fad(300,500)}瓦里斯\N{\b0\fs12}“八爪蜘蛛”
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.20,0:21:30.90,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(538,214)\fad(300,500)}灰虫子\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.00,0:21:56.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(64,227)\fad(300,500)}弥桑黛
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.00,0:27:10.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(508,241)\fad(300,500)}艾莉亚·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}无名之辈
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.00,0:28:05.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(670,216)\fad(300,500)}贾昆·赫加尔\N{\b0\fs12}无面者
Dialogue: 0,0:29:07.80,0:29:09.80,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(115,207)\fad(300,500)}卢斯·波顿\N{\b0\fs12}北境守护
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.50,0:29:19.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(338,200)\fad(300,500)}拉姆斯·波顿\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.00,0:32:50.70,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(609,211)\fad(300,500)}瓦妲·佛雷\N{\b0\fs12}卢斯·波顿之妻
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.50,0:35:57.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(468,274)\fad(300,500)}珊莎·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.30,0:36:01.30,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(240,267)\fad(300,500)}塔斯的布蕾妮\N{\b0\fs12}“美人”
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.50,0:36:49.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(67,272)\fad(300,500)}波德瑞克·派恩\N{\b0\fs12}侍从
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.20,0:37:03.20,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(568,254)\fad(300,500)}“臭佬”\N{\b0\fs12}席恩·葛雷乔伊
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.00,0:38:45.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(336,269)\fad(300,500)}巴隆·葛雷乔伊\N{\b0\fs12}铁群岛之王
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.00,0:38:57.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(208,241)\fad(300,500)}亚拉·葛雷乔伊\N{\b0\fs12}巴隆之女
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.50,0:44:57.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(475,244)\fad(300,500)}梅丽珊卓\N{\b0\fs12}红袍祭司
Dialogue: 0,0:52:07.50,0:52:11.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(498,162)\fad(300,500)}白灵\N{\b0\fs12}琼恩·雪诺的冰原狼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.20,0:02:46.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,再跟他打一轮 奈德\N{\fs16}Give him another go, Ned.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.62,0:02:48.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那是我父亲\N{\fs16}That's my father.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.67,0:02:50.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有我叔叔班扬\N{\fs16}And my Uncle Benjen.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.96,0:02:54.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,抬高盾牌 不然我会把你的脑袋敲得嗡嗡响\N{\fs16}Keep your shield up or I'll ring your head like a bell.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.38,0:03:04.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们好开心\N{\fs16}They were all so happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.80,0:03:07.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你曾经也是\N{\fs16}So were you once.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.78,0:03:16.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别显摆了\N{\fs16}- Stop showing off.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.28,0:03:17.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,莱安娜！\N{\fs16}Benjen: Lyanna!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.95,0:03:19.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我姑姑莱安娜\N{\fs16}My Aunt Lyanna.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.73,0:03:22.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我在墓窖中见过她的雕像\N{\fs16} I've seen her statue in the crypt.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.24,0:03:25.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,父亲从不谈论她\N{\fs16}My father never talked about her.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.46,0:03:34.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你别在这儿碍事行吗？我们正练武呢\N{\fs16}Benjen:  Would you get out of here? We're sparring.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.33,0:03:38.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,等奈德去了鹰巢城 看你和谁练武\N{\fs16}Who are you gonna spar with when Ned goes off to the Eyrie?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.59,0:03:39.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不知道\N{\fs16}Benjen:  I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.75,0:03:41.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他怎么样？\N{\fs16}What about him?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.76,0:03:44.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,威利斯 过来\N{\fs16}Wylis, come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.32,0:03:52.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,阿多？\N{\fs16}Hodor?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.32,0:03:54.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,可他有巨人的血统\N{\fs16}Benjen:  But he's got giant's blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.44,0:03:57.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而你训练有素 依我看是场公平对决\N{\fs16}And you've got training. Sounds like a fair match to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.07,0:04:00.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,班杨冲锋前总会扬起下巴\N{\fs16}Benjen always lifts his chin when he's about to charge.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.78,0:04:03.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他躲避时则会收回下巴 小姐\N{\fs16}And lowers it when he's going to dodge, my lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.61,0:04:05.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,阿多会说话？\N{\fs16}Hodor talks?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.95,0:04:13.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让少爷们去练武 威利斯\N{\fs16}You leave the fighting to the little lords, Wylis.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.01,0:04:16.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,赶紧过来 那不是你该待的地方\N{\fs16}Come along, now. It's no place for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.59,0:04:19.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,噢 奶妈 看看他的体格\N{\fs16}Oh, Nan, look at the size of him.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.18,0:04:21.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他要是好好练武 一定所向披靡\N{\fs16}If he ever learned to fight, he'd be unstoppable.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.55,0:04:24.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哎，他不会练的，他只是个马僮罢了\N{\fs16}Well, he's never going to learn to fight because he's a stable boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.63,0:04:26.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,放过他吧\N{\fs16}So leave him be.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.60,0:04:28.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,该走了\N{\fs16}It is time to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.97,0:04:30.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,拜托 再等一会儿\N{\fs16}Please, a little longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.74,0:04:46.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你终于向我展示了我真正在乎的东西\N{\fs16}You finally show me something I care about
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.82,0:04:48.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,却又将我带走\N{\fs16}and then you drag me away.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.46,0:04:52.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,海底的风景纵然美丽\N{\fs16}It is beautiful beneath the sea,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.21,0:04:54.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但若待得太久 你会被淹死\N{\fs16}but if you stay too long, you'll drown.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.58,0:04:58.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没被淹死 我回家了\N{\fs16}I wasn't drowning. I was home.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.81,0:05:14.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,威利斯\N{\fs16}Wylis.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.10,0:05:15.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,阿多\N{\fs16}Hodor.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.85,0:05:17.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我见到了小时候的你\N{\fs16}I saw you as a boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.69,0:05:20.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你能说话\N{\fs16}You could talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.61,0:05:23.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,后来发生了什么？\N{\fs16}What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.28,0:05:25.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,阿多\N{\fs16}Hodor.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.61,0:05:31.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,梅拉在哪儿？\N{\fs16}Where's Meera?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.37,0:05:35.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,阿多\N{\fs16}Hodor.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.45,0:06:03.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不该待在这儿\N{\fs16}You shouldn't be here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.15,0:06:05.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,洞外不安全\N{\fs16}It's not safe outside the cave.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.95,0:06:07.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没有哪里是安全的\N{\fs16}It's not safe anywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.07,0:06:13.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我看到阿多以前不是这样的\N{\fs16}I saw that Hodor wasn't always Hodor.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.46,0:06:15.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 阿多 - 他的真名叫威利斯\N{\fs16}- Hodor. -  His real name is Wylis.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.66,0:06:19.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他会说话、能打架……还有……\N{\fs16}And he could talk and fight and-- and then--
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.92,0:06:22.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,怎么了？\N{\fs16}What's wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.42,0:06:28.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,三眼乌鸦说大战将至\N{\fs16}The Three-Eyed Raven says there's a war coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.39,0:06:30.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而我们就在那里面打仗？\N{\fs16}And we're going to fight it in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.04,0:07:02.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,布兰登·史塔克需要你\N{\fs16}Brandon Stark needs you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.09,0:07:07.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,要我干什么？我坐在那里\N{\fs16}For what? I sit in there
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.30,0:07:09.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,看他坠入幻梦 然后什么都没有发生\N{\fs16}and I watch him have his visions and nothing ever happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.68,0:07:12.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他不会永远留在这里\N{\fs16}He isn't going to stay here forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.35,0:07:15.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,等到出去的那一天 他会需要你\N{\fs16}And out there he needs you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.55,0:07:44.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,时间到了 戴佛斯爵士\N{\fs16}Alliser:  It's time, Ser Davos.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.55,0:07:46.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,打开门 让里面的弟兄\N{\fs16}Open the door and the men inside
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.00,0:07:49.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,和平地出来\N{\fs16}can rejoin their brothers in peace.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.68,0:07:59.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们甚至会将狼放生到长城以北 让它回到自己的地方\N{\fs16}We'll even set the wolf free north of the Wall where it belongs.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.68,0:08:04.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,今晚没人会死\N{\fs16}Nobody needs to die tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.74,0:08:10.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不擅长打打杀杀\N{\fs16}I've never been much of a fighter.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.17,0:08:20.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但很抱歉这次不能让步\N{\fs16}Apologies for what you're about to see.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.88,0:08:29.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,上吧\N{\fs16}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.09,0:09:17.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,进攻！\N{\fs16}Attack!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.77,0:09:27.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,上啊 你们这群懦夫！\N{\fs16}Fight, you cowards!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.88,0:10:01.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,该死的叛徒\N{\fs16}You fucking traitor.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.05,0:10:04.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这里真正的叛徒\N{\fs16}The only traitors here are the ones
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.27,0:10:07.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是那些将匕首捅进总司令心脏的人\N{\fs16}who shoved their knives into their Lord Commander's heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.31,0:10:10.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,千百年来\N{\fs16}For thousands of years the Night's Watch
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.90,0:10:13.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,守夜人都在保卫黑城堡  抵御野人\N{\fs16}has held Castle Black against the wildlings.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.65,0:10:15.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,到你为止\N{\fs16}Until you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.49,0:10:28.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,将他们关进牢房 他们罪有应得\N{\fs16}Throw them into the cells where they belong.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.00,0:11:03.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,挨了很多刀\N{\fs16}Tormund:  Took a lot of knives.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.92,0:11:09.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我去吩咐手下收拾木头\N{\fs16}I'll have my men get the wood for a fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.79,0:11:12.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,准备火葬\N{\fs16}Bodies to burn.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.13,0:11:23.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,嘘 嘿\N{\fs16}Man:  Shh, hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.43,0:11:26.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,然后她来了 趾高气扬的瑟曦太后\N{\fs16}Right, so there she is, high and mighty Queen Cersei,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.06,0:11:29.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奶子和丰臀在微风中摇摆\N{\fs16}tits and ass jiggling in the breeze.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.31,0:11:32.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她突然看向我\N{\fs16}All of a sudden she looks my way.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.39,0:11:35.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,微笑着对我说：“怎么样？”\N{\fs16}Gives me a little smile like, "Well?"
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.40,0:11:37.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,接下来 你们知道的 我从不害羞\N{\fs16}So, all right, you know, I've never been shy
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.90,0:11:40.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我那话儿大得很，我把它掏了出来\N{\fs16}and I'm blessed down south, so I put it right out.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.70,0:11:43.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她从没见过这么好的家伙\N{\fs16}She's never seen anything like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.66,0:11:46.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是说 她习惯了她弟弟的 可我听说\N{\fs16}I mean, she's used to her brother and from what I hear,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.12,0:11:48.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,詹姆·兰尼斯特那话儿还不如这根指头\N{\fs16}Jaime Lannister's half an inch shy of an inch.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.41,0:11:50.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,喔！\N{\fs16}Ooh!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.24,0:11:54.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她看到我的 我对天发誓她舔了舔嘴唇\N{\fs16}She sees it and I swear to the gods she licks her lips.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.33,0:11:56.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那个 你们都了解我\N{\fs16}Well, you all know me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.00,0:11:59.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们知道这事儿我没骗人\N{\fs16}You know I wouldn't lie about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.08,0:13:18.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别挡我的路\N{\fs16}Get out of my way.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.50,0:13:20.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,国王有令 陛下\N{\fs16}King's orders, Your Grace.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.72,0:13:25.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,国王的命令是什么？\N{\fs16}What are the king's orders?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.39,0:13:28.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他希望您留在红堡 陛下\N{\fs16}He would like you to remain in the Red Keep, Your Grace,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.31,0:13:29.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,为了您的安全\N{\fs16}for your own protection.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.51,0:13:34.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想阻止我参加自己女儿的葬礼？\N{\fs16}You're barring me from attending my own daughter's funeral?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.27,0:13:38.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,请原谅我 陛下 但国王命令我不得让您通过\N{\fs16}Forgive me, Your Grace, by the king's command, I cannot let you pass.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.90,0:13:41.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我要跟我儿子谈一谈\N{\fs16}I would like to speak to my son.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.07,0:13:44.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他已经离开红堡了 陛下\N{\fs16}He has left the Red Keep, Your Grace.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.64,0:14:16.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她长大了\N{\fs16}She grew up.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.06,0:14:19.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,快长大了\N{\fs16}Jaime:  Almost.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.19,0:14:21.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,杀害崔斯丹王子的凶手找到了吗？\N{\fs16}Have we caught Prince Trystane's killers?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.20,0:14:26.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我觉得可能是母亲干的\N{\fs16}I expect it was Mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.40,0:14:28.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你母亲不会那样做的\N{\fs16}Your mother wouldn't do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.49,0:14:29.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不 她会的\N{\fs16}Yes, she would.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.32,0:14:34.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你在生她的气吗？\N{\fs16}Are you angry with her?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.08,0:14:37.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-当然没有  -那你为什么不让她来？\N{\fs16}- Of course not. - Then why didn't you let her come?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.08,0:14:40.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她完全有权来这儿\N{\fs16}She has every right to be here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.92,0:14:45.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我听说她不能出现在圣堂\N{\fs16}They told me she wouldn't be allowed in the sept.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.55,0:14:47.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果她试图——\N{\fs16}If she had tried--
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.42,0:14:49.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不会再有人把你母亲关起来了\N{\fs16}They're not putting your mother in a cell ever again.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.84,0:14:51.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只要我在就不会\N{\fs16}Not while I'm here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.40,0:14:56.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你为什么没去看过她？\N{\fs16}Why haven't you gone to see her?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.52,0:15:02.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她所承受的一切都是为了你\N{\fs16}Everything she endured, she did it for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.94,0:15:05.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你以为我不知道吗？\N{\fs16}Don't you think I know that?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.28,0:15:11.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对不起\N{\fs16}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.08,0:15:14.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我去不了\N{\fs16}But I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.00,0:15:16.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,为什么？\N{\fs16}Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.79,0:15:21.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,教团武装抓走她和玛格丽\N{\fs16}When the Faith Militant seized her and Margaery,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.46,0:15:23.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我做了什么？\N{\fs16}what did I do?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.88,0:15:28.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们让她像妓女一样游街\N{\fs16}When they paraded her through the streets like a whore,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.71,0:15:30.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我又做了什么？\N{\fs16}what did I do?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.63,0:15:33.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们都有无能为力的时候\N{\fs16}We all fail sometimes.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.10,0:15:37.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,国王本该是全境守护者\N{\fs16}The king is supposed to be the Protector of the Realm.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.56,0:15:41.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,可如果连自己的妻子和母亲都守护不了\N{\fs16}If I can't even protect my own wife or my own mother,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.14,0:15:42.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那我算什么？\N{\fs16}what good am I?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.94,0:15:45.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去看看你母亲 请求她原谅\N{\fs16}Go and see your mother and ask her to forgive you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.45,0:15:50.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,陛下\N{\fs16}Your Grace.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.74,0:15:52.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,队长大人\N{\fs16}Lord Commander.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.54,0:15:55.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我想见我妻子\N{\fs16}I want to see my wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.37,0:15:57.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,诸神在等待玛格丽王后\N{\fs16}The gods wait for Queen Margaery
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.83,0:16:01.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,忏悔罪行 请求宽恕\N{\fs16}to confess her crimes and seek their mercy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.33,0:16:04.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,国王也得等\N{\fs16}The king must wait as well.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.33,0:16:06.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去看你母亲 托曼\N{\fs16}Go and see your mother, Tommen.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.18,0:16:19.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你真是胆大包天\N{\fs16}You're a bold man.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.85,0:16:22.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,恰恰相反\N{\fs16}On the contrary.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.52,0:16:25.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我诚惶诚恐\N{\fs16}I fear a great deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.19,0:16:28.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,天父 圣母\N{\fs16}The Father, the Mother,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.49,0:16:30.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,战士\N{\fs16}the Warrior.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.59,0:16:43.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你知道我们为什么要用这些石头？\N{\fs16}Do you know why we use these stones?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.42,0:16:48.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,为的是提醒自己不要害怕死亡\N{\fs16}To remind us not to fear death.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.43,0:16:51.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们在现世闭上眼睛 在来世会重新睁开\N{\fs16}We close our eyes on this world and open them on the next.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.80,0:16:54.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你一定非常渴望来世\N{\fs16}You must long for the next life.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.05,0:16:57.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,说实话 我害怕来世\N{\fs16}In truth, I fear that, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.69,0:17:00.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你囚禁并侮辱了我的姐姐\N{\fs16}You imprisoned and humiliated my sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.72,0:17:03.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的姐姐寻求诸神的宽恕\N{\fs16}Your sister sought the gods' mercy
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.44,0:17:05.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,以赎清罪过\N{\fs16}and atoned for her sin.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.31,0:17:07.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那我的罪过呢？\N{\fs16}What about my sins?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.81,0:17:13.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我违背神圣的誓言 背后捅刀 杀死了我的国王\N{\fs16}I broke a sacred oath and stabbed my king in the back.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.20,0:17:17.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我杀了我的堂弟\N{\fs16}I killed my own cousin.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.74,0:17:19.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,诸神判定我弟弟有罪\N{\fs16}When the gods judged my brother guilty,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.74,0:17:22.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我却帮他逃脱了制裁\N{\fs16}I helped him escape their justice.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.63,0:17:26.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我要怎么赎罪\N{\fs16}What atonement do I deserve?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.72,0:17:30.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你要血染圣堂？\N{\fs16}You would spill blood in this holy place?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.09,0:17:33.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,噢，诸神才不会在意\N{\fs16}Oh, the gods won't mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.59,0:17:36.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们制造的鲜血比我们凡人多得多\N{\fs16}They've spilled more blood than the rest of us combined.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.01,0:17:40.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那就动手吧\N{\fs16}Go on, then.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.26,0:17:43.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我罪有应得 我们都一样\N{\fs16}I deserve it. We all do.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.98,0:17:46.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们都是软弱、虚妄的生灵\N{\fs16}We are weak, vain creatures.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.68,0:17:49.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只因圣母慈悲才得以存活\N{\fs16}We live only by the Mother's mercy.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.87,0:18:07.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,想救你 恐怕他们还得靠近些\N{\fs16}They should be closer if you mean for them to save you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.96,0:18:09.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不需要\N{\fs16}I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.96,0:18:12.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想杀我 他们阻止不了\N{\fs16}They'd never reach me before you struck.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.96,0:18:14.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我在众寡更悬殊的情形下战斗过\N{\fs16}I've fought against worse odds.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.71,0:18:17.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,的确 我们中的很多人会送命\N{\fs16}No doubt many of us would fall.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.80,0:18:20.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我们算得了什么，嗯？\N{\fs16}But who are we, hmm?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.94,0:18:23.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们无名无姓 居无定所\N{\fs16}We have no names, no family.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.69,0:18:27.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们每个人都很弱小\N{\fs16}Every one of us is poor and powerless.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.69,0:18:30.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但合在一起\N{\fs16}And yet together,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.19,0:18:32.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,足以推翻强权\N{\fs16}we can overthrow an empire.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.18,0:19:04.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,母亲\N{\fs16}Tommen:  Mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.44,0:19:19.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她的下葬礼服是红色还是金色？\N{\fs16}Did they put her in the red gown or the gold?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.69,0:19:22.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,金色\N{\fs16}Gold.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.50,0:19:24.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很好 她喜欢这个颜色\N{\fs16}Good. It was always her color.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.28,0:19:30.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很抱歉把你关在这里\N{\fs16}I'm sorry for keeping you here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.87,0:19:35.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不该这样，但我……\N{\fs16} I shouldn't have, but I was--
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.88,0:19:41.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不想再次失去你\N{\fs16}I didn't want to lose you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.22,0:19:43.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我理解\N{\fs16}I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.22,0:19:47.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,见到你很高兴\N{\fs16}I'm glad to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.22,0:19:52.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我知道……我应该早点来\N{\fs16}I know I should have come sooner.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.86,0:19:56.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我想来的 我错了\N{\fs16}I wanted to. I was wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.57,0:19:59.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没关系\N{\fs16}It's all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.24,0:20:04.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不，有关系\N{\fs16}No, it isn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.24,0:20:08.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我早该把他们全部处死\N{\fs16}I should have executed all of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.04,0:20:10.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在大麻雀他们侮辱你之前\N{\fs16}I should have pulled down the sept
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.91,0:20:15.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我就该把教会掀个底朝天\N{\fs16}onto the High Sparrow's head before I let them do that to you,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.08,0:20:17.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,为了我 你就会这么做\N{\fs16}as you would have for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.55,0:20:21.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您教我变得坚强…\N{\fs16}You raised me to be strong...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.26,0:20:24.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没能做到\N{\fs16}and I wasn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.23,0:20:28.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我想坚强起来\N{\fs16}But I want to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.93,0:20:32.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,帮帮我吧\N{\fs16}Help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.10,0:20:38.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,随时随地\N{\fs16}Always.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.02,0:21:09.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果没了那话儿 我会杯不离手\N{\fs16}If I lost my cock, I'd drink all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.81,0:21:16.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,无意冒犯\N{\fs16}Meaning no offense.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.28,0:21:19.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他笑话侏儒 我笑话太监\N{\fs16}He makes dwarf jokes, I make eunuch jokes.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.15,0:21:20.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没笑话侏儒\N{\fs16}I do not make dwarf jokes.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.53,0:21:22.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你在脑子里笑话了\N{\fs16}- You think them.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.73,0:21:27.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,行了 说说被烧掉的船\N{\fs16}So, the fleet. It's been burned.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.29,0:21:31.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们一直在清查下手的人，迄今为止毫无线索\N{\fs16}We are searching for the men who burned the ships, but nobody saw anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.16,0:21:33.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我相信 继续下去一定会有所收获\N{\fs16}Surely there's some good news lurking somewhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.71,0:21:36.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,阿斯塔波和渊凯已不再向我们求助\N{\fs16}Astapor and Yunkai have stopped asking us for aid.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.88,0:21:39.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也许是他们的小阴谋\N{\fs16}Perhaps they can tell us their secret.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.63,0:21:42.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奴隶主夺回了那两座城市\N{\fs16}The Masters have retaken both cities.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.17,0:21:46.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们收复了除弥林外的整个奴隶湾\N{\fs16}Outside of Meereen, the whole of Slaver's Bay has returned to the slavers.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.81,0:21:52.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们的龙呢？金字塔下还有两条龙啊\N{\fs16}What about the dragons? We have two of them here beneath the pyramid.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.01,0:21:54.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,它们不肯进食\N{\fs16}They are not eating.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.85,0:21:57.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,丹妮莉丝女王离开后 它们没碰过任何食物\N{\fs16}They haven't touched any food since Queen Daenerys left.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.69,0:22:00.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,丹妮莉丝是龙女王\N{\fs16}Daenerys is the dragon queen.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.52,0:22:03.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,显然 让龙饿着是不好的\N{\fs16}Can't very well let the dragons starve, that's obvious.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.44,0:22:06.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果龙不想吃 你如何强迫它吃？\N{\fs16}If a dragon does not want to eat, how do you force him to eat?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.86,0:22:09.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,龙不适合关起来\N{\fs16}Dragons do not do well in captivity.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.25,0:22:11.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-你怎么知道？ -我就是知道\N{\fs16}- How do you know this? - That's what I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.70,0:22:14.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不仅好酒，知道的事也不少\N{\fs16}I drink and I know things.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.70,0:22:19.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,伊耿用来征服维斯特洛的巨龙\N{\fs16}The dragons Aegon used to conquer Westeros
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.96,0:22:22.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,它们一飞冲天 扶摇万里\N{\fs16}ranged over hundreds of miles.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.54,0:22:24.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,可到了后来 丹妮莉丝的先辈们\N{\fs16}Then Daenerys's ancestors
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.43,0:22:27.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,把它们用铁链锁在坑里\N{\fs16}started chaining them up in pens.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.38,0:22:29.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,短短几代之后\N{\fs16}A few generations later,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.43,0:22:33.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,最后几条龙还没猫大\N{\fs16}the last dragons were no larger than cats.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.22,0:22:36.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,必须卸掉锁链 否则它们就废了\N{\fs16}They must be unchained or they'll waste away.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.73,0:22:39.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,弥桑黛\N{\fs16}Missandei,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.78,0:22:43.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你接近那些龙多少次了？\N{\fs16}how many times were you in the company of these dragons?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.40,0:22:47.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-很多次  -它们可曾伤害你？\N{\fs16}- Many times. - And did they ever harm you?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.20,0:22:49.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,从未有过\N{\fs16}Never.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.29,0:22:51.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,龙是智慧生物\N{\fs16}Dragons are intelligent.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.57,0:22:54.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,某些学士声称它们比人还聪明\N{\fs16}More intelligent than men according to some maesters.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.49,0:22:56.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,它们对朋友友好\N{\fs16}They have affection for their friends
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.91,0:22:58.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对敌人则是满腔怒火\N{\fs16}and fury for their enemies.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.41,0:23:02.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-我可是他们的朋友  -它们会明白这个？\N{\fs16}- I am their friend. - Do they know that?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.05,0:23:06.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,当然 它们该吃晚饭了\N{\fs16}They will. It's time they had their supper.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.09,0:24:39.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是你们妈妈的朋友\N{\fs16}I'm friends with your mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.24,0:24:48.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是来帮忙的\N{\fs16}I'm here to help.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.99,0:24:51.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不能把帮忙的人吃掉哟\N{\fs16}Don't eat the help.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.83,0:24:57.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我小时候\N{\fs16}When I was a child,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.33,0:25:00.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,叔叔问我命名日想要什么礼物\N{\fs16}an uncle asked what gift I wanted for my name day.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.03,0:25:03.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我求叔叔说想要一条龙\N{\fs16}I begged him for one of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.75,0:25:07.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我甚至告诉他：“不用太大只的也行。”\N{\fs16}"It wouldn't even have to be a big dragon," I told him.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.13,0:25:11.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,“像我这么小的就好。”\N{\fs16}"It could be little like me."
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.05,0:25:22.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所有人都乐坏了 好像这是他们听过的最滑稽的事\N{\fs16}Everyone laughed like it was the funniest thing they had ever heard.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.52,0:25:25.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,然后我父亲告诉我\N{\fs16}Then my father told me
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.81,0:25:29.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,最后的巨龙死在一个世纪之前\N{\fs16}the last dragon had died a century ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.86,0:25:32.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那晚 我哭着入睡\N{\fs16}I cried myself to sleep that night.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.99,0:25:43.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,可是……你看看现在\N{\fs16}But here you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.98,0:26:54.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,下回我再冒出这种念头\N{\fs16}Next time I have an idea like that,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.20,0:26:55.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,务必照我脸上来一拳\N{\fs16}punch me in the face.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.00,0:27:11.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是谁？\N{\fs16}What's your name?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.31,0:27:20.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是谁？\N{\fs16}What's your name?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.47,0:27:23.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-无名之辈  -我不信\N{\fs16}- No one. - I don't believe that.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.93,0:27:26.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你自己也不信\N{\fs16}- You don't believe that.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.71,0:28:00.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你到底是谁？\N{\fs16}Who are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.72,0:28:02.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,无名之辈\N{\fs16}No one.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.85,0:28:05.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果女孩说出她的名字\N{\fs16}If a girl says her name,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.35,0:28:08.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,某人会让她今晚在屋子里睡觉\N{\fs16}a man will let her sleep under a roof tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.44,0:28:10.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女孩没有名字\N{\fs16}A girl has no name.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.86,0:28:13.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果女孩说出她的名字\N{\fs16}If a girl says her name,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.19,0:28:15.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,某人今晚会给她吃的\N{\fs16}a man will feed her tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.36,0:28:17.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女孩没有名字\N{\fs16}A girl has no name.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.15,0:28:20.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果女孩说出她的名字\N{\fs16}If a girl says her name,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.95,0:28:23.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,某人会把眼睛还给她\N{\fs16}a man will give her eyes back.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.04,0:28:27.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女孩没有名字\N{\fs16}A girl has no name.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.88,0:28:37.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,来吧\N{\fs16}Come.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.34,0:28:47.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别管了\N{\fs16}Leave it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.34,0:28:50.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女孩不再是乞丐\N{\fs16} A girl is not a beggar anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.86,0:29:01.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们过来的路上发现了那些尸体\N{\fs16}We came upon the bodies on our way here.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.11,0:29:06.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,六具尸体？这就是你最好的猎人？\N{\fs16}Half a dozen men? Your best hunters?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.41,0:29:08.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很明显有人帮他们\N{\fs16}They obviously had help.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.17,0:29:11.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,珊莎小姐当然不可能凭一己之力干掉这些人\N{\fs16}I didn't think Lady Sansa killed them all by herself.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.34,0:29:14.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,多谢你的报告，卡史塔克大人\N{\fs16}Thank you for this report, Lord Karstark.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.76,0:29:17.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们知道她去了哪里\N{\fs16}We know where she's going.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.21,0:29:18.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她哥哥在黑城堡\N{\fs16}Her brother's at Castle Black.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.04,0:29:20.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奈德·史塔克仅剩的儿子？\N{\fs16}Ned Stark's last surviving son?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.84,0:29:22.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,琼恩·雪诺是个私生子，不是史塔克\N{\fs16}Jon Snow is a bastard, not a Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.01,0:29:26.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不也是，父亲\N{\fs16}So was I, Father.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.18,0:29:28.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只要有一个史塔克尚在人间\N{\fs16}Your hold on the North will never be secure
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.35,0:29:30.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您在北境的统治就永无宁日\N{\fs16}as long as a Stark can walk through that door.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.72,0:29:33.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,黑城堡的南面是不设防的\N{\fs16}Castle Black isn't defended on the southern side.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.44,0:29:37.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而且那里没剩下几个人，都是些农夫和窃贼而已\N{\fs16}And the few men left are barely men at all. Farm boys and thieves.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.39,0:29:41.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一支小分队就能攻陷黑城堡 杀掉琼恩·雪诺——\N{\fs16}With a small force, we could storm the castle, kill Jon Snow--
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.45,0:29:44.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谋杀守夜人军团总司令？\N{\fs16}Murder the Lord Commander of the Night's Watch?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.48,0:29:47.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是要逼反北境所有的家族\N{\fs16}You'd unite every house in the North against us.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.87,0:29:50.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们用不着所有的家族\N{\fs16}We don't need every house in the North.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.99,0:29:53.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,安柏家 曼德勒家 卡史塔克家\N{\fs16} The Umbers, the Manderlys, and the Karstarks
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.71,0:29:57.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们麾下的军队比北境其他家族加起来还多\N{\fs16}command more soldiers than all the other houses combined.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.66,0:30:00.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有他们的支持就没人能挑战我们\N{\fs16}With their support, none could challenge us.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.72,0:30:04.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,罗柏国王将我父亲斩首那一天 史塔克就失去了我家族的支持\N{\fs16}The Starks lost my house the day King Robb cut off my father's head.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.84,0:30:07.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,北境是时候更换新鲜血液了\N{\fs16}It's time for new blood in the North.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.85,0:30:19.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果你执意像疯狗般行事\N{\fs16}If you acquire a reputation as a mad dog,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.69,0:30:21.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别人就会把你视为疯狗\N{\fs16}you'll be treated as a mad dog.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.61,0:30:24.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,呼来喝去 最后杀了喂猪\N{\fs16}Taken out back and slaughtered for pig feed.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.86,0:30:27.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大人们\N{\fs16}Maester:  My lords.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.86,0:30:30.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,瓦妲夫人诞下一胎\N{\fs16} Lady Walda has given birth.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.33,0:30:32.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是个男婴\N{\fs16}A boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.37,0:30:34.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,脸蛋红扑扑的 很健康\N{\fs16} Red-cheeked and healthy.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.00,0:30:38.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,祝贺您 波顿大人\N{\fs16}My congratulations, Lord Bolton.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.43,0:30:49.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,祝贺您 父亲\N{\fs16}Congratulations, Father.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.80,0:30:53.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我很期待见到弟弟\N{\fs16}I look forward to meeting my new brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.97,0:31:00.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你永远是我的长子\N{\fs16}You'll always be my firstborn.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.90,0:31:04.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谢谢您能这样说\N{\fs16}Thank you for saying that.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.28,0:31:06.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这对我意义非凡\N{\fs16}It means a great deal to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.02,0:31:45.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,沃肯学士\N{\fs16}Maester Wolkan,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.41,0:31:49.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,向北境所有家族送出信鸦 传达卢斯·波顿的死讯\N{\fs16} send ravens to all the northern houses. Roose Bolton is dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.91,0:31:53.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他被敌人毒杀\N{\fs16}Poisoned by our enemies.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.45,0:32:01.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他怎样死的？\N{\fs16}How did he die?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.13,0:32:07.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,被敌人毒杀\N{\fs16}Poisoned by his enemies.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.93,0:32:10.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你在跟你的主人说话 敬语呢？\N{\fs16}You're talking to your lord. Use respect.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.30,0:32:14.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,请原谅 老爷\N{\fs16}Forgive me, my lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.30,0:32:19.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,请瓦妲夫人带着婴儿来见我\N{\fs16}Send for Lady Walda and the baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.86,0:32:22.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她还在休息 老爷\N{\fs16}She's resting, my lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.23,0:32:28.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,立刻去办 大人\N{\fs16}At once, my lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.26,0:32:55.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这就是他啊\N{\fs16}There he is.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.23,0:32:57.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他太棒了 是不是？\N{\fs16}Isn't he wonderful?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.85,0:33:02.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我能抱抱他吗？\N{\fs16}May I hold him?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.98,0:33:06.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,当—当然\N{\fs16}Of-- of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.11,0:33:18.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,小弟弟\N{\fs16}Little brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.20,0:33:21.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,波顿大人唤我们来的\N{\fs16}Lord Bolton sent for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.20,0:33:22.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你见着他了吗\N{\fs16}Have you seen him?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.43,0:33:34.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的 请跟我来 母亲\N{\fs16}Of course. Follow me, Mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.12,0:33:54.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,波顿大人在哪儿？\N{\fs16}Where is Lord Bolton?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.24,0:34:06.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,坐下！\N{\fs16}- Down!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.21,0:34:09.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没事的 没事 嘘\N{\fs16}- Walda:  It's all right. Come on, shh.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.22,0:34:12.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这儿很冷 拉姆斯 我得给他喂奶\N{\fs16} It's cold out here, Ramsay. I need to feed him.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.76,0:34:21.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,拉姆斯 你父亲在哪儿？\N{\fs16}Ramsay, where is your father?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.23,0:34:24.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,拉姆斯\N{\fs16}Ramsay.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.69,0:34:34.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,波顿大人在哪儿？\N{\fs16}Where is Lord Bolton?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.45,0:34:43.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我就是波顿大人\N{\fs16}I am Lord Bolton.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.38,0:34:55.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,拉姆斯\N{\fs16}Ramsay.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.63,0:34:57.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,拉姆斯，求求你\N{\fs16}Ramsay, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.43,0:35:00.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会离开临冬城的  我回河间地去\N{\fs16}I'll leave Winterfell. I'll go back to the Riverlands.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.47,0:35:07.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,求你了\N{\fs16}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.47,0:35:09.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,拉姆斯\N{\fs16}Ramsay.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.36,0:35:13.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他是你弟弟啊\N{\fs16}He's your brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.15,0:35:18.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我比较喜欢当独生子\N{\fs16}I prefer being an only child.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.97,0:35:41.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我看见她跟一个男的同行\N{\fs16}Brienne:  I saw her with a man.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.98,0:35:43.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那人应该不会伤害她\N{\fs16}I don't think he hurt her.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.89,0:35:47.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他俩彼此都不想分开\N{\fs16}She didn't want to leave him, he didn't want to leave her.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:49.15,0:35:50.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不知道她去哪儿了？\N{\fs16}You don't know which way she went?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.07,0:35:53.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我花了三天时间找她\N{\fs16}I spent three days looking for her.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.44,0:35:54.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,却一无所获\N{\fs16}She disappeared.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.27,0:35:58.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她看上去怎么样？\N{\fs16}How'd she look?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.86,0:36:01.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,挺好的\N{\fs16}She looked good.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.11,0:36:04.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只是穿着不像个小姐的样子\N{\fs16}She wasn't exactly dressed like a lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.50,0:36:07.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是了 她一直都是\N{\fs16}No, she wouldn't be.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.29,0:36:11.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,临冬城里发生了什么？\N{\fs16}What happened at Winterfell?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.88,0:36:26.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我早就该跟你走\N{\fs16}I should have gone with you while I had the chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.55,0:36:29.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,珊莎小姐 那是个艰难的选择\N{\fs16}It was a difficult choice, my lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.89,0:36:37.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我们不能回避\N{\fs16}We've all had to make difficult choices.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.83,0:36:59.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们不该生火的\N{\fs16}We shouldn't be lighting fires.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.14,0:37:00.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这不安全\N{\fs16}It's not safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.30,0:37:01.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他会继续追杀我们\N{\fs16}He won't stop hunting us.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.75,0:37:03.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们只需赶到黑城堡\N{\fs16}We just have to make it to Castle Black.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.51,0:37:05.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只要找到琼恩 拉姆斯就抓不到我们了\N{\fs16}Once we're with Jon, Ramsay won't be able to touch us.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.09,0:37:08.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我只要踏进黑城堡 琼恩就会杀了我\N{\fs16}Jon will have me killed the moment I step through the gate.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.01,0:37:10.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不会让他那么做\N{\fs16}I won't let him.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.76,0:37:12.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会告诉他布兰和瑞肯的真相\N{\fs16}I'll tell him the truth about Bran and Rickon.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.57,0:37:17.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有我杀掉磨坊男孩来代替他们的真相\N{\fs16}And the truth about the farm boys I killed in their place.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.90,0:37:21.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有我把罗德利克爵士砍头的真相\N{\fs16}And the truth about Ser Rodrik, who I beheaded.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.66,0:37:26.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有我背叛罗柏的真相\N{\fs16}And the truth about Robb, who I betrayed.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.20,0:37:31.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,当你披上黑衣，一切罪行都会被宽恕\N{\fs16}When you take the black, all your crimes are forgiven.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.12,0:37:32.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不愿被宽恕\N{\fs16}I don't want to be forgiven.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.46,0:37:37.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我对您的家族所做的一切\N{\fs16}I can never make amends to your family
Dialogue: 0,0:37:37.59,0:37:39.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,永远无法弥补\N{\fs16}for the things I've done.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.01,0:37:43.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们本来可以保护你安全无恙\N{\fs16}They'll keep you safer than I ever could.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.13,0:37:50.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不和我们一起走？\N{\fs16}You're not coming with us?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:52.94,0:37:56.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我真想把你一路带到长城\N{\fs16}I would have taken you all the way to the Wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.56,0:37:59.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,为此我宁愿献出生命\N{\fs16}I would have died to get you there.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.16,0:38:18.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我可以带走一匹马吗？\N{\fs16}May I take one of the horses?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.00,0:38:24.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你要去哪里？\N{\fs16}Where will you go?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.01,0:38:28.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,回家\N{\fs16}Home.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.57,0:38:41.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,葛洛佛家族夺回了深林堡\N{\fs16}Yara:  The Glovers have retaken Deepwood Motte.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.82,0:38:44.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那些守卫它的铁种呢？\N{\fs16}And the ironborn who held it?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.16,0:38:47.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们战至最后一人\N{\fs16}They died fighting to a man.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.95,0:38:51.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,逝者不死\N{\fs16}What is dead may never die.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.25,0:38:53.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,逝者不死\N{\fs16}What is dead may never die.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.53,0:38:55.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但他们死了\N{\fs16}But they did
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.67,0:38:58.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,入侵行动失败了\N{\fs16}and our invasion died with them.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.42,0:39:01.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,深林堡是我们在大陆的最后一个据点\N{\fs16}Deepwood Motte was our last stronghold on the mainland.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.67,0:39:03.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们会攻取更多\N{\fs16}Then we will take more.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.38,0:39:06.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,为什么？为了更多的松果和岩石？\N{\fs16}Why? For more pinecones and rocks?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.80,0:39:11.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为这是我的命令\N{\fs16}Because I order it.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:11.35,0:39:13.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们在海上不可战胜\N{\fs16}We can defeat anyone at sea,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.44,0:39:15.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我们守不住城堡和土地\N{\fs16}but we'll never hold lands and castles
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.72,0:39:17.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,打不过大陆上的军队\N{\fs16}against mainland armies.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.31,0:39:19.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果我的船长们违抗命令 擅离职守\N{\fs16}Not if our captains defy my orders,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.69,0:39:24.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,把部下消耗在愚蠢的任务中 我们当然会输\N{\fs16}abandon their posts, and sacrifice our men on foolish missions.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:24.23,0:39:26.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不会为试图营救席恩而道歉\N{\fs16}I won't apologize for trying to rescue Theon.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:26.28,0:39:27.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那么他在哪里?\N{\fs16}Then where is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.48,0:39:29.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的王国又在哪里？\N{\fs16}Where is your kingdom?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:30.07,0:39:34.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们能拿下那些城堡 是因为北方佬去了南方打仗\N{\fs16}We took those castles because the northerners marched off to war.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.16,0:39:36.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,现在仗打完了\N{\fs16}That war is over.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.33,0:39:38.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,上一次我们做得过火的时候\N{\fs16}The last time we provoked them too far,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.21,0:39:40.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我在那窗前眼睁睁看着他们突破了我们的城墙\N{\fs16}I watched from that window as they breached our walls
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.96,0:39:42.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,摧毁了我们的塔楼\N{\fs16} and knocked down our towers.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.05,0:39:44.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那天我失去了两个哥哥\N{\fs16} I lost two brothers that day.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.92,0:39:47.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我失去了三个儿子\N{\fs16}And I lost three sons.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.89,0:39:50.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们说，这是五王之战\N{\fs16}The War of the Five Kings, they call it.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.92,0:39:52.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好吧，其他四个都死了\N{\fs16}Well, the other four are dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.93,0:39:56.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,等你统治铁群岛时 想怎么和平都随你\N{\fs16}When you rule the Iron Islands, you can wage all the peace you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.26,0:39:58.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但现在，闭上嘴，服从我\N{\fs16}But for now, shut your mouth and obey
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.23,0:40:00.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不然我找个听话的来当继承人\N{\fs16}or I will make another heir who will.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.69,0:40:41.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让开\N{\fs16}Let me pass.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.98,0:40:47.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,蠢货 给你的国王让路\N{\fs16}You fool, move aside for your king.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:48.36,0:40:50.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我一直都是这样做的 不是吗 哥哥？\N{\fs16}Haven't I always, brother?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.13,0:41:04.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我以为你早在异乡的海底烂成了骨头\N{\fs16}I thought you'd be rotting under some foreign sea by now.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.58,0:41:07.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,逝者不死\N{\fs16}What is dead may never die.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.17,0:41:13.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我走以后，习俗变了？\N{\fs16}Has the custom changed since I've been gone?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:13.22,0:41:15.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不应该重复这句话吗？\N{\fs16}Aren't you supposed to repeat the words?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:15.56,0:41:18.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不用我掺和也能嘲弄我们的神\N{\fs16}You can mock our god without my help.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.73,0:41:21.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没有嘲弄淹神\N{\fs16}I don't mock the Drowned God.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:21.60,0:41:24.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我就是淹神\N{\fs16}I am the Drowned God.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.57,0:41:26.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,从旧镇到魁尔斯\N{\fs16}From Oldtown to Qarth,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.52,0:41:30.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,无论是谁，看见我的船帆就会祈祷\N{\fs16}when men see my sails, they pray.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.00,0:41:42.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你老了 哥哥\N{\fs16}You're old, brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.54,0:41:44.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的时代过去了\N{\fs16} You've had your time.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.45,0:41:46.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是时候退位让贤了\N{\fs16}Now let another rule.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.87,0:41:50.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我听说你在玉海的风暴里\N{\fs16}I heard you lost your mind
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.13,0:41:53.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,丧失了理智\N{\fs16}during a storm on the Jade Sea.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.30,0:41:58.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们把你绑在桅杆上以防你跳海\N{\fs16}They tied you to the mast to keep you from jumping overboard.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:58.77,0:42:00.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没错\N{\fs16}They did.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:00.39,0:42:04.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,风暴过去后 你割了他们的舌头\N{\fs16}And when the storm passed, you cut out their tongues.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.06,0:42:06.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我需要安静\N{\fs16}I needed silence.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.28,0:42:10.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,什么样的铁种\N{\fs16}What kind of an ironborn
Dialogue: 0,0:42:10.61,0:42:14.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,会在风暴中失去理智？\N{\fs16}loses his senses during a storm?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:14.62,0:42:18.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我就是风暴 哥哥\N{\fs16}I am the storm, brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.57,0:42:20.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,世上唯一的风暴\N{\fs16}The first storm and the last.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:22.38,0:42:24.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而你挡我的路了\N{\fs16}And you're in my way.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:02.45,0:43:06.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,主 请将您的仆人巴隆收归波涛之下\N{\fs16}Lord, take your servant Balon back beneath the waves.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:07.00,0:43:10.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,以他的血肉喂养您王国的子民\N{\fs16}Feed the creatures of your kingdom on his flesh.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:10.46,0:43:12.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,将他的骨骸归于深邃的大海\N{\fs16}Pull his bones down to your depths
Dialogue: 0,0:43:12.59,0:43:15.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,与他的祖先和孩子一同长眠\N{\fs16}to rest beside his ancestors and his children.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:15.46,0:43:17.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,逝者不死\N{\fs16}All: What is dead may never die.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:26.94,0:43:29.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会找出凶手\N{\fs16}I'm going to find out who did this.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:29.56,0:43:32.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会把他们活着拿去喂鲨鱼\N{\fs16}I'm going to feed them to the sharks while they live.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:34.31,0:43:37.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我以海盐王座发誓\N{\fs16}I swear it by the Salt Throne.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:37.20,0:43:40.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不能以海盐王座发誓\N{\fs16}The Salt Throne is not yours to swear upon,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:40.15,0:43:42.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,除非选王会选择了你\N{\fs16}not unless the kingsmoot chooses you.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:42.32,0:43:44.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我父亲想要我来统治\N{\fs16}My father would have wanted me to rule.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:44.29,0:43:47.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你父亲无权这样做 律法讲得清清楚楚\N{\fs16}Your father does not get to choose. The law is clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:49.83,0:43:52.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也许你会胜出\N{\fs16}Perhaps you'll win.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:52.08,0:43:55.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也许你会成为史上首位统治铁民的女人\N{\fs16}Perhaps you'll be the first woman in history to rule the ironborn.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:56.59,0:43:58.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也许不会\N{\fs16}And perhaps not.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:15.19,0:44:16.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,进来\N{\fs16}Come in.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:23.03,0:44:26.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,抱歉 夫人 我不是有意打扰\N{\fs16}I'm sorry, my lady. Didn't mean to interrupt.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:26.83,0:44:28.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你没有打扰我\N{\fs16}You interrupt nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:40.63,0:44:43.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我想您知道我为何而来\N{\fs16}I assume you know why I'm here.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:45.05,0:44:46.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你告诉我我才能知道\N{\fs16}I will after you tell me.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:46.69,0:44:48.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是关于总司令\N{\fs16}It's about the Lord Commander.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:48.97,0:44:51.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,前总司令\N{\fs16}The former Lord Commander.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:52.78,0:44:54.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,必须是这样吗？\N{\fs16}Does he have to be?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:57.73,0:44:59.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想要什么？\N{\fs16}What are you asking?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:03.90,0:45:07.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您是否知道有什么魔法……\N{\fs16}Do you know of any magic...
Dialogue: 0,0:45:09.41,0:45:11.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,能帮到他？\N{\fs16}that could help him?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:11.13,0:45:12.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,带他回来？\N{\fs16}Bring him back?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:12.58,0:45:15.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果你想帮助他 就让他安息吧\N{\fs16}If you want to help him, leave him be.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:15.30,0:45:17.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我说的事，能做到吗?\N{\fs16}Can it be done?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:17.58,0:45:20.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,的确存在这样的能力\N{\fs16}There are some with this power.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:20.25,0:45:22.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-怎么做？ -我不知道\N{\fs16}-  How?  - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:22.92,0:45:23.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您见过吗？\N{\fs16}Have you seen it done?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:27.23,0:45:29.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我见过一个死而复生的人\N{\fs16}I met a man who came back from the dead,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:29.76,0:45:32.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但施法的祭司……\N{\fs16}but the priest who did it--
Dialogue: 0,0:45:32.98,0:45:34.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这种事本不该进行\N{\fs16}it shouldn't have been possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:34.98,0:45:38.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但它确实可行 现在也应该可以\N{\fs16}But it was. It could be now.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:38.27,0:45:40.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不行\N{\fs16}Not for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:44.74,0:45:46.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您不行？\N{\fs16}Not for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:50.45,0:45:54.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我见过您喝下致命的毒药\N{\fs16}I saw you drink poison that should have killed you.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:54.20,0:45:57.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我见过您生下影子的恶魔\N{\fs16}I saw you give birth to a demon made of shadows.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:57.42,0:46:00.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我曾笃信的一切\N{\fs16}Everything I believed,
Dialogue: 0,0:46:00.13,0:46:03.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我曾在圣火中目睹的伟大胜利\N{\fs16}the great victory I saw in the flames,
Dialogue: 0,0:46:03.63,0:46:05.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,全是谎言\N{\fs16}all of it was a lie.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:09.60,0:46:11.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你一直都是对的\N{\fs16}You were right all along.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:11.64,0:46:14.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,光之王从未给予我启示\N{\fs16}The Lord never spoke to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:14.47,0:46:16.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那就让他见鬼去\N{\fs16}Fuck him, then.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:16.53,0:46:18.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让他们都见鬼去\N{\fs16}Fuck all of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:20.20,0:46:23.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很显然我不是个虔诚的人\N{\fs16}I'm not a devout man, obviously.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:23.98,0:46:27.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,七神 淹神 树神 对我来说都是一样的\N{\fs16}Seven gods, drowned gods, tree gods, it's all the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:30.41,0:46:33.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不是在向光之王求助\N{\fs16}I'm not asking the Lord of Light for help.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:33.29,0:46:37.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是在向那个曾向我展现奇迹的女人求助\N{\fs16}I'm asking the woman who showed me that miracles exist.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:39.75,0:46:41.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我从未有过这种天赋\N{\fs16}I never had this gift.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:42.05,0:46:44.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您试过吗？\N{\fs16}Have you ever tried?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:27.03,0:50:29.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,求你了\N{\fs16}Please.

