[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.2.2012.322
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: Game of Thrones S06E10
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 衣柜
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 衣柜
Script Updated By: 衣柜
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 720
PlayResY: 404
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Titles,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles_L,Microsoft YaHei,24,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Character_L,Microsoft YaHei,28,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,4,10,10,10,1
Style: Character_B,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Author,Microsoft YaHei,16,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,1,10,10,10,1
Style: QR code - BG,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000019FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,400,400,0,0,1,0,0,5,0,0,0,1
Style: QR code - code,Arial,20,&H00000000,&H000019FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,200,200,0,0,1,0,0,5,0,0,0,1
Style: Titles - 1,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,5,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles - 2,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles - 3 -,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H0001031B,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000429,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Subtitle,Microsoft YaHei,26,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:11.54,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(1000,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx89\fscy89\p1\move(298,257,298,257,120,1400)}m -11 -35 l -11 39 l 63 39 l 63 -35{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:11.54,Titles - 2,,0,0,0,,{\fad(1000,500)\move(340,280,340,280,300,1400)\p1\fscx40\fscy40}m -86 -116 b -89 -117 -89 -117 -95 -119 l -97 -115 l -85 -105 l -116 -102 b -116 -100 -116 -98 -116 -97 l -108 -91 l -96 -91 l -116 -63 l -105 -69 l -96 -47 l -74 -63 l -77 -69 l -91 -63 l -91 -77 l -88 -80 l -66 -49 l -46 -63 l -58 -66 l -66 -74 l -49 -80 l -60 -91 l -74 -83 l -80 -91 l -77 -94 l -46 -94 l -52 -108 l -71 -105 b -69 -107 -67 -110 -66 -113 m -31 -119.875 l -33 -119 b -34 -113 -36 -107 -38 -102 l -46 -97 b -42 -93 -38 -89 -35 -85 l -44 -63 b -41 -64 -38 -65 -35 -66 l -35 -52 l -33 -47 l -27 -55 l -27 -69 l -21 -63 l -21 -69 l -19 -72 l -27 -88 l -21 -94 l -21 -99 l -27 -102 l -27 -102 l -30 -116 m -21 -113 l -21 -105 l -21 -99 l -21 -94 l -19 -85 l -19 -66 l -21 -49 l -19 -47 l -7 -52 l 26 -52 l 18 -66 l -7 -63 l -5 -69 l 6 -69 l 18 -69 l 20 -99 l -7 -94 l -7 -83 l 6 -85 l 6 -80 l -7 -77 l -7 -94 l -10 -99 l 23 -102 l 18 -116 l -10 -110 l -19 -116 m -105 -38 l -116 -41 l -110 -13 l -102 -19 l -102 -30 l -63 -33 l -55 -19 l -46 -41 l -49 -44 m -88 -33 l -91 -24 l -99 -24 l -105 -16 l -102 -13 l -85 -16 l -85 -10 l -94 -8 l -85 -16 l -102 -13 l -108 1 l -88 1 l -88 4 l -116 6 l -116 9 l -110 15 l -88 15 l -85 26 l -77 23 l -74 15 l -52 15 l -49 15 l -52 4 l -74 6 l -71 1 l -55 -2 l -60 -13 l -74 -10 l -74 -13 l -55 -16 l -63 -24 l -74 -24 l -80 -33 m -46 -41 l -38 -2 l -41 23 l -38 26 l 1 20 l 15 26 l 18 23 l 18 -8 l 20 -41 l 20 -44 l -24 -38 l -35 -41 l -35 -30 l -13 -30 l -19 -21 l -33 -19 l -33 -13 l -21 -13 l -33 6 l -33 15 l -13 -5 l -13 1 l -21 6 l -13 12 l -2 9 l -2 -8 l 9 -10 l 12 -19 l 1 -21 l -2 -27 l 9 -33 l 6 -16 l 6 -10 l 9 12 l -2 9 l -30 12 l -30 12 l -27 -2 l -27 -2 l -30 -16 l -27 -21 l -35 -41 m -126 -127 l -130 -130 l -129 38 l 34 37 l 35 -135 l -130 -131 l -127 -127 l 30 -129 l 31 32 l -124 34
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:11.54,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(386,224.2)\fad(1000,500)\b0\fs18\bord1} 最专业冰火字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:11.54,Titles - 1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(384,165.2)\fad(1000,500)}\N{\fs32\c&HFFFFFF&\b1}诚意奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:11.54,Titles - 1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(385,197.2)\fad(1000,500)\b0}专注GOT剧集{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.24,0:00:22.04,Author,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(113,330)}翻译{\fs24}{\b1} 埃尔夫歪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.06,0:00:24.79,Author,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(546,93)}翻译{\fs24\b1} 牛德君
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.64,0:00:26.89,Author,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(105,103)}翻译{\fs24\b1} Noxumos
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.49,0:00:18.59,Author,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(544,97)}翻译{\fs24\b1} 依依Eva
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.79,0:00:31.29,Author,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(108,96)}翻译{\fs24\b1} 兮迩CeCe
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.59,0:00:33.59,Author,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(468,94)}校对{\fs24\b1} 北落师门
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.19,0:00:42.59,Author,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(522,92)}校对{\fs24\b1} 屈畅 赵琳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.09,0:00:48.29,Author,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(438,296)}后期{\fs24\b1} SerGawen@huiji.wiki
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.55,0:00:53.94,Author,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(311,65)}监制{\fs24\b1} 临冬城的狮子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.71,0:00:50.91,Author,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(419,135)}监制{\fs24\b1} 北落师门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.62,0:01:02.64,Author,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(472,103)} 推广 {\fs24\b1}baozhenyuawabi
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.71,0:01:12.33,Author,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(130,324)}策划{\fs24\b1} 衣柜军团
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.97,0:01:21.72,Author,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(110,102)}特别顾问{\fs24}{\b1} 屈畅(ccxx)@史诗图书
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:23.70,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\t(\fscx150\fscy150,150)\p1\move(277,278,289,305,1,4381)}m -15 -18 l -15 -17 l -14 -16 l -13 -16 l -11 -15 l -6 -16 b -8 -15 -8 -15 -11 -13 l -14 -9 l -12 -9 l -10 -8 l -5 -9 b -4 -8 -2 -6 6 -7 l 7 -7 l 3 -8 l 1 -10 b 2 -14 5 -17 3 -19 l 2 -21 l 5 -21 l 3 -22 l 0 -23 l 0 -24 l 4 -26 l 8 -23 l 16 -21 b 20 -23 25 -24 28 -36 l 27 -35 b 26 -35 26 -35 22 -37 b 25 -34 25 -32 24 -32 l 17 -34 l 23 -30 b 22 -29 20 -27 19 -29 l 14 -33 b 15 -31 17 -29 16 -26 b 13 -25 11 -24 7 -27 l 11 -31 l 10 -36 b 10 -32 11 -32 8 -30 b 7 -30 5 -29 4 -29 b 3 -30 2 -31 0 -34 l 3 -28 l -1 -27 l -5 -30 l -7 -34 l -6 -30 l -3 -27 l -8 -28 l -15 -32 l -10 -27 l -6 -25 l -4 -25 l -7 -23 l -10 -21 l -3 -21 l -5 -20 l -7 -21 l -7 -22 l -8 -22 l -13 -19{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:23.70,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\pos(301.714,255.889)\fad(300,500)\frx360\t(20,200,\frx0)\fs28\b1}君临{\fs12\b0} King's Landing
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.35,0:00:27.77,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\move(420,300,420,280)\fs25\p1}m -17 -23 l -10 -8 l -19 -15 l -12 -1 l -24 -9 l -14 6 l -25 1 l -16 9 l -13 17 l -15 24 l 18 24 l 13 19 l 15 12 l 22 4 l 13 10 l 25 -3 l 20 0 l 14 3 l 17 -3 l 22 -11 l 13 -4 l 18 -21 l 13 -15 l 10 -13 l 11 -26 l 7 -16 l 7 -28 l 3 -16 l 0 -32 l -2 -15 l -6 -22 l -8 -28 l -8 -11{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.35,0:00:27.77,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(380,230,380,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}红堡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.35,0:00:27.77,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(425,250,425,235)\fad(300,500)\fs12\b0} Red Keep
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.63,0:01:36.63,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(338,265)\fad(1250,1000)\frx50\t(1200,2500,\frx0)\fs28} {\b1}多恩\N{\fs12\b0}Dorne
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.14,0:00:37.15,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fs28\b1\pos(278,256)}孪河城{\fs12\b0}The Twins
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.54,0:00:47.05,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(335,176)\fad(1000,1000)\frx25\fs28\b1\frz-22\t(0,1800,\frz-0)}临冬城\N{\fs12\b0}\NWinterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.04,0:01:08.74,Titles,,0,30,200,,{\fad(100,50)\frx75\t(0,3500,\frx-0)\fs28} {\b1}绝境长城{\fs12\b0} the Wall
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.47,0:01:24.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(355,250,370,250)\fs28\b1}弥林
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.47,0:01:24.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(365,260,355,260)\fad(100,1000)\fs12\b0}Meereen
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.36,0:01:31.36,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(337,158)\fs14} 联合出品
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.36,0:01:31.36,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(360,195)\fs24} 史诗图书 | 冰火中文维基 | 黑城堡奇幻微刊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.36,0:01:31.36,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(360,214)\fs15} Epic Books         ASOIAF.huiji.wiki        微信号：Heichengbao
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.04,0:01:14.38,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(496.323,318.666)} {\fs24\b1} 史诗图书 {\fs18\b0} 正统奇幻的圣殿
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.34,0:01:00.32,Titles,,0,0,100,,{\fs25\fad(100,1000)} {\b0} 最专业的华语冰火资料站：        冰与火之歌{\fs20}中文维基\N\N{\c&HFFFFFF&}http://asoiaf.huiji.wiki
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.54,0:01:00.32,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,1000)\pos(410,285)\fs25\c&HC1DFED&} {\b1\p1\fscx60\fscy60}m 31 -6 l -21 40 l 34 22 m 29 -8 l -3 -12 l -24 40{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.14,0:01:40.00,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(460,310)\fad(500,500)\fs14} {\c&HC1DFED&}根据长篇小说
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.14,0:01:40.00,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(552,334)\fad(500,500)} {\fs24}《{\b1}冰与火之歌{\b0}》{\fs14} 改编
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.14,0:01:40.00,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(587,357)\fad(500,500)} {\fs12} 原著 {\fs20} 乔治·R·R·马丁
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.36,0:01:49.67,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(350,294)\fad(300,500)\fs56.267\fn宋体\b1}权力的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.36,0:01:49.67,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(349,322)\fad(300,500)\c&HFFFFFF&\b1\fs22}衣柜字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.74,0:01:55.30,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(428,118.44)\fad(500,500)\p1}m -18.625 0 l -18.625 0 l 281.25 0 l 281.25 1.125 l -18.625 1.125{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.74,0:01:55.30,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(231.125,202.841)\p1\fscx35\fscy35}m -86 -116 b -89 -117 -89 -117 -95 -119 l -97 -115 l -85 -105 l -116 -102 b -116 -100 -116 -98 -116 -97 l -108 -91 l -96 -91 l -116 -63 l -105 -69 l -96 -47 l -74 -63 l -77 -69 l -91 -63 l -91 -77 l -88 -80 l -66 -49 l -46 -63 l -58 -66 l -66 -74 l -49 -80 l -60 -91 l -74 -83 l -80 -91 l -77 -94 l -46 -94 l -52 -108 l -71 -105 b -69 -107 -67 -110 -66 -113 m -31 -119.875 l -33 -119 b -34 -113 -36 -107 -38 -102 l -46 -97 b -42 -93 -38 -89 -35 -85 l -44 -63 b -41 -64 -38 -65 -35 -66 l -35 -52 l -33 -47 l -27 -55 l -27 -69 l -21 -63 l -21 -69 l -19 -72 l -27 -88 l -21 -94 l -21 -99 l -27 -102 l -27 -102 l -30 -116 m -21 -113 l -21 -105 l -21 -99 l -21 -94 l -19 -85 l -19 -66 l -21 -49 l -19 -47 l -7 -52 l 26 -52 l 18 -66 l -7 -63 l -5 -69 l 6 -69 l 18 -69 l 20 -99 l -7 -94 l -7 -83 l 6 -85 l 6 -80 l -7 -77 l -7 -94 l -10 -99 l 23 -102 l 18 -116 l -10 -110 l -19 -116 m -105 -38 l -116 -41 l -110 -13 l -102 -19 l -102 -30 l -63 -33 l -55 -19 l -46 -41 l -49 -44 m -88 -33 l -91 -24 l -99 -24 l -105 -16 l -102 -13 l -85 -16 l -85 -10 l -94 -8 l -85 -16 l -102 -13 l -108 1 l -88 1 l -88 4 l -116 6 l -116 9 l -110 15 l -88 15 l -85 26 l -77 23 l -74 15 l -52 15 l -49 15 l -52 4 l -74 6 l -71 1 l -55 -2 l -60 -13 l -74 -10 l -74 -13 l -55 -16 l -63 -24 l -74 -24 l -80 -33 m -46 -41 l -38 -2 l -41 23 l -38 26 l 1 20 l 15 26 l 18 23 l 18 -8 l 20 -41 l 20 -44 l -24 -38 l -35 -41 l -35 -30 l -13 -30 l -19 -21 l -33 -19 l -33 -13 l -21 -13 l -33 6 l -33 15 l -13 -5 l -13 1 l -21 6 l -13 12 l -2 9 l -2 -8 l 9 -10 l 12 -19 l 1 -21 l -2 -27 l 9 -33 l 6 -16 l 6 -10 l 9 12 l -2 9 l -30 12 l -30 12 l -27 -2 l -27 -2 l -30 -16 l -27 -21 l -35 -41 m -126 -127 l -130 -130 l -129 38 l 34 37 l 35 -135 l -130 -131 l -127 -127 l 30 -129 l 31 32 l -124 34{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.74,0:01:55.30,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(293,112.813)\fad(500,500)\b1}协力制作
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.74,0:01:55.30,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(293,157.827)\fad(500,500)}史诗图书\N{\fs13.504}Epic Books
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.74,0:01:55.30,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(405.5,157.827)\fad(500,500)}ASOIAF.huiji.wiki\N{\fs13.504}冰火中文维基
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.74,0:01:55.30,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(518,157.827)\fad(500,500)}黑城堡\N{\fs13.504}EPICASTLE
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.64,0:01:55.24,Titles_L,,260,0,163,,{\pos(310,300)\fad(500,500)\fs16\b0}第十集
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.64,0:01:55.24,Titles_L,,300,0,132,,{\pos(310,340)\fad(500,500)}凛冬的寒风\N{\fs16\b0}The Winds of Winter
Dialogue: 0,1:06:40.76,1:07:54.80,Titles,,0,0,20,,{\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(360,393)}衣柜字幕组出品{\b0}    维基新站网址：{\c&H00FF40}HTTP://AsoIaF.HuiJi.WiKi
Dialogue: 0,1:06:40.76,1:07:54.80,Titles,,0,0,40,,{\be1\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(360,372)}本集关键字：{\c&H5650F3\b0}学城  佛雷派  鼠厨师
Dialogue: 0,1:06:40.76,1:07:17.13,Titles,,0,0,40,,{\be1\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(360,40)}本季翻译：{\b0}艾莉娅的缝衣针 SaintHS 依依Eva 喵羽Ambrosia 兮迩CeCe 牛德君 埃尔夫歪 JOooker 蓝山脚下的林顿 Noxumos Reasno
Dialogue: 0,1:06:40.76,1:07:17.13,Titles,,0,0,40,,{\be1\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(360,79)}翻译：{\b0}凯冯·兰尼斯特（AKA.拉拉兄控凯冯，1990-2016）\N{\b1}校对：{\b0}屈畅ccxx 路人运气哥 赵琳 北落师门 守誓剑 pksunking 龙的命根子
Dialogue: 0,1:07:18.86,1:07:54.80,Titles,,0,0,40,,{\be1\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(360,39)}后期：{\b0}加文·维斯特林\N监制：临冬城的狮子 北落师门     推广：baozhenyuawabi
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.35,0:23:05.39,Character_L,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(62,276)}孪河城\N{\b0\fs17}河间地
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.00,0:28:16.21,Character_L,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(62,276)}参天塔\N{\b0\fs17}旧镇，学城
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.50,0:31:58.14,Character_L,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(62,276)}临冬城\N{\b0\fs17}北境
Dialogue: 0,1:02:10.03,1:02:15.40,Character_L,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(44,243)}君临\N{\b0\fs17}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.04,0:02:10.04,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(418,260)}瑟曦·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}太后
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.35,0:02:15.39,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(629,259)}托曼·拜拉席恩\N{\b0\fs12}国王
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.66,0:02:27.70,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(248,226)}"大麻雀"\N{\b0\fs12}总主教
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.88,0:02:45.93,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(659,283)}玛格丽·提利尔\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.09,0:03:28.13,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(100,251)}洛拉斯·提利尔\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.11,0:03:48.15,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(253,314)}梅斯·提利尔\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.20,0:05:11.24,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(121,223)}派席尔\N{\b0\fs12}大学士
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.06,0:09:48.10,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(135,254)}“魔山”\N{\b0\fs12}御林铁卫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.88,0:10:26.93,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(427,226)}兰赛尔·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}瑟曦的堂弟
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.14,0:11:50.18,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(76,249)}科本\N{\b0\fs12}学士
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.54,0:14:22.54,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(162,211)}凯冯·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.36,0:18:20.40,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(561,332)}乌尼亚\N{\b0\fs12}修女
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.44,0:23:08.48,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(582,260)}瓦德·佛雷\N{\b0\fs12}孪河城侯爵
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.95,0:23:18.59,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(635,257)}詹姆·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.96,0:23:30.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(80,288)}罗索·佛雷\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.96,0:23:30.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(532,285)}黑瓦德·佛雷\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.04,0:23:45.04,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(79,246)}波隆\N{\b0\fs12}骑士
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.02,0:28:00.06,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(111,251)}山姆威尔·塔利\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.69,0:28:00.73,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(452,259)}吉莉\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.02,0:32:07.06,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(447,218)}琼恩·雪诺\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.56,0:32:45.60,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(571,241)}戴佛斯·席渥斯\N{\b0\fs12}洋葱骑士
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.60,0:32:49.65,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(374,350)}梅丽珊卓\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.00,0:36:38.99,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(250,230)}珊莎·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.52,0:39:09.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(300,267)}艾拉莉亚·沙德\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.52,0:39:09.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(641,213)}奥芭娅·沙德\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.32,0:39:12.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(170,233)}奥莲娜·雷德温\N{\b0\fs12}荆棘女王
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.55,0:39:23.99,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(150,290)}娜梅莉亚·沙德\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:26.90,0:39:28.24,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(390,230)}特蕾妮·沙德\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:20.26,0:40:24.31,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(174,253)}瓦里斯\N{\b0\fs12}“八爪蜘蛛”
Dialogue: 0,0:40:25.98,0:40:30.02,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(246,278)}丹妮莉丝·坦格利安\N{\b0\fs12}弥林的女王
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.80,0:40:59.84,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(287,193)}达里奥·纳哈里斯\N{\b0\fs12}雇佣兵
Dialogue: 0,0:44:16.55,0:44:23.59,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(581,273)}提利昂·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}“小恶魔”
Dialogue: 0,0:48:59.61,0:49:04.15,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(265,236)}艾莉亚·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:43.37,0:50:47.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(361,260)}培提尔·贝里席\N{\b0\fs12}小指头
Dialogue: 0,0:52:47.88,0:52:52.93,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(406,251)}班扬·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:53:02.40,0:53:05.44,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(683,283)}梅拉·黎德\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:53:02.40,0:53:05.44,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(450,123)}布兰·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:56:39.54,0:56:44.58,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(666,175)}莱安娜·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:58:35.27,0:58:38.27,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(515,289)}莱安娜·莫尔蒙\N{\b0\fs12}熊岛伯爵夫人
Dialogue: 0,0:58:39.44,0:58:40.44,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(515,289)}威曼·曼德勒\N{\b0\fs12}白港伯爵
Dialogue: 0,0:58:50.12,0:58:51.16,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(164,250)}罗贝特·葛洛佛\N{\b0\fs12}深林堡伯爵
Dialogue: 0,0:58:58.67,0:59:00.71,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(340,185)}克雷·赛文\N{\b0\fs12}赛文城伯爵
Dialogue: 0,1:04:39.14,1:04:45.18,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(100,330)}席恩·葛雷乔伊\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,1:04:45.06,1:04:49.10,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(516,314)}亚拉·葛雷乔伊\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.14,0:04:23.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,陛下\N{\fs16}Your Grace.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.60,0:04:27.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,审判即将开始\N{\fs16}The trial will be getting under way soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.76,0:05:01.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,给钱啊\N{\fs16}You got my money?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.26,0:05:03.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一会再说 走开\N{\fs16}Later. Go away.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.29,0:05:16.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大学士\N{\fs16}Grand Maester.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.53,0:05:59.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,洛拉斯·提利尔爵士\N{\fs16}Ser Loras Tyrell.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.84,0:06:03.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是否已准备好在七神面前接受审判\N{\fs16}Are you prepared to stand trial
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.67,0:06:07.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,承认罪行抑或证明清白\N{\fs16}and profess your guilt or innocence before the Seven?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.98,0:06:12.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不必审判了\N{\fs16}There'll be no need for a trial.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.88,0:06:17.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我在七神面前坦白\N{\fs16}I confess before the Seven
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.39,0:06:19.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,完全承认我所犯之罪\N{\fs16}and freely admit to my crimes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.89,0:06:23.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你将坦白哪些罪行？\N{\fs16}To which crimes will you be confessing?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.50,0:06:26.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,全部\N{\fs16}All of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.80,0:06:29.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我和男人睡觉\N{\fs16}I lay with other men
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.60,0:06:33.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,其中包括叛国者蓝礼·拜拉席恩\N{\fs16}including the traitor Renly Baratheon.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.54,0:06:39.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我在诸神面前发了伪誓\N{\fs16}I perjured myself before the gods.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.41,0:06:41.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我堕落\N{\fs16}I am guilty of depravity...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.21,0:06:45.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不诚\N{\fs16}dishonesty,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.31,0:06:46.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,放荡 自负\N{\fs16}profligacy,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.88,0:06:49.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因而有罪\N{\fs16}and arrogance.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.85,0:06:51.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如今我已觉悟\N{\fs16}I see that now.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.66,0:06:55.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我服从七神旨意\N{\fs16}I humble myself before the Seven
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.99,0:06:59.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,接受任何诸神认为公正的惩罚\N{\fs16}and accept whatever punishment the gods deem just.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.43,0:07:06.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,诸神的惩罚是残忍的\N{\fs16}The gods' judgment is fierce,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.40,0:07:08.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也是公平的\N{\fs16}but also fair.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.04,0:07:12.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,战士对自以为可以逍遥法外之人\N{\fs16}The Warrior punishes those who believe themselves
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.51,0:07:14.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,施以惩罚\N{\fs16}beyond the reach of justice.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.28,0:07:19.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而圣母则对跪在她面前的人\N{\fs16}But the Mother shows her mercy
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.45,0:07:23.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,示以仁慈\N{\fs16}to those who kneel before her.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.29,0:07:33.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我对我犯下的罪行负全部责任\N{\fs16}I take full responsibility for my many sins
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.10,0:07:36.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我放弃我所有的欲望\N{\fs16}and unburden myself of my desires.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.07,0:07:43.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如今我唯愿\N{\fs16}My only remaining wish
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.11,0:07:45.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,献身于七神\N{\fs16}is to devote my life to the Seven.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.51,0:07:48.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,愿我成为前车之鉴\N{\fs16}May I be a living example of their grace
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.98,0:07:51.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,以为教训\N{\fs16}for others to witness.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.22,0:07:56.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你完全明白\N{\fs16}You understand fully
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.79,0:07:58.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这意味着什么吗？\N{\fs16}what this means?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.07,0:08:00.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fs16}I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.79,0:08:04.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我将放弃提利尔之名\N{\fs16}I will abandon the Tyrell name
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.03,0:08:08.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,及与家族相关的一切\N{\fs16}and all that goes with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.16,0:08:11.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我将放弃贵族身份及在高庭的一切权利\N{\fs16}I will renounce my lordship and my claims on Highgarden.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.57,0:08:17.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,永不娶妻\N{\fs16}I will never marry
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.91,0:08:20.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,永不生子\N{\fs16}and I will never father children.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.74,0:08:25.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,洛拉斯兄弟\N{\fs16}Brother Loras...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.27,0:08:30.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我要求你将生命献于七神\N{\fs16}...I ask you to dedicate your life to the seven gods.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.96,0:08:37.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你会为了保卫自己的信仰\N{\fs16}Will you fight to defend your faith
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.86,0:08:40.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,与异教徒和叛教者斗争到底吗？\N{\fs16}against heretics and apostates?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.40,0:08:41.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会\N{\fs16}I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.09,0:09:12.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不 我不能让他们……\N{\fs16}No, I can't let them...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.36,0:09:15.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,信仰才是正道 父亲\N{\fs16}Faith is the way, Father.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.89,0:09:39.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fs16}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.29,0:09:41.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我准备好了\N{\fs16}I'm ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.43,0:09:51.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我得走了 我……\N{\fs16}I have to go. I'm...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.03,0:09:53.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我要赶去参加审判了\N{\fs16}I'm late for the trial.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.12,0:10:09.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你把他毁容了\N{\fs16}You mutilated him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.32,0:10:11.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你承诺过的\N{\fs16}You gave me your word.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.32,0:10:13.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我信守承诺\N{\fs16}And I have kept my word.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.79,0:10:16.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一旦王太后的审判结束\N{\fs16}Once the queen mother's trial is concluded,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.66,0:10:18.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,洛拉斯兄弟将被释放\N{\fs16}Brother Loras is free to leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.79,0:10:20.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那么王太后现在何处？\N{\fs16}And where is the queen mother?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.80,0:10:24.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她的坐轿从未离开红堡\N{\fs16}Her litter never left the Red Keep.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.17,0:10:28.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,看起来王太后并不想出席她的审判\N{\fs16}It appears the queen mother doesn't wish to attend her own trial.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.51,0:10:33.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去红堡 把她带来\N{\fs16}Go to the Red Keep and show her the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.03,0:11:01.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去叫其他人\N{\fs16}Get the others.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.85,0:11:45.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,国王在哪里？\N{\fs16}Where's the king?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.75,0:11:50.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,恐怕在别的地方\N{\fs16}Elsewhere, I'm afraid.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.79,0:11:52.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是什么意思？\N{\fs16}What's the meaning of this?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.52,0:11:54.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我听说……\N{\fs16}I was told that...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.06,0:11:58.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我还有更重要的事情要做\N{\fs16}I have more important things to do with my time
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.26,0:11:59.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是在浪费我的时间……\N{\fs16}than waste them in the presence...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.73,0:12:02.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别急 大学士 我对你并无恶意\N{\fs16}Please, Grand Maester. I bear you no ill will.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.87,0:12:06.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果可以 请原谅我\N{\fs16}Please forgive me if you can.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.97,0:12:40.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我也不忍心这样 大人\N{\fs16}This pains me, my lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.20,0:12:42.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,无论您做错过什么 您都不应孤独地死在\N{\fs16}Whatever your faults, you do not deserve
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.37,0:12:45.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这样一个冰冷黑暗的地方\N{\fs16}to die alone in such a cold, dark place.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.44,0:12:49.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但有时我们唯有辞旧\N{\fs16}But sometimes before we can usher in the new,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.28,0:12:53.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,才能迎新\N{\fs16}the old must be put to rest.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.59,0:13:37.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你躲得越久 下场越惨\N{\fs16}The longer you wait, the worse it'll be for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.65,0:14:06.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你要干什么？\N{\fs16}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.06,0:15:16.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,事情有些不对\N{\fs16}There's something wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.22,0:15:18.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您不必担心 陛下\N{\fs16}You have nothing to fear, Your Grace.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.79,0:15:20.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,审判不久便会开始\N{\fs16}The trial will begin shortly.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.76,0:15:23.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,瑟曦不在这里 托曼也不在\N{\fs16}Cersei is not here. Tommen is not here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.57,0:15:24.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你觉得他们为什么不在？\N{\fs16}Why do you think they're not here?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.00,0:15:26.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果被控告之人不到场\N{\fs16}If the accused is not here,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.93,0:15:29.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她的审判仍要进行\N{\fs16}she will be tried regardless.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.10,0:15:31.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谁都不能摆脱诸神的裁决……\N{\fs16}We cannot escape the justice of the gods...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.44,0:15:34.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,忘了你那些神吧 现在听我说！\N{\fs16}Forget about the bloody gods and listen to what I'm telling you!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.18,0:15:37.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,瑟曦知道她不到场的后果\N{\fs16}Cersei understands the consequences of her absence
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.71,0:15:39.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而她还是没来\N{\fs16}and she is absent anyway,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.58,0:15:43.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这意味着她不打算承担这些后果\N{\fs16}which means she does not intend to suffer those consequences.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.55,0:15:47.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,推迟审判 我们必须全部离开\N{\fs16}The trial can wait. We all need to leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.21,0:16:15.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们现在必须全部离开！\N{\fs16}We all need to leave now!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.95,0:16:22.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,洛拉斯\N{\fs16}Loras.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.82,0:16:24.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,和我在一起\N{\fs16}Stay with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.44,0:16:40.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让我过去 让我过去\N{\fs16}Let me through. Let me through.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.11,0:16:44.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让开\N{\fs16}Get out of my way.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.72,0:16:54.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让我们过去\N{\fs16}Let us through.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.11,0:18:26.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,坦白\N{\fs16}Confess.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.32,0:18:30.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,坦白\N{\fs16}Confess.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.62,0:18:36.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,－不 －坦白\N{\fs16}- No. - Confess.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.23,0:18:49.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,坦白 这令人愉悦\N{\fs16}Confess. It felt good.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.17,0:18:52.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,殴打我 饿着我\N{\fs16}Beating me, starving me,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.97,0:18:55.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,恐吓我 羞辱我\N{\fs16}frightening me, humiliating me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.88,0:19:02.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你这样做不是因为你关心我能否赎罪\N{\fs16}You didn't do it because you cared about my atonement.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.54,0:19:05.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你这样做是因为这令你愉悦\N{\fs16}You did it because it felt good.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.69,0:19:08.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我明白\N{\fs16}I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.06,0:19:10.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我做什么事情也是因为这令我愉悦\N{\fs16}I do things because they feel good.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.46,0:19:16.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我喝酒因为这样令我愉悦\N{\fs16}I drink because it feels good.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.90,0:19:21.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我杀死了丈夫因为摆脱他纠缠令我愉悦\N{\fs16}I killed my husband because it felt good to be rid of him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.34,0:19:29.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我睡我的亲弟弟因为他进入我令我愉悦\N{\fs16}I fuck my brother because it feels good to feel him inside me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.41,0:19:31.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,关于睡我弟弟这一点我撒谎了……\N{\fs16}I lie about fucking my brother...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.51,0:19:37.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为能让我们的儿子远离可恶的伪君子 这令我愉悦\N{\fs16}because it feels good to keep our son safe from hateful hypocrites.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.32,0:19:42.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我杀了你的大麻雀……\N{\fs16}I killed your High Sparrow...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.06,0:19:46.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有他的小麻雀们……\N{\fs16}and all his little sparrows...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.90,0:19:51.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所有的修士 修女\N{\fs16}all his septons, all his septas,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.27,0:19:54.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所有他那些肮脏的士兵\N{\fs16}all his filthy soldiers,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.20,0:19:57.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为看着他们烧成灰烬 这令人愉悦\N{\fs16}because it felt good to watch them burn.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.24,0:20:03.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,想象一下他们的震惊和痛苦 真是令人愉悦\N{\fs16}It felt good to imagine their shock and their pain.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.18,0:20:06.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没有什么更快乐的事了\N{\fs16}No thought has ever given me greater joy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.22,0:20:15.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,时机对了 连坦白都这么令人愉悦\N{\fs16}Even confessing feels good under the right circumstances.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.90,0:20:23.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你一直都很沉默\N{\fs16}You've always been quiet.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.91,0:20:34.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我说过 我会是你死之前看到的最后一个人\N{\fs16}I said my face would be the last thing you saw before you died.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.98,0:20:37.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还记得么？\N{\fs16}Do you remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.15,0:20:39.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fs16}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.38,0:20:43.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我很高兴能看到你\N{\fs16}I'm glad to see your face.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.55,0:20:48.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我已经准备好迎接七神\N{\fs16}I'm ready to meet the gods.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.59,0:20:49.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,什么？\N{\fs16}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.93,0:20:53.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,现在？\N{\fs16}Now?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.96,0:20:55.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,今天？\N{\fs16}Today?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.50,0:21:00.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你今天不会死\N{\fs16}You're not going to die today.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.44,0:21:05.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你得要好一阵子才能死\N{\fs16}You're not going to die for quite a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.34,0:21:10.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,格雷果爵士\N{\fs16}Ser Gregor.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.35,0:21:16.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这位是格雷果·克里冈爵士\N{\fs16}This is Ser Gregor Clegane.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.72,0:21:19.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他也很沉默\N{\fs16}He's quiet, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.43,0:21:32.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的神已经抛弃你了\N{\fs16}Your gods have forsaken you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.30,0:21:35.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,现在 信奉他为神吧\N{\fs16}This is your god now.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.65,0:21:48.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不\N{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.55,0:21:50.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不要\N{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.25,0:21:55.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,耻辱\N{\fs16}Shame.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.59,0:21:58.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,耻辱\N{\fs16}Shame.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.93,0:22:02.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,耻辱\N{\fs16}Shame.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.53,0:22:10.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我很抱歉  陛下\N{\fs16}I'm very sorry, Your Grace.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.57,0:22:13.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,非常抱歉\N{\fs16}Very sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.12,0:22:59.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,为了兰尼斯特家族！\N{\fs16}For House Lannister!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.59,0:23:01.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,听我怒吼！\N{\fs16}Hear me roar!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.16,0:23:09.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,为了佛雷家族！\N{\fs16}For House Frey!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.46,0:23:12.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,并肩战斗！\N{\fs16}We stand together!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.63,0:23:15.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,希望我们的友谊\N{\fs16}May we stand together through the centuries,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.60,0:23:18.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,万古长青\N{\fs16}good friends to the last.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.17,0:23:22.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,愿我们戳翻敌人的时候\N{\fs16}And when we drive our swords through our enemies' hearts,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.31,0:23:26.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,念叨着同样的话\N{\fs16}may we speak the words of our alliance,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.21,0:23:29.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,“佛雷和兰尼斯特向你\N{\fs16}"The Freys and the Lannisters
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.72,0:23:31.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,致以亲切问候”\N{\fs16}send their regards."
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.24,0:23:51.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你压根什么事情都不用做 对吧？\N{\fs16}You don't even have to do anything, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.14,0:23:55.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你坐在那 好像一大块牛肉\N{\fs16}You just sit there, a rich slab of beef,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.51,0:23:56.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,其他人就跟鸟儿一样飞过来啄食\N{\fs16}and all the birds come pecking.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.04,0:23:59.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 要上她的话不用跟我客气 - 她才不想要我\N{\fs16}- You're welcome to her. - She doesn't want me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.55,0:24:01.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她那下面要的是你的金手指\N{\fs16}She wants your golden fingers up her twat.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.82,0:24:05.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那两个可是盯着你呢\N{\fs16}Those two have their eyes on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.09,0:24:09.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们盯着的是你 傻逼\N{\fs16}They have their eyes on you, cunt.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.69,0:24:11.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不是我的菜\N{\fs16}Not my type.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.79,0:24:13.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,头发还不够黄？\N{\fs16}Not blonde enough?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.83,0:24:19.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女士们 来认识一下黑水湾的波隆爵士\N{\fs16}Ladies, have you met Ser Bronn of the Blackwater,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.37,0:24:21.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他可是黑水湾之战的英雄\N{\fs16}hero of the Battle of Blackwater Bay?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.64,0:24:24.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 收了吧 - 我不是很有兴致\N{\fs16}- There you go. - Maybe I'm not in the mood.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.84,0:24:28.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不操白不操\N{\fs16}Fuck it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.91,0:24:32.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没必要因为我是一个受封的骑士就叫爵士\N{\fs16}No need to call me ser just because I'm an anointed knight.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.39,0:24:39.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这次事情进展顺利\N{\fs16}This came together rather well.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.56,0:24:43.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的父亲肯定会很满意\N{\fs16}Your father would be pleased.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.82,0:24:45.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我敢保证他一定是\N{\fs16}I'm sure he would be.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.13,0:24:50.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,艾德慕已经重新关押了\N{\fs16}Edmure is back in a cell.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.07,0:24:54.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不能杀了我的女婿 这可不对\N{\fs16}Can't go killing my son by law. It wouldn't be right.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.80,0:24:56.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,会损害家族名声\N{\fs16}Give the family a bad name.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.44,0:25:04.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所以大名鼎鼎的黑鱼是被小卒杀死的 对吧？\N{\fs16}So the famous Blackfish killed by foot soldiers, eh?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.48,0:25:07.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,话都传开了 一代传奇就这么……\N{\fs16}Legendary warrior, everyone said.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.85,0:25:11.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您会亲自上战场打仗吗 佛雷大人？\N{\fs16}Have you done much fighting yourself, Lord Frey?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.25,0:25:13.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我年纪大了玩不了\N{\fs16}I'm a bit old for all that.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.89,0:25:16.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不 说的是你年轻的时候\N{\fs16}No, but back in your day.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.69,0:25:19.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,打仗的目的\N{\fs16}The purpose of fighting
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.73,0:25:22.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是击败对手 不是吗？\N{\fs16}is defeating your enemies, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.03,0:25:25.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我打败了我的对手们\N{\fs16}I've defeated mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.13,0:25:28.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奔流城已经被徒利家族统治了一千年\N{\fs16}Riverrun belonged to House Tully for a thousand years.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.94,0:25:30.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,现在是我的了\N{\fs16}Now it's mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.60,0:25:32.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这叫什么？\N{\fs16}What do you call that?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.01,0:25:34.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,胜利\N{\fs16}Victory.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.38,0:25:36.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的 你是一个伟大的征服者\N{\fs16}Yes, you're a great conqueror.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.48,0:25:42.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,来啊 取笑我啊 小子 你以为我介意吗？\N{\fs16}Go on, mock me, boy. You think I mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.35,0:25:45.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,徒利家族取笑了我那么多年\N{\fs16}The Tullys mocked me for years.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.19,0:25:47.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,史塔克家族也取笑过我\N{\fs16}The Starks mocked me.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.46,0:25:48.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们现在在哪？\N{\fs16}Where are they now?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.02,0:25:51.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你说起战争的时候像个专家\N{\fs16}You talk about war as if you're an expert,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.59,0:25:53.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我记得有一场你参与的战斗\N{\fs16}but the one battle I remember you fighting,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.00,0:25:56.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你被少狼主罗柏·史塔克俘虏了\N{\fs16}you were captured by Robb Stark, the Young Wolf.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.00,0:25:59.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不过也不重要\N{\fs16}But it doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.00,0:26:03.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们两个弑君者在这坐得好好的\N{\fs16}Here we are now, two kingslayers.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.44,0:26:07.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们知道那些人当着面卑躬屈膝\N{\fs16}We know what it's like to have them grovel to our faces
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.41,0:26:10.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,背后却冷言冷语\N{\fs16}and snigger behind our backs.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.51,0:26:12.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们不在乎 对吧？\N{\fs16}We don't mind, do we?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.18,0:26:16.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,恐惧是件不可思议的事情\N{\fs16}Fear is a marvelous thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.25,0:26:17.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,可他们不害怕佛雷家\N{\fs16}They don't fear the Freys, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.95,0:26:20.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们害怕的是兰尼斯特家\N{\fs16}They fear the Lannisters.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.79,0:26:23.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们给了你河间地是让你守住这里\N{\fs16}We gave you the Riverlands to hold the Riverlands.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.26,0:26:25.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果你每次都搞丢\N{\fs16}If we have to ride north and take them back for you
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.79,0:26:28.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,每次都要我们来替你夺回地盘\N{\fs16}every time you lose them,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.30,0:26:30.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那我们要你有何用？\N{\fs16}why do we need you?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.95,0:26:53.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,给我看\N{\fs16}Show me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.42,0:26:58.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,陛下  没必要……\N{\fs16}Your Grace, there's no need...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.49,0:26:59.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,给我看\N{\fs16}Show me.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.77,0:27:16.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您对陛下的葬礼有什么想法？\N{\fs16}What are your thoughts concerning the king's funeral?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.28,0:27:18.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,鉴于贝勒大圣堂已不再适合\N{\fs16}As the Sept of Baelor is no longer an option,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.05,0:27:22.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,或许在王座厅举行仪式？\N{\fs16}perhaps a ceremony in the throne room?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.29,0:27:27.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他应该和他外祖父\N{\fs16}He should be with his grandfather,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.52,0:27:30.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,以及哥哥 妹妹一起\N{\fs16}his brother, his sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.79,0:27:35.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,烧了吧\N{\fs16}Burn him
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.56,0:27:38.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,把他的骨灰埋在大圣堂的废墟\N{\fs16}and bury his ashes where the sept once stood.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.26,0:28:37.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你好\N{\fs16}Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.40,0:28:48.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,黑城堡雪诺总司令的信\N{\fs16}From Lord Commander Snow at Castle Black.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.72,0:29:04.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我要……\N{\fs16}I'm...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.09,0:29:06.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我要成为新学士\N{\fs16}I'm to be the new maester.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.42,0:29:25.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,根据我们的记录\N{\fs16}According to our records,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.67,0:29:27.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,杰奥·莫尔蒙才是总司令\N{\fs16}Jeor Mormont is Lord Commander.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.84,0:29:30.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他死了\N{\fs16}He died.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.68,0:29:33.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们没收到黑城堡学士发来的报告\N{\fs16}We received no report from the maester at Castle Black.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.35,0:29:36.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,伊蒙学士在选举之后病情加重\N{\fs16}Maester Aemon became quite ill shortly after the election.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.34,0:29:38.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他也去世了\N{\fs16}He's since passed away.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.05,0:29:42.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这就是为什么我会来到此地\N{\fs16}Which is why I'm here.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.36,0:29:48.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这不合规矩\N{\fs16}This is irregular.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.30,0:29:50.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的  可是……\N{\fs16}Yes, well...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.33,0:29:53.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我觉得生活也并非总是循规蹈矩\N{\fs16}I suppose that life is irregular.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.55,0:30:08.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,博士会和你讨论规矩的问题\N{\fs16}The archmaester will discuss these irregularities with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.22,0:30:14.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在此期间  你可以使用图书馆\N{\fs16}In the meantime, you are permitted to use the library.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.36,0:30:16.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,跟我来\N{\fs16}Follow me.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.19,0:30:21.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女人和小孩不许进入\N{\fs16}No women or children.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.44,0:32:17.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,设宴的时候\N{\fs16}When we had feasts,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.85,0:32:20.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的家人会上坐在这儿\N{\fs16}our family would sit up here...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.12,0:32:24.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我却坐在那里\N{\fs16}and I'd sit down there.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.35,0:32:28.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,本可能更糟的  琼恩 雪诺\N{\fs16}Could have been worse, Jon Snow.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.02,0:32:30.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你有过家\N{\fs16}You had a family.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.89,0:32:32.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有过宴会\N{\fs16}You had feasts.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.23,0:32:37.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是 你说得对  我比大多数私生子都幸运\N{\fs16}Aye, you're right. I was luckier than most.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:52.81,0:32:54.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那是什么？\N{\fs16}What is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.12,0:32:58.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,告诉他\N{\fs16}Tell him.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.09,0:33:03.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,告诉他这是谁的东西\N{\fs16}Tell him who it belonged to.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.16,0:33:09.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,希琳公主\N{\fs16}The Princess Shireen.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.86,0:33:12.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,告诉他你对她做了什么\N{\fs16}Tell him what you did to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.55,0:33:15.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,告诉他！\N{\fs16}Tell him!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.04,0:33:23.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们烧死了她\N{\fs16}We burned her at the stake.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.89,0:33:39.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,为什么？\N{\fs16}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.33,0:33:42.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,军队被困 马匹都快死了\N{\fs16}The army was trapped. The horses were dying.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.53,0:33:45.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-那是唯一的办法 -你活活烧死了一个小女孩！\N{\fs16}- It was the only way. - You burned a little girl alive!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.70,0:33:47.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我只是奉真主之命行事\N{\fs16}I only do what my Lord commands.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.23,0:33:50.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果他命令你烧死孩子 那他便是邪恶的\N{\fs16}If he commands you to burn children, your Lord is evil.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:53.67,0:33:55.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们因为他才能活下来\N{\fs16}We are standing here because of him.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.88,0:34:00.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,琼恩·雪诺能复活 也都是真主的旨意\N{\fs16}Jon Snow is alive because the Lord willed it.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.25,0:34:03.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我爱那个孩子 我对她视如己出\N{\fs16}I loved that girl like she was my own.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:03.95,0:34:07.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她是个好孩子 善良的孩子 你却杀了她！\N{\fs16}She was good. She was kind. And you killed her!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.46,0:34:10.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这也是她父亲的意思\N{\fs16}So did her father.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.23,0:34:14.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她的母亲的意思\N{\fs16}So did her mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.90,0:34:19.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她的双亲也知道那是唯一的办法\N{\fs16}Her own blood knew it was the only way.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.23,0:34:21.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那办法有用吗？\N{\fs16}The only way for what?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.94,0:34:23.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们都死了\N{\fs16}They all died anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.31,0:34:27.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你告诉每个人史坦尼斯就是预言中那个人\N{\fs16}You told everyone Stannis was the one.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.41,0:34:29.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你让史坦尼斯相信你 所有人都被耍了\N{\fs16}You had him believing it, all of them fooled.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.84,0:34:32.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-你撒谎 -我没有撒谎\N{\fs16}- And you lied. - I didn't lie.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.05,0:34:35.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我只是弄错了\N{\fs16}I was wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.48,0:34:38.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对 你弄错了\N{\fs16}Aye, you were wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.55,0:34:42.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,多少人因为你的错而死？\N{\fs16}How many died because you were wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.43,0:34:51.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我请求您以谋杀罪处决这个女人\N{\fs16}I ask your leave to execute this woman for murder.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:51.43,0:34:53.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她已承认了罪行\N{\fs16}She admits to the crime.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.74,0:34:58.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你有什么要为自己辩护的吗？\N{\fs16}Do you have anything to say for yourself?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.01,0:35:02.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,多少年前我就准备去死了\N{\fs16}I've been ready to die for many years.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.55,0:35:07.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果光之王不需要我了 我随时可以去死 但他还需要我\N{\fs16}If the Lord was done with me, so be it, but he's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.68,0:35:10.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你见过夜王 琼恩·雪诺\N{\fs16}You've seen the Night King, Jon Snow.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.98,0:35:14.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你知道大战在即\N{\fs16}You know the great war is still to come.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:14.35,0:35:17.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你知道死人的军团就要来了\N{\fs16}You know the army of the dead will be upon us soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.56,0:35:21.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你知道我可以助你赢得这场大战\N{\fs16}And you know I can help you win that war.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.41,0:35:37.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,今天就骑马南下\N{\fs16}Ride south today.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.78,0:35:40.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,若你再返回北境\N{\fs16}If you return to the North,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.78,0:35:43.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会以杀人罪处你绞刑\N{\fs16}I'll have you hanged as a murderer.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.13,0:36:03.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,若你胆敢回来\N{\fs16}If you ever come back this way,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.84,0:36:06.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会亲自处决你\N{\fs16}I will execute you myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.20,0:36:41.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我让人收拾好了领主的房间给你\N{\fs16}I'm having the lord's chamber prepared for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.74,0:36:44.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,母亲和父亲的房间？\N{\fs16}Mother and Father's room?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.25,0:36:48.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那属于你\N{\fs16}You should take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.48,0:36:51.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不是史塔克\N{\fs16}I'm not a Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.36,0:36:53.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对我来说 你是\N{\fs16}You are to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:57.62,0:36:59.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,临冬城属于你\N{\fs16}You're the Lady of Winterfell.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.39,0:37:03.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是你应得的 因为你我们才能站在这儿\N{\fs16}You deserve it. We're standing here because of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.40,0:37:06.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在谷地骑士冲进来之前 我们本来一败涂地\N{\fs16}The battle was lost until the Knights of the Vale rode in.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.00,0:37:09.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而他们是因你而来\N{\fs16}They came because of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.21,0:37:16.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你告诉我是贝里席大人把你卖给了波顿家\N{\fs16}You told me Lord Baelish sold you to the Boltons.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.24,0:37:18.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,-是他 -你信任他？\N{\fs16}- He did. - And you trust him?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.23,0:37:21.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,傻瓜才会信任小指头\N{\fs16}Only a fool would trust Littlefinger.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.89,0:37:27.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我应该告诉你的\N{\fs16}I should have told you about him,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:27.75,0:37:31.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,告诉你谷地骑士的事\N{\fs16}about the Knights of the Vale.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.19,0:37:32.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对不起\N{\fs16}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.97,0:37:45.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们必须信任彼此\N{\fs16}We need to trust each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:46.77,0:37:49.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们不能起内讧\N{\fs16}We can't fight a war amongst ourselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.14,0:37:51.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们现在有太多的敌人\N{\fs16}We have so many enemies now.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.44,0:38:09.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,琼恩\N{\fs16}Jon.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.03,0:38:13.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,从学城来了一只渡鸦\N{\fs16}A raven came from the Citadel.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.57,0:38:15.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,白色的渡鸦\N{\fs16}A white raven.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.17,0:38:19.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,凛冬已至\N{\fs16}Winter is here.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.99,0:38:35.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好吧 就像父亲从小答应我们的那样 不是吗？\N{\fs16}Well, Father always promised, didn't he?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.20,0:38:52.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,上一个提利尔来多恩的时候\N{\fs16}The last time a Tyrell came to Dorne,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.47,0:38:54.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他被杀掉了\N{\fs16}he was assassinated.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.67,0:38:57.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一百个红蝎子 对吗？\N{\fs16}100 red scorpions, was it?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.34,0:38:59.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不必害怕我们 奥莲娜夫人\N{\fs16}You have nothing to fear from us, Lady Olenna.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:59.95,0:39:02.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们谋杀了自己的亲王\N{\fs16}You murder your own prince,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.18,0:39:03.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还指望我信任你们？\N{\fs16}but you expect me to trust you?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.02,0:39:06.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们邀请您来多恩 因为我们需要您的帮助\N{\fs16}We invited you to Dorne because we needed your help.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.09,0:39:09.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您来多恩 因为您需要我们的帮助\N{\fs16}You came to Dorne because you needed our help.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.17,0:39:12.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你叫什么来着？\N{\fs16}What is your name again?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.94,0:39:14.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,芭芭拉？\N{\fs16}Barbaro?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.35,0:39:15.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奥芭娅\N{\fs16}Obara.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.23,0:39:18.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奥芭娅 你看起来像个愤怒的小男孩\N{\fs16}Obara. You look like an angry little boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.46,0:39:21.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别妄自揣测我需要什么\N{\fs16}Don't presume to tell me what I need.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.20,0:39:24.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,原谅我姐姐 尽管她缺少外交手腕 但其他方面···\N{\fs16}Forgive my sister. What she lacks in diplomacy, she makes...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:24.64,0:39:28.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,请闭嘴 亲爱的 你没什么要说的？\N{\fs16}Do shut up, dear. Anything from you?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.24,0:39:30.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没有？很好\N{\fs16}No? Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:30.24,0:39:32.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让成年女人说话吧\N{\fs16}Let the grown women speak.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.54,0:39:36.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,兰尼斯特家族已向提利尔家族宣战\N{\fs16}The Lannisters have declared war on House Tyrell.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.55,0:39:39.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们也早已向多恩宣战\N{\fs16}They have declared war on Dorne.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.62,0:39:43.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们想活下去就必须结盟\N{\fs16}We must be allies now if we wish to survive.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.56,0:39:47.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,瑟曦偷走了我的未来\N{\fs16}Cersei stole the future from me.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.63,0:39:49.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她杀了我的儿子\N{\fs16}She killed my son.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.50,0:39:51.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她杀了我的孙子\N{\fs16}She killed my grandson.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.63,0:39:54.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她杀了我的孙女\N{\fs16}She killed my granddaughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.94,0:39:57.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我现在想要的不是活下去\N{\fs16}Survival is not what I'm after now.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.87,0:40:00.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你说得完全正确\N{\fs16}You're absolutely right.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.14,0:40:02.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我措辞不当\N{\fs16}I chose the wrong words.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.81,0:40:05.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我提议的不是活下去\N{\fs16}It is not survival I offer.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.41,0:40:07.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而是你的渴望\N{\fs16}It is your heart's desire.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.58,0:40:12.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的渴望是什么？\N{\fs16}And what is my heart's desire?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.35,0:40:16.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,复仇\N{\fs16}Vengeance.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.69,0:40:17.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,正义\N{\fs16}Justice.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.53,0:40:23.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,血与火\N{\fs16}Fire and blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:29.87,0:40:32.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您的船差不多准备好了\N{\fs16}Your ships are nearly ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.77,0:40:35.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我看到他们在绘制船帆\N{\fs16}I saw them painting the sails.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:38.51,0:40:42.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我很想看看多斯拉克人在“毒水”上面表现如何\N{\fs16}I'm curious to see how the Dothraki do on the poison water.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.42,0:40:44.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不跟我们走\N{\fs16}You're not coming with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.69,0:40:49.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有新战略？\N{\fs16}New strategy?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.02,0:40:53.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想让次子团从西海岸登陆？\N{\fs16}You want the Second Sons to attack from the west coast?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.33,0:40:55.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果我们攻下凯岩城\N{\fs16}If we take Casterly Rock,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:56.03,0:40:59.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,当你进攻君临时 兰尼斯特家就无处可逃了\N{\fs16}the Lannisters will have nowhere to run when you hit King's Landing.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.70,0:41:01.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不去维斯特洛\N{\fs16}You're not going to Westeros.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.73,0:41:04.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你和次子团在这儿守着\N{\fs16}You're staying here with the Second Sons.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.77,0:41:07.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,弥林终于迎来了和平\N{\fs16}There's finally peace in Meereen.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.51,0:41:10.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,弥林人将推选自己的领导人 而你来维护和平\N{\fs16}You will keep the peace while the people choose their own leaders.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:12.15,0:41:13.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去他的弥林\N{\fs16}Fuck Meereen.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:14.05,0:41:15.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去他的人民\N{\fs16}Fuck the people.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.05,0:41:18.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我来在这儿是为了你 不是为了他们\N{\fs16}I'm here for you, not them.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.42,0:41:20.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你答应过我\N{\fs16}You promised me.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:20.19,0:41:23.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,“我的剑是你的了 我的生命也是你的”\N{\fs16}"My sword is yours. My life is yours."
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.22,0:41:26.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这就是我的命令\N{\fs16}This is what I command.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:27.26,0:41:29.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果我要统治维斯特洛\N{\fs16}If I'm going to rule in Westeros,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:29.53,0:41:32.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就需要缔结联盟\N{\fs16}I'll need to make alliances.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.13,0:41:35.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,最好的方式便是联姻\N{\fs16}The best way to make alliances is with marriage.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:38.84,0:41:40.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这次你要嫁给谁？\N{\fs16}Who are you marrying this time?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.77,0:41:44.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不知道 也许不嫁\N{\fs16}I don't know. Maybe no one.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.24,0:41:47.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但你需要引诱那些大贵族们？\N{\fs16}But you need to lure all the noble houses to the table?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:47.45,0:41:49.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是个女王还是个鱼饵？\N{\fs16}Are you a queen or fish bait?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:51.85,0:41:54.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不能把情人带回维斯特洛\N{\fs16}I can't bring a lover to Westeros.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.92,0:41:57.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一个国王会毫不犹豫的带回去\N{\fs16}A king wouldn't think twice about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:57.26,0:42:00.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这就是你想要的喽？成为我的男宠？\N{\fs16}So that's what you want? To be my mistress?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:00.26,0:42:03.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不为此骄傲 但我也不在乎哪个喷香水的贵族\N{\fs16}I'm not proud. I don't care what perfumed aristocrat
Dialogue: 0,0:42:03.66,0:42:05.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在王座厅里坐在你身边\N{\fs16}sits beside you in the throne room.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.87,0:42:08.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不想要王冠 我只要你\N{\fs16}I don't want a crown. I want you.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.88,0:42:18.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我爱你\N{\fs16}I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.18,0:42:20.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我能带给你快乐\N{\fs16}And I make you happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:21.24,0:42:22.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你知道的\N{\fs16}You know I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:24.85,0:42:28.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,带上我 让我为你而战\N{\fs16}Bring me with you. Let me fight for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:36.16,0:42:37.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不能\N{\fs16}I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:47.17,0:42:48.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那矮子告诉你这么做的？\N{\fs16}The dwarf told you to do this?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.01,0:42:50.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没人告诉我怎么做\N{\fs16}No one tells me to do anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:50.78,0:42:53.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,聪明的家伙 无可反驳的逻辑\N{\fs16}Clever fellow. Can't argue with his logic.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.05,0:42:55.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我在那边对你没有用\N{\fs16}I'm no use to you over there.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:55.88,0:42:57.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别生气\N{\fs16}Don't get angry.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:57.25,0:43:00.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没生气 只是自怨自艾罢了\N{\fs16}I'm not angry. I'm full of self-pity.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:00.52,0:43:02.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谁才能追随你呢？\N{\fs16}Who comes after you?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:02.22,0:43:05.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谁有资格追随风暴降生的丹妮莉丝 龙之母？\N{\fs16}Who can ever follow Daenerys Stormborn, the Mother of Dragons?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.49,0:43:07.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我想 会有一大帮女人吧\N{\fs16}A great number of women, I imagine.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:13.97,0:43:15.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,关于维护弥林和巨龙湾的详细指令\N{\fs16}Specific orders will be left for you
Dialogue: 0,0:43:15.90,0:43:18.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,将会留给你\N{\fs16}regarding the welfare of Meereen and the Bay of Dragons.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:18.94,0:43:20.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,巨龙湾？\N{\fs16}Bay of Dragons?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.84,0:43:23.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们不能再继续叫它奴隶湾了 是吧？\N{\fs16}We can't call it Slaver's Bay anymore, can we?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:26.85,0:43:30.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你会得到那个你期待已久的王座 我非常确定\N{\fs16}You'll get that throne you want so badly, I'm sure of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:31.48,0:43:33.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我希望那能带给你快乐\N{\fs16}I hope it brings you happiness.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:38.76,0:43:41.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我十分同情维斯特洛的领主们\N{\fs16}I pity the lords of Westeros.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:41.46,0:43:43.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们对即将到来的事一无所知\N{\fs16}They have no idea what's coming for them.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:44.81,0:43:47.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,再见 达里奥·纳哈里斯\N{\fs16}Farewell, Daario Naharis.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:06.35,0:44:08.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他反应如何？\N{\fs16}How did he take it?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:08.75,0:44:10.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没掉泪\N{\fs16}No tears.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:12.89,0:44:15.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我知道对你而言很难说出口\N{\fs16}I know it was hard for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:15.63,0:44:17.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你拒绝了一个真正爱你的男人\N{\fs16}You turned away a man who truly loves you
Dialogue: 0,0:44:17.76,0:44:20.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就因为他可能成为你在七大王国的负担\N{\fs16}because he would have been a liability in the Seven Kingdoms.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:23.24,0:44:26.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但正是这种自我牺牲 让你成为一个伟大的统治者\N{\fs16}That's the kind of self-sacrifice that makes for a good ruler,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:27.04,0:44:29.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果这么说能安慰你的话\N{\fs16}if it's any consolation.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:32.11,0:44:33.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不能\N{\fs16}It's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:34.01,0:44:36.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是啊 我也觉得不能\N{\fs16}No, I suppose not.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:36.42,0:44:37.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不擅长安慰别人\N{\fs16}I'm terrible at consoling.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:38.05,0:44:40.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是啊 你的确不擅长\N{\fs16}Yes, you really are.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:43.52,0:44:47.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好 那来谈谈眼前发生的一切吧？\N{\fs16}All right, how about the fact that this is actually happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:49.23,0:44:52.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你有了军队 有了舰船\N{\fs16}You have your armies, you have your ships,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:52.20,0:44:54.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你还有龙\N{\fs16}you have your dragons.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.30,0:44:56.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你已经拥有了\N{\fs16}Everything you've ever wanted
Dialogue: 0,0:44:56.37,0:44:59.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所有打懂事起想拥有的东西\N{\fs16}since you were old enough to want anything,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:59.37,0:45:01.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,任你差遣\N{\fs16}it's all yours for the taking.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:03.01,0:45:04.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你害怕吗？\N{\fs16}Are you afraid?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:08.11,0:45:09.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很好\N{\fs16}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:10.08,0:45:12.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你现在已经身处权力的游戏之中\N{\fs16}You're in the great game now.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:12.92,0:45:15.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而权力的游戏是很可怕的\N{\fs16}And the great game's terrifying.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:15.59,0:45:18.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那些不怕失败的\N{\fs16}The only people who aren't afraid of failure
Dialogue: 0,0:45:18.16,0:45:20.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,都是你父亲那种疯子\N{\fs16}are madmen like your father.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:22.36,0:45:24.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你知道我害怕的是什么吗？\N{\fs16}Do you know what frightens me?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:25.93,0:45:28.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我与一个爱我的男人告别\N{\fs16}I said farewell to a man who loves me.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:30.47,0:45:34.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一个我以为我在乎的人\N{\fs16}A man I thought I cared for.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:34.14,0:45:36.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我毫无感觉\N{\fs16}And I felt nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.71,0:45:39.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只是不耐烦得说出来\N{\fs16}Just impatient to get on with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:42.72,0:45:45.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他不是第一个爱你的人\N{\fs16}He wasn't the first to love you
Dialogue: 0,0:45:45.89,0:45:47.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也不会是最后一个\N{\fs16}and he won't be the last.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:51.86,0:45:56.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好吧 你安慰我这件事 彻底失败了\N{\fs16}Well, you have completely failed to console me.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:59.33,0:46:04.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好吧 听我说 自打记事起 我就是个愤世嫉俗的人\N{\fs16}For what it's worth, I've been a cynic for as long as I can remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:04.14,0:46:06.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,每个人都和我说 让我信点什么……\N{\fs16}Everyone's always asking me to believe in things...
Dialogue: 0,0:46:07.04,0:46:10.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,家庭 七神 国王 我自己\N{\fs16}family, gods, kings, myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:10.88,0:46:12.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,听起来非常诱人\N{\fs16}It was often tempting
Dialogue: 0,0:46:12.81,0:46:15.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,直到我看见信仰把人们变成什么样子\N{\fs16}until I saw where belief got people.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:16.52,0:46:19.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所以我说不 你们还是把信仰留给自己吧\N{\fs16}So I said no, thank you to belief.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:19.22,0:46:22.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而如今我在这\N{\fs16}And yet here I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:25.23,0:46:27.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我相信你\N{\fs16}I believe in you.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:29.43,0:46:31.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很尴尬 真的\N{\fs16}It's embarrassing, really.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:33.90,0:46:35.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我都可以拔剑起誓\N{\fs16}I'd swear you my sword,
Dialogue: 0,0:46:35.80,0:46:38.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,可惜我没有佩剑\N{\fs16}but I don't actually own a sword.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:38.94,0:46:40.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我需要的是你的谏言\N{\fs16}It's your counsel I need.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:41.04,0:46:43.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,它们属于您\N{\fs16}It's yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:43.58,0:46:45.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,从现在直到永远\N{\fs16}Now and always.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:46.51,0:46:48.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好\N{\fs16}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:49.65,0:46:51.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我……\N{\fs16}I...
Dialogue: 0,0:46:51.78,0:46:53.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我给你做了件东西\N{\fs16}I had something made for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:55.26,0:46:57.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不确定做得对不对\N{\fs16}I'm not sure if it's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:07.10,0:47:09.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,提利昂·兰尼斯特\N{\fs16}Tyrion Lannister,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:09.90,0:47:11.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我命你为女王之手\N{\fs16}I name you Hand of the Queen.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:46.04,0:47:48.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不是我女儿 是吧？\N{\fs16}You're not one of mine, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:48.68,0:47:50.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不是 老爷\N{\fs16}No, my lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:50.28,0:47:51.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我也觉得不是\N{\fs16}Didn't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:52.04,0:47:54.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你太漂亮了\N{\fs16}Too pretty.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:58.55,0:48:01.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我那些该死的白痴儿子都在哪儿？\N{\fs16}Where are my damn moron sons?!
Dialogue: 0,0:48:01.45,0:48:05.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,黑瓦德和罗索答应过中午就到\N{\fs16}Black Walder and Lothar promised to be here by midday.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:05.29,0:48:07.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们在这儿 老爷\N{\fs16}They're here, my lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:07.23,0:48:10.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在这儿 那他们在干什么？ 修剪屌毛吗？\N{\fs16}Well, what are they doing, trimming their cunt hairs?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:10.63,0:48:12.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,告诉他们立刻过来\N{\fs16}Tell them to come here now.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:12.80,0:48:15.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但他们已经在这儿了 老爷\N{\fs16}But they're already here, my lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:19.10,0:48:22.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在这儿 老爷\N{\fs16}Here, my lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:40.39,0:48:42.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,切开他们可不那么容易\N{\fs16}They weren't easy to carve.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:44.10,0:48:46.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,尤其是黑瓦德\N{\fs16}Especially Black Walder.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:47.81,0:48:48.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,什么……\N{\fs16}What...
Dialogue: 0,0:48:56.08,0:48:57.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的名字是艾莉亚·史塔克\N{\fs16}My name is Arya Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:57.84,0:48:59.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我希望你知道\N{\fs16}I want you to know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:59.45,0:49:02.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你这辈子所见的最后一件事\N{\fs16}The last thing you're ever going to see
Dialogue: 0,0:49:02.28,0:49:05.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就是死时看着史塔克家族的人冲你微笑\N{\fs16}is a Stark smiling down at you as you die.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:59.81,0:50:01.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,原谅我 小姐\N{\fs16}Forgive me, my lady...
Dialogue: 0,0:50:03.24,0:50:06.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果我打断了你的祈祷……\N{\fs16}if you're at prayer.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:06.35,0:50:08.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我已经不再祈祷了\N{\fs16}I'm done with all that.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:10.55,0:50:13.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在我还是个小女孩时 每天都来这里\N{\fs16}I came here every day when I was a girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:14.79,0:50:17.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,祈祷自己能去别的地方\N{\fs16}I prayed to be somewhere else.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:17.72,0:50:21.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那时 我只想到自己想要什么 从没想过我拥有什么\N{\fs16}Back then I only thought about what I wanted, never about what I had.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:25.53,0:50:26.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我太蠢了\N{\fs16}I was a stupid girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:27.07,0:50:29.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那时你还是个孩子\N{\fs16}You were a child.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:32.30,0:50:34.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想要什么？\N{\fs16}What do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:34.87,0:50:37.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我以为你知道\N{\fs16}I thought you knew what I wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:37.34,0:50:38.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不知道\N{\fs16}I was wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:39.04,0:50:41.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不 你知道\N{\fs16}No, you weren't.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:44.45,0:50:46.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,每次需要做决定前\N{\fs16}Every time I'm faced with a decision,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:46.12,0:50:48.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我都会闭上眼睛 看到同一个画面\N{\fs16}I close my eyes and see the same picture.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:50.06,0:50:53.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,每当我要采取行动时 我都会问自己\N{\fs16}Whenever I consider an action, I ask myself
Dialogue: 0,0:50:53.56,0:50:57.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这会帮我把画面的内容变成现实吗？\N{\fs16}will this action help to make this picture a reality?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:59.67,0:51:02.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,把它拽出脑海\N{\fs16}Pull it out of my mind
Dialogue: 0,0:51:02.54,0:51:04.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,放到现实中？\N{\fs16}and into the world?
Dialogue: 0,0:51:06.47,0:51:09.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只有在答案肯定时 我才会行动\N{\fs16}And I only act if the answer is yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:12.21,0:51:15.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一副我自己……\N{\fs16}A picture of me...
Dialogue: 0,0:51:15.24,0:51:17.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,坐在铁王座上……\N{\fs16}on the Iron Throne...
Dialogue: 0,0:51:19.59,0:51:21.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而你坐我在身边的画面\N{\fs16}and you by my side.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:31.56,0:51:33.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很美的画面\N{\fs16}It's a pretty picture.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:39.01,0:51:42.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这场大战的消息很快会传遍七大王国\N{\fs16}News of this battle will spread quickly through the Seven Kingdoms.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:42.61,0:51:46.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所有人都会知道 我为史塔克家族而战\N{\fs16}I've declared for House Stark for all to hear.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:46.21,0:51:48.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你也曾效忠过别的家族 贝里席大人\N{\fs16}You've declared for other houses before, Lord Baelish.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:48.78,0:51:51.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,可你从未停止过为自己谋利\N{\fs16}It's never stopped you from serving yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:51.58,0:51:53.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,过去的已经过去\N{\fs16}The past is gone for good.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:53.89,0:51:55.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你可以坐在这感伤时光的流逝\N{\fs16}You can sit here mourning its departure
Dialogue: 0,0:51:56.06,0:51:58.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,或者去为未来做好准备\N{\fs16}or you can prepare for the future.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:59.09,0:52:01.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你 吾爱\N{\fs16}You, my love,
Dialogue: 0,0:52:01.66,0:52:04.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就是史塔克家族的未来\N{\fs16}are the future of House Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:04.40,0:52:08.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,北境联盟会站在谁的身后？\N{\fs16}Who should the North rally behind?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:08.17,0:52:10.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是奈德与凯特琳·史塔克在临冬城\N{\fs16}A trueborn daughter of Ned and Catelyn Stark
Dialogue: 0,0:52:10.97,0:52:12.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,生下的嫡女\N{\fs16}born here at Winterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:52:12.97,0:52:16.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还是生于南方没有母亲的私生子？\N{\fs16}or a motherless bastard born in the south?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:42.64,0:52:44.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们就此别过吧\N{\fs16}This is where I leave you.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:44.97,0:52:46.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不跟我们一起走吗？\N{\fs16}You're not coming with us?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:48.24,0:52:51.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,长城不仅仅是冰和石头\N{\fs16}The Wall is not just ice and stone.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:51.74,0:52:54.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,古老的咒语被镌刻在它的地基之中\N{\fs16}Ancient spells were carved into its foundations.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:56.72,0:52:58.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,强大的魔法\N{\fs16}Strong magic
Dialogue: 0,0:52:58.88,0:53:02.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,以保护它身后的人们\N{\fs16}to protect men from what lies beyond.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:02.12,0:53:05.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只要它仍然矗立 死人就无法通过\N{\fs16}And while it stands, the dead cannot pass.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:06.06,0:53:07.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我就无法通过\N{\fs16}I cannot pass.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:23.78,0:53:25.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那你要去哪儿？\N{\fs16}Where will you go?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:25.81,0:53:27.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大战将至\N{\fs16}The great war is coming
Dialogue: 0,0:53:27.45,0:53:30.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而我依然为生灵而战\N{\fs16}and I still fight for the living.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:32.32,0:53:34.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会尽我所能···\N{\fs16}I'll do what I can...
Dialogue: 0,0:53:35.79,0:53:37.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,倾尽此生\N{\fs16}as long as I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:41.89,0:53:43.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谢谢你 班杨叔叔\N{\fs16}Thank you, Uncle Benjen.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:44.10,0:53:46.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,祝你们好运\N{\fs16}I wish you both good fortune.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:25.71,0:54:28.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你确定自己准备好了？\N{\fs16}Are you sure you're ready for this?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:28.34,0:54:31.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我现在是三眼乌鸦了\N{\fs16}I'm the Three-Eyed Raven now.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:31.54,0:54:33.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我必须为此做好准备\N{\fs16}I have to be ready for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:08.01,0:55:10.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奈德？\N{\fs16}Ned?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:10.12,0:55:12.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,莱安娜\N{\fs16}Lyanna.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:12.72,0:55:14.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是你吗？\N{\fs16}Is that you?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:18.59,0:55:20.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,真的是你吗？\N{\fs16}Is that really you?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:25.53,0:55:27.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不是在做梦吧？\N{\fs16}You're not a dream?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:28.57,0:55:30.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不 不是梦\N{\fs16}No, I'm not a dream.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:32.34,0:55:34.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我在这儿\N{\fs16}I'm here.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:35.88,0:55:37.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就在这里\N{\fs16}Right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:37.74,0:55:40.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我很想你 哥哥\N{\fs16}I've missed you, big brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:43.42,0:55:45.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我也很想你\N{\fs16}I've missed you, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:49.76,0:55:51.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我想要变得勇敢\N{\fs16}I want to be brave.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:54.29,0:55:56.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你很勇敢\N{\fs16}You are.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:56.90,0:55:59.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没有\N{\fs16}I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:01.83,0:56:04.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不想死\N{\fs16}I don't want to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:04.70,0:56:06.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是不会死的\N{\fs16}You're not going to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:10.74,0:56:12.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,给她端些水来！\N{\fs16}Get her some water!
Dialogue: 0,0:56:12.68,0:56:14.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 不 不要水 - 这里有学士吗？\N{\fs16}- No, no water. - Is there a maester?
Dialogue: 0,0:56:15.08,0:56:17.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,听我说 奈德\N{\fs16}Listen to me, Ned.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:23.82,0:56:26.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果劳勃发现 他会···\N{\fs16}If Robert finds out, he'll...
Dialogue: 0,0:56:26.66,0:56:28.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你知道他会的\N{\fs16}you know he will.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:28.63,0:56:30.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你必须保护他\N{\fs16}You have to protect him.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:33.57,0:56:35.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,向我保证 奈德\N{\fs16}Promise me, Ned.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:37.87,0:56:39.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,向我保证\N{\fs16}Promise me.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:51.88,0:56:53.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,向我保证 奈德\N{\fs16}Promise me, Ned.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:58.32,0:57:00.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,向我保证\N{\fs16}Promise me.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:30.69,0:57:33.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不能指望着谷地的骑士\N{\fs16}You can't expect Knights of the Vale
Dialogue: 0,0:57:33.69,0:57:36.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,与野人侵略者们并肩而战\N{\fs16}to side with wildling invaders.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:36.43,0:57:40.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们没有侵略 我们是被邀请的\N{\fs16}We didn't invade. We were invited.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:40.47,0:57:42.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我可没请\N{\fs16}Not by me.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:42.27,0:57:44.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,自由民 北方人\N{\fs16}The free folk, the northerners,
Dialogue: 0,0:57:44.17,0:57:46.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,以及谷地的骑士们共同英勇杀敌\N{\fs16}and the Knights of the Vale fought bravely,
Dialogue: 0,0:57:46.64,0:57:48.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,并肩奋战 方才取得胜利\N{\fs16}fought together, and we won.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:49.04,0:57:53.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我父亲曾经常说在战场上见真朋友\N{\fs16}My father used to say we find our true friends on the battlefield.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:53.88,0:57:56.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,波顿已败\N{\fs16}The Boltons are defeated.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:56.58,0:57:58.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,战争结束了\N{\fs16}The war is over.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:58.62,0:58:00.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,凛冬已至\N{\fs16}Winter has come.
Dialogue: 0,0:58:00.62,0:58:04.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果学士们是对的 那这将是一千年来最冷的冬天\N{\fs16}If the maesters are right, it'll be the coldest one in a thousand years.
Dialogue: 0,0:58:04.22,0:58:07.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们应该回家 做好抵御风暴的准备\N{\fs16}We should ride home and wait out the coming storms.
Dialogue: 0,0:58:07.76,0:58:09.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,战争尚未结束\N{\fs16}The war is not over.
Dialogue: 0,0:58:09.96,0:58:12.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我对你保证 朋友\N{\fs16}And I promise you, friend,
Dialogue: 0,0:58:12.10,0:58:15.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,真正的敌人不会等到风暴结束\N{\fs16}the true enemy won't wait out the storm.
Dialogue: 0,0:58:15.13,0:58:16.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他将带来风暴\N{\fs16}He brings the storm.
Dialogue: 0,0:58:36.62,0:58:40.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你儿子在红色婚礼上被人屠杀 曼德勒大人\N{\fs16}Your son was butchered at the Red Wedding, Lord Manderly,
Dialogue: 0,0:58:40.79,0:58:42.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但你拒绝了征召\N{\fs16}but you refused the call.
Dialogue: 0,0:58:45.97,0:58:48.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你发誓效忠史塔克家族 葛洛佛大人\N{\fs16}You swore allegiance to House Stark, Lord Glover,
Dialogue: 0,0:58:49.07,0:58:51.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但在他们最需要的时候\N{\fs16}but in their hour of greatest need,
Dialogue: 0,0:58:51.77,0:58:53.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你拒绝了征召\N{\fs16}you refused the call.
Dialogue: 0,0:58:55.87,0:58:57.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而你 赛文大人\N{\fs16}And you, Lord Cerwyn,
Dialogue: 0,0:58:58.01,0:59:01.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的父亲被拉姆斯·波顿活活剥皮\N{\fs16}your father was skinned alive by Ramsay Bolton.
Dialogue: 0,0:59:01.98,0:59:04.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你仍旧拒绝了征召\N{\fs16}Still you refused the call.
Dialogue: 0,0:59:07.55,0:59:11.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但莫尔蒙家族不忘\N{\fs16}But House Mormont remembers.
Dialogue: 0,0:59:11.52,0:59:14.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,北境不忘\N{\fs16}The North remembers.
Dialogue: 0,0:59:14.33,0:59:18.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,除史塔克之外再无北境之王\N{\fs16}We know no king but the King in the North whose name is Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:59:20.67,0:59:22.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不在乎他是否是私生子\N{\fs16}I don't care if he's a bastard.
Dialogue: 0,0:59:22.53,0:59:25.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他流着奈德·史塔克的血液\N{\fs16}Ned Stark's blood runs through his veins.
Dialogue: 0,0:59:25.24,0:59:29.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,从今天直到最后 他都是我的国王\N{\fs16}He's my king from this day until his last day.
Dialogue: 0,0:59:46.39,0:59:48.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,莫尔蒙小姐的话不中听\N{\fs16}Lady Mormont speaks harshly
Dialogue: 0,0:59:49.06,0:59:50.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,却是真话\N{\fs16}and truly.
Dialogue: 0,0:59:53.77,0:59:58.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的儿子为少狼主罗柏·史塔克而死\N{\fs16}My son died for Robb Stark, the Young Wolf.
Dialogue: 0,0:59:58.97,1:00:02.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我以为有生之年我们不会找到其他国王了\N{\fs16}I didn't think we'd find another king in my lifetime.
Dialogue: 0,1:00:02.14,1:00:04.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你需要时 我并没有派军队出征\N{\fs16}I didn't commit my men to your cause
Dialogue: 0,1:00:04.68,1:00:07.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为我不想更多曼德勒家族的人无谓送死\N{\fs16}'cause I didn't want more Manderlys dying for nothing.
Dialogue: 0,1:00:09.58,1:00:11.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我错了\N{\fs16}But I was wrong.
Dialogue: 0,1:00:16.76,1:00:18.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,琼恩·雪诺报了红色婚礼之仇\N{\fs16}Jon Snow avenged the Red Wedding.
Dialogue: 0,1:00:19.73,1:00:21.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他是白狼主\N{\fs16}He is the White Wolf.
Dialogue: 0,1:00:21.59,1:00:24.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,北境之王\N{\fs16}The King in the North.
Dialogue: 0,1:00:32.00,1:00:34.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没能与你并肩作战\N{\fs16}I did not fight beside you on the field
Dialogue: 0,1:00:34.57,1:00:38.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我将为此终生抱憾\N{\fs16}and I will regret that until my dying day.
Dialogue: 0,1:00:38.92,1:00:42.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一个人犯错时必须承认错误\N{\fs16}A man can only admit when he was wrong
Dialogue: 0,1:00:42.85,1:00:44.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,然后请求原谅\N{\fs16}and ask forgiveness.
Dialogue: 0,1:00:47.42,1:00:49.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没什么需要原谅的 大人\N{\fs16}There's nothing to forgive, my lord.
Dialogue: 0,1:00:52.32,1:00:54.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,更多的战斗即将接踵而至\N{\fs16}There will be more fights to come.
Dialogue: 0,1:00:54.93,1:00:58.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,葛洛佛家族将追随史塔克家族\N{\fs16}House Glover will stand behind House Stark
Dialogue: 0,1:00:58.56,1:01:00.86,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,正如千年来我们所做的一样\N{\fs16}as we have for a thousand years.
Dialogue: 0,1:01:02.70,1:01:04.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而我将站在琼恩·雪诺的身后……\N{\fs16}And I will stand behind Jon Snow...
Dialogue: 0,1:01:07.37,1:01:09.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,北境之王！\N{\fs16}the King in the North!
Dialogue: 0,1:01:11.34,1:01:14.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,北境之王！\N{\fs16}The King in the North!
Dialogue: 0,1:01:14.35,1:01:55.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,北境之王！北境之王！\N{\fs16}The King in the North! The King in the North!
Dialogue: 0,1:01:57.82,1:01:59.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,全军停下！\N{\fs16}Company halt!
Dialogue: 0,1:02:02.83,1:02:04.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,停下！\N{\fs16}Halt!
Dialogue: 0,1:02:06.17,1:02:08.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,停下！\N{\fs16}Halt!
Dialogue: 0,1:02:20.27,1:02:21.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,快！\N{\fs16}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,1:03:15.97,1:03:19.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我现在宣布 兰尼斯特家族的瑟曦\N{\fs16}I now proclaim Cersei of the House Lannister
Dialogue: 0,1:03:19.84,1:03:22.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,加冕为瑟曦·兰尼斯特一世\N{\fs16}First of Her Name,
Dialogue: 0,1:03:22.57,1:03:25.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,安达尔人和先民的女王\N{\fs16}Queen of the Andals and the First Men,
Dialogue: 0,1:03:26.04,1:03:29.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,七国统治者暨全境守护者\N{\fs16}Protector of the Seven Kingdoms.
Dialogue: 0,1:04:15.09,1:04:17.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女王万岁\N{\fs16}Long may she reign.
Dialogue: 0,1:04:17.26,1:04:19.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女王万岁\N{\fs16}Long may she reign.

