[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.0.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title:
Original Script:
Original Translation:
Original Timing:
Original Editing:
Script Updated By:
Update Details:
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 360
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
Scroll Position: 752
Active Line: 762
Video Zoom Percent: 0.75
Video File: Game.of.Thrones.S03E01.720p.HDTV.x264-EVOLVE.mkv
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
Video Aspect Ratio: c1.77778
Video Position: 73597
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: 片头介绍,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C2E0EC,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 正文,Microsoft YaHei,26,&H00C2E0EC,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 人物介绍+,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C2E0EC,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,4,10,10,10,1
Style: 人物介绍,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C2E0EC,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Default,SimHei,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.26,0:00:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快撤！\N{\fs16}Fall back!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.10,0:00:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(115.556,250.896)}{\pos(480,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}山姆威尔·塔利{\b0}\N{\fs12}守夜人事务官
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.61,0:01:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟？\N{\fs16}Brother?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.60,0:02:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(502.445,173.881)}{\pos(250,190)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}杰奥·莫尔蒙{\b0}\N{\fs12}守夜人总司令 “熊老”
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.66,0:02:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渡鸦送出去了么？\N{\fs16}Did you send the ravens?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.60,0:02:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着我 塔利\N{\fs16}Tarly, look at me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.84,0:02:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渡鸦送出去了么？\N{\fs16}Did you send the ravens?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.50,0:02:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(559.111,284.03)}{\pos(80,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}葛兰{\b0}\N{\fs12}守夜人游骑兵
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.50,0:02:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(390.667,290.298)}{\pos(300,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}“忧郁的”艾迪{\b0}\N{\fs12}守夜人事务官
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.50,0:02:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(154.223,289.402)}{\pos(300,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}雷斯特{\b0}\N{\fs12}守夜人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.81,0:02:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你的职责\N{\fs16}That was your job.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.98,0:02:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你唯一的职责\N{\fs16}Your only job.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.26,0:02:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得回长城去\N{\fs16}We need to get back to the Wall.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.96,0:03:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路途艰难\N{\fs16}It's a long march.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.63,0:03:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道将要面对什么\N{\fs16}We know what's out there,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.43,0:03:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我们必须赶回 必须发出警报\N{\fs16}but we have to make it,have to warn them{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.20,0:03:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则 在凛冬结束之前\N{\fs16}or before winter's done,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.07,0:03:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有你认识的人\N{\fs16}everyone you've ever known{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.27,0:03:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都会死\N{\fs16}will be dead.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.30,0:03:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\pos(320,305)}{\fs20}{\b1}{\bord0}{\c&HC2E0EC&}双语特效字幕\N{\b0}百度贴吧{\fs25}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\b1}衣柜字幕组{\fs16\b0}{\c&HC2E0EC&}\N{\b1}专注GOT剧集 华语冰火最专业字幕{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.80,0:03:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(395,183)}{\pos(420,265)}{\fs14}{\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1}{\c&HC2E0EC&}翻译{\fs22}    {\b1} 北落师门{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.10,0:03:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(382,265)}{\pos(390,320)}{\fs14}{\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1}{\c&HC2E0EC&}翻译{\fs22}   {\b1} barossa{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.80,0:03:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(175,264)}{\pos(140,325)}{\fs14}{\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1}{\c&HC2E0EC&}翻译{\fs22}   {\b1} 美少年天银石\N{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.60,0:03:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)}{\frx360}{\t(20,200,\frx0)}{\pos(320,250)}{\fs25\b1}君临{\fs12\b0} King's Landing
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.90,0:03:33.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(354,105)}{\pos(170,160)}{\fs14}{\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1}{\c&HC2E0EC&}翻译{\fs22}   {\b1} 泰温公爵\N{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.60,0:03:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)}{\fs25\b1}{\move(380,235,380,240)}红堡
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.60,0:03:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)}{\fs12\b0} {\move(425,245,425,235)}Red Keep
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.70,0:03:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(153,256)}{\pos(420,295)}{\fs14}{\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1}{\c&HC2E0EC&}校对{\fs22}   {\b1} 旧镇老翁{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.60,0:03:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)}{\frx45\t(\frx0)\t(700\fry20)}{\move(400,240,450,240,50,10)}{\fs26\b1}龙石岛{\fs17\b0} Dragonstone
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.40,0:03:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(183,224)}{\pos(250,160)}{\fs14}{\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1}{\c&HC2E0EC&}校对{\fs22}   {\b1} 临冬城的狮子\N{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.40,0:03:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)}{\frx45\t(\frx0)\t(700\fry20)}{\move(400,220,450,220,50,10)}{\fs26\b1}赫伦堡{\fs17\b0} Harrenhal
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.10,0:04:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(477,225)}{\pos(240,300)}{\fs14}{\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1}{\c&HC2E0EC&}复校{\fs22}   {\b1} 托曼·兰尼斯特  守誓剑{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.30,0:04:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(214,256)}{\pos(410,270)}{\fs14}{\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1}{\c&HC2E0EC&}复校{\fs22}   {\b1}艾莉娅的缝衣针  FuriousFurion\N{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.40,0:04:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)}{\frx25}{\pos(340,190)}{\fs25\b1}临冬城{\fs12\b0} Winterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.70,0:04:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(137,277)}{\pos(430,300)}{\fs14}{\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1}{\c&HC2E0EC&}精校{\fs22}  {\b1} 龙的命根子{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.10,0:04:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(391,146)}{\pos(170,205)}{\fs14}{\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1}{\c&HC2E0EC&}监制{\fs22}   {\b1} 临冬城的狮子 北落师门\N{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.80,0:04:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(120,249)}{\pos(340,275)}{\fs14}{\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1}{\c&HC2E0EC&}后期{\fs22}   {\b1}poplar{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.90,0:04:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(355,123)}{\pos(210,280)}{\fs14}{\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1}{\c&HC2E0EC&}策划{\fs22}   {\b1} baozhenyuawabi{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.30,0:04:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(142,240)}{\pos(430,150)}{\fs14}{\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1}{\c&HC2E0EC&}特别顾问{\fs22}   {\b1}屈畅(ccxx){\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.10,0:04:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)}{\frx45}{\move(340,240,340,240)}{\fs25} {\b1}绝境长城{\fs12\b0} the Wall
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.60,0:04:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}{\move(340,240,340,180)}{\fs25} {\b1}绝境长城{\fs12\b0} the Wall
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.70,0:04:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}{\pos(320,320)}{\fs25}{\c&HC2E0EC&}最专业的华语冰火资料站：冰与火之歌中文维基{\b0}\N{\fs20\c&HFFFFFF&} http://zh.asoiaf.wikia.com/
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.80,0:04:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)} {\pos(240,225)}{\fs18} 百度冰与火之歌贴吧  &  百度权力的游戏贴吧   {\fs12} 联合出品
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.90,0:04:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(412,244)}{\frx45\t(\frx0)}{\pos(200,140)}{\fs25} {\b1}阿斯塔波{\fs12\b0}Astapor
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.80,0:04:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(484,269)}{\pos(400,240)}{\fs12} {\c&HC2E0EC&}根据长篇小说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.80,0:04:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(538,296)} {\pos(450,270)}{\fs24}《{\b1}冰与火之歌{\b0}》{\fs12} 改编
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.80,0:04:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(576,319)} {\pos(540,295)}{\fs12} 原著 {\fs20} 乔治·R·R·马丁
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.86,0:04:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fe134}{\fad(500,500)}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\pos(320,285)}{\fs25} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord0}{\c&H24EFFF&\fn微软雅黑\fs24}权力的游戏{\c&H24EFFF&}\N{\fe134}{\fn微软雅黑}{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}第三季 第一集\N{\fscy100}{\fe134}{\fn微软雅黑}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\fs20}衣柜字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.40,0:05:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}{\pos(335,235)}{\fs18}{\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1}{\c&HC2E0EC&}{\fs12}第一集 {\fs18} "Valar Dohaeris"\N{\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.10,0:05:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)}{\pos(580,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}叮当衫{\b0}\N{\fs12} 野人 “骸骨之王”
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.90,0:05:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(442.222,260)}{\pos(300,260)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}琼恩·雪诺{\b0}\N{\fs12}守夜人事务官
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.90,0:05:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(172.222,254.478)}{\pos(470,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}耶哥蕊特{\b0}\N{\fs12} 野人 “火吻而生”
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.02,0:06:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是第一次见到巨人吧 琼恩·雪诺？\N{\fs16}First time you've seen a giant, Jon Snow?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.59,0:06:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过可别盯太久 他们害羞得很\N{\fs16}Well, don't stare too long.They're shy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.43,0:06:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等害羞的劲儿过去了 他们可要生气了\N{\fs16}When they stop being shy,they get angry.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.93,0:06:24.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦他们开始生气了\N{\fs16}And when they're angry,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.10,0:06:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会像砸钉子一样把人砸到地上\N{\fs16}I've seen them pound a man straight into the ground{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.24,0:06:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是我可亲眼见过的\N{\fs16}like a hammer on a nail.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.95,0:06:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 是乌鸦！ - 乌鸦！\N{\fs16}- Crow! - Crow!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.58,0:06:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 看那边！ - 乌鸦！\N{\fs16}- Look over there! - Crow!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.72,0:06:47.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乌鸦！看呐！快看！\N{\fs16}Crow! Look over here!Look!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.59,0:06:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 看呐 乌鸦过来了！\N{\fs16}Ah, look, crow coming!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.76,0:06:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乌鸦！\N{\fs16}Crow!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.03,0:06:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你穿错衣服了\N{\fs16}You're wearing the wrong color.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.90,0:06:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼斯曾经是个游骑兵\N{\fs16}Mance was a ranger.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.40,0:07:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们乌鸦从心底渴望自由飞翔\N{\fs16}In your hearts, all you crows want to fly free.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.57,0:07:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我成了自由人 是否有离开的自由？\N{\fs16}When I'm free,will I be free to go?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.51,0:07:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 乌鸦！ - 乌鸦！\N{\fs16}- Crow! - Crow!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.54,0:07:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然可以\N{\fs16}Sure, you will.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.88,0:07:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊！\N{\fs16}Oh!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.11,0:07:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我也有猎杀你的自由\N{\fs16}And I'll be free to kill you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.35,0:07:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这帮小子无法无天\N{\fs16}Got no respect, this lot.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.65,0:07:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他们犯错的时候可没有父亲扇他们耳光\N{\fs16}Got no fathers to slap 'em when they're foul.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.86,0:07:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们的父亲怎么了？\N{\fs16}What happened to their fathers?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.73,0:07:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些死在你们这些乌鸦手上\N{\fs16}Some of them were killed by crows like you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.87,0:07:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脸色别这么难看啊 琼恩·雪诺\N{\fs16}Don't look so grim, Jon Snow.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.97,0:07:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是曼斯·雷德喜欢你 你自然可以多活一两天\N{\fs16}If Mance Rayder likes you,you'll live another day.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.04,0:07:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是他不喜欢……\N{\fs16}And if he don't...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.50,0:08:03.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我闻到了乌鸦的气味\N{\fs16}I smell a crow.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.20,0:08:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们杀了他的同伴\N{\fs16}We killed his friends.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.40,0:08:07.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻思着你可能想问这家伙点什么\N{\fs16}Thought you'd want to question this one.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.44,0:08:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一只乌鸦宝宝能问出什么来？\N{\fs16}What do we want with a baby crow?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.37,0:08:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这只乌鸦宝宝杀了断掌科林\N{\fs16}This baby killed Qhorin Halfhand.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.34,0:08:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想加入我们\N{\fs16}He wants to be one of us.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.05,0:08:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那断手的杂种杀了我的朋友\N{\fs16}That half - handed cunt killed friends of mine.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.29,0:08:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身形都有你两倍大\N{\fs16}Friends twice your size.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.59,0:08:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲说过 只要你一剑穿心\N{\fs16}My father told me big men fall just as quick as little ones{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.30,0:08:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大个子和小个子一样 眨眼就死\N{\fs16}if you put a sword through their hearts.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.80,0:08:39.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有不少小个子\N{\fs16}Plenty of little men{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.67,0:08:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要拿剑穿了我的心\N{\fs16}tried to put their swords through my heart.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.64,0:08:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今他们的小骨头\N{\fs16}And there's plenty of little skeletons{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.44,0:08:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都被埋在林子里了\N{\fs16}buried in the woods.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.88,0:08:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 小子 你叫什么？ - 琼恩·雪诺\N{\fs16}- What's your name, boy? - Jon Snow.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.12,0:09:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下\N{\fs16}Your Grace.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.69,0:09:05.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下？\N{\fs16}Your Grace?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.16,0:09:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听见了没？\N{\fs16}Did you hear that?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.86,0:09:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从今以后 我放屁的时候你们最好跪下来\N{\fs16}From now on, you'd better kneel every time I fart.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.97,0:09:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起来吧 孩子\N{\fs16}Stand, boy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.51,0:09:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长城之外 我们不向任何人下跪\N{\fs16}We don't kneel for anyone beyond the Wall.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.25,0:09:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 你就是奈德·史塔克的私生子\N{\fs16}So, you're Ned Stark's bastard.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.42,0:09:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你的礼物 骸骨之王\N{\fs16}Thank you for the gift,Lord of Bones.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.59,0:09:31.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以走了\N{\fs16}You can leave us.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.76,0:09:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那姑娘喜欢你\N{\fs16}The girl likes you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.60,0:09:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢她么 雪诺？\N{\fs16}You like her back, Snow?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.80,0:09:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为了这个加入我们的？\N{\fs16}That why you want to join us?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.20,0:09:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别慌张 小子\N{\fs16}Don't panic, boy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.01,0:09:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天杀的守夜人让你戒掉女色\N{\fs16}This isn't the damned Night's Watch{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.24,0:09:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们这儿可没这套\N{\fs16}where we make you swear off girls.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.48,0:09:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才被你误认成我的那个在吃鸡的是“巨人克星”托蒙德\N{\fs16}This chicken eater you thought was king is Tormund Giantsbane.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.18,0:09:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不相信\N{\fs16}Can't believe this pup{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.65,0:10:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小崽子能杀了断掌\N{\fs16}killed the Halfhand.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.99,0:10:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我们的敌人\N{\fs16}He was our enemy{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.40,0:10:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(406.889,202.538)}{\pos(470,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}曼斯·雷德{\b0}\N{\fs12} 野人首领 “塞外之王”
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.22,0:10:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他死了我很高兴\N{\fs16}and I'm glad he's dead.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.87,0:10:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他曾是我的兄弟\N{\fs16}He was my brother once.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.60,0:10:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时他的手还没断\N{\fs16}Back when he had a whole hand.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.84,0:10:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么跟着他的？\N{\fs16}What were you doing with him?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.30,0:10:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(523.333,271.493)}{\pos(470,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}托蒙德{\b0}\N{\fs12} 野人掠袭者 “巨人克星”
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.84,0:10:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,司令大人把我派到断掌手下锻炼\N{\fs16}The Lord Commander sent me to the Halfhand for seasoning.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.18,0:10:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？\N{\fs16}Why?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.05,0:10:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想让我有朝一日可以独挡一面\N{\fs16}He wants me to lead one day.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.85,0:10:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你却在这里 成了叛徒\N{\fs16}But here you are, a traitor{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.35,0:10:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跪在塞外之王的脚下\N{\fs16}kneeling before the King - beyond - the - Wall.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.89,0:10:41.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我是叛徒 那你也一样\N{\fs16}If I'm a traitor, then you are, too.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.70,0:10:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要加入我们 琼恩·雪诺？\N{\fs16}Why do you want to join us, Jon Snow?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.01,0:10:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要自由\N{\fs16}I want to be free.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.01,0:11:03.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 恐怕不是\N{\fs16}No, I don't think so.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.42,0:11:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看你真正想要的\N{\fs16}I think what you want most of all{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.38,0:11:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是逞英雄\N{\fs16}is to be a hero.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.62,0:11:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我问你最后一次\N{\fs16}I'll ask you one last time{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.59,0:11:15.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要加入我们？\N{\fs16}why do you want to join us?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.03,0:11:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们北上的时候停在卡斯特的堡垒\N{\fs16}We stopped at Craster's Keep on the way north.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.10,0:11:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看见……\N{\fs16}I saw...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.57,0:11:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看见什么？\N{\fs16}You saw what?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.44,0:11:33.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看见卡斯特把他的亲生儿子\N{\fs16}I saw Craster take his own baby boy{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.54,0:11:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遗弃在森林里\N{\fs16}and leave it in the woods.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.31,0:11:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看见有东西带走了它\N{\fs16}I saw what took it.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.12,0:11:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说你看见它们中的一个？\N{\fs16}You're telling me you saw one of them?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.06,0:11:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么是什么让你舍弃了你的弟兄？\N{\fs16}And why would that make you desert your brothers?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.60,0:11:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我告诉司令大人的时候\N{\fs16}Because when I told the Lord Commander,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.70,0:11:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他早已经知道了\N{\fs16}he already knew.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.67,0:12:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万年以前\N{\fs16}Thousands of years ago, the First Men{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.34,0:12:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先民曾跟异鬼战斗 而且击败了他们\N{\fs16}battled the White Walkers and defeated them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.71,0:12:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想加入愿为生者而战的阵营\N{\fs16}I want to fight for the side that fights for the living.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.75,0:12:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来对了么？\N{\fs16}Did I come to the right place?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.72,0:12:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得给你找件新斗篷\N{\fs16}We'll need to find you a new cloak.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.10,0:12:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(535.111,241.94)}{\pos(280,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}波隆{\b0}\N{\fs12}佣兵
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.61,0:12:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那条布摘了怎么样？\N{\fs16}What if you took off that bit there?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.95,0:12:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就不打算留一点想象的空间？\N{\fs16}Don't you want to leave something to the imagination?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.59,0:12:54.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题是 我实在缺乏想象力\N{\fs16}Trouble is, I've never had much imagination.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.06,0:12:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你来脱好了\N{\fs16}I want you to take it off.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.97,0:13:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用嘴\N{\fs16}Mouth.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.44,0:13:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波隆爵士 波隆爵士\N{\fs16}Ser Bronn. Ser Bronn.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.51,0:13:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都没听见\N{\fs16}I didn't hear that.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.30,0:13:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(347.778,185.373)}{\pos(250,240)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}波德瑞克·派恩{\b0}\N{\fs12}提利昂的侍从
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.52,0:13:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 抱歉 爵士 - 退出去\N{\fs16}- Apologies, ser. - Back away.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.55,0:13:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫你往后退 退到屋子外面\N{\fs16}Keep backing away till you're outside this establishment.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.52,0:13:29.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 然后再后退一点 - 提利昂大人派我来\N{\fs16}- Then back away some more. - Lord Tyrion sent me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.19,0:13:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要剁了你 小子\N{\fs16}I will murder you, boy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.19,0:13:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说这事关乎生死\N{\fs16}He said it was a matter of life and death.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.51,0:13:54.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 波德？ - 我是你姐姐\N{\fs16}- Pod? - It's your sister.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.10,0:13:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)}{\pos(180,200)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}提利昂·兰尼斯特{\b0}\N{\fs12}“小恶魔”
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.95,0:13:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太后\N{\fs16}The queen.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.10,0:14:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(383.111,244.179)}{\pos(320,280)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}瑟曦·兰尼斯特{\b0}\N{\fs12}摄政太后
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.07,0:14:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们来干嘛的？\N{\fs16}What are they doing here?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.37,0:14:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是保护我吧 不让我进去么？\N{\fs16}Protecting me, I assume.Will you let me in?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.01,0:14:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 你不能进来\N{\fs16}No, I don't think so.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.44,0:14:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我想杀了你\N{\fs16}If I wanted to kill you,do you think{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.18,0:14:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得这堵木头门能挡着我？\N{\fs16}I'd let a wooden door stop me?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.85,0:14:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不能进来\N{\fs16}They stay outside.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.39,0:14:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不怕你 小弟弟\N{\fs16}I'm not afraid of you,little brother.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.64,0:14:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你来干嘛？ - 我来看看你的脸\N{\fs16}- Why are you here? - I wanted to see your face.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.07,0:14:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说你的鼻子没了 现在看来没那么恐怖\N{\fs16}They said you'd lost your nose, but it's not as gruesome as all that.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.98,0:14:58.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砍我鼻子的那个人没的可不止鼻子\N{\fs16}The man who cut me lost more than his nose.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.15,0:15:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但愿如此\N{\fs16}I should hope so.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.55,0:15:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些叛徒想要乔佛里的脑袋 却丢了他们自己的\N{\fs16}The rebels came for Joffrey's head, they lost their own.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.89,0:15:05.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是父亲的功劳\N{\fs16}Thanks to Father.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.99,0:15:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是父亲的功劳\N{\fs16}Thanks to Father.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.96,0:15:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然，要杀我的可不是个叛徒\N{\fs16}Of course, it wasn't a rebel who tried to kill me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.10,0:15:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是？怪了\N{\fs16}No? Curious.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.66,0:15:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这国王之手的房间可真够寒酸的\N{\fs16}Bit of a comedown from chamber of the Hand.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.50,0:15:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过反正太大的房间你也用不着\N{\fs16}But then I don't suppose you need much room.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.74,0:15:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大学士派席尔也这么取笑过我\N{\fs16}Grand Maester Pycelle made the same joke.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.74,0:15:27.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定特别骄傲 能和蛋都垂到膝盖的老头一样招笑\N{\fs16}You must be proud to be as funny as a man whose balls brush his knees.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.08,0:15:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今天要跟父亲见面？\N{\fs16}You're meeting Father today?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.88,0:15:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道\N{\fs16}How do you know that?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.98,0:15:33.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有很多密探\N{\fs16}Because I have hundreds of spies in my employ.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.85,0:15:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情报总管刚好欠我几个人情\N{\fs16}The Master of Whisperers owes me a favor or two.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.96,0:15:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲跟我说了 你到底想要什么？\N{\fs16}Father told me. What do you want from him?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.03,0:15:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要什么？ 他可是我父亲\N{\fs16}What do I want from him? He's my father.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.69,0:15:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我用得着要什么吗？\N{\fs16}Do I need to want something?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.76,0:15:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信他深爱我\N{\fs16}I'm sure he loves me dearly,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.90,0:15:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像任何一个父亲深爱他的\N{\fs16}as any father loves his child,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.64,0:15:55.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝儿子\N{\fs16}his baby boy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.34,0:15:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是自从来到君临\N{\fs16}Yet he hasn't come to visit once{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.47,0:15:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一次都没来看过我\N{\fs16}since arriving in King's Landing.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.11,0:16:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的脸被劈成两半 躺在床上奄奄一息\N{\fs16}I lay here, my face split in half,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.28,0:16:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他都没来看过我\N{\fs16}but Father never came.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.92,0:16:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的我都要哭了\N{\fs16}You're going to make me cry.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.39,0:16:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么想知道我对他的要求？\N{\fs16}Why do you care what I want from him?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.22,0:16:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你曾在父亲面前造谣\N{\fs16}Because you've slandered me to Father before.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.29,0:16:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,造谣？什么时候？\N{\fs16}Slandered? When?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.56,0:16:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟他说我在凯岩城的时候\N{\fs16}You told him I had my guards{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.83,0:16:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾命令卫兵殴打侍女\N{\fs16}beat that servant girl at Casterly Rock.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.73,0:16:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确实让卫兵打了她\N{\fs16}You did have your guards beat her.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.60,0:16:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个只有九岁的小女孩\N{\fs16}A girl of nine, I believe.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.87,0:16:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那会儿我也才九岁\N{\fs16}I was nine, too.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.70,0:16:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没记错的话 她为此瞎了一只眼\N{\fs16}She lost an eye, if I remember correctly.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.77,0:16:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没记错的话\N{\fs16}If I remember correctly,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.21,0:16:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她以后再也不敢偷项链了\N{\fs16}she never stole a necklace again.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.14,0:16:40.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事是真的 就不算造谣\N{\fs16}It's not slander if it's true.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.08,0:16:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你今天又想跟父亲说什么真话？\N{\fs16}And what's this truth you plan on telling him today?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.82,0:16:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我要跟父亲说的话\N{\fs16}Why are you so nervous{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.58,0:16:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会让你这么不安？\N{\fs16}about what I'm going to say to Father?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.85,0:16:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你是个骗子\N{\fs16}Because you're a liar.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.96,0:16:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定会说我和乔佛里的坏话\N{\fs16}I expect you'll tell lies about me, about Joffrey.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.06,0:16:54.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如？\N{\fs16}Any lies in particular?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.26,0:16:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是挺聪明\N{\fs16}You're a clever man,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.73,0:17:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是比你自己想的可差远了\N{\fs16}but you're not half as clever as you think you are.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.04,0:17:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也比你聪明多了\N{\fs16}Still makes me more clever than you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.58,0:17:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看这俩金光闪闪的勇士哟\N{\fs16}Oh, look at these two shining warriors.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.91,0:17:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特林·马兰爵士还有这个…\N{\fs16}Ser Taryn Mant and...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.42,0:17:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁他妈关心是什么骑士\N{\fs16}Ser Whosit of Whocares.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.30,0:17:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(238.111,202.179)}{\pos(320,280)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}马林·特兰{\b0}\N{\fs12}御林铁卫
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.18,0:17:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马林·特兰 爵士\N{\fs16}Ser Meryn Trant.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.59,0:17:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在下是黑水河的波隆爵士\N{\fs16}Ser Bronn of the Blackwater.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.16,0:17:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你不是骑士 - 波德\N{\fs16}- You're no knight. - Pod.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.79,0:17:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑水河的波隆爵士\N{\fs16}Ser Bronn of the Blackwater{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.26,0:17:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是国王陛下亲自册封的\N{\fs16}was anointed by the king himself.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.23,0:17:28.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不过是个一夜暴富的恶棍罢了\N{\fs16}You're an up - jumped cutthroat,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.93,0:17:30.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅此而已\N{\fs16}nothing more.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.57,0:17:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的没错\N{\fs16}That's exactly who I am.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.54,0:17:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你就是个穿着华丽盔甲的蛆\N{\fs16}And you're a grub in fancy armor{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.34,0:17:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起打仗 我看你更擅长殴打小女孩\N{\fs16}who's better at beating little girls than fighting men.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.64,0:17:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在嘛 我跟提利昂大人约好了\N{\fs16}Now, I have an appointment with Lord Tyrion.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.44,0:17:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你敢碰一下门\N{\fs16}You put your hand on that door,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.31,0:17:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就砍了你的手\N{\fs16}you lose the hand.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.73,0:18:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不仅享受阳光下的散步 大人\N{\fs16}As much as I appreciate a walk in the sunshine, your lordship,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.47,0:18:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还很想知道你为什么要叫我来\N{\fs16}I am wondering why you sent for me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.64,0:18:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这城市里想杀我的人不计其数\N{\fs16}A number of people in this city want to kill me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.77,0:18:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你却在保护我\N{\fs16}You're here to protect me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.11,0:18:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这活我可干了挺久\N{\fs16}I've been doing that for a while now.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.34,0:18:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这活没让你变得人见人烦么\N{\fs16}Do you grow bored protecting me?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.14,0:18:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这活只让我变穷了\N{\fs16}I grow poor protecting you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.64,0:18:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穷？ 穷？\N{\fs16}Poor? Poor?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.61,0:18:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可是在我的照顾下才成为骑士的\N{\fs16}Under my patronage you've become a knight,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.68,0:18:21.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在都是都城守备队的队长了\N{\fs16}you've served as Commander of the City Watch.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.78,0:18:24.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 废话少说 - 你肯定没少中饱私囊\N{\fs16}- Briefly. - I'm sure you filled your pockets.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.55,0:18:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我可是身无分文\N{\fs16}And now my pockets are empty.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.66,0:18:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是让我尝了点甜头\N{\fs16}You've given me a taste for the finer things.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.03,0:18:31.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你要是还想继续被保护的话\N{\fs16}And if you want me to carry on protecting you,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.06,0:18:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就得出更高价才行\N{\fs16}you'll need to pay more.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.43,0:18:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我还以为咱俩是朋友呢 - 确实是\N{\fs16}- I thought we were friends. - We are.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.93,0:18:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我是个佣兵 我的武力是用来出售的\N{\fs16}But I'm a sellsword. I sell my sword.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.73,0:18:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不是用来帮朋友的\N{\fs16}I don't loan it out to friends as a favor.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.54,0:18:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 开价吧 - 双倍\N{\fs16}- How much? - Double.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.00,0:18:43.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 双倍？ - 我现在可是骑士了\N{\fs16}- Double? - I'm a knight now.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.21,0:18:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑士可值双倍的价儿\N{\fs16}Knights are worth double.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.67,0:18:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我连自己现在正付你多少都不知道\N{\fs16}I don't even know how much I'm paying you now.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.08,0:18:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这正说明你完全付得起\N{\fs16}Which means you can afford it.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.10,0:19:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(157.334,254.477)}{\pos(200,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}戴佛斯·席渥斯{\b0}\N{\fs12}“洋葱骑士”
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.18,0:19:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿，在这儿！\N{\fs16}Here. Here!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.03,0:19:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救救我！\N{\fs16}Help me!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.19,0:20:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁？\N{\fs16}Who are you?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.02,0:20:11.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾参与过黑水河之战\N{\fs16}I was in the battle at Blackwater.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.50,0:20:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个船长 也是个骑士\N{\fs16}I was a captain and a knight.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.30,0:20:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爵士 你效忠哪个国王？\N{\fs16}Aye, ser, and serving which king?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.74,0:20:28.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维斯特洛唯一的真王 - -\N{\fs16}The one true king of Westeros - -{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.15,0:20:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史坦尼斯·拜拉席恩\N{\fs16}Stannis Baratheon.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.76,0:20:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你死了\N{\fs16}I thought you were dead.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.43,0:20:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都是这么想的\N{\fs16}Everyone thought you were dead.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.30,0:20:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(157.334,254.477)}{\pos(200,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}萨拉多·桑恩{\b0}\N{\fs12}里斯海盗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.37,0:20:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你儿子呢？\N{\fs16}And your son?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.41,0:21:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可能像你一样游上岸了\N{\fs16}He may have swam ashore as you did.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.84,0:21:03.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 我眼睁睁看着他死于野火\N{\fs16}No, the wildfire took him. I saw it.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.39,0:21:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很遗憾 老友\N{\fs16}I'm so sorry, my friend.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.66,0:21:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也曾失去一个儿子\N{\fs16}I, too, have lost a son.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.23,0:21:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是世界上最糟糕的事儿\N{\fs16}There is nothing worse in this world.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.27,0:21:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 戴佛斯 你是个好父亲\N{\fs16}But, Davos, you were a good father.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.54,0:21:30.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我真的是好父亲 他就不会死\N{\fs16}If I was a good father, he'd still be here.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.04,0:21:34.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史坦尼斯还活着？\N{\fs16}Stannis lives?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.71,0:21:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在龙石岛舔伤口呢\N{\fs16}He licks his wounds at Dragonstone.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.95,0:21:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会带我过去吗？\N{\fs16}Will you take me there?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.75,0:21:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龙石岛对我来说啥都不剩了\N{\fs16}There is nothing for me at Dragonstone.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.18,0:21:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战争还没结束\N{\fs16}This war is not over.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.68,0:21:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说 也许\N{\fs16}Not for you, maybe.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.05,0:21:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是对于萨拉多·桑恩 战争到此为止了\N{\fs16}But for Salladhor Saan, the war is over.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.82,0:21:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都曾宣誓效忠于史坦尼斯陛下\N{\fs16}We're both sworn to King Stannis.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.86,0:21:51.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不效忠于任何人\N{\fs16}I am sworn to no man.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.36,0:21:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我承诺提供30艘船 你们则承诺给我荣华富贵\N{\fs16}I promised you 30 ships and you promised me riches and glory.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.20,0:21:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给了船\N{\fs16}I delivered the ships.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.73,0:21:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史坦尼斯从不放弃 从不\N{\fs16}Stannis never gives up. Never.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.93,0:22:01.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 他将从新组织—— - 他已经输了\N{\fs16}- Now he will regroup - - - He's a broken man.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.37,0:22:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的舰队在黑水湾全军覆没\N{\fs16}His fleet lies at the bottom of Blackwater Bay.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.87,0:22:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说他谁都不见——\N{\fs16}They say he sees no one - -{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.54,0:22:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的将士 甚至他的妻子\N{\fs16}not his generals, not even his wife.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.81,0:22:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只剩下那个红袍女\N{\fs16}Only the Red Woman{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.85,0:22:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他耳边瞎嘀咕\N{\fs16}whispering in his ear,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.25,0:22:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼扯些火焰中的影像\N{\fs16}telling him what she sees in the flames{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.12,0:22:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不就是火烧大活人\N{\fs16}and burning men alive.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.79,0:22:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？\N{\fs16}What?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.26,0:22:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史坦尼斯归来后点了场大火\N{\fs16}They built a great fire when Stannis returned.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.79,0:22:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有反对她的人都被称为\N{\fs16}All those who spoke against her she called{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.73,0:22:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暗黑仆人\N{\fs16}servants of darkness.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.30,0:22:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传说她边吟唱边烧那些人\N{\fs16}They say she sang to them as they burned.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.64,0:22:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个海盗\N{\fs16}I'm a pirate.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.18,0:22:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个走私贩子\N{\fs16}You're a smuggler.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.51,0:22:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暗黑仆人\N{\fs16}Servants of darkness.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.21,0:22:45.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒觉得龙石岛才是我们得避开的地方\N{\fs16}I'm thinking Dragonstone is a good place for us to avoid.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.52,0:22:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带我回去 求你\N{\fs16}Take me back there, please.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.82,0:22:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又不能让史坦尼斯反对她\N{\fs16}You cannot turn Stannis against her.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.75,0:22:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许不能 但是我可以杀了她\N{\fs16}Maybe not, but I could carve her heart out.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.42,0:22:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以试试看\N{\fs16}You could try.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.06,0:22:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是失败了 他们会烧了你\N{\fs16}If you fail, they will burn you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.46,0:22:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是成功了 他们还是会烧了你\N{\fs16}If you succeed, they'll burn you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.36,0:23:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你才刚捡了条命\N{\fs16}And you've only just come back to life.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.53,0:23:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再活久点儿吧 老友\N{\fs16}Stay alive a little longer, my friend.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.80,0:23:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫我老友 你我在我婚礼上喝得大醉一场\N{\fs16}You call me friend. You drank with me on my wedding day.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.57,0:23:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还跟我在我的4次婚礼上大醉4场呐\N{\fs16}And you drank with me on four of my wedding days,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.07,0:23:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我从没求你帮过忙\N{\fs16}but I don't ask you for favors.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.01,0:23:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须阻止她\N{\fs16}I have to stop her.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.64,0:23:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 帮我这个忙\N{\fs16}Please, do this for me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.62,0:23:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是死了\N{\fs16}When you are dead,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.02,0:23:23.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就把你的骨头装在个小袋子里\N{\fs16}I will gather your bones in a little sack{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.49,0:23:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好让你那可怜的寡妇挂在脖子上\N{\fs16}and let your widow wear them around her neck.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.54,0:23:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得在距离赫伦堡1000米的地方设下包围圈\N{\fs16}We should set the siege lines 1,000 yards from Harrenhal.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.60,0:23:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(96.621,161.607)}{\pos(200,280)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}罗柏·史塔克{\b0}\N{\fs12}北境之王
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.60,0:23:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(528.423,157.907)}{\pos(380,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}卢斯·波顿{\b0}\N{\fs12}恐怖堡伯爵
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.84,0:23:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用包围 魔山守不了一片废墟\N{\fs16}There won't be a siege. The Mountain can't defend a ruin.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.64,0:23:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想只要泰温·兰尼斯特下令\N{\fs16}I imagine the Mountain will defend{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.18,0:23:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是哪魔山都会抵抗到底\N{\fs16}whatever Tywin Lannister tells him to defend.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.08,0:23:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从牛津之战后 兰尼斯特就一直在和我们捉迷藏\N{\fs16}The Lannisters have been running from us since Oxcross.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.28,0:23:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想战斗 男人都想要场光明正大的战斗\N{\fs16}I'd love a fight. The men would love a fight.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.02,0:23:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕咱们是得不到了\N{\fs16}I don't think we're going to get one.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.30,0:24:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(487.423,271.907)}{\pos(380,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}瑞卡德·卡史塔克{\b0}\N{\fs12}卡霍城伯爵
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.77,0:24:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,200个北方人被人像羊一样屠宰\N{\fs16}200 Northmen slaughtered like sheep.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.21,0:24:52.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这命债我们一定要讨回来 朋友\N{\fs16}The debt will be repaid, my friend.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.25,0:24:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了他们 也为了你的儿子\N{\fs16}For them and for your sons.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.08,0:24:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是么？\N{\fs16}Will it?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.32,0:24:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在泥巴里腐烂\N{\fs16}They rot in the ground{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.65,0:25:01.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶手却逃之夭夭\N{\fs16}while their killer runs free.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.89,0:25:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弑君者不会自由很久的\N{\fs16}The Kingslayer won't remain free for long.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.86,0:25:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经派出最好的人去追他了\N{\fs16}My best hunters are after him.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.10,0:25:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(407.922,169.967)}{\pos(250,280)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}凯特琳·徒利{\b0}\N{\fs12}艾德·史塔克的遗孀
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.38,0:25:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 一个梅利斯特？ - 杰米爵士\N{\fs16}- A Mallister? - Ser Jeremy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.38,0:25:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲的人\N{\fs16}My father's bannerman.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.21,0:25:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找间屋子把她关起来\N{\fs16}Find her a chamber that will serve as a cell.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.50,0:26:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(79.852,268.904)}{\pos(480,300)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}泰丽莎{\b0}\N{\fs12}罗柏的王后
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.49,0:26:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是你母亲\N{\fs16}She's your mother.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.89,0:26:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她放跑了詹姆·兰尼斯特\N{\fs16}She freed Jaime Lannister.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.56,0:26:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰尼斯特夺走了他们的儿子\N{\fs16}The Lannisters robbed them of their sons{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.96,0:26:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而她 则夺走了他们的正义\N{\fs16}and she robbed them of their justice.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.80,0:26:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水\N{\fs16}Water.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.24,0:26:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水\N{\fs16}Water.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.91,0:26:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这伤口需要清洗缝合\N{\fs16}This needs to be cleaned and closed.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.71,0:26:32.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫什么 朋友？\N{\fs16}What's your name, friend?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.92,0:26:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科本\N{\fs16}Qyburn.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.82,0:26:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能活下来真幸运\N{\fs16}You're lucky to be alive.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.39,0:26:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸运？\N{\fs16}Lucky?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.15,0:26:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\frz-35\fn微软雅黑\fs20\pos(553,68)}…先发制人…扫荡整片森林…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.15,0:26:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\frz-35\fn微软雅黑\fs20\pos(479,106)}…想在我们的地盘上捡漏…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.15,0:26:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\frz-35\fn微软雅黑\fs20\pos(410,135)}…可能会持续很久 我们必须猎获足够数量以填补…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.15,0:26:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\frz-35\fn微软雅黑\fs20\pos(360,184)}…可能需要长时间依赖这些补给直到…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.15,0:26:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\frz-35\fn微软雅黑\fs20\pos(311,224)}猎获众多者赏…我…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.15,0:26:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\frz-35\fn微软雅黑\fs20\pos(96,141)}…等到时机成熟…就会…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.40,0:26:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)}{\pos(380,200)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}泰温·兰尼斯特{\b0}\N{\fs12}凯岩城公爵 国王之手
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.82,0:27:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你带着这徽章挺合适\N{\fs16}The badge looks good on you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.72,0:27:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差点就比我带着还合适了\N{\fs16}Almost as good as it looked on me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.63,0:27:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这新职位让你挺享受的？\N{\fs16}Are you enjoying your new position?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.40,0:27:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我像是在享受？\N{\fs16}Am I enjoying it?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.94,0:27:25.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当国王之手的时候可开心了\N{\fs16}I was very happyas Hand of the King.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:25.37,0:27:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fs16}Yes.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.44,0:27:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说了\N{\fs16}I heard how happy you were.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.34,0:27:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把妓女都带到我床上去了\N{\fs16}You brought a whore into my bed.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.95,0:27:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那会儿还不是你的床呢\N{\fs16}It wasn't your bed at the time.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.98,0:27:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把你送来是辅佐国王的\N{\fs16}I sent you here to advise the king.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.95,0:27:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给了你真正的权力和职位\N{\fs16}I gave you real power and authority.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.02,0:27:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你却选择\N{\fs16}You chose to spend your days{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.39,0:27:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同以往一样\N{\fs16}as you always have,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.59,0:27:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和妓女鬼混\N{\fs16}bedding harlots{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.06,0:27:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和小偷共饮\N{\fs16}and drinking with thieves.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.16,0:27:59.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时我也和妓女共饮\N{\fs16}Occasionally I drank with the harlots.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.00,0:28:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提利昂 你到底想要什么？\N{\fs16}What do you want, Tyrion?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.85,0:28:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么人人都以为我意有所图\N{\fs16}Why does everyone assume I want something?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.88,0:28:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不能只是想来看看亲爱的老爸吗？\N{\fs16}Can't I simply visit with my beloved father?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.82,0:28:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这个亲爱的老爸\N{\fs16}My beloved father who{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.45,0:28:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在儿子英勇负伤之后\N{\fs16}somehow forgot to visit his wounded son{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.67,0:28:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知怎么的忘记来看儿子了\N{\fs16}after he fell on the battlefield.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.06,0:28:19.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,派席尔大学士保证你的伤势不致命\N{\fs16}Maester Pycelle assured me your wounds were not fatal.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.66,0:28:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你在赫伦堡的废墟上忙着开会时\N{\fs16}I organized the defense of this city{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.70,0:28:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我组建了这座城市的防御\N{\fs16}while you held court in the ruins of Harrenhal.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.90,0:28:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敌人军临城下时 是我领军迎战\N{\fs16}I led the foray when the enemies were at the gate{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.67,0:28:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你的外孙 国王陛下\N{\fs16}while your grandson, the king,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.97,0:28:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却躲在城墙后面发抖\N{\fs16}quivered in fear behind the walls.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.64,0:28:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为了家族血染沙场\N{\fs16}I bled in the mud for our family.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.21,0:28:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而下场呢\N{\fs16}And as my reward,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.78,0:28:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却是被丢进个小黑牢里\N{\fs16}I was trundled off to some dark little cell.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.15,0:28:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我想要什么呢？\N{\fs16}But what do I want?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.49,0:28:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点该死的感激会是一个不错的开始\N{\fs16}A little bloody gratitude would be a start.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.66,0:28:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戏子和歌手才需要喝彩\N{\fs16}Jugglers and singers require applause.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.93,0:28:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个兰尼斯特\N{\fs16}You are a Lannister.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.40,0:28:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次我在战场上负伤\N{\fs16}Do you think I demanded a garland of roses{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.47,0:29:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为只要塞我个玫瑰花环就行了吗\N{\fs16}every time I suffered a wound on a battlefield?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.20,0:29:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？\N{\fs16}Hmm?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.24,0:29:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今 我有七国要料理\N{\fs16}Now, I have seven kingdoms to look after{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.07,0:29:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中三地正公然叛乱\N{\fs16}and three of them are in open rebellion.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.44,0:29:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直说你到底想怎么样吧\N{\fs16}So tell me what you want.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.12,0:29:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要我应得的\N{\fs16}I want what is mine by right.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.62,0:29:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詹姆是你的大儿子理应继承你的领土和头衔\N{\fs16}Jaime is your eldest son, heir to your lands and titles.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.03,0:29:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他是御林铁卫不能娶妻也没有继承人\N{\fs16}But he is a Kingsguard, forbidden from marriage or inheritance.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.33,0:29:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詹姆从披上白袍那天起\N{\fs16}The day Jaime put on the white cloak,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.40,0:29:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就自动放弃了对凯岩城的继承权\N{\fs16}he gave up his claim to Casterly Rock.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.21,0:29:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我是你的儿子 是你法定的继承人\N{\fs16}I am your son and lawful heir.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.25,0:29:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要凯岩城？\N{\fs16}You want Casterly Rock?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.91,0:29:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它本就属于我\N{\fs16}It is mine by right.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.45,0:29:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会给你找个和你的名头\N{\fs16}We'll find you accommodations{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.59,0:29:53.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更相称的封地\N{\fs16}more suited to your name{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.53,0:29:55.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当作是在黑水湾一战中\N{\fs16}and as a reward for your accomplishments{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.93,0:29:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你战功的褒奖吧\N{\fs16}during the battle of Blackwater Bay.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.50,0:30:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时机成熟之后 再给你安排个\N{\fs16}And when the time is right, you will be given a position{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.53,0:30:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既合适你发挥才智\N{\fs16}fit for your talents{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.24,0:30:06.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又维护我们声誉的职务\N{\fs16}so that you can serve your family{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.81,0:30:08.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维护我们的名望\N{\fs16}and protect our legacy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.94,0:30:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是干得好\N{\fs16}And if you serve faithfully,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.61,0:30:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能得到一名适合你的妻子\N{\fs16}you will be rewarded with a suitable wife.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.18,0:30:17.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我宁愿被蛆虫吃光\N{\fs16}And I would let myself be consumed by maggots{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:17.05,0:30:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不会玷污家族名誉\N{\fs16}before mocking the family name{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.35,0:30:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把凯岩城交给你\N{\fs16}and making you heir to Casterly Rock.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:22.89,0:30:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？ 为什么？\N{\fs16}- Why? - Why?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.72,0:30:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然还问我这个？\N{\fs16}You ask that?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.89,0:30:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你这个害死母亲而出世的人？\N{\fs16}You, who killed your mother to come into the world?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.33,0:30:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个怪胎 畸形 不听话的主\N{\fs16}You are an ill - made, spiteful little creature{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.53,0:30:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心中装满妒忌 淫欲缠身 尽耍小聪明\N{\fs16}full of envy, lust, and low cunning.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.54,0:30:42.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世人的律法让你冠我的姓氏 穿我的衣服\N{\fs16}Men's laws give you the right to bear my name{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.14,0:30:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我无法证明你不是我的种\N{\fs16}and display my colors since I cannot prove that you are not mine.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.45,0:30:50.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诸神为了教导我谦逊之道 迫使我\N{\fs16}And to teach me humility,the gods have condemned me{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.85,0:30:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目睹你佩着雄狮纹章 四处蹒跚招摇\N{\fs16}to watch you waddle about wearing that proud lion{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.29,0:30:58.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是我父亲的纹章 我祖父的纹章！\N{\fs16}that was my father's sigil and his father's before him.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.22,0:30:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但无论诸神还是世人\N{\fs16}But neither gods nor men{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.96,0:31:02.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不能强迫我把凯岩城交给你\N{\fs16}will ever compel me to let you turn Casterly Rock{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.89,0:31:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让它变成你的妓院\N{\fs16}into your whorehouse.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.03,0:31:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚吧\N{\fs16}Go, now.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.07,0:31:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再也休提凯岩城的继承权\N{\fs16}Speak no more of your rights to Casterly Rock.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.81,0:31:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚\N{\fs16}Go.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.99,0:31:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 还有一件事\N{\fs16}Oh, one more thing.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.46,0:31:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次教我在你床上发现妓女 我就吊死她\N{\fs16}The next whore I catch in your bed I'll hang.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.60,0:31:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多恩 它往多恩去\N{\fs16}Dorne.It's going to Dorne.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.44,0:31:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要去多恩？它载着丝绸而去\N{\fs16}- Why Dorne? - It's carrying silk{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.38,0:31:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它本该载着酒酿而归\N{\fs16}and it's supposed to bring back wine in exchange.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.88,0:32:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是它将一去不返\N{\fs16}But it's not coming back.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.25,0:32:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,船长已在冒险中疲惫\N{\fs16}The captain's tired of risking his life{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.60,0:32:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(497.959,276.512)}{\pos(80,310)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}珊莎·史塔克{\b0}\N{\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.60,0:32:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(106.642,278.704)}{\pos(280,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}雪伊{\b0}\N{\fs12}珊莎的侍女
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.89,0:32:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让君临的老爷和夫人们\N{\fs16}so King's Landing lords and ladies{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.09,0:32:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝着更好的美酒直到不省人事\N{\fs16}can get drunk on better wine than they deserve.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.53,0:32:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会留在多恩\N{\fs16}He's going to stay in Dorne.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.76,0:32:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里没有冬天 美丽又温暖\N{\fs16}Wait out the winter where it's beautiful and warm.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.13,0:32:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我遇到过一些多恩来的人 他们可不这么美丽也不这么温暖\N{\fs16}I met some people in Dorne who weren't so beautiful and warm.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.94,0:32:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别毁了我的游戏\N{\fs16}Don't ruin the game.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.94,0:32:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早说了 我不想玩游戏\N{\fs16}I told you, I don't want to play.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.78,0:32:26.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个艘船又怎么样？\N{\fs16}What about that one there?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.85,0:32:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一艘？\N{\fs16}That one?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.35,0:32:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它要去瓦伦提斯\N{\fs16}It's going to Volantis.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.38,0:32:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？\N{\fs16}Why?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.85,0:32:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为当我坐船去瓦伦提斯的时候\N{\fs16}Because when I got on a ship in Volantis,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.59,0:32:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样的船\N{\fs16}it looked like that one.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.16,0:32:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游戏又不是这样玩的\N{\fs16}That's not how the game works.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.99,0:32:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不应该直接把答案说出来\N{\fs16}You're not supposed to just blurt out the right answer.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.60,0:32:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要编一个故事\N{\fs16}You've got to invent a story{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.23,0:32:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要描述这艘船到哪里去 为什么去\N{\fs16}about where the ship is going and why.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.70,0:32:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我既然已经知道了真相 为什么还要编故事呢\N{\fs16}Why should I make up a story. when I know the truth?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.60,0:32:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为真相\N{\fs16}Because the truth{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.67,0:32:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么很可怕 要么很无聊\N{\fs16}is always either terrible or boring.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.24,0:32:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天气不错\N{\fs16}Lovely day for it.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.05,0:32:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,适合观赏船只\N{\fs16}Watching the ships.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.98,0:33:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝里席大人\N{\fs16}Lord Baelish.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.99,0:33:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以允许我和珊莎小姐聊聊\N{\fs16}Might I speak with Lady Sansa{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.60,0:33:07.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(476.66,192.591)}{\pos(200,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}培提尔·贝里席{\b0}\N{\fs12} 财政大臣 “小指头”
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.06,0:33:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能单独聊几句吗？\N{\fs16}alone for a moment?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.17,0:33:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不久前 我见过你的母亲\N{\fs16}I saw your mother not long ago.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.44,0:33:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她非常想见你\N{\fs16}She's very eager to see you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.51,0:33:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有你的妹妹\N{\fs16}And your sister.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.85,0:33:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾莉亚还活着？\N{\fs16}Arya's alive?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.75,0:33:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说过你会带我回家\N{\fs16}You said you'd take me home.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.65,0:33:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说过君临就是你的家\N{\fs16}You said King's Landing was your home.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.22,0:33:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你属于国王\N{\fs16}You are the property of the crown.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.62,0:33:44.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带你走就是叛国之罪\N{\fs16}Stealing you would be treason.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.03,0:33:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你说漏了嘴 哪怕只是一个人听到\N{\fs16}If you were to tell just one person - -{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.30,0:33:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我不会告诉任何人 - 我怎么知道你不会\N{\fs16}- I won't tell anyone. - How do I know?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.33,0:33:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我不会撒谎\N{\fs16}Because I'm a terrible liar.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.30,0:33:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你声称自己不会撒谎\N{\fs16}You said so yourself.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:53.97,0:33:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 贝里席大人 告诉我怎么做吧 告诉我什么时候\N{\fs16}Please, Lord Baelish. Tell me what to do. Tell me when.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.37,0:34:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正在等候一纸命令\N{\fs16}I'm waiting for word on an assignment{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.94,0:34:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让我远远地离开这儿\N{\fs16}that will take me far away from the capital.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.21,0:34:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我起航时\N{\fs16}When I set sail,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.91,0:34:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许可以捎上你\N{\fs16}I might be able to take you with me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.48,0:34:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你一收到信号必须马上离开\N{\fs16}But you'll need to be ready to leave on a moment's notice.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.92,0:34:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是她的贴身女仆？\N{\fs16}You're her handmaiden?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.10,0:34:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(130.742,247.841)}{\pos(50,200)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}萝丝{\b0}\N{\fs12}妓女
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.22,0:34:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 你是他的...?\N{\fs16}Yes. And you're his...?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.09,0:34:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮他打理生意\N{\fs16}I help manage his affairs.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.60,0:34:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 他可是个大人物 - 她也一样\N{\fs16}- He's an important person. - So is she.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.04,0:34:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我长大在她父亲的城堡的阴影下\N{\fs16}I grew up in the shadow of her father's castle.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.60,0:34:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她出生那日\N{\fs16}The day she was born, they rang the bells{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.64,0:34:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钟声从日出一直响到日落\N{\fs16}from sunrise till sunset.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.41,0:34:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们混的都不错 你和我\N{\fs16}We've both done rather well, you and I.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.62,0:34:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\fs16}Yes.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.42,0:34:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑到我们的出身\N{\fs16}Given where we started.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.69,0:34:50.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是哪里\N{\fs16}And where is that?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.39,0:34:54.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像我们这样的姑娘\N{\fs16}It's not easy for girls like us{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.49,0:34:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要出人头地可不容易\N{\fs16}to dig our way out.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.43,0:35:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照顾她要小心点\N{\fs16}Watch out for her.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.07,0:35:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一向如此\N{\fs16}I always do.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.94,0:35:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照顾她要小心点他\N{\fs16}Watch out for her with him.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.60,0:35:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(474.731,280)}{\pos(280,280)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}丹妮莉丝·坦格利安{\b0}\N{\fs12}风暴降生 龙之母
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.10,0:36:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(527.588,223.787)}{\pos(150,280)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}乔拉·莫尔蒙{\b0}\N{\fs12}熊老之子 “大熊”
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.93,0:36:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们长得真快\N{\fs16}They're growing fast.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.24,0:36:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不够快\N{\fs16}Not fast enough.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.94,0:36:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等不了那么久\N{\fs16}I can't wait that long.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.44,0:36:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要一支军队\N{\fs16}I need an army.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.45,0:36:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天黑之前 我们就会到达阿斯塔波了\N{\fs16}We'll be in Astapor by nightfall.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.78,0:36:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些人说 无垢者是世上最强的士兵\N{\fs16}Some say the Unsullied are the greatest soldiers in the world.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:24.99,0:36:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最强的"奴隶"士兵\N{\fs16}The greatest slave - soldiers in the world.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.82,0:36:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这两字决定了性质\N{\fs16}The distinction means a good deal to some people.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.16,0:36:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些人还有更好的想法\N{\fs16}Do those people have any better ideas{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.03,0:36:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来帮助你登上铁王座吗\N{\fs16}about how to put you on the Iron Throne?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.00,0:36:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天天气不错 不和你吵\N{\fs16}It's too beautiful a day to argue.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.44,0:36:44.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对\N{\fs16}You're right.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.87,0:36:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是一个在海上度过的好天\N{\fs16}Another lovely day on the high seas.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.41,0:36:51.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别嘲笑他们\N{\fs16}Don't mock them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.21,0:36:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是第一批乘船渡海的多斯拉克人\N{\fs16}They're the first Dothraki who have ever been on a ship.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.65,0:36:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们跟随我穿越了毒水\N{\fs16}They followed me across the poison water.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.02,0:36:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们能 别人也能\N{\fs16}If they'll do it, others will.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:57.35,0:36:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟随一个真正的卡拉萨——\N{\fs16}And with a true khalasar - -{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.92,0:37:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多斯拉克人只服从力量 卡丽熙\N{\fs16}The Dothraki follow strength above all, khaleesi.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.06,0:37:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你证明自己足够强大 你就会有一个真正的卡拉萨\N{\fs16}You'll have a true khalasar when you prove yourself strong.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.86,0:37:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前不可能\N{\fs16}And not before.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.10,0:37:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(171.243,276.08)}{\pos(100,300)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}史坦尼斯·拜拉席恩{\b0}\N{\fs12}狭海中的王
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.32,0:37:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下\N{\fs16}Your Grace.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.90,0:37:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说你已经死了\N{\fs16}I heard you were dead.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.51,0:37:53.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没死透\N{\fs16}Not yet.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.51,0:37:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望能和您私下谈谈 陛下\N{\fs16}I had hoped to speak to you alone, Your Grace.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.45,0:38:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就是\N{\fs16}We are alone.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.46,0:38:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下 您是合法的王\N{\fs16}Your Grace, you are the rightful king.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.66,0:38:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不仅仅是血脉\N{\fs16}Not only by blood.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.57,0:38:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个荣誉的人 公正的人\N{\fs16}You're an honorable man, a just man.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.57,0:38:22.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一场战争要打\N{\fs16}And there is still\Na war to fight.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.91,0:38:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正在打\N{\fs16}I am fighting.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.64,0:38:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把阶下囚烧死就行了？\N{\fs16}By burning prisoners alive?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.58,0:38:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你说要怎么惩罚异教徒呢 戴佛斯大人？\N{\fs16}How would you punish the infidels, Ser Davos?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.38,0:38:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不因为人们信什么神去评判他们\N{\fs16}I do not judge people for the gods they worship.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.85,0:38:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我是这种人\N{\fs16}If I did, I'd have thrown you in the sea{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.99,0:38:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你踏上龙石岛之前 我就应该把你丢进海里\N{\fs16}before you ever set foot on Dragonstone.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.82,0:38:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我不是你的敌人 - 你正是我的敌人\N{\fs16}- I'm not your enemy. - You are my enemy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.40,0:38:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑水湾上 你是在和我作战吗？\N{\fs16}Was it me you fought on Blackwater Bay?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:50.10,0:38:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我点燃了你的船吗？\N{\fs16}Did I set your ships ablaze?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.10,0:39:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(258.312,255.748)}{\pos(250,300)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}梅丽珊卓{\b0}\N{\fs12}光之王的“红袍祭司”
Dialogue: 0,0:38:56.11,0:39:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当野火成百上千地杀死我们的人的时候 我不在那儿\N{\fs16}I wasn't there when the wildfire killed our men by the thousands.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.25,0:39:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来可以救他们的\N{\fs16}I could have saved those men.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.95,0:39:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你本来可以得到那座城的\N{\fs16}You would have taken the city,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.65,0:39:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史坦尼斯现在本应坐上了那张王座了\N{\fs16}Stannis would now sit upon his rightful throne,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.52,0:39:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该站在他身边\N{\fs16}and you would stand beside him.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.22,0:39:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我当时不在那里\N{\fs16}But I wasn't there{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.79,0:39:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为你的鼓动 国王选择把我留下\N{\fs16}because you convinced your king to leave me behind.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:24.64,0:39:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听见了那些惨叫吗\N{\fs16}Do you hear them screaming?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.71,0:39:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些在水中燃烧的人\N{\fs16}All those burning men in the water{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.04,0:39:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们哭爹喊娘\N{\fs16}crying for their mothers,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.75,0:39:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呼天抢地\N{\fs16}for their gods for help?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.65,0:39:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到黑水河将他们吞没\N{\fs16}Until the moment the Blackwater swallowed them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.26,0:39:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用不着绝望 戴佛斯大人\N{\fs16}Don't despair, Ser Davos.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.69,0:39:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉你儿子的是真的\N{\fs16}What I told your son is true.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.09,0:39:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死于火中\N{\fs16}Death by fire{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:53.50,0:39:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是最纯净的死亡\N{\fs16}is the purest death.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.10,0:39:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个女人邪恶至极！\N{\fs16}This woman is evil!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.40,0:40:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是恶魔之母\N{\fs16}She's the mother of demons.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:01.07,0:40:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他关进地牢\N{\fs16}Take him to the dungeon and lock him in a cell.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:03.94,0:40:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 陛下！ - 快点\N{\fs16}- Your Grace! - Come on.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.48,0:40:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你选择了黑暗 戴佛斯爵士\N{\fs16}You've chosen the darkness, Ser Davos.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.78,0:40:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 她会毁了我们所有人！ - 我会为你祈祷\N{\fs16}- She will destroy us all! - I will pray for you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.71,0:40:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下！\N{\fs16}Your Grace!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.90,0:40:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)}{\pos(420,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}乔佛里·拜拉席恩{\b0}\N{\fs12}铁王座上的王
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.14,0:40:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下 落轿\N{\fs16}Halt. Down.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.91,0:40:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下 落轿\N{\fs16}Halt. Down.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:51.92,0:40:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么停下？\N{\fs16}Why have we stopped?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.32,0:40:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下 是玛格丽小姐的命令\N{\fs16}It's Lady Margaery, Your Grace.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.16,0:41:02.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要干嘛？谁允许她这么做？\N{\fs16}What is she doing? Who gave her permission?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.07,0:41:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐 我们应该带着卫兵 小姐\N{\fs16}My lady. We should have guards, my lady.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.00,0:41:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？\N{\fs16}Why?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.90,0:41:13.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(319.295,289.568)}{\pos(140,280)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}玛格丽·提利尔{\b0}\N{\fs12}乔佛里的未婚妻
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.51,0:41:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让一让\N{\fs16}Pardon me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:20.29,0:41:23.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留步 小姐 你会弄脏裙子\N{\fs16}Stop, my lady. You'll ruin your dress.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.76,0:41:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还有很多裙子\N{\fs16}I have others.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.36,0:41:33.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要传话给她吗 陛下？\N{\fs16}Would you like to speak with her, Your Grace?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:36.74,0:41:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用\N{\fs16}No.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.11,0:41:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸是个战士\N{\fs16}He was a soldier.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.84,0:41:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当战船攻入黑水河湾的时候\N{\fs16}He went to fight on the walls{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.78,0:41:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他去城墙作战了\N{\fs16}when the ships came into Blackwater Bay.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:45.38,0:41:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再也没回来\N{\fs16}He never came back.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:47.48,0:41:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妈妈呢？\N{\fs16}And your mother?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.31,0:41:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出生的时候她就死了\N{\fs16}She died when she had me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.29,0:41:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有坏蛋想要攻进城\N{\fs16}Bad men wanted to come into this city{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.59,0:42:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要干坏事 你父亲阻止了他们\N{\fs16}and do terrible things, but your father stopped them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:06.26,0:42:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后每次看到这个骑士\N{\fs16}Whenever you look at this knight,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.30,0:42:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你会想起你父亲\N{\fs16}I want you to remember your father.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:13.81,0:42:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是骑士\N{\fs16}He wasn't a knight.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.64,0:42:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是个战士\N{\fs16}He was just a soldier.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:17.61,0:42:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑士们发誓要做什么？\N{\fs16}And what do knights swear to do?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:20.01,0:42:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主持正义 保护弱小\N{\fs16}Protect the weak and uphold the good.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.38,0:42:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你父亲做到了 你应该为他感到骄傲\N{\fs16}Your father did that. Be proud of him.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:29.85,0:42:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你父亲也是战士吗？\N{\fs16}Was your father a soldier, too?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:34.09,0:42:36.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也应该感到骄傲\N{\fs16}You should be proud, too.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:38.83,0:42:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在乔佛里国王的领导下\N{\fs16}Under King Joffrey's leadership,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.16,0:42:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的父亲拯救了这座城市\N{\fs16}your fathers saved the city.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:43.93,0:42:46.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拯救了我们所有人\N{\fs16}They saved us all.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:46.27,0:42:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从现在开始 我们会照顾你们\N{\fs16}From now on, we're going to take care of you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:52.04,0:42:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照顾所有人\N{\fs16}All of you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:00.88,0:43:02.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们需要什么食物\N{\fs16}Come to me for whatever you need to feed them,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:02.92,0:43:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有衣服或者房子 尽管来找我\N{\fs16}clothe them, or house them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:06.79,0:43:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接找我\N{\fs16}Directly to me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:23.64,0:43:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 陛下 - 陛下\N{\fs16}- Your Grace. - Your Grace.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:25.84,0:43:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请坐 坐\N{\fs16}Please, sit. Sit.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:27.48,0:43:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉 小姐\N{\fs16}I do apologize, my lady.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:29.98,0:43:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御前会议刚刚结束\N{\fs16}Small council meetings.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:32.35,0:43:34.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候浪费国王的时间\N{\fs16}At what point does it become treason{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:34.48,0:43:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会被判处叛国罪就好了\N{\fs16}to waste the king's time?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:41.06,0:43:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一件漂亮的礼服 小姐\N{\fs16}That's a lovely gown, my lady.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:42.83,0:43:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 非常适合你\N{\fs16}Yes, it suits you perfectly.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:44.86,0:43:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜你肯定很冷\N{\fs16}I imagine you might be rather cold.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:47.30,0:43:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下 高庭的气候向来很温和\N{\fs16}The climate is a bit more forgiving back in Highgarden, Your Grace.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:50.70,0:43:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的小姐 要不要仆人给你拿个披肩来？\N{\fs16}Shall I have them bring you a shawl, my lady?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:54.44,0:43:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢您的关心 陛下\N{\fs16}I am touched by your concern, Your Grace.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:56.94,0:44:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所幸我们提利尔的血液总是很热情\N{\fs16}Luckily for us Tyrells,our blood runs quite warm.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:00.18,0:44:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 是不是 洛拉斯？ - 没错\N{\fs16}- Doesn't it, Loras? - Yes.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:00.90,0:44:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(148.553,247.608)}{\pos(50,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}洛拉斯·提利尔{\b0}\N{\fs12}“百花骑士”
Dialogue: 0,0:44:02.18,0:44:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洛拉斯 王后的礼服华丽极了 不是吗？\N{\fs16}Loras, isn't the queen's gown magnificent?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:05.32,0:44:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那织工 刺绣 还有那金属饰品\N{\fs16}The fabric, the embroidery, the metalwork.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:08.22,0:44:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从来没见过像这个一样的衣服\N{\fs16}I've never seen anything like it.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:09.89,0:44:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你做了王后 你会发现身着一点护甲总是有用的\N{\fs16}You might find a bit of armor quite useful{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:11.82,0:44:14.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定很快你就会体会到\N{\fs16}once you become queen.Perhaps before.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:14.46,0:44:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔佛里告诉我今天早上从圣堂返回的时候\N{\fs16}Joffrey tells me you stopped your carriage at Flea Bottom{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:18.30,0:44:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在跳蚤窝下轿了\N{\fs16}on your way back from the sept this morning.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.10,0:44:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我去了一家孤儿院\N{\fs16}Yes. I paid a visit to an orphanage{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:24.50,0:44:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总主教大人向我提到过的\N{\fs16}the High Septon told me about.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:26.07,0:44:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在高庭的时候玛格丽就为穷人们做过很多事\N{\fs16}Margaery does a great deal of work with the poor back in Highgarden.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:28.77,0:44:33.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便是最底层的百姓 只要敞开心扉接触他们\N{\fs16}The lowest among us are no different from the highest if you give them a chance{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:33.11,0:44:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会发现他们和贵族没有区别\N{\fs16}and approach them with an open heart.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:35.45,0:44:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敞开心扉？在跳蚤窝如果你不小心的话\N{\fs16}An open heart is what you'll get in Flea Bottom{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:37.52,0:44:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只会被“敞开心脏”\N{\fs16}if you're not careful, my dear.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:39.12,0:44:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不久前那里就曾有暴徒袭击我们\N{\fs16}Not long ago, we were attacked by a mob there.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:43.02,0:44:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带着充足的护卫也没能阻止他们\N{\fs16}We had a full complement of guards that didn't stop them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:45.96,0:44:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国王都差点丧命\N{\fs16}The king barely escaped with his life.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:48.96,0:44:52.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我母后向来喜欢夸大其辞\N{\fs16}My mother's always had a penchant for drama.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:52.50,0:44:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随着她年龄渐长\N{\fs16}Facts become less and less important to her{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:55.07,0:44:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越来越夸张了\N{\fs16}as she grows older.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:57.14,0:45:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暴徒根本没有威胁到我们的安全\N{\fs16}Our lives were never truly in danger.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:01.27,0:45:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然 你是对的\N{\fs16}You're right, of course.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:03.04,0:45:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你是你父亲的儿子\N{\fs16}But you are your father's son.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:06.31,0:45:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人可没有国王的勇敢\N{\fs16}We can't all have a king's bravery.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:16.66,0:45:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饥饿会把人变成野兽\N{\fs16}Hunger turns men into beasts.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:18.89,0:45:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴提利尔家族能在这方面提供帮助\N{\fs16}I'm glad House Tyrell has been able to help in this regard.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:22.76,0:45:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们告诉我有100辆从河湾地而来的货车近日就会到达君临\N{\fs16}They tell me 100 wagons arrive daily now from the Reach.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:26.63,0:45:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小麦 大麦 还有苹果 七神保佑我们今年获得丰收\N{\fs16}Wheat, barley, apples.We've had a blessed harvest.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:30.17,0:45:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然在需要的时候\N{\fs16}And, of course, it's our duty to assist the capital{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:32.87,0:45:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,援助都城是我们的责任\N{\fs16}in time of need.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:34.94,0:45:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然如洛拉斯爵士所说\N{\fs16}Well, as Ser Loras said,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:36.68,0:45:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽小姐以前就做过这种...\N{\fs16}Lady Margaery has done this sort of...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:39.85,0:45:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慈善活动\N{\fs16}charitable work before.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:42.92,0:45:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想她应该知道自己在做什么\N{\fs16}I'm sure she knows what she's doing.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:46.32,0:45:48.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然\N{\fs16}I'm sure she does.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:17.19,0:46:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些无垢者已经在这里站了整整一天一夜\N{\fs16}The Unsullied have stood here for a day and a night{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:20.02,0:46:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不吃不喝\N{\fs16}with no food or water.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:28.32,0:46:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们还将一动不动站到死亡来临\N{\fs16}They will stand until they drop.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:32.78,0:46:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们称之为“顺从”\N{\fs16}Such is their obedience.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:36.30,0:46:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(446.553,218.608)}{\pos(50,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}克拉兹尼·莫·纳克罗兹{\b0}\N{\fs12}阿斯塔波的奴隶主
Dialogue: 0,0:46:36.30,0:46:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(340.553,184.608)}{\pos(50,250)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}弥桑黛{\b0}\N{\fs12}奴隶翻译
Dialogue: 0,0:46:36.94,0:46:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们应该符合我的要求\N{\fs16}They may suit my needs.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:39.04,0:46:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我他们是怎么训练的\N{\fs16}Tell me of their training.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:41.50,0:46:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,302)}维斯特洛女人对他们很满意
Dialogue: 0,0:46:43.80,0:46:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(310.667,300.667)}但没有赞扬 以便压价
Dialogue: 0,0:46:48.60,0:46:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(321.333,300.667)}她想知道无垢者是如何被训练的
Dialogue: 0,0:46:52.20,0:46:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(321.333,296.667)}告诉她她该知道的 笼统点
Dialogue: 0,0:46:59.00,0:47:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(318.667,303.333)}天气太热了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:00.86,0:47:03.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们五岁起接受训练\N{\fs16}They begin their training at five.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:03.63,0:47:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天从黎明一直练到天黑\N{\fs16}Every day they drill from dawn to dusk{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:05.63,0:47:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到熟练掌握短剑\N{\fs16}until they have mastered the shortsword,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:07.83,0:47:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盾牌和三种长矛\N{\fs16}the shield, and the three spears.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:10.27,0:47:13.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四个男孩里只有一个存活\N{\fs16}Only one boy in four survives this rigorous training.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:16.08,0:47:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们绝对服从 绝对忠诚\N{\fs16}Their discipline and loyalty are absolute.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:19.98,0:47:21.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且全无恐惧\N{\fs16}They fear nothing.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:21.78,0:47:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最勇敢的人也害怕死亡\N{\fs16}Even the bravest men fear death.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:25.60,0:47:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(324,299.333)}骑士说最勇敢的人也害怕死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:47:29.70,0:47:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,299.333)}告诉那老头 他闻上去浑身尿臭
Dialogue: 0,0:47:35.20,0:47:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(328,299.333)}真这样说 主人？
Dialogue: 0,0:47:36.20,0:47:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,298)}当然不能这样说
Dialogue: 0,0:47:37.60,0:47:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,302)}你是女人还是母羊 问得出这么愚蠢的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:47:45.97,0:47:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的主人说无垢者不是人\N{\fs16}My master says the Unsullied are not men.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:48.98,0:47:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死亡对他们而言不算什么\N{\fs16}Death means nothing to them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:51.88,0:47:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(314.667,304.667)}告诉这无知的西方婊子
Dialogue: 0,0:47:56.30,0:47:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(313.333,302)}让她睁开狗眼
Dialogue: 0,0:47:59.85,0:48:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他请您留心观察 陛下\N{\fs16}He begs you attend to this carefully, Your Grace.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:17.47,0:48:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉善主大人 不必如此\N{\fs16}Tell the good master there is no need.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:19.92,0:48:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还操心他们的乳头？
Dialogue: 0,0:48:23.68,0:48:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这愚蠢的婊子知不知道他们的卵蛋已经被割了？
Dialogue: 0,0:48:27.25,0:48:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的主人说男人不需要乳头\N{\fs16}My master points out that men don't need nipples.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:34.55,0:48:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:48:36.01,0:48:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小人很高兴为主人效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:48:46.03,0:48:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在赢得尖刺盔之前\N{\fs16}To win his shield,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:48.23,0:48:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无垢者必须拿一枚银币去奴隶市场\N{\fs16}an Unsullied must go to the slave marts with a silver mark,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:52.00,0:48:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到一个哭叫着的新生儿 并在其母眼前将其杀死\N{\fs16}find a newborn and kill it before its mother's eyes.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:59.31,0:49:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的主人说 通过这样的方法\N{\fs16}This way, my master says,we make certain{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:01.78,0:49:03.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,方能确定他心中未留有丝毫软弱之处\N{\fs16}there is no weakness left in them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:05.22,0:49:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们从母亲怀中抢走婴儿\N{\fs16}You take a babe from its mother's arms,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:08.05,0:49:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在她注视之下将其杀死 然后支付一枚银币以补偿她的痛苦？\N{\fs16}kill it as she watches, and pay for her pain with a silver coin?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:12.39,0:49:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很生气
Dialogue: 0,0:49:14.41,0:49:16.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她问是不是支付一枚银币给那母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:49:16.95,0:49:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为新生儿的价钱
Dialogue: 0,0:49:19.52,0:49:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这唠唠叨叨的婊子真是个软心肠的蠢货
Dialogue: 0,0:49:26.27,0:49:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的主人告诉您\N{\fs16}My master would like you to know that the silver is paid{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:28.91,0:49:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钱乃是付给孩子的主人 不是给母亲\N{\fs16}to the baby's owner, not the mother.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:37.62,0:49:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们有多少无垢者待售？\N{\fs16}How many do you have to sell?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:44.92,0:49:46.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,8,000\N{\fs16}8,000.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:46.71,0:49:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉这维斯特洛婊子她要在明天之前决定
Dialogue: 0,0:49:51.53,0:49:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克拉兹尼主人请您速做决定\N{\fs16}Master Kraznys asks that you please hurry.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:54.20,0:49:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对无垢者感兴趣的买家很多\N{\fs16}Many other buyers are interested.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:07.18,0:50:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,8,000个死去的新生儿\N{\fs16}8,000 dead babies.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:10.38,0:50:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无垢者是终结一切的工具\N{\fs16}The Unsullied are a means to an end.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:12.99,0:50:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我买了他们 这些人\N{\fs16}Once I own them, these men - -{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:15.39,0:50:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不是人 不再是人了\N{\fs16}They're not men. Not anymore.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:17.92,0:50:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我拥有一支奴隶军队 我成了什么？\N{\fs16}Once I own an army of slaves, what will I be?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:21.33,0:50:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您想 这些奴隶属于您或者克拉兹尼和他那样的人\N{\fs16}Do you think these slaves will have better lives{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:23.43,0:50:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会给他们更好的生活呢？\N{\fs16}serving Kraznys and men like him or serving you?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:40.58,0:50:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对他们更加公正\N{\fs16}You'll be fair to them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:42.11,0:50:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会为了达到目的让他们残疾\N{\fs16}You won't mutilate them to make a point.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:49.46,0:50:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不会命令他们杀死新生儿\N{\fs16}You won't order them to murder babies.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:51.69,0:50:54.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会保证他们有吃有穿\N{\fs16}You'll see they're properly fed and sheltered.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:54.56,0:50:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们已经经受了严重的不公正待遇\N{\fs16}A great injustice has been done to them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:58.57,0:51:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭上双眼也不会有任何改变\N{\fs16}Closing your eyes will not undo it.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:57.89,0:51:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是男巫们\N{\fs16}The warlocks.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:03.30,0:52:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我欠您一条命 先生\N{\fs16}I owe you my life, ser.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:06.20,0:52:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我深感荣幸\N{\fs16}The honor is mine,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:07.87,0:52:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女王陛下\N{\fs16}my queen.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:13.44,0:52:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识他？\N{\fs16}You know this man?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:15.74,0:52:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识他\N{\fs16}I know him{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:17.58,0:52:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是七国最强大的战士\N{\fs16}as one of the greatest fighters the Seven Kingdoms has ever seen{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:22.08,0:52:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及劳勃·拜拉席恩的御前侍卫队长\N{\fs16}and as the Lord Commander of Robert Baratheon's Kingsguard.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:27.99,0:52:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,劳勃国王已经死了\N{\fs16}King Robert is dead.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:29.96,0:52:32.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找了您很久 丹妮莉丝·风暴降生\N{\fs16}I have been searching for you, Daenerys Stormborn,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:32.86,0:52:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想请求您的宽恕\N{\fs16}to ask your forgiveness.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:35.43,0:52:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾发誓保卫你的家族\N{\fs16}I was sworn to protect\Nyour family.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:40.20,0:52:42.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我却没做到\N{\fs16}I failed them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:47.30,0:52:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(454,293)}{\pos(273,272)}{\fs16} {\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1\b1}巴利斯坦·赛尔弥\N{\fs12}前任御林铁卫队长 “无畏的”
Dialogue: 0,0:52:47.54,0:52:49.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是巴利斯坦·赛尔弥\N{\fs16}I am Barristan Selmy,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:49.84,0:52:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你父亲的御前侍卫\N{\fs16}Kingsguard to your father.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:52.18,0:52:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请允许我加入你的御前侍卫\N{\fs16}Allow me to join your Queensguard{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:54.62,0:52:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会再次辜负你\N{\fs16}and I will not fail you again.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:53:06.80,0:53:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}{\pos(320,120)}{\fs18}{\fn微软雅黑}{\bord1}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\fs18\b1}衣柜字幕组出品{\b0} {\fs18}
