[Script Info]
Title:To Aru Majutsu no Index II 06 gb
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H28000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,DFGBrushRD-W7,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FF860B,&H00FF0000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,1,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正卡通简体,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FF860B,&H00A85400,&H00930000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,2,7,10,10,10,134
Style: edcn,方正粗倩_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H64800040,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: edjp,DFPSoGei-W7,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H64800040,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,128
Style: staff,黑体,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: title,华文中宋,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H14000000,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: netitle,方正行楷_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
;Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,=============================================================Logo
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.24,0:01:55.65,LOGO1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(250,430)\fnDFNMingXBold-B5\fs50}{\shad0}{\1c&H4D81DF\fs50}囧\N　{\1c&H455EDC\fs50}\N齒{\1c&H3035CE\fs50}\N輪{\1c&4028D1}\N{\fs55\b0}の
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.24,0:01:55.65,LOGO1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,250)\fnDFNMingXBold-B5}{\shad0}{\fs25}{\1c&H4D81DF}爆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.24,0:01:55.65,LOGO1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,275)\fnDFNMingXBold-B5}{\shad0}{\fs25}{\1c&H5B76CC}肝
Dialogue: 2,0:01:52.24,0:01:55.65,LOGO1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(191,307)\fnDFNMingXBold-B5}{\shad0}{\fs65}真
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.24,0:01:55.65,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(225,275)}{\shad0}{\1c&H2e41e2}{\fs90}{\frz90}▆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.24,0:01:55.65,LOGO3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(202,355)}{\shad0}{\1c&4028D1}{\fs85}H
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.24,0:01:55.65,LOGO3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(199,403)}{\shad0}{\1c&341FD7}{\fs105}K
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.24,0:01:55.65,LOGO3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(193,465)}{\shad0}{\1c&341FD7}{\fs130}G
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.24,0:01:55.65,LOGO3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(170,360)\fad(0,0)}{\shad0}{\frz90}{\fs20}{\1c&341FD7}hkgfansub
;Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,=============================================================OP
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.92,0:01:42.00,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}fu woo.. fu woo
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.26,0:01:45.48,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Try to be glorious believer.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.70,0:01:52.21,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Just to.. go on.. realize soulful heart
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.22,0:01:55.58,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Let's fly faraway!　届きたい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.71,0:01:59.03,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}君と約束した未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.10,0:02:02.24,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}躊躇いも　踏み越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.31,0:02:09.28,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}飛び立てる　胸に　響く　夢があるから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.79,0:02:16.43,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}朝の陽射しの眩しさに　今日も街は目を覚まして
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.58,0:02:23.37,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}爽やかな風が運んだ　予感に心弾ませた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.59,0:02:30.38,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}瞳に映った　景色が輝きだしたら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.54,0:02:37.61,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}自然に　通じ合う想い　無邪気な笑顔咲かせた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.07,0:02:42.48,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}手を伸ばし　抱きしめた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.70,0:02:45.95,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}色鮮やかな現実は
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.06,0:02:49.33,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}誰一人　壊せない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.35,0:02:52.98,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}いつだって　ずっと信じてるから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.99,0:02:54.67,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}For shining truth！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.71,0:02:59.88,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}もしいつか　戸惑い　心が震えても
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.94,0:03:03.05,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}迷いなく　手を繋ぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.13,0:03:09.67,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}駆け出すよ　強い　絆がここにあるから！
;Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,=============================================================ED
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.21,0:32:35.36,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}「ひとりじゃない」
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.57,0:32:40.39,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}これからも　We are Special "ONE"
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.51,0:33:01.39,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}瞳を閉じれば　そっと　めぐりめぐる
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.44,0:33:05.32,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ほら　一緒に過ごした日
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.84,0:33:14.64,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}はしゃいだり　たまには　ちょっとすれ違ったり
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.75,0:33:19.03,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}それぞれが　大事なメモリー
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.15,0:33:32.17,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}きっと忘れないよ　笑顔に出逢えたから
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.30,0:33:38.65,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ひとつひとつ　未来へ続く
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.82,0:33:44.53,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}レベル超えた　チカラが重なり
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.70,0:33:54.24,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ひとりきりでは　とても叶いそうにない夢さえ
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.35,0:34:01.64,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}みんながいるから　歩き出せるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,=============================================================Main
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.00,0:00:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人看著你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.06,0:00:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初春 情況怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.56,0:00:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根據新的通報
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.04,0:00:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歹徒有6人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.63,0:00:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現場沒改變 請你抓緊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.88,0:00:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然的話
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.74,0:00:33.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然的話...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.62,0:00:36.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那六個人會...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.42,0:00:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是風紀委員
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.42,0:00:39.49,*Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(453,436)}<Judgement>
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.74,0:00:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...全部變成受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.44,0:00:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.20,0:00:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太猛了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.61,0:00:59.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是咋回事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.94,0:01:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 實在太感謝你了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.29,0:01:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.68,0:01:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別客氣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.39,0:01:08.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再三無視我的忠告
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.91,0:01:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出於興趣向非特定多數人進行戰鬥的現行犯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.41,0:01:14.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以個人名義逮捕姐姐大人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.63,0:01:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.05,0:01:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想被這麼多圍觀路人擠壞麼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.03,0:01:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 空出一條路來 趕緊讓開
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.35,0:01:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我們到達現場了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.98,0:01:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 趁事情還沒麻煩起來快走
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.90,0:01:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.01,0:01:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 姐姐大人

Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.25,0:03:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感受到視線？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.33,0:03:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.11,0:03:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是 那麼多人圍觀著呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.02,0:03:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是指那些
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.38,0:03:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該怎麼說呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.59,0:03:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 這感覺已經不是第一次了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.90,0:03:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人 社會對幻想御手事件的熱議還沒平息哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.90,0:03:38.04,*Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(382,436)}<Level Upper>
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.36,0:03:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擊倒幻想猛獸
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.36,0:03:40.14,*Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(452,438)}<AIM Burst>
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.29,0:03:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,並解決了這次事件的姐姐大人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.44,0:03:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可謂是焦點人物
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.24,0:03:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過那是個秘密啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.82,0:03:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又沒上新聞
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.07,0:03:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能小看傳言的威力
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.24,0:03:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勢必會有人用艷羨的目光看你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.64,0:03:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也會有因短暫的能力被奪走而惱羞成怒
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.37,0:04:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像剛才那些壞人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.90,0:04:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我都勸了你多少次盡量避免引人注目了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.82,0:04:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種視線我才不會放在心上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.92,0:04:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過那卻是...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.49,0:04:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是讓我全身電流逆流般的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.30,0:04:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有那個視線會那樣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.16,0:04:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那那那那不就是「老大哥在看著你」嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.44,0:04:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「老大哥在看著你」？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.02,0:04:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是當下最熱門的都市傳說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.14,0:04:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然射到後背的謎之視線
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.76,0:04:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回頭一看 誰都不在
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.09,0:04:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過確實感受到了視線在逐漸靠近
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.97,0:04:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不久後 被視線纏住的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.15,0:04:48.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再也不敢走出房間一步
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.84,0:04:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因為從門背後
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.27,0:04:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感受到了視線
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.59,0:04:56.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使如此
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.02,0:04:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某一刻 一位女生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.19,0:05:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鼓起了勇氣去看貓眼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.61,0:05:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.26,0:05:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.38,0:05:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 你們不怕麼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.61,0:05:15.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不怕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.56,0:05:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 佐天真是的 又說這種都市傳說
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.86,0:05:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 但是很熱門嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.75,0:05:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是壓力太大了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.90,0:05:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為御坂學姐是焦點人物嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.01,0:05:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.49,0:05:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 初春 你的移動終端在動哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.98,0:05:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.10,0:05:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 為什麼會知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.25,0:05:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從電磁波的強弱判斷
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.33,0:05:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才在用的GPS一直沒關
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.04,0:05:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日子越來越不好過了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.52,0:05:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使是那個GPS也一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.23,0:05:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不僅姐姐大人一個
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.14,0:06:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們也總是暴露在視線中呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.46,0:06:03.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的確是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.36,0:06:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近警備員也強化了管制
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.36,0:06:08.32,*Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(365,438)}<Antiskill>
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.71,0:06:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說來 現在還有了裝在書包上的防盜攝像頭哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.17,0:06:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裝在書包上？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.23,0:06:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是接受了家長申請的老師
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.73,0:06:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給小學生裝的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.43,0:06:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了讓家長全天候瞭解孩子在哪裡幹些什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.77,0:06:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 用不用做到這地步啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.90,0:06:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為長期壓力過大 對能力控制帶來壞影響
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.32,0:06:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最終使只屬於自己的現實產生扭曲也有可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.32,0:06:39.47,*Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,436)}<Personal Reality>
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.30,0:06:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎麼說 這裡是學園都市
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.83,0:06:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耿耿於懷也沒用
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.20,0:06:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人也請放鬆一點
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.21,0:06:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被這種事弄花「常盤臺Ace」的招牌就不值了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.56,0:06:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.64,0:06:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是太在意了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.95,0:07:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎...也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.69,0:07:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你們
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.21,0:07:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太緊張了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.60,0:07:44.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太緊張了 太緊張了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.64,0:07:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太緊張了...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.74,0:07:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.16,0:07:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.03,0:07:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.88,0:08:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喲 電光閃閃
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.12,0:08:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.47,0:08:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你搞的鬼！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.09,0:08:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.69,0:08:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你幹什麼...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.20,0:08:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少裝蒜了！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.96,0:08:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.42,0:08:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近一直在盯著我的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.89,0:08:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.17,0:08:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問...你到底在說啥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.19,0:08:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就說你一直盯著我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.59,0:08:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.56,0:08:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說來 為啥我非得盯著你看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.27,0:08:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.45,0:08:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原因是...這個嘛...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.12,0:08:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你臉好紅哦 是不是發燒了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.45,0:08:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少囉嗦 跟我決勝負
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.22,0:08:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之跟我比一場
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.45,0:08:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這裡做個了斷 看看你是不是犯人...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.35,0:08:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.13,0:08:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.68,0:08:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這種地方使用能力
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.65,0:08:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.51,0:08:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不 那 那個
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.18,0:09:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 不好意思 只是這傢伙在胡鬧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.12,0:09:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我才沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.74,0:09:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是 我們明白啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.06,0:09:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬上到清校時間了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.45,0:09:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快回宿舍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.18,0:09:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊沒有異常
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.76,0:09:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是有學生情侶在打情罵俏
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.75,0:09:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.62,0:09:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打情罵俏 這...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.37,0:09:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 趕緊回宿舍
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.91,0:09:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯 好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.47,0:09:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是太自作多情了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.19,0:09:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.04,0:09:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是男人麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.69,0:09:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來只是我杞人憂天 這就放心了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.12,0:09:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 我可是真的很頭疼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.74,0:09:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.85,0:09:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才那下 讓我堅信不疑了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.33,0:09:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,堅信啥
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.49,0:09:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然是這次事件的真相
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.95,0:09:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 你知道犯人是誰了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.86,0:09:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某種意義上
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.99,0:09:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.73,0:09:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說白了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.94,0:10:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是姐姐大人自己
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.44,0:10:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.25,0:10:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是說姐姐大人的想法 離真相也不遠了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.87,0:10:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.57,0:10:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,例如說那裙底下的短褲
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.09,0:10:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有短褲下面 通訊購物買的限量版呱太內褲
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.93,0:10:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為啥你會知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.87,0:10:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有床底下的Kill熊和呱太睡衣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.31,0:10:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他印有企鵝啊 鱷魚啊 甚至有點傻的公仔圖案等等的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.58,0:10:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各種各樣幼稚到讓人看不過眼的內衣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.09,0:10:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算平常認為沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.16,0:10:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在心底還是覺得這樣很難為情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.20,0:10:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,潛意識到此終於浮出表面
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.18,0:10:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.85,0:10:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.83,0:10:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.12,0:10:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.79,0:10:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.34,0:10:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我背後
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.65,0:10:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人 沒人往這邊看哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.35,0:10:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我出來 卑鄙小人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.22,0:11:00.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然不知道你在打什麼算盤
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.87,0:11:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我隨時奉陪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.68,0:11:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別玩陰的 現身啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.70,0:11:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.26,0:11:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐天 打攪了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.17,0:11:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.16,0:11:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.41,0:11:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁我兩手拿滿東西就為所欲為
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.42,0:11:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.74,0:11:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說來 你買了什麼過來
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.93,0:11:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各種零食
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.84,0:11:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難得來過夜嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.70,0:11:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 這也算零食麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.16,0:11:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 佐天你沒吃過嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.29,0:11:51.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸收了湯汁而變得有點軟的草莓
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.30,0:11:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加上那洋溢著酸酸甜甜風味的湯汁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.96,0:11:55.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可謂一絕哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.91,0:11:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 所以內褲也穿有草莓花紋的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.96,0:12:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟內褲無關！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.66,0:12:04.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 咋回事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.74,0:12:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明很好吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.98,0:12:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 白井 怎麼...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.30,0:12:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 嗯 沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.80,0:12:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 現在初春也在
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.55,0:12:15.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 好 再見
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.74,0:12:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.35,0:12:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白井說要過來
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.89,0:12:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.45,0:12:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.79,0:12:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想問個問題
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.45,0:12:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.25,0:12:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這網站 除了之前我說的那些就沒別的了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.29,0:12:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.17,0:12:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.24,0:12:39.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我發現了這個
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.48,0:12:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好猛 你怎麼找的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.61,0:12:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手段各種各樣啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.34,0:12:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實這是學校秘密網站之一
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.63,0:12:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學校？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.65,0:12:53.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 是常盤臺的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.70,0:12:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這 這是...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.97,0:13:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婚後光子 一看帖就暴露出你身份了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.60,0:13:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婚後？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.13,0:13:05.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是養有很可愛的蟒蛇那個啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.78,0:13:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之 既然有實際受害人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.68,0:13:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「老大哥在看著你」就不是單純的都市傳說了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.13,0:13:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有可能是一個事件
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.56,0:13:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什麼人出於什麼目的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.26,0:13:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趕緊進行其它調查
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.80,0:13:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 不過之前
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.94,0:13:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這件事 麻煩對姐姐大人保密
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.37,0:13:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.07,0:13:34.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以她的性格
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.34,0:13:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一知道 肯定又是一個人去行動了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.87,0:13:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的確是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.30,0:13:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯人由我來抓
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.06,0:13:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是白井黑子 身為姐姐大人馬前卒的使命
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.41,0:13:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.67,0:13:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,援助你的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.14,0:13:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就讓作為白井和御坂學姐朋友的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.52,0:13:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們來做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.50,0:14:06.50,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(413.5,10)\fs23}{\bord0\shad0}{\fad(0,0)}{\fscx92}#EX{\fscx98\b0} 御坂學姐{\1c&H4D81DF}現在是焦點人物嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.60,0:14:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.68,0:14:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 真頭痛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.76,0:14:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平常走開的捷徑因為施工就過不去了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.34,0:14:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡就成了條單行道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.23,0:14:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到頭來回到原處了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.11,0:14:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渴死我了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.59,0:14:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿瓶果汁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.22,0:14:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.09,0:14:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 御坂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.42,0:14:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你好像很累啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.98,0:14:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 真不好意思 打攪你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.97,0:14:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺這裡能靜下心來
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.83,0:14:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且保安措施還這麼好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.77,0:14:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御坂學姐 你想喝椰子汽水還是黃豆面煉乳？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.59,0:14:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說來 今天怎麼不見黑子和初春
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.98,0:14:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她們出去巡邏了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.27,0:14:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天巡完就直接回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.07,0:14:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.50,0:15:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 馬上就換班了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.12,0:15:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要一起去充充電？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.79,0:15:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,充電？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.76,0:15:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教你們我珍藏的消除壓力法
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.51,0:15:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消除壓力法？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.23,0:15:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.02,0:15:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.37,0:15:17.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.31,0:15:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收費浴室？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.92,0:15:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天還亮的時候就去泡澡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.43,0:15:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到傍晚涼爽的時候再回宿舍
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.85,0:15:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是超爽的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.61,0:15:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 大家去泡澡啊 真好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.10,0:15:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我們接下來就回宿舍了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.12,0:15:39.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你通知我們
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.21,0:15:42.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也請你們繼續盡興
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.99,0:15:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為為為為為為什麼知道我在那論壇上發帖
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.80,0:15:50.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,調查能力太強了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.87,0:15:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是白井
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.20,0:15:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個就別說了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.50,0:15:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能回答我的問題
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.93,0:15:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你感受到的視線是怎樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.07,0:16:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很遺憾 我並非受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.29,0:16:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.04,0:16:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事實上
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.20,0:16:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「老大哥在看著你」的受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.44,0:16:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我們游泳部的學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.01,0:16:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.65,0:16:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是為了鼓勵她
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.59,0:16:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在論壇上發帖警告有可能在看帖的犯人罷了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.43,0:16:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.13,0:16:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為陌生人著想的這份菩薩心腸
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.50,0:16:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說來我自小就跟爸爸一起參加UNESCO主辦的各種座談會...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.50,0:16:32.14,*Default3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,<UNESCO>: 聯合國教科文組織
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.15,0:16:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼你們也去那個論壇發貼？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.60,0:16:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說來 相互鼓勵和表關心的回帖是很多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.29,0:16:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你們 有聽我在說嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.05,0:16:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能讓我們見見她
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.38,0:16:47.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估計不行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.15,0:16:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她說對視線...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.04,0:16:54.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對那似乎讓全身電流都逆流的視線很恐懼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.44,0:16:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一直將自己關在房間
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.04,0:17:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我們也只有通過論壇跟她交流
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.45,0:17:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請你們盡快抓到犯人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.92,0:17:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都認死了自己被都市傳說玩弄
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.90,0:17:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連公開表示都不敢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.53,0:17:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得他們太可憐了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.23,0:17:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全身電流都逆流...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.77,0:17:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我們會盡力的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.20,0:17:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再問一個問題
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.76,0:17:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的能力是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.75,0:17:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣 早點泡澡舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.92,0:17:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的超有解放感的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.42,0:17:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這時間很多人還在上課或者去補習班
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.81,0:17:39.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人少 就像包場一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.14,0:17:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 也只限於學園都市
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.40,0:17:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御坂 不用這麼萎縮嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.04,0:17:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的 還在發育嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.47,0:17:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我不是這個原因
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.71,0:17:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然是有點在意
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.57,0:17:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過現在這樣更能平靜下來
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.72,0:18:05.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗髮水那些可以隨便用哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.46,0:18:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.14,0:18:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御坂學姐先用如何
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.00,0:18:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御坂學姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.80,0:18:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐 佐天？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.26,0:18:28.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的背後 就請交給我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.41,0:18:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為御坂學姐一直都是堅定地眼看前方
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.13,0:18:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我現在才能平安無事地在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.75,0:18:40.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以背後就交給我們
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.60,0:18:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還是像往常一樣積極向前吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.07,0:18:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 好像很好玩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.05,0:18:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,固法學姐也一起來嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.10,0:18:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 我也來？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.36,0:18:56.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊 來啊來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.72,0:18:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.32,0:18:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.53,0:19:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊～真爽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.19,0:19:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣 充足電了吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.50,0:19:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 神清氣爽的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.84,0:19:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也要謝謝佐天
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.63,0:19:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡 我也沒做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.91,0:19:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次跟白井和初春一起來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.10,0:19:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.40,0:19:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 我們走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.54,0:19:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 這裡的門...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.02,0:19:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記得來的時候不是拉門啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.98,0:19:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.71,0:19:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 御坂
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.72,0:19:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不像你啊 居然上課時打瞌睡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.34,0:19:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.66,0:19:59.94,*Default3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.23,0:20:01.40,*Default3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真少見
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.17,0:20:00.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 快坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.19,0:20:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你們也安靜點
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.37,0:20:03.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連這種地方都...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.98,0:20:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.97,0:20:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御坂學姐 難道又感覺到了？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.67,0:20:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒 完全沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.89,0:20:25.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.27,0:20:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.32,0:20:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.81,0:20:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.04,0:20:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.70,0:21:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.00,0:21:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查到了什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.25,0:21:23.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回來啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.82,0:21:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.81,0:21:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐天送來的犒勞品
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.15,0:21:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有白井的份 給
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.02,0:21:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.58,0:21:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為能力限定不了 說不准
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.71,0:21:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒能在數據庫確認到相應的能力和能力者
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.54,0:21:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能查的地方都查過了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.83,0:21:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不是能力者做的話
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.50,0:22:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初春 還想你幫忙查一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.71,0:22:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.82,0:22:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人 難得星期天
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.76,0:22:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼早上哪裡呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.86,0:22:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.11,0:22:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去買東西罷了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.31,0:22:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.76,0:22:35.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶爾想一個人閒逛一下
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.70,0:22:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.48,0:22:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是黑子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.76,0:22:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對象開始行動了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.82,0:22:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊已經確認了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.60,0:22:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目標呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.77,0:22:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前正在追蹤
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.24,0:22:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正逐漸接近對象
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.46,0:22:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託你調查的東西呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.30,0:22:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在平行作業
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.62,0:22:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還剩一點了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.66,0:22:57.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.82,0:22:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然棋子還沒集齊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.92,0:23:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來就要隨機應變
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.44,0:23:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託你們了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.77,0:23:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.78,0:23:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見鬼「老大哥在看著你」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.06,0:23:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要看就隨你看
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.85,0:23:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.46,0:23:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會再回頭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.64,0:23:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.34,0:23:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來...了！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.73,0:23:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這條路是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.18,0:23:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 御坂學姐 一大早的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.00,0:24:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 我之前說的捷徑嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.12,0:24:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在這條路完全成了單行道
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.13,0:24:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果真的有人在看我的話
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.54,0:24:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必定在前面
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.43,0:24:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到...你了？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.75,0:24:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你是怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.26,0:24:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警備員？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.46,0:24:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 你是之前在公園那個...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.53,0:24:36.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 而且還是上次見過的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.78,0:24:38.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底在這裡幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.48,0:24:43.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不 那個 沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.72,0:24:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實是有個都市傳說叫「老大哥在看著你」
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.59,0:24:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想揭發那個的真相
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.06,0:24:56.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「老大哥在看著你」？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.76,0:24:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.39,0:25:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你相信這無憑無據的都市傳說 就到這裡了？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.19,0:25:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非也
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.90,0:25:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這並不是什麼都市傳說
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.91,0:25:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑子 為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.51,0:25:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「老大哥在看著你」根本就是犯罪行為
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.45,0:25:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這件事你應該最清楚不過吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.72,0:25:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「老大哥」本人
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.08,0:25:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 警備員兼長點上機學園前能力開發主管
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.20,0:25:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,城南朝來
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.67,0:25:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.21,0:25:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 城南 你認識她？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.62,0:25:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 那個...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.10,0:25:36.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓姐姐大人遭罪的視線
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.87,0:25:39.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其真身就是電磁波吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.51,0:25:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本姐姐大人...發電系能力者
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.76,0:25:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擁有辨別與其能力有關的各種現象
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.98,0:25:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說 自然界存在的各種電場 磁場
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.51,0:25:55.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有電磁波
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.51,0:25:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管願意與否
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.95,0:26:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能力者平常都會在無意識中處理這些辨識到的現象
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.97,0:26:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你反過來利用這點
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.21,0:26:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做出了一個發射讓他們最不舒服的波長的裝置
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.44,0:26:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓接受方誤以為是別人的視線
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.76,0:26:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你有什麼根據
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.32,0:26:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「關於發電能力者的特殊知覺及其應用」
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.61,0:26:25.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耐人尋味的論文呢
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.71,0:26:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 我們也只是剛找到 沒能通讀全文
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.66,0:26:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.66,0:26:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明顯就有古怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.47,0:26:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這部機器
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.00,0:26:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能說明一下是用來幹什麼的麼
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.42,0:26:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 城南 這到底是怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.58,0:26:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼說
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.01,0:26:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這場騷動的元兇 就是你咯
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.79,0:26:57.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不斷對同系統的能力者進行實驗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.36,0:27:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,經過幻想御手事件的風波後
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.33,0:27:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最終將姐姐大人定為目標
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.74,0:27:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在學生佔全人口80%的這座城市裡
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.06,0:27:11.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是加強管制期間中的警備員的話
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.43,0:27:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自然能輕易地接觸到她了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.44,0:27:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.49,0:27:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炸彈？想自爆麼
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.48,0:27:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種東西 看我轟它到樓頂
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.62,0:27:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎 怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.39,0:27:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白井 御坂學姐 怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.66,0:27:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白井 御坂學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.00,0:27:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初春 初春 聽得見麼
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.02,0:27:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白井
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.58,0:27:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們中了城南的音響閃光彈
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.65,0:27:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,視覺和聽覺暫時失效了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.24,0:27:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你聽得見的話
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.11,0:27:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請馬上去追城南
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.55,0:27:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.05,0:27:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 從這裡的話
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.94,0:28:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 居然這麼快就露餡了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.98,0:28:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑去哪裡
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.25,0:28:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整座城市都是攝像頭和警備員
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.81,0:28:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 這裡就算ok了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.82,0:28:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 那接下來...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.75,0:28:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊的學生
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.33,0:28:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是警備員
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.50,0:28:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了調查事件 借用你們的快艇
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.79,0:28:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 等等
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.96,0:28:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼突然 我們很難做的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.38,0:28:26.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過後跟你們學校聯繫
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.48,0:28:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快解開繩子
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.69,0:28:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝 過後寄感謝信給你們
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.38,0:28:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 夠幸運的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:42.50,0:28:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣就不會有人發現
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.13,0:28:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能一口氣去到學區外
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.26,0:28:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暫時先逃出學園都市
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.50,0:28:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等風頭過去後 肯定會再...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.41,0:28:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼你會在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.11,0:29:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼我會在這裡？
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.31,0:29:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為你 也被人看著呢
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.46,0:29:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 快艇太犯規了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.12,0:29:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結束了～
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.71,0:30:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎 怎麼這樣 我受不起啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.34,0:30:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別客氣別客氣 這次是你的功勞
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.60,0:30:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們也別客氣 儘管吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.43,0:30:08.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.96,0:30:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 這麼多Pasticceria Manicagni的限定蛋糕
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.32,0:30:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來 像長點上機這種名校的老師
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.54,0:30:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到被解雇後會惱羞成怒 做出那種事來
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.20,0:30:27.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,長點上機學園在能力開發方面
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.09,0:30:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是學園都市No.1的名校
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.56,0:30:34.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此 作為能力開發主管
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.65,0:30:36.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,培養不出超能力者
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.65,0:30:36.51,*Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(482,436)}<Level 5>
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.66,0:30:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壓力應該很大吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.61,0:30:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然不知道解雇她的真正理由
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.72,0:30:46.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同為名校的常盤臺 卻擁有兩個超能力者
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.72,0:30:46.68,*Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(618,436)}<Level 5>
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.29,0:30:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中還有這麼出名的姐姐大人
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.25,0:30:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記恨她的理由 估計也是八九不離十了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.42,0:30:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...不過話說回來
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.87,0:31:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真虧你能察覺到受害者全是發電系能力者
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.12,0:31:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.42,0:31:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 「如果不是能力者做的話
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.79,0:31:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那應該就是開發方」的推理太讚了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.45,0:31:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,印證我觀點的是你吧 初春
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.88,0:31:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有在調查期間 一直關注著姐姐大人的佐天
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.50,0:31:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果大家不齊心協力的話
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.28,0:31:24.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次事件是解決不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.92,0:31:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒 沒有啦
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.20,0:31:30.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過還是比不過白井啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.78,0:31:34.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在詢問途中 害怕「老大哥」出現
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.21,0:31:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,專門去收費浴場看一下御坂學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.82,0:31:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他還有...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.92,0:31:40.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等 初春...初春
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.01,0:31:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一說到要守護御坂學姐
Dialogue: 0,0:31:41.37,0:31:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就無論何時何地
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.37,0:31:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待在「老大哥」可能出現的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.53,0:31:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那才是24小時全天候關注啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.17,0:31:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是絕對模仿不來的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.47,0:31:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初春 你是故意的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.23,0:32:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就覺得奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.61,0:32:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算有人盯著我
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.36,0:32:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進到更衣室和房間也太扯了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.44,0:32:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐...姐姐大人
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.30,0:32:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是那個...誤...會
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.81,0:32:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,覺悟
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.42,0:32:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.87,0:32:20.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.58,0:32:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.74,0:32:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死變態！
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.39,0:32:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正因為這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.94,0:32:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才無法放棄當姐姐大人的馬前卒啊～



