[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.0.1
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title:诸神字幕
Original Script:诸神字幕组
Original Timing:Maize
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1920
PlayResY:1080
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: JP,EPSON 正楷書体Ｍ,56,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,0,0,66,128
Style: JP-furigana,EPSON 正楷書体Ｍ,27.5,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0.5,2,0,0,50,128
Style: CN,方正楷体_GBK,60,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,0,0,2,134
Style: Disclaimer,方正准圆_GBK,50,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: title,@方正楷体_GBK,90,&H00000000,&HFF103A19,&H96027206,&H96027206,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,1,1,0,8,30,100,50,134
Style: TOP,方正准圆_GBK,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 1,0:00:11.05,0:00:13.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寒っ もう冬の風だなぁ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.61,0:00:17.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全く 相変わらず軟弱なやつだ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.57,0:00:20.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そもそも そんな鉛筆のような図体してるから
Dialogue: 1,0:00:20.49,0:00:22.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寒さに弱いのだ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.18,0:00:24.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生のほうこそ 冬眠でもするつもりか
Dialogue: 1,0:00:25.07,0:00:26.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉襦袢でブクブクだぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:27.12,0:00:27.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だと
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.18,0:00:30.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これは肉ではない 毛だ 毛
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.91,0:00:33.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冬毛というものを知らんのか 全く
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.95,0:00:37.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その割には ここ最近 更に重くなってる気がするけど
Dialogue: 1,0:00:41.52,0:00:43.77,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,トンボ トンボだぞ 夏目
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.93,0:00:45.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待って 待って 待って
Dialogue: 1,0:00:45.49,0:00:46.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい おい 先生
Dialogue: 1,0:00:46.79,0:00:50.19,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,トンボちゃん 待って トンボ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.53,0:00:53.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがないなぁ もう
Dialogue: 1,0:01:00.02,0:01:04.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,トン トン トン ボ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:54.53,0:00:58.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 1,0:01:11.85,0:01:16.11,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっ こ こら やめか くすぐったい 夏 夏目
Dialogue: 1,0:01:16.31,0:01:19.07,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いくら私の冬毛がぷりちでモコモコだから
Dialogue: 1,0:01:19.24,0:01:23.50,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懐くな 苦しい 止せんか 夏目
Dialogue: 1,0:01:23.72,0:01:24.48,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えぃ？
Dialogue: 1,0:01:26.00,0:01:27.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狸掴まえたぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:01:28.77,0:01:29.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狸
Dialogue: 1,0:01:30.49,0:01:32.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何者だ
Dialogue: 1,0:01:32.50,0:01:35.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あっ 狸 お話しした
Dialogue: 1,0:01:35.37,0:01:37.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あっ 本当だ
Dialogue: 1,0:01:39.51,0:01:40.56,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何者だ
Dialogue: 1,0:02:09.29,0:02:11.69,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よしよし 痛くない 痛くない
Dialogue: 1,0:02:12.11,0:02:15.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣くなよ もう 泣いちゃいけないんだぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:02:16.00,0:02:18.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お兄ちゃんなんだからなぁ
Dialogue: 1,0:02:18.29,0:02:21.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣いたら 一つ目の鬼が来るんだからなぁ
Dialogue: 1,0:02:22.14,0:02:23.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一つ目？
Dialogue: 1,0:02:23.26,0:02:25.61,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,取って頂戴
Dialogue: 1,0:02:27.42,0:02:30.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NO NO これは 堪らん
Dialogue: 1,0:02:30.49,0:02:35.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,付き合ってられるか 今の内に抜き足差し足 ガット
Dialogue: 1,0:02:47.75,0:02:49.56,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面倒な人の子め
Dialogue: 1,0:02:51.21,0:02:52.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前ら
Dialogue: 1,0:02:52.44,0:02:54.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腹が空いてるなら 私が相手になるぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:02:55.31,0:02:57.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こいつらは私のおやつだ 
Dialogue: 1,0:02:57.16,0:02:58.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪我をしたくなかったら
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 1,0:02:59.00,0:03:02.15,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこらで獣の他食いでもお相手にするんだなぁ
Dialogue: 1,0:03:16.49,0:03:17.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,低級どもめが
Dialogue: 1,0:03:24.50,0:03:27.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狸は子供を食べるの？
Dialogue: 1,0:03:27.33,0:03:30.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食べるか それに私は狸ではない
Dialogue: 1,0:03:30.70,0:03:32.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱりお話しした
Dialogue: 1,0:03:34.37,0:03:35.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何者だ
Dialogue: 1,0:03:36.04,0:03:38.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やれやれ 仕方あるまい
Dialogue: 1,0:03:38.25,0:03:40.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだそうだ 喋る狸だ
Dialogue: 1,0:03:40.95,0:03:42.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文句あるかい
Dialogue: 1,0:03:47.80,0:03:51.56,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すごい ずるずる ふかふか ぽよぽよだ
Dialogue: 1,0:03:51.95,0:03:56.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}滑べ ブヨブヨ
Dialogue: 1,0:03:52.47,0:03:56.69,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大体 お前らみたいな幼い人の子がこんな山奥に
Dialogue: 1,0:03:56.90,0:03:59.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何をやっているのだ やめん
Dialogue: 1,0:04:00.15,0:04:01.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お使いなのだ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:01.92,0:04:03.87,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三ッ森ストアに行くのだ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:04.14,0:04:06.09,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三ッ森スター？
Dialogue: 1,0:04:06.29,0:04:08.56,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,違うよ 三ッ森ストア
Dialogue: 1,0:04:08.76,0:04:10.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三ッ森スドー？
Dialogue: 1,0:04:10.57,0:04:13.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これだから 人の子は苦手なのだ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:13.68,0:04:17.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ともかく こんな妖かし物だらけの森は離れて
Dialogue: 1,0:04:17.47,0:04:21.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人の子の扱いが上手いやつを探しとするかなぁ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:36.95,0:04:40.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こ こら そんなに引っ張ったら 苦しいだろうが
Dialogue: 1,0:04:40.46,0:04:41.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっ やめ こら
Dialogue: 1,0:04:42.78,0:04:46.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全く 先生のやつ どこまで行ったんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:48.13,0:04:51.34,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おお 夏目 何キョロキョロしてるんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:51.53,0:04:53.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どっかに可愛い子ちゃんでもいるのか
Dialogue: 1,0:04:54.13,0:04:56.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何言ってんだよ お前じゃあるまいし
Dialogue: 1,0:04:56.57,0:04:59.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だと 人聞きの悪いことを言うな
Dialogue: 1,0:04:59.55,0:05:01.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,言ってんのは西村だろう
Dialogue: 1,0:05:01.91,0:05:04.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うちのニャンコ先生 見なかったか？
Dialogue: 1,0:05:04.51,0:05:06.39,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おお ニャンニャン先生か？
Dialogue: 1,0:05:06.53,0:05:09.09,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ううん 見なかったけどなぁ
Dialogue: 1,0:05:09.30,0:05:11.42,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だ 行方不明か
Dialogue: 1,0:05:11.62,0:05:13.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捜索隊 結成するか
Dialogue: 1,0:05:14.94,0:05:17.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや いいんだ いつもこんな感じだし
Dialogue: 1,0:05:18.01,0:05:19.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そのうち 帰ってくるだろう
Dialogue: 1,0:05:19.77,0:05:22.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうそう 夕飯には戻るだろう
Dialogue: 1,0:05:22.35,0:05:23.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食い意地張ってるもんなぁ
Dialogue: 1,0:05:24.06,0:05:25.42,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確かに 
Dialogue: 1,0:05:29.36,0:05:33.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全く そろそろ知った顔に出会っても良さそうなもんだが
Dialogue: 1,0:05:38.22,0:05:41.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん？ ど ど どこに どこに行った？
Dialogue: 1,0:05:43.15,0:05:46.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}よいしょ よいしょ
Dialogue: 1,0:05:44.84,0:05:47.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NO やめ こ こら
Dialogue: 1,0:05:58.14,0:06:01.77,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こ こ こら やめ くすぐったい
Dialogue: 1,0:06:01.98,0:06:04.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,は は 放せ 放せて ちょっと
Dialogue: 1,0:06:05.45,0:06:07.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}帽子 帽子
Dialogue: 1,0:06:06.18,0:06:06.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NO
Dialogue: 1,0:06:07.16,0:06:09.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やめか こら
Dialogue: 1,0:06:22.33,0:06:26.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何で 私が こんな目に
Dialogue: 1,0:06:27.64,0:06:30.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おや 斑様ではございませんか
Dialogue: 1,0:06:30.69,0:06:32.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今日はまた良いお日和で
Dialogue: 1,0:06:33.05,0:06:35.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お日和 お昼なり
Dialogue: 1,0:06:35.95,0:06:39.42,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前たち 助かった 
Dialogue: 1,0:06:48.32,0:06:51.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そう言えば普通の人の子には見えないんだった
Dialogue: 1,0:06:51.85,0:06:54.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そもそも夏目のやつが変わり者なのだ
Dialogue: 1,0:06:55.75,0:06:59.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん？人の子など連れて 晩酌の用意でございますか
Dialogue: 1,0:06:59.88,0:07:02.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,つまみ おつまみ
Dialogue: 1,0:07:02.63,0:07:05.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好きで連れ歩いているのではない 全く
Dialogue: 1,0:07:05.85,0:07:09.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだ お前たちに聞きたいことがあったのだ
Dialogue: 1,0:07:10.52,0:07:11.87,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それはお珍しい
Dialogue: 1,0:07:12.05,0:07:14.68,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我々に分かることなら何なりと
Dialogue: 1,0:07:14.87,0:07:17.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何なり ぼんやり
Dialogue: 1,0:07:17.73,0:07:20.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい 人の子 ちょっと こっち 来い
Dialogue: 1,0:07:20.69,0:07:22.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何者だ
Dialogue: 1,0:07:23.58,0:07:26.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前たち どこに行きたいんだった？
Dialogue: 1,0:07:26.82,0:07:28.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう一度言ってみろ
Dialogue: 1,0:07:28.28,0:07:30.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へえ 何で
Dialogue: 1,0:07:30.36,0:07:31.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さっき言ったもん
Dialogue: 1,0:07:31.85,0:07:33.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいから 言ってみんか
Dialogue: 1,0:07:33.81,0:07:38.77,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へえ ええとね ハムとね 乳乳買うの
Dialogue: 1,0:07:38.96,0:07:41.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それと ぱくりんチョコも買っていいって
Dialogue: 1,0:07:42.76,0:07:44.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ぱくりんチョ？ 乳乳？
Dialogue: 1,0:07:45.11,0:07:47.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それでね 三ッ森ストアに行くの
Dialogue: 1,0:07:47.93,0:07:50.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ママがね 歩いてすぐだからって
Dialogue: 1,0:07:53.84,0:07:57.39,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そういうわけだ お前たちならこいつらの言ってることを
Dialogue: 1,0:07:57.56,0:07:58.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分かるだろう
Dialogue: 1,0:07:58.57,0:08:01.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいや そんな 無茶振りですって
Dialogue: 1,0:08:01.78,0:08:04.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無茶振り 無茶無理
Dialogue: 1,0:08:04.73,0:08:07.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この役たたずどもめ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:14.88,0:08:17.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ そう そう言えば 先程
Dialogue: 1,0:08:17.54,0:08:21.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この先の大岩の辺りで丙殿にお会いしましたぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:21.20,0:08:23.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あのお方ならば あるいは
Dialogue: 1,0:08:23.36,0:08:25.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ならば バトンタッチ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:39.54,0:08:41.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お待たせ 柊
Dialogue: 1,0:08:44.20,0:08:45.77,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん？何か？
Dialogue: 1,0:08:45.98,0:08:50.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいえ 主様でもそういった者がお好きなのだなぁっと
Dialogue: 1,0:08:50.40,0:08:51.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ これかい？
Dialogue: 1,0:08:52.12,0:08:55.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,子供の頃からこれだけは止められなくてねえ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:55.50,0:08:56.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ぱくりんチョコ
Dialogue: 1,0:09:05.30,0:09:08.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全く そろそろ中級どもが言っていた
Dialogue: 1,0:09:08.65,0:09:11.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大岩の辺りに出ても良さそうなものだが
Dialogue: 1,0:09:17.60,0:09:19.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう 歩けない 抱っこ 
Dialogue: 1,0:09:20.06,0:09:22.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ええ 嫌だよ 僕だって
Dialogue: 1,0:09:29.44,0:09:32.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よしよし 痛くない痛くない
Dialogue: 1,0:09:32.44,0:09:34.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,い 痛くないもん
Dialogue: 1,0:09:36.49,0:09:41.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣くなよ もう 泣いちゃいけないんだぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:09:43.40,0:09:45.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これは 堪らん
Dialogue: 1,0:09:45.71,0:09:49.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう 付き合いきれん 私は逃げるぞ 逃げるぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:09:52.56,0:09:55.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱っこ 抱っこ
Dialogue: 1,0:09:55.86,0:10:00.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっ ちょっ わっ わっ 分かった しかし
Dialogue: 1,0:10:00.49,0:10:09.07,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて おんぶにしてくれ してくれ してくれ
Dialogue: 1,0:10:13.79,0:10:16.15,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確か こっちの方に
Dialogue: 1,0:10:17.87,0:10:19.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あれ？ 夏目じゃないか
Dialogue: 1,0:10:20.22,0:10:20.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 1,0:10:21.17,0:10:24.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散歩か 今日は暖かいもんなぁ
Dialogue: 1,0:10:24.22,0:10:26.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ そうなんだけど
Dialogue: 1,0:10:26.22,0:10:28.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生と はぐれちゃって
Dialogue: 1,0:10:28.41,0:10:29.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ポン太か
Dialogue: 1,0:10:29.39,0:10:32.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此処に来るまででは ちょっと見なかったなぁ
Dialogue: 1,0:10:33.04,0:10:34.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうか いや いいんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:10:35.11,0:10:38.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いつものことだし 晩ご飯までには戻るだろう
Dialogue: 1,0:10:38.94,0:10:40.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だろうなぁ
Dialogue: 1,0:10:40.21,0:10:44.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの先生が塔子さんの晩飯を逃すはずがない
Dialogue: 1,0:10:44.20,0:10:45.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全く
Dialogue: 1,0:10:59.92,0:11:01.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ど どこに行った
Dialogue: 1,0:11:02.54,0:11:03.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よいしょ
Dialogue: 1,0:11:04.26,0:11:09.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NO やめんか こら やめんか
Dialogue: 1,0:11:14.49,0:11:18.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こら やめんか くすぐたい 放せ 放せ
Dialogue: 1,0:11:20.11,0:11:21.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴロゴロ
Dialogue: 1,0:11:22.01,0:11:25.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NO ストップ ストップ ストップ
Dialogue: 1,0:11:37.80,0:11:41.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何で 私がこんな目に
Dialogue: 1,0:11:39.15,0:11:42.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}もう一回 待って 待って
Dialogue: 1,0:11:43.07,0:11:46.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おいや ネコだるま 妙な所で合うじゃないか
Dialogue: 1,0:11:46.73,0:11:49.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丙か 助かった
Dialogue: 1,0:11:50.55,0:11:54.07,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前 この下の大岩の辺りにいると聞いたが
Dialogue: 1,0:11:54.99,0:11:57.68,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あたし 朝からずっとここにいたけどね
Dialogue: 1,0:12:01.84,0:12:03.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中級どもめ
Dialogue: 1,0:12:03.79,0:12:06.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの二人の言い草を呑みにするとは
Dialogue: 1,0:12:06.32,0:12:08.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前もヤキが回ったね
Dialogue: 1,0:12:09.00,0:12:12.48,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それはそうと 人の子なぞ連れて何だい
Dialogue: 1,0:12:12.65,0:12:14.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それはおやつかい
Dialogue: 1,0:12:14.40,0:12:18.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好きで連れ歩いてるのではない 全く
Dialogue: 1,0:12:18.57,0:12:22.11,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おお そうだ お前に聞きたいことがあったのだ
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 1,0:12:22.30,0:12:25.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい 人の子 ちょっと こっち 来い
Dialogue: 1,0:12:27.75,0:12:28.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何者だ
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 1,0:12:29.77,0:12:32.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前たち どこに行きたいんだった 
Dialogue: 1,0:12:32.73,0:12:33.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう一度言ってみろ
Dialogue: 1,0:12:33.82,0:12:35.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へえ また？
Dialogue: 1,0:12:36.14,0:12:37.56,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さっき 言ったもん
Dialogue: 1,0:12:38.52,0:12:40.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいから 言ってみるか
Dialogue: 1,0:12:40.43,0:12:45.39,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ええとね 三ッ森ストアはね おれんちから 真っすぐだって
Dialogue: 1,0:12:45.55,0:12:48.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それと ぱくりんチョコも買っていいって
Dialogue: 1,0:12:49.29,0:12:54.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まあまあ よし ここは一つ この丙様が占って信ぜよう
Dialogue: 1,0:12:55.44,0:12:57.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当か たっ頼む
Dialogue: 1,0:12:57.28,0:13:00.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今度ばかりはお前の背に毫光が射して見えるぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:13:01.11,0:13:02.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見ておいで
Dialogue: 1,0:13:25.24,0:13:27.41,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さって これでよし
Dialogue: 1,0:13:30.59,0:13:32.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんなんの これ 変なの
Dialogue: 1,0:13:33.33,0:13:36.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何をするんだい この人の子め
Dialogue: 1,0:13:37.38,0:13:40.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,落ち着け 落ち着け いや 悪かった 悪かった
Dialogue: 1,0:13:40.69,0:13:43.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,落ち着いてくれ 頼む まぁ 
Dialogue: 1,0:13:52.69,0:13:54.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捜し物は艮の方角だね
Dialogue: 1,0:13:54.75,0:13:56.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艮？ 北東か
Dialogue: 1,0:13:56.81,0:14:01.15,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あぁ 何やら強い気の持ち主が助けるだろうとあるぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:14:01.34,0:14:03.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何と それは心強い
Dialogue: 1,0:14:03.67,0:14:06.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まぁ 道中気をつけるんだねぇ
Dialogue: 1,0:14:06.56,0:14:08.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その強い気の持ち主ってんのも
Dialogue: 1,0:14:08.99,0:14:11.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一筋縄じゃ行かないやつかもしれないしね
Dialogue: 1,0:14:23.06,0:14:24.42,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あら 夏目君 
Dialogue: 1,0:14:24.65,0:14:26.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田 多軌
Dialogue: 1,0:14:26.24,0:14:27.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶然ね
Dialogue: 1,0:14:27.59,0:14:29.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あぁ 買い物？
Dialogue: 1,0:14:30.48,0:14:34.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それがね これこれ ぱくりんチョコ
Dialogue: 1,0:14:35.31,0:14:38.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多軌ちゃんと話してたら食べたことないって言うから
Dialogue: 1,0:14:38.59,0:14:41.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だって一度食べたら病み付きだって
Dialogue: 1,0:14:42.12,0:14:46.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当なんだってば 知らない方が不思議なくらい
Dialogue: 1,0:14:46.23,0:14:48.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君は？ 食べたことあるでしょう
Dialogue: 1,0:14:49.05,0:14:54.19,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや 同級生が食べてるのは見たことがあった かな
Dialogue: 1,0:14:54.39,0:14:56.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へえ そうなんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:14:58.03,0:15:00.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃ これ 一本あげる
Dialogue: 1,0:15:00.87,0:15:03.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あぁ ありがとう
Dialogue: 1,0:15:04.08,0:15:06.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中毒になっても知らないからね
Dialogue: 1,0:15:07.05,0:15:09.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃぁ 月曜日 学校でね
Dialogue: 1,0:15:09.71,0:15:17.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あぁ あっ そうだ この辺でニャンコ先生見かけなかったか
Dialogue: 1,0:15:17.81,0:15:20.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へえ つるふか先生がどうかしたの
Dialogue: 1,0:15:20.68,0:15:24.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや ただ 散歩中にはぐれただけなんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:24.21,0:15:29.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だ ブサイクちゃんなら晩ご飯には戻って来るんじゃないの
Dialogue: 1,0:15:29.22,0:15:31.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あぁ 俺もそう思うよ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:31.66,0:15:34.56,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも 何となく ちょっと 今 
Dialogue: 1,0:15:34.75,0:15:38.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何時になくピンチに陥ってる気がしてさぁ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:50.20,0:15:52.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全く そろそろ丙が言っていた
Dialogue: 1,0:15:52.75,0:15:56.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,強い気の助っ人に出会っても良さそうなもんだが
Dialogue: 1,0:16:01.33,0:16:03.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう 歩けない
Dialogue: 1,0:16:07.18,0:16:11.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣くなよ もう 泣いちゃいけないんだぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:16:13.70,0:16:14.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こりゃ 堪らん 
Dialogue: 1,0:16:15.15,0:16:20.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう 付き合いきれん 早く 助っ人よ 現れてくれん
Dialogue: 1,0:16:20.66,0:16:24.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おおや 何やら騒がしいと思えば
Dialogue: 1,0:16:24.72,0:16:29.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんな所に鏡餅が 奇っ怪なこともあるものであります
Dialogue: 1,0:16:30.46,0:16:34.68,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっ ちょび髭 強い気の助っ人というのは貴様か
Dialogue: 1,0:16:34.86,0:16:37.87,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何のことやら分かりませぬが
Dialogue: 1,0:16:38.04,0:16:42.34,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この辺りでは私ほどの高貴な身の物はおりませぬゆえ
Dialogue: 1,0:16:42.51,0:16:45.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それは私のことでありましょう
Dialogue: 1,0:16:45.33,0:16:49.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何を生意気な 大体私は鏡餅ではない
Dialogue: 1,0:16:49.64,0:16:52.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食えるか 食えんのか ホレホレ
Dialogue: 1,0:16:52.97,0:16:56.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そのような薄汚れた鏡餅を頂いたら
Dialogue: 1,0:16:56.80,0:16:59.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,良い年は迎えられないのであります
Dialogue: 1,0:17:00.37,0:17:05.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう それにしても 夏目殿の隠れてつまみ食いでありますか
Dialogue: 1,0:17:05.61,0:17:08.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やはり 根分けものなのであります
Dialogue: 1,0:17:08.41,0:17:11.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんなことだから ぶくぶくと大きくなるのであります
Dialogue: 1,0:17:11.70,0:17:13.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好きで連れ歩いているのではない
Dialogue: 1,0:17:14.15,0:17:18.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全く そうだ お前が助っ人というなら
Dialogue: 1,0:17:18.21,0:17:20.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この謎に答えてもらおう
Dialogue: 1,0:17:20.29,0:17:21.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい 人の子
Dialogue: 1,0:17:24.05,0:17:25.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何者だ
Dialogue: 1,0:17:25.46,0:17:29.48,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,煩い お前たち どこに行こうとしていたのだ
Dialogue: 1,0:17:29.66,0:17:31.15,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう一度 言ってみろ
Dialogue: 1,0:17:31.32,0:17:37.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あのね お使いなの 俺ね ぱくりんチョコ 大好きなの
Dialogue: 1,0:17:37.60,0:17:39.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三ッ森ストアにあるの
Dialogue: 1,0:17:39.83,0:17:41.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だから買うの
Dialogue: 1,0:17:42.09,0:17:46.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三つ子の魂百まで的なあれでありましょうか
Dialogue: 1,0:17:46.77,0:17:50.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんな ちんまいのが そんな恨みごと抱えてたら 世も末だわ
Dialogue: 1,0:17:50.80,0:17:55.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それを言うなら 水が染みたら白米ホクホクって感じだろうなぁ
Dialogue: 1,0:17:55.36,0:17:58.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何のことやら さっぱりなのであります
Dialogue: 1,0:17:58.79,0:18:01.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっかましい ならば お前の方こそ 
Dialogue: 1,0:18:01.49,0:18:03.50,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっと 上手いことを言ってみろ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:03.65,0:18:08.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ホレホレホレ どうだ 言えまい ほれ 言ってみろうって ホレホレ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:08.38,0:18:10.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水も滴るいい女 
Dialogue: 1,0:18:10.97,0:18:13.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三つ数えて１，２，３
Dialogue: 1,0:18:13.67,0:18:16.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三つの句振ったり度
Dialogue: 1,0:18:16.77,0:18:18.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だ そりゃ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:23.91,0:18:28.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三ッ森ストア ハム 牛乳 竹輪 パクリんチョコ二個
Dialogue: 1,0:18:28.91,0:18:30.11,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だ そりゃ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:30.26,0:18:35.07,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これは初めてのお使い的な物でありますな
Dialogue: 1,0:18:48.87,0:18:51.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あそこなのであります
Dialogue: 1,0:18:51.57,0:18:53.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三ッ森ストアだ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:53.19,0:18:54.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三ッ森ストアだ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:56.33,0:18:59.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい 飛び出したら危ないぞ 気をつけろう
Dialogue: 1,0:19:07.35,0:19:16.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全く 役に立ったんだか何だか分からんが 世話になったなぁ
Dialogue: 1,0:19:16.46,0:19:20.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょび髭 この借りは何れ返してやる
Dialogue: 1,0:19:20.24,0:19:23.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何時でも来いなのであります
Dialogue: 1,0:19:29.30,0:19:30.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんでいるの 
Dialogue: 1,0:19:30.95,0:19:31.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,マアマア
Dialogue: 1,0:19:32.15,0:19:35.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どこで寄り道してたの もう真っ黒になって
Dialogue: 1,0:19:36.04,0:19:39.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あまんり 遅いから 心配したんだから
Dialogue: 1,0:19:40.27,0:19:43.61,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,良かったね マアマアはずっと探してたんだぞう
Dialogue: 1,0:19:43.78,0:19:48.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,マアマア あのね 狸さんがね おんぶしてくれた
Dialogue: 1,0:19:48.36,0:19:50.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだよ 喋るんだよ
Dialogue: 1,0:19:51.11,0:19:54.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後ね 紐で引っ張ってくれた
Dialogue: 1,0:19:54.40,0:19:59.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうねぇ そうねぇ よかったねぇ 無事で良かった 本当に
Dialogue: 1,0:20:00.91,0:20:02.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次は一緒に来ようね
Dialogue: 1,0:20:02.86,0:20:03.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだね
Dialogue: 1,0:20:06.34,0:20:10.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あら 猫ちゃん 今日はこんな所までお散歩？
Dialogue: 1,0:20:35.67,0:20:36.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お帰り
Dialogue: 1,0:20:37.94,0:20:38.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ただいま
Dialogue: 1,0:20:40.36,0:20:42.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうしたの お出迎え
Dialogue: 1,0:20:42.74,0:20:45.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいえ はい お帰りなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.05,0:00:13.27,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好冷 已经入冬了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.61,0:00:17.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 还是那么弱不禁风
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.57,0:00:20.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是因为瘦得跟铅笔似的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.49,0:00:22.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才这么怕冷
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.18,0:00:24.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师你才是要冬眠的节奏吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.07,0:00:26.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉制衬衫又膨胀了一号的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.12,0:00:27.96,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说神马
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.18,0:00:30.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是肉好么 是毛 毛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.91,0:00:33.81,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然不知道有冬毛 真是孤陋寡闻
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.95,0:00:37.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是么 那怎么感觉你最近又重了些啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.52,0:00:43.77,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜻蜓 是蜻蜓 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.93,0:00:45.40,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 等等 等等
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.49,0:00:46.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 喂 老师
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.79,0:00:50.19,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小蜻蜓 等等我 蜻蜓
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.53,0:00:53.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真拿你没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.02,0:01:04.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜻 蜓 酱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.65,0:00:58.56,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur4\pos(1741,490)}猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.65,0:00:58.56,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur4\pos(1082,706)}和
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.65,0:00:58.56,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur4\pos(314,482)}初次跑腿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.85,0:01:16.11,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手  好痒 夏 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.31,0:01:19.07,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管我的冬毛如此松软可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.24,0:01:23.50,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别贴着我 好痒 住手 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.72,0:01:24.48,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.00,0:01:27.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我抓住狸猫了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.77,0:01:29.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狸猫
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.49,0:01:32.30,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.50,0:01:35.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 狸猫说话了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.37,0:01:37.01,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的耶
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.51,0:01:40.56,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.29,0:02:11.69,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了 不痛不痛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.11,0:02:15.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别哭了 真是的 不能哭哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.00,0:02:18.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥在哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.29,0:02:21.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你如果哭的话 就会招来独眼鬼哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.14,0:02:23.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独眼鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.26,0:02:25.61,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一杯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.42,0:02:30.29,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,no no  真是受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.49,0:02:35.94,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才懒得陪你们 就趁现在 开溜
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.75,0:02:49.56,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的小屁孩真是麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.21,0:02:52.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.44,0:02:54.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果想饱腹的话 本大爷来陪你们玩玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.31,0:02:57.01,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是我的下酒菜
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.16,0:02:58.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是不想缺胳膊少腿的话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.00,0:03:02.15,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就到别处找东西吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.49,0:03:17.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乌合之众
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.50,0:03:27.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狸猫也会吃小孩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.33,0:03:30.52,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃个鬼啊 况且本大爷根本不是狸猫
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.70,0:03:32.29,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然会说话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.37,0:03:35.66,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何方妖魔？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.04,0:03:38.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 对待小屁孩不能认真
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.25,0:03:40.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊是啊 我就是会说话的狸猫
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.95,0:03:42.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样 有意见
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.80,0:03:51.56,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 滑滑的 软软的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.95,0:03:56.54,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}滑溜溜 胖乎乎的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.47,0:03:56.69,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这种人类的小孩子来这种深山
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.90,0:03:59.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底想干嘛 快停手
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.15,0:04:01.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是来跑腿的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.92,0:04:03.87,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去三森商店
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.14,0:04:06.09,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三森星？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.29,0:04:08.56,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 三森商店
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.76,0:04:10.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三森商店
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.57,0:04:13.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说小屁孩真麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.68,0:04:17.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 赶紧先离开这个满是妖怪的森林
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.47,0:04:21.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再去找一个保姆来交接
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.95,0:04:40.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 别牵这么紧 很难受啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.46,0:04:41.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停 住手 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.78,0:04:46.40,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 老师又跑到哪里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.13,0:04:51.34,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 夏目 在东张西望什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.53,0:04:53.94,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里有可爱妹纸吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.13,0:04:56.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢 他又不是你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.57,0:04:59.35,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 别老说我坏话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.55,0:05:01.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若要人不说 除非己莫为
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.91,0:05:04.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有看见我家的猫咪老师吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.51,0:05:06.39,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 喵喵老师啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.53,0:05:09.09,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 没看到
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.30,0:05:11.42,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 不知道去哪了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.62,0:05:13.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要成立搜索队吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.94,0:05:17.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不用了 它总是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.01,0:05:19.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该已经回去了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.77,0:05:22.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 晚饭的时候就该回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.35,0:05:23.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它可是只馋猫
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.06,0:05:25.42,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.36,0:05:33.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是 这么久了居然连个认识的人都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.22,0:05:41.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？ 哪 去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.15,0:05:46.86,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}嘿咻 嘿咻
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.84,0:05:47.30,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,no 别动 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.14,0:06:01.77,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别 别动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.98,0:06:04.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放 放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.45,0:06:07.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}帽子 帽子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.18,0:06:06.94,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,no
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.16,0:06:09.10,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别动 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.33,0:06:26.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我会摊上这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.64,0:06:30.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 这不是斑大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.69,0:06:32.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真是个好天气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.05,0:06:35.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好天气 快起来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.95,0:06:39.42,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你们啊 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.32,0:06:51.63,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来普通的小孩是看不见你们的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.85,0:06:54.72,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目才是不正常的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.75,0:06:59.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 带了小孩子 晚上要一醉方休吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.88,0:07:02.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下酒菜 下酒菜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.63,0:07:05.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是我想把他们带来的 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.85,0:07:09.37,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 有件事要问你们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.52,0:07:11.87,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是稀奇
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.05,0:07:14.68,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等必当知无不言 言无不尽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.87,0:07:17.54,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,言无不尽 尽在不言中
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.73,0:07:20.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 熊孩子 过来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.69,0:07:22.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何方妖魔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.58,0:07:26.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是想去哪来着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.82,0:07:28.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.28,0:07:30.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.36,0:07:31.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚不是说过了么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.85,0:07:33.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  快说
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.81,0:07:38.77,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 那个 是要买火腿和牛奶
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.96,0:07:41.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 也可以买脆心巧克力
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.76,0:07:44.91,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脆心？ 牛奶？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.11,0:07:47.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是要去三森商店
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.93,0:07:50.72,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈说很近的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.84,0:07:57.39,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样 想必你们的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.56,0:07:58.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都应该能听懂吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.57,0:08:01.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 对俺来说就是天方夜谭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.78,0:08:04.52,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天方夜谭 无能为力
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.73,0:08:07.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个废物
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.88,0:08:17.35,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 刚刚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.54,0:08:21.01,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那边的巨石附近看到了丙大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.20,0:08:23.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那位大人或许…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.36,0:08:25.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能 交接完毕
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.54,0:08:41.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了 柊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.20,0:08:45.77,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.98,0:08:50.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 只是没想到主上还喜欢这种东西
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.40,0:08:51.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.12,0:08:55.29,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从小就只对这个欲罢不能
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.50,0:08:56.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脆心巧克力
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.30,0:09:08.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 算算差不多该到了中级他们说的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.65,0:09:11.72,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巨石附近了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.60,0:09:19.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走不动了 抱抱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.06,0:09:22.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 不要 我也走不动了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.44,0:09:32.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了 不痛不痛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.44,0:09:34.96,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来就不疼嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.49,0:09:41.12,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别哭了 真是的 不能哭哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.40,0:09:45.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.71,0:09:49.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受够了 我管不了了 我要开溜咯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.56,0:09:55.63,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱抱 抱抱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.86,0:10:00.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 喂 好 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.49,0:10:09.07,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我只能背你啊 背你 背你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.79,0:10:16.15,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得好像是这个方向
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.87,0:10:19.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.22,0:10:20.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.17,0:10:24.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在散步吗 今天天气满暖和的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.22,0:10:26.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.22,0:10:28.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师它和我走散了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.41,0:10:29.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胖太吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.39,0:10:32.86,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一路过来 没有遇到过它
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.04,0:10:34.94,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 算了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.11,0:10:38.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正总是这样 晚饭的时候就会回来了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.94,0:10:40.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.21,0:10:44.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它可不会错过塔子阿姨的晚饭
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.20,0:10:45.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真理
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.92,0:11:01.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去 去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.54,0:11:03.91,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿咻
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.26,0:11:09.63,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,no 别动  喂 别动
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.49,0:11:18.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 住手 好痒 放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.11,0:11:21.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚滚滚
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.01,0:11:25.01,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,no 停 停 停下来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.80,0:11:41.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我要摊上这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.15,0:11:42.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}再来一次 等等 等等
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.07,0:11:46.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 这不是猫球吗 怎么会在这里碰见你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.73,0:11:49.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是丙啊 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.55,0:11:54.07,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么听说你在下游的巨石附近啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.99,0:11:57.68,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从早上开始就一直在这呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.84,0:12:03.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的中级家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.79,0:12:06.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然相信那两个人说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.32,0:12:08.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也老马失蹄了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.00,0:12:12.48,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 你为什么把小孩子带到这来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.65,0:12:14.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是点心吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.40,0:12:18.37,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是我想把他们带来的 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.57,0:12:22.11,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 有件事想问你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.30,0:12:25.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 熊孩子 过来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.75,0:12:28.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何方妖孽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.77,0:12:32.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是想去哪来着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.73,0:12:33.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.82,0:12:35.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 又要
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.14,0:12:37.56,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是刚刚说过了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.52,0:12:40.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  快说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.43,0:12:45.39,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 要去三森商店 说是从我们家笔直过去就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.55,0:12:48.40,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 可以买脆心巧克力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.29,0:12:54.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 姑且让本大仙为你们占上一卦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.44,0:12:57.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗 那就拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.28,0:13:00.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在顿时觉得从你的背后闪耀出了万丈金光
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.11,0:13:02.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.24,0:13:27.41,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.59,0:13:32.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么 好奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.33,0:13:36.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么 该死的熊孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.38,0:13:40.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静 冷静啊 抱歉 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.69,0:13:43.37,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你冷静啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.69,0:13:54.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来他们要找到东西在东北方
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.75,0:13:56.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东北方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.81,0:14:01.15,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 在那里会遇到一位可靠的贵人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.34,0:14:03.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗 总算有盼头了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.67,0:14:06.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路上要小心
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.56,0:14:08.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位可靠的贵人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.99,0:14:11.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许不会那么容易就帮你们的忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.06,0:14:24.42,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是夏目同学
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.65,0:14:26.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田 多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.24,0:14:27.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真巧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.59,0:14:29.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来买东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.48,0:14:34.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩 买这个 脆心巧克力
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.31,0:14:38.37,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和多轨说了这个后 她居然说从来没吃过
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.59,0:14:41.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你说这个吃一次就会上瘾什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.12,0:14:46.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的是真的啦 倒是没吃过的人才太不可思议了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.23,0:14:48.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目你吃过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.05,0:14:54.19,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 只看过同学吃过
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.39,0:14:56.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.03,0:15:00.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这个给你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.87,0:15:03.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.08,0:15:06.81,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是上瘾了可别怪我哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.05,0:15:09.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那星期一学校见
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.71,0:15:17.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 有在附近看到猫咪老师吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.81,0:15:20.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 那只手感很好的猫咪老师怎么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.68,0:15:24.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 只是散步的时候走散了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.21,0:15:29.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样 土肥猫晚饭就会回来了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.22,0:15:31.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩 我也是这样想的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.66,0:15:34.56,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 总感觉它现在正…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.75,0:15:38.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摊上了一件麻烦事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.20,0:15:52.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 丙不是说会有贵人来相助吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.75,0:15:56.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么还不来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.33,0:16:03.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经 走不动了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.18,0:16:11.10,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别哭啊 不能哭哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.70,0:16:14.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是受不了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.15,0:16:20.37,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真心干不了了 贵人快快出现吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.66,0:16:24.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 我还以为什么事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.72,0:16:29.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然这里有圆形年糕 怪事年年有 今年特别多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.46,0:16:34.68,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泥 泥鳅胡子 所谓贵人原来就是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.86,0:16:37.87,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.04,0:16:42.34,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这一带再没有高贵如我的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.51,0:16:45.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵人大概就是指我了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.33,0:16:49.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嚣张什么 说起来我才不是年糕
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.64,0:16:52.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能吃掉我吗 来吃我啊 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.97,0:16:56.63,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是吃了这么脏的年糕
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.80,0:16:59.72,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来年肯定倒霉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.37,0:17:05.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 你是在瞒着夏目殿下偷吃点心吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.61,0:17:08.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然江山易改本性难移啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.41,0:17:11.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你才会跟个球似的鼓起来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.70,0:17:13.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是我想把他们带来的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.15,0:17:18.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 如果你就是贵人的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.21,0:17:20.10,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就帮我解开这个谜吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.29,0:17:21.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 熊孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.05,0:17:25.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何方妖孽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.46,0:17:29.48,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烦不烦啊 你们想去哪来着
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.66,0:17:31.15,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.32,0:17:37.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 是去跑腿的 我超爱脆心巧克力
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.60,0:17:39.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三森商店有卖
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.83,0:17:41.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以要去买
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.09,0:17:46.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是类似「三岁看八十」的意思吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.77,0:17:50.63,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种小屁孩要是能说出那样的话 世界末日也就到了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.80,0:17:55.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们最多就只能说说「白米沾水后就成热乎乎的白米饭了」之类的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.36,0:17:58.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是些什么啊 完全不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.79,0:18:01.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少啰嗦 那你来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.49,0:18:03.50,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说点更加上档次的来听听
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.65,0:18:08.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说啊 怎么 不行吧 说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.38,0:18:10.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出水芙蓉好女人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.97,0:18:13.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数三声 1,2,3
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.67,0:18:16.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被逼用「三」来造句
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.77,0:18:18.40,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.91,0:18:28.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三森商店 火腿 牛奶 烤鱼卷 脆心巧克力两个
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.91,0:18:30.11,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.26,0:18:35.07,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这应该是第一次跑腿的购货单吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.87,0:18:51.37,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.57,0:18:53.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三森商店
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.19,0:18:54.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三森商店
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.33,0:18:59.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 别跑这么快 危险 小心点
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.35,0:19:16.29,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 也不知道你是不是贵人 还是谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.46,0:19:20.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泥鳅胡子 改天还你人情
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.24,0:19:23.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随时恭候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.30,0:19:30.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们怎么也在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.95,0:19:31.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.15,0:19:35.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们绕去哪里了 天都黑了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.04,0:19:39.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好久没回来 真是让人担心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.27,0:19:43.61,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事太好了 妈妈一直在找你们哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.78,0:19:48.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 狸猫先生帮助了我们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.36,0:19:50.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对哦 还会说话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.11,0:19:54.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我牵着它
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.40,0:19:59.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 是啊 你们没事真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.91,0:20:02.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次一起来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.86,0:20:03.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.34,0:20:10.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 小猫咪 今天到这散步来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.67,0:20:36.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.94,0:20:38.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.36,0:20:42.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 来接我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.74,0:20:45.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 恩 欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.20,0:01:04.70,Disclaimer,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\blur5}本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)制作,仅供学习交流之用，若您喜欢本作品,请支持正版
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.20,0:01:09.90,Disclaimer,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\blur5}日听：archer   翻译：有明の月   校对：夜神    时间轴：葛蔓    压制：娜夏
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,

Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.05,0:00:13.27,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(693.921875,930)\an8}さむ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.05,0:00:13.27,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}ふゆ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.05,0:00:13.27,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1058.03125,930)\an8}かぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.61,0:00:17.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(609.8984375,930)\an8}まった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.61,0:00:17.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(777.953125,930)\an8}あいか
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.61,0:00:17.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1058.03125,930)\an8}なんじゃく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.57,0:00:20.31,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(861.9765625,930)\an8}えんぴつ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.57,0:00:20.31,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1198.0703125,930)\an8}ずうたい
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.49,0:00:22.02,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.953125,930)\an8}さむ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.49,0:00:22.02,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,930)\an8}よわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.18,0:00:24.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.875,930)\an8}せんせい
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.18,0:00:24.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}とうみん
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.07,0:00:26.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(763.9453125,930)\an8}にくじばん
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.12,0:00:27.96,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.984375,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.18,0:00:30.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.953125,930)\an8}にく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.18,0:00:30.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1128.046875,930)\an8}け
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.18,0:00:30.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1268.09375,930)\an8}け
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.91,0:00:33.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(581.890625,930)\an8}ふゆげ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.91,0:00:33.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.0078125,930)\an8}し
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.91,0:00:33.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1310.1015625,930)\an8}まった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.95,0:00:37.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.84375,930)\an8}わり
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.95,0:00:37.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(763.9453125,930)\an8}さいきん
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.95,0:00:37.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.984375,930)\an8}さら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.95,0:00:37.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(988.015625,930)\an8}おも
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.95,0:00:37.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1324.109375,930)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.52,0:00:43.77,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1212.078125,930)\an8}なつめ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.93,0:00:45.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(707.921875,930)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.93,0:00:45.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.984375,930)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.93,0:00:45.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1100.046875,930)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.49,0:00:46.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1100.046875,930)\an8}せんせい
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.79,0:00:50.19,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(988.0078125,930)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.85,0:01:16.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1380.1328125,930)\an8}なつ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.85,0:01:16.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1492.171875,930)\an8}なつめ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.31,0:01:19.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(623.90625,930)\an8}わたし
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.31,0:01:19.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(750.1875,930)\an8}ふゆ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.31,0:01:19.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.4609375,930)\an8}げ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.24,0:01:23.50,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(609.890625,930)\an8}なつ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.24,0:01:23.50,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(805.953125,930)\an8}くる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.24,0:01:23.50,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}よ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.24,0:01:23.50,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1282.1015625,930)\an8}なつめ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.00,0:01:27.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(813.328125,930)\an8}たぬき
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.00,0:01:27.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(882.609375,930)\an8}つか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.77,0:01:29.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,930)\an8}たぬき
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.49,0:01:32.30,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,930)\an8}なにもの
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.50,0:01:35.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.9765625,930)\an8}たぬき
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.50,0:01:35.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1016.0234375,930)\an8}はなし
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.37,0:01:37.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}ほんとう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.51,0:01:40.56,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,930)\an8}なにもの
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.29,0:02:11.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.9765625,930)\an8}いた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.29,0:02:11.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1128.0546875,930)\an8}いた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.11,0:02:15.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(483.859375,930)\an8}な
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.11,0:02:15.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.984375,930)\an8}な
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.00,0:02:18.06,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(707.9296875,930)\an8}にい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.29,0:02:21.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(469.859375,930)\an8}な
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.29,0:02:21.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(721.9375,930)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.29,0:02:21.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(833.96875,930)\an8}め
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.29,0:02:21.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}おに
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.29,0:02:21.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1058.03125,930)\an8}く
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.14,0:02:23.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.9765625,930)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.14,0:02:23.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(988.0078125,930)\an8}め
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.26,0:02:25.61,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.96875,930)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.26,0:02:25.61,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.0234375,930)\an8}ちょうだい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.42,0:02:30.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1086.0625,930)\an8}たま
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.49,0:02:35.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(343.8203125,930)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.49,0:02:35.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(455.8515625,930)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.49,0:02:35.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.9765625,930)\an8}いま
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.49,0:02:35.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(988.0078125,930)\an8}うち
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.49,0:02:35.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1100.0390625,930)\an8}ぬ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.49,0:02:35.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1212.0703125,930)\an8}あし
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.49,0:02:35.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1268.0859375,930)\an8}さ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.49,0:02:35.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1380.1171875,930)\an8}あし
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.75,0:02:49.56,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.9609375,930)\an8}めんどう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.75,0:02:49.56,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,930)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.75,0:02:49.56,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1072.03125,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.21,0:02:52.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,930)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.44,0:02:54.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.875,930)\an8}はら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.44,0:02:54.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.90625,930)\an8}す
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.44,0:02:54.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}わたし
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.44,0:02:54.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1142.0546875,930)\an8}あいて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.31,0:02:57.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,930)\an8}わたし
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.16,0:02:58.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(707.9296875,930)\an8}けが
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.00,0:03:02.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(623.90625,930)\an8}けもの
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.00,0:03:02.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(735.9375,930)\an8}た
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.00,0:03:02.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.953125,930)\an8}ぐ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.00,0:03:02.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1100.0390625,930)\an8}あいて
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.49,0:03:17.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.96875,930)\an8}ていきゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.50,0:03:27.17,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(707.9296875,930)\an8}たぬき
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.50,0:03:27.17,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.96875,930)\an8}こども
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.50,0:03:27.17,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(988.0078125,930)\an8}た
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.33,0:03:30.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}わたし
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.33,0:03:30.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(581.890625,930)\an8}た
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.33,0:03:30.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1114.046875,930)\an8}たぬき
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.70,0:03:32.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1016.015625,930)\an8}はなし
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.37,0:03:35.66,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,930)\an8}なにもの
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.04,0:03:38.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}しかた
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.25,0:03:40.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1058.03125,930)\an8}しゃべ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.25,0:03:40.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1170.0625,930)\an8}たぬき
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.95,0:03:42.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.96875,930)\an8}もんく
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.95,0:03:56.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(805.953125,150)\an2}す
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.47,0:03:56.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(917.9921875,930)\an8}おさな
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.47,0:03:56.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(413.84375,930)\an8}だいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.47,0:03:56.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(581.8984375,930)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.47,0:03:56.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1030.0234375,930)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.47,0:03:56.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1142.0546875,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.47,0:03:56.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1450.140625,930)\an8}やまおく
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.90,0:03:59.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.90625,930)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.15,0:04:01.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.9765625,930)\an8}つか
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.92,0:04:03.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(679.921875,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.92,0:04:03.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.953125,930)\an8}モン
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.92,0:04:03.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1072.03125,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.14,0:04:06.09,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.953125,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.14,0:04:06.09,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.984375,930)\an8}モ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.29,0:04:08.56,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(721.9296875,930)\an8}ちが
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.29,0:04:08.56,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(917.9921875,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.29,0:04:08.56,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1030.0234375,930)\an8}モン
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.76,0:04:10.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.953125,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.76,0:04:10.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.984375,930)\an8}モン
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.57,0:04:13.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(889.984375,930)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.57,0:04:13.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.57,0:04:13.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1142.0546875,930)\an8}にがて
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.68,0:04:17.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(833.96875,930)\an8}あや
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.68,0:04:17.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}もの
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.68,0:04:17.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1282.09375,930)\an8}もり
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.68,0:04:17.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1394.125,930)\an8}はな
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.47,0:04:21.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(399.84375,930)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.47,0:04:21.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(511.875,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.47,0:04:21.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(623.90625,930)\an8}あつか
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.47,0:04:21.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.9609375,930)\an8}うま
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.47,0:04:21.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1128.046875,930)\an8}さが
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.95,0:04:40.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(833.96875,930)\an8}ひ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.95,0:04:40.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}ぱ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.95,0:04:40.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1198.078125,930)\an8}くる
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.78,0:04:46.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(511.8671875,930)\an8}まった
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.78,0:04:46.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(679.921875,930)\an8}せんせい
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.78,0:04:46.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1184.0703125,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.13,0:04:51.34,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(679.921875,930)\an8}なつめ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.13,0:04:51.34,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.9609375,930)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.53,0:04:53.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(763.9453125,930)\an8}かわい
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.53,0:04:53.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.984375,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.13,0:04:56.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.875,930)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.13,0:04:56.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(581.890625,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.13,0:04:56.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.57,0:04:59.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(553.8828125,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.57,0:04:59.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(777.953125,930)\an8}ひとぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.57,0:04:59.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}わる
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.57,0:04:59.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1254.0859375,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.55,0:05:01.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(679.921875,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.55,0:05:01.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.0234375,930)\an8}にしむら
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.91,0:05:04.31,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(945.9921875,930)\an8}せんせい
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.91,0:05:04.31,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1058.03125,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.51,0:05:06.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1142.0546875,930)\an8}せんせい
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.53,0:05:09.09,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(833.96875,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.30,0:05:11.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(777.9453125,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.30,0:05:11.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}ゆくえ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.30,0:05:11.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1058.03125,930)\an8}ふめい
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.62,0:05:13.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(777.9453125,930)\an8}そうさく
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.62,0:05:13.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(861.96875,930)\an8}たい
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.62,0:05:13.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}けっせい
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.94,0:05:17.83,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1240.0859375,930)\an8}かん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.01,0:05:19.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(889.984375,930)\an8}かえ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.77,0:05:22.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(889.984375,930)\an8}ゆうはん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.77,0:05:22.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1086.0390625,930)\an8}もど
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.35,0:05:23.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(651.9140625,930)\an8}く
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.35,0:05:23.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.953125,930)\an8}いじ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.35,0:05:23.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.9765625,930)\an8}は
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.06,0:05:25.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.984375,930)\an8}たし
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.36,0:05:33.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(273.8046875,930)\an8}まった
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.36,0:05:33.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.9140625,930)\an8}し
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.36,0:05:33.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(805.9609375,930)\an8}かお
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.36,0:05:33.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(917.9921875,930)\an8}で
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.36,0:05:33.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.36,0:05:33.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1198.0703125,930)\an8}よ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.22,0:05:41.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1240.09375,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.98,0:06:04.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.953125,930)\an8}はな
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.98,0:06:04.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(932,930)\an8}はな
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.45,0:06:07.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(889.9765625,150)\an2}ぼうし
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.45,0:06:07.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1030.0234375,150)\an2}ぼうし
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.33,0:06:26.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(707.921875,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.33,0:06:26.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.96875,930)\an8}わたし
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.33,0:06:26.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1156.0625,930)\an8}め
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.64,0:06:30.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(743.3125,930)\an8}まだら
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.64,0:06:30.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(812.59375,930)\an8}さま
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.69,0:06:32.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(707.9296875,930)\an8}きょう
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.69,0:06:32.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,930)\an8}よ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.69,0:06:32.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1156.0546875,930)\an8}ひより
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.05,0:06:35.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(861.96875,930)\an8}ひより
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.05,0:06:35.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1030.0234375,930)\an8}ひ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.95,0:06:39.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(805.953125,930)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.95,0:06:39.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}たす
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.32,0:06:51.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(511.875,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.32,0:06:51.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(707.9296875,930)\an8}ふつう
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.32,0:06:51.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.96875,930)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.32,0:06:51.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.32,0:06:51.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1128.046875,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.85,0:06:54.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(763.9453125,930)\an8}なつめ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.85,0:06:54.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1072.03125,930)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.85,0:06:54.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1240.078125,930)\an8}もの
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.75,0:06:59.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(497.8671875,930)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.75,0:06:59.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(609.8984375,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.75,0:06:59.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(777.9453125,930)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.75,0:06:59.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}ばんしゃく
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.75,0:06:59.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1170.0625,930)\an8}ようい
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.63,0:07:05.65,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(497.8671875,930)\an8}す
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.63,0:07:05.65,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(665.9140625,930)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.63,0:07:05.65,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(777.9453125,930)\an8}ある
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.63,0:07:05.65,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1366.1171875,930)\an8}まった
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.85,0:07:09.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(665.921875,930)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.85,0:07:09.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(889.984375,930)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.52,0:07:11.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1016.015625,930)\an8}めずら
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.05,0:07:14.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(623.90625,930)\an8}われわれ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.05,0:07:14.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(763.9453125,930)\an8}わ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.05,0:07:14.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1156.0546875,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.87,0:07:17.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(777.9453125,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.73,0:07:20.32,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(679.9140625,930)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.73,0:07:20.32,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.9453125,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.73,0:07:20.32,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1324.1171875,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.69,0:07:22.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,930)\an8}なにもの
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.58,0:07:26.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(581.890625,930)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.58,0:07:26.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.82,0:07:28.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.9765625,930)\an8}いちど
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.82,0:07:28.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.28,0:07:30.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.36,0:07:31.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.85,0:07:33.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.81,0:07:38.77,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1288.48828125,930)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.81,0:07:38.77,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1184.8125,930)\an8}にゅうにゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.96,0:07:41.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1114.046875,930)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.76,0:07:44.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1100.78125,930)\an8}にゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.76,0:07:44.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1183.328125,930)\an8}にゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.11,0:07:47.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(833.96875,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.11,0:07:47.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}もん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.11,0:07:47.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1226.078125,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.93,0:07:50.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(833.96875,930)\an8}アユ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.84,0:07:57.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(749.9453125,930)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.84,0:07:57.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1310.1015625,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.56,0:07:58.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.9609375,930)\an8}わ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.57,0:08:01.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(988.015625,930)\an8}むちゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.57,0:08:01.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1072.0390625,930)\an8}ぶ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.78,0:08:04.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(777.9453125,930)\an8}むちゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.78,0:08:04.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(861.96875,930)\an8}ぶ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.78,0:08:04.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1030.0234375,930)\an8}むちゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.78,0:08:04.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1142.0546875,930)\an8}むり
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.73,0:08:07.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.96875,930)\an8}やく
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.88,0:08:17.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1030.0234375,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.88,0:08:17.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1254.09375,930)\an8}さきほど
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.54,0:08:21.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(953.3671875,930)\an8}ひのえ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.54,0:08:21.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1022.6484375,930)\an8}どの
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.54,0:08:21.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(511.875,930)\an8}さき
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.54,0:08:21.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(651.9140625,930)\an8}おおいわ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.54,0:08:21.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.953125,930)\an8}あた
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.54,0:08:21.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1184.0625,930)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.20,0:08:23.17,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(833.9609375,930)\an8}かた
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.54,0:08:41.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(889.9765625,930)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.54,0:08:41.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1086.0390625,930)\an8}ひいらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.20,0:08:45.77,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(988.0078125,930)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.98,0:08:50.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(497.875,930)\an8}ぬし
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.98,0:08:50.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(553.890625,930)\an8}さま
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.98,0:08:50.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}もの
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.98,0:08:50.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1170.0625,930)\an8}す
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.12,0:08:55.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(455.859375,930)\an8}こども
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.12,0:08:55.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(595.8984375,930)\an8}ころ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.12,0:08:55.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.0234375,930)\an8}や
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.30,0:09:08.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.875,930)\an8}まった
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.30,0:09:08.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(917.9921875,930)\an8}ちゅうきゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.30,0:09:08.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1170.0625,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.65,0:09:11.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(511.875,930)\an8}おおいわ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.65,0:09:11.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(651.9140625,930)\an8}あた
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.65,0:09:11.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.9609375,930)\an8}で
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.65,0:09:11.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(988.0078125,930)\an8}よ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.60,0:09:19.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.96875,930)\an8}アユ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.60,0:09:19.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1100.046875,930)\an8}だ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.06,0:09:22.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.96875,930)\an8}いや
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.06,0:09:22.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.03125,930)\an8}ぼく
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.44,0:09:32.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(889.984375,930)\an8}いた
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.44,0:09:32.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1114.046875,930)\an8}いた
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.44,0:09:34.96,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(861.9765625,930)\an8}いた
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.49,0:09:41.12,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(483.859375,930)\an8}な
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.49,0:09:41.12,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.984375,930)\an8}な
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.40,0:09:45.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}たま
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.71,0:09:49.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(553.8828125,930)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.71,0:09:49.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(665.9140625,930)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.71,0:09:49.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}わたし
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.71,0:09:49.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1086.0390625,930)\an8}に
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.71,0:09:49.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1338.1171875,930)\an8}に
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.56,0:09:55.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(805.953125,930)\an8}だ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.56,0:09:55.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}だ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.86,0:10:00.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1114.0546875,930)\an8}わ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.79,0:10:16.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(749.9375,930)\an8}たし
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.79,0:10:16.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1114.046875,930)\an8}ほう
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.87,0:10:19.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(917.9921875,930)\an8}なつめ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.22,0:10:20.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,930)\an8}たぬま
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.17,0:10:24.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.90625,930)\an8}さんぽ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.17,0:10:24.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(833.96875,930)\an8}きょう
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.17,0:10:24.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}あった
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.22,0:10:28.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(721.9296875,930)\an8}せんせい
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.41,0:10:29.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(988.0078125,930)\an8}た
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.39,0:10:32.86,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(441.8515625,930)\an8}ここ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.39,0:10:32.86,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(581.890625,930)\an8}く
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.39,0:10:32.86,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1170.0625,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.11,0:10:38.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(889.984375,930)\an8}ばん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.11,0:10:38.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}はん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.11,0:10:38.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1282.09375,930)\an8}もど
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.21,0:10:44.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(567.890625,930)\an8}せんせい
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.21,0:10:44.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(735.9375,930)\an8}とうこ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.21,0:10:44.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(988.0078125,930)\an8}ばん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.21,0:10:44.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.0234375,930)\an8}めし
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.21,0:10:44.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1156.0546875,930)\an8}のが
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.20,0:10:45.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,930)\an8}まった
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.92,0:11:01.33,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1030.0234375,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.49,0:11:18.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1212.078125,930)\an8}はな
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.49,0:11:18.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1352.125,930)\an8}はな
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.80,0:11:41.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(721.9296875,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.80,0:11:41.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(861.9765625,930)\an8}わたし
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.80,0:11:41.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1142.0546875,930)\an8}め
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.15,0:11:42.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.953125,150)\an2}いっかい
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.15,0:11:42.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,150)\an2}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.15,0:11:42.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1128.0546875,150)\an2}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.07,0:11:46.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(932,930)\an8}みょう
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.07,0:11:46.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.03125,930)\an8}ところ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.07,0:11:46.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1156.0625,930)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.47,0:11:49.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(805.953125,930)\an8}ひのえ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.47,0:11:49.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}たす
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.55,0:11:54.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(497.8671875,930)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.55,0:11:54.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(693.9296875,930)\an8}した
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.55,0:11:54.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(833.96875,930)\an8}おおいわ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.55,0:11:54.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}あた
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.55,0:11:54.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1310.1015625,930)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.99,0:11:57.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(693.9296875,930)\an8}あさ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.84,0:12:03.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.9765625,930)\an8}ちゅうきゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.79,0:12:06.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(679.921875,930)\an8}ふたり
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.79,0:12:06.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.9609375,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.79,0:12:06.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,930)\an8}ぐさ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.79,0:12:06.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.0234375,930)\an8}の
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.32,0:12:08.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(763.9453125,930)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.32,0:12:08.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.0234375,930)\an8}まわ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.00,0:12:12.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(861.9765625,930)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.00,0:12:12.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.00,0:12:12.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1142.0546875,930)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.00,0:12:12.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1310.1015625,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.40,0:12:18.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.875,930)\an8}す
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.40,0:12:18.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(693.921875,930)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.40,0:12:18.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(805.953125,930)\an8}ある
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.40,0:12:18.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1338.109375,930)\an8}まった
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.57,0:12:22.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.9609375,930)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.57,0:12:22.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.9921875,930)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.30,0:12:25.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(679.9140625,930)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.30,0:12:25.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.9453125,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.30,0:12:25.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1324.1171875,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.75,0:12:28.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,930)\an8}なにもの
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.77,0:12:32.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(609.8984375,930)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.77,0:12:32.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.73,0:12:33.65,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.9765625,930)\an8}いちど
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.73,0:12:33.65,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.14,0:12:37.56,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.52,0:12:40.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.43,0:12:45.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(497.8671875,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.43,0:12:45.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(609.8984375,930)\an8}もん
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.43,0:12:45.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1338.1171875,930)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.55,0:12:48.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1114.046875,930)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.29,0:12:54.83,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1107.421875,930)\an8}ひのえ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.29,0:12:54.83,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1176.703125,930)\an8}さま
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.29,0:12:54.83,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(861.9765625,930)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.29,0:12:54.83,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1282.1015625,930)\an8}うらな
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.29,0:12:54.83,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1450.1484375,930)\an8}しん
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.44,0:12:57.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(805.953125,930)\an8}ほんとう
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.44,0:12:57.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1086.0390625,930)\an8}たの
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.28,0:13:00.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.8515625,930)\an8}こんど
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.28,0:13:00.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.953125,930)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.28,0:13:00.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.984375,930)\an8}せ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.28,0:13:00.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.0234375,930)\an8}ごうこう
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.28,0:13:00.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1184.0625,930)\an8}さ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.28,0:13:00.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1352.109375,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.11,0:13:02.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.96875,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.59,0:13:32.76,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1128.0546875,930)\an8}へん
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.33,0:13:36.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(609.8984375,930)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.33,0:13:36.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1142.0546875,930)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.33,0:13:36.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1254.0859375,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.38,0:13:40.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.8359375,930)\an8}お
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.38,0:13:40.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(539.8671875,930)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.38,0:13:40.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(679.9140625,930)\an8}お
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.38,0:13:40.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.9453125,930)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.38,0:13:40.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1072.0390625,930)\an8}わる
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.38,0:13:40.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1324.1171875,930)\an8}わる
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.69,0:13:43.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(651.90625,930)\an8}お
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.69,0:13:43.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(763.9375,930)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.69,0:13:43.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1072.03125,930)\an8}たの
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.69,0:13:54.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,930)\an8}ごん
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.69,0:13:54.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(707.9296875,930)\an8}さが
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.69,0:13:54.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.9609375,930)\an8}もの
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.69,0:13:54.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1072.03125,930)\an8}ほうがく
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.75,0:13:56.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(833.9609375,930)\an8}ごん
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.75,0:13:56.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}ほくとう
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.81,0:14:01.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(469.8671875,930)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.81,0:14:01.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.9140625,930)\an8}つよ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.81,0:14:01.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(749.9453125,930)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.81,0:14:01.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(861.9765625,930)\an8}も
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.81,0:14:01.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}ぬし
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.81,0:14:01.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1086.0390625,930)\an8}たす
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.34,0:14:03.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(749.9375,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.34,0:14:03.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1086.0390625,930)\an8}こころづよ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.67,0:14:06.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(777.953125,930)\an8}どうちゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.67,0:14:06.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(861.9765625,930)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.56,0:14:08.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(707.9296875,930)\an8}つよ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.56,0:14:08.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.9609375,930)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.56,0:14:08.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,930)\an8}も
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.56,0:14:08.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.0234375,930)\an8}ぬし
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.99,0:14:11.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(511.875,930)\an8}ひとすじなわ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.99,0:14:11.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(735.9375,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.06,0:14:24.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1030.0234375,930)\an8}なつめくん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.65,0:14:26.02,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(889.9765625,930)\an8}ささだ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.65,0:14:26.02,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1030.0234375,930)\an8}たき
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.24,0:14:27.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,930)\an8}ぐうぜん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.59,0:14:29.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.59,0:14:29.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1058.03125,930)\an8}もの
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.31,0:14:38.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(343.828125,930)\an8}たき
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.31,0:14:38.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(651.9140625,930)\an8}はな
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.31,0:14:38.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,930)\an8}た
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.31,0:14:38.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1436.1328125,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.59,0:14:41.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(735.9375,930)\an8}いちど
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.59,0:14:41.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.9609375,930)\an8}た
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.59,0:14:41.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.0234375,930)\an8}や
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.59,0:14:41.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1156.0546875,930)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.12,0:14:46.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(413.84375,930)\an8}ほんとう
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.12,0:14:46.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(861.9765625,930)\an8}し
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.12,0:14:46.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1086.0390625,930)\an8}ほう
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.12,0:14:46.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1198.0703125,930)\an8}ふ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.12,0:14:46.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1254.0859375,930)\an8}し
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.12,0:14:46.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1310.1015625,930)\an8}ぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.23,0:14:48.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(581.890625,930)\an8}なつめくん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.23,0:14:48.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(833.96875,930)\an8}た
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.05,0:14:54.19,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(539.8828125,930)\an8}どうきゅうせい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.05,0:14:54.19,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(707.9296875,930)\an8}た
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.05,0:14:54.19,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.0234375,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.03,0:15:00.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1016.0234375,930)\an8}いっぽん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.08,0:15:06.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(623.90625,930)\an8}ちゅうどく
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.08,0:15:06.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(988.0078125,930)\an8}し
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.05,0:15:09.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,930)\an8}げつようび
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.05,0:15:09.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1100.046875,930)\an8}がっこう
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.71,0:15:17.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(833.9765625,930)\an8}へん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.71,0:15:17.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1198.078125,930)\an8}せんせい
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.71,0:15:17.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1282.1015625,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.81,0:15:20.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}せんせい
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.68,0:15:24.02,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.984375,930)\an8}ちゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.68,0:15:24.02,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.9609375,930)\an8}さんぽ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.21,0:15:29.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(217.7890625,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.21,0:15:29.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(861.9765625,930)\an8}ばん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.21,0:15:29.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}はん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.21,0:15:29.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1142.0546875,930)\an8}もど
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.21,0:15:29.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1310.1015625,930)\an8}く
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.22,0:15:31.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(861.9765625,930)\an8}おれ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.22,0:15:31.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1086.0390625,930)\an8}おも
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.66,0:15:34.56,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(777.9453125,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.66,0:15:34.56,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1282.1015625,930)\an8}いま
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.75,0:15:38.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(483.8671875,930)\an8}いつ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.75,0:15:38.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,930)\an8}おちい
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.75,0:15:38.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1184.0625,930)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.20,0:15:52.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(609.8984375,930)\an8}まった
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.20,0:15:52.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}ひのえ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.20,0:15:52.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1086.0390625,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.75,0:15:56.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(371.8359375,930)\an8}つよ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.75,0:15:56.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(483.8671875,930)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.75,0:15:56.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(595.8984375,930)\an8}すけ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.75,0:15:56.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(707.9296875,930)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.75,0:15:56.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.9609375,930)\an8}で
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.75,0:15:56.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.9765625,930)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.75,0:15:56.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1100.0390625,930)\an8}よ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.33,0:16:03.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}アユ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.18,0:16:11.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(483.859375,930)\an8}な
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.18,0:16:11.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.984375,930)\an8}な
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.70,0:16:14.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}たま
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.15,0:16:20.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(483.859375,930)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.15,0:16:20.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(595.890625,930)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.15,0:16:20.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.984375,930)\an8}はや
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.15,0:16:20.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.03125,930)\an8}すけ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.15,0:16:20.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1156.0625,930)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.15,0:16:20.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1296.109375,930)\an8}あらわ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.66,0:16:24.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(777.953125,930)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.66,0:16:24.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}さわ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.66,0:16:24.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1226.078125,930)\an8}おも
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.72,0:16:29.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(469.859375,930)\an8}ところ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.72,0:16:29.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(609.8984375,930)\an8}かがみもち
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.72,0:16:29.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(777.953125,930)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.72,0:16:29.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(889.984375,930)\an8}かい
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.46,0:16:34.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(707.9296875,930)\an8}ひげ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.46,0:16:34.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.9609375,930)\an8}つよ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.46,0:16:34.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.9921875,930)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.46,0:16:34.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1016.0234375,930)\an8}すけ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.46,0:16:34.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1128.0546875,930)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.46,0:16:34.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1492.15625,930)\an8}きさま
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.86,0:16:37.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(623.90625,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.86,0:16:37.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,930)\an8}わ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.04,0:16:42.34,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.8515625,930)\an8}あた
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.04,0:16:42.34,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(651.9140625,930)\an8}わたし
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.04,0:16:42.34,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.984375,930)\an8}こうき
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.04,0:16:42.34,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.0234375,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.04,0:16:42.34,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1156.0546875,930)\an8}もの
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.51,0:16:45.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(763.9453125,930)\an8}わたし
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.33,0:16:49.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(911.359375,930)\an8}だいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.33,0:16:49.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1008.6484375,930)\an8}わたし
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.33,0:16:49.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.875,930)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.33,0:16:49.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(693.921875,930)\an8}なまいき
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.33,0:16:49.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1142.0546875,930)\an8}かがみもち
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.64,0:16:52.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(595.890625,930)\an8}く
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.64,0:16:52.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.96875,930)\an8}く
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.97,0:16:56.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1072.03125,930)\an8}かがみもち
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.97,0:16:56.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.9609375,930)\an8}うす
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.97,0:16:56.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.9765625,930)\an8}よご
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.97,0:16:56.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1212.0703125,930)\an8}いただ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.80,0:16:59.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(539.8828125,930)\an8}よ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.80,0:16:59.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(651.9140625,930)\an8}とし
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.80,0:16:59.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(763.9453125,930)\an8}むか
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.37,0:17:05.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(763.953125,930)\an8}なつめ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.37,0:17:05.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.9765625,930)\an8}どの
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.37,0:17:05.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(960.0078125,930)\an8}かく
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.37,0:17:05.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1296.1015625,930)\an8}ぐ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.61,0:17:08.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(749.9453125,930)\an8}ね
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.61,0:17:08.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(805.9609375,930)\an8}わ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.41,0:17:11.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1058.03125,930)\an8}おお
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.70,0:17:13.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(567.890625,930)\an8}す
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.70,0:17:13.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(735.9375,930)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.70,0:17:13.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.96875,930)\an8}ある
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.15,0:17:18.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(511.8671875,930)\an8}まった
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.15,0:17:18.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.9921875,930)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.15,0:17:18.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1016.0234375,930)\an8}すけ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.15,0:17:18.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1128.0546875,930)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.21,0:17:20.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.953125,930)\an8}なぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.21,0:17:20.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.984375,930)\an8}こた
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.29,0:17:21.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.29,0:17:21.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1086.0390625,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.05,0:17:25.26,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,930)\an8}なにもの
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.46,0:17:29.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.84375,930)\an8}うるさ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.46,0:17:29.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(623.90625,930)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.46,0:17:29.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(988.015625,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.66,0:17:31.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(861.96875,930)\an8}いちど
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.66,0:17:31.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.32,0:17:37.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(567.8828125,930)\an8}つか
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.32,0:17:37.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.9609375,930)\an8}おれ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.32,0:17:37.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1408.140625,930)\an8}だいす
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.60,0:17:39.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(707.9296875,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.60,0:17:39.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.9609375,930)\an8}もん
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.83,0:17:41.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(988.0078125,930)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.09,0:17:46.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(631.76953125,930)\an8}たましい
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.09,0:17:46.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(728.07421875,930)\an8}ひゃく
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.09,0:17:46.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.8515625,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.09,0:17:46.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(539.8828125,930)\an8}ご
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.09,0:17:46.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.9765625,930)\an8}てき
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.77,0:17:50.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(946,930)\an8}うら
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.77,0:17:50.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1170.0625,930)\an8}かか
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.77,0:17:50.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1478.15625,930)\an8}よ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.77,0:17:50.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1590.1875,930)\an8}すえ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.80,0:17:55.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(357.828125,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.80,0:17:55.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(609.90625,930)\an8}みず
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.80,0:17:55.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(721.9375,930)\an8}し
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.80,0:17:55.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}はくまい
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.80,0:17:55.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1394.125,930)\an8}かん
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.36,0:17:58.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(497.8671875,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.79,0:18:01.33,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1156.0625,930)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.79,0:18:01.33,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1268.09375,930)\an8}ほう
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.49,0:18:03.50,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(805.9609375,930)\an8}うま
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.49,0:18:03.50,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1114.046875,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.65,0:18:08.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(721.9296875,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.65,0:18:08.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1114.0546875,930)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.38,0:18:10.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.984375,930)\an8}したた
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.38,0:18:10.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.953125,930)\an8}みず
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.38,0:18:10.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1128.046875,930)\an8}おんな
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.97,0:18:13.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(707.9296875,930)\an8}みっ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.97,0:18:13.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.9609375,930)\an8}かぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.67,0:18:16.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(735.9375,930)\an8}みっ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.67,0:18:16.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.984375,930)\an8}く
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.67,0:18:16.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,930)\an8}ふ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.67,0:18:16.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1184.0625,930)\an8}たび
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.77,0:18:18.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(833.9609375,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.91,0:18:28.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(343.8125,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.91,0:18:28.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(455.84375,930)\an8}もり
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.91,0:18:28.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.9765625,930)\an8}ぎゅうにゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.91,0:18:28.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1016.0234375,930)\an8}ちくわ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.91,0:18:28.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1520.171875,930)\an8}に
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.91,0:18:28.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1576.1875,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.91,0:18:30.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(833.9609375,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.26,0:18:35.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(623.90625,930)\an8}はじ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.26,0:18:35.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.984375,930)\an8}つか
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.26,0:18:35.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1016.015625,930)\an8}てき
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.26,0:18:35.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1128.046875,930)\an8}もの
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.57,0:18:53.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.953125,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.57,0:18:53.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.984375,930)\an8}モン
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.19,0:18:54.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(791.953125,930)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.19,0:18:54.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(903.984375,930)\an8}もり
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.33,0:18:59.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(595.8984375,930)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.33,0:18:59.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(707.9296875,930)\an8}だ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.33,0:18:59.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(931.9921875,930)\an8}あぶ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.33,0:18:59.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1184.0703125,930)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.35,0:19:16.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(231.7890625,930)\an8}まった
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.35,0:19:16.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(371.8359375,930)\an8}やく
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.35,0:19:16.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(483.8671875,930)\an8}た
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.35,0:19:16.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(819.9609375,930)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.35,0:19:16.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(988.0078125,930)\an8}わ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.35,0:19:16.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1324.109375,930)\an8}せわ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.46,0:19:20.06,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(693.921875,930)\an8}ひげ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.46,0:19:20.06,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(889.984375,930)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.46,0:19:20.06,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1058.03125,930)\an8}いず
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.46,0:19:20.06,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1170.0625,930)\an8}かえ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.24,0:19:23.33,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(651.9140625,930)\an8}いつ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.24,0:19:23.33,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.96875,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.15,0:19:35.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(609.8984375,930)\an8}よ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.15,0:19:35.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(721.9296875,930)\an8}みち
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.15,0:19:35.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1142.0546875,930)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.15,0:19:35.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1254.0859375,930)\an8}くろ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.04,0:19:39.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(763.9453125,930)\an8}おそ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.04,0:19:39.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.03125,930)\an8}しんぱい
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.27,0:19:43.61,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(413.84375,930)\an8}よ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.27,0:19:43.61,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1170.0625,930)\an8}さが
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.78,0:19:48.17,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(833.96875,930)\an8}たぬき
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.36,0:19:50.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(974.0078125,930)\an8}しゃべ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.11,0:19:54.22,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.90625,930)\an8}あと
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.11,0:19:54.22,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(777.953125,930)\an8}ひも
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.11,0:19:54.22,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(889.984375,930)\an8}ひ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.11,0:19:54.22,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1002.015625,930)\an8}ぱ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.40,0:19:59.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1156.0625,930)\an8}ぶじ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.40,0:19:59.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1296.1015625,930)\an8}よ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.40,0:19:59.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1576.1875,930)\an8}ほんとう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.91,0:20:02.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(735.9375,930)\an8}つぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.91,0:20:02.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(875.9765625,930)\an8}いっしょ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.91,0:20:02.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1016.015625,930)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.34,0:20:10.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(567.890625,930)\an8}ねこ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.34,0:20:10.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.9765625,930)\an8}きょう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.34,0:20:10.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1156.0625,930)\an8}ところ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.34,0:20:10.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1408.1328125,930)\an8}さんぽ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.67,0:20:36.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,930)\an8}かえ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.36,0:20:42.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1114.046875,930)\an8}でむか
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.74,0:20:45.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(1044.03125,930)\an8}かえ