[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: Default Aegisub file
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 720
PlayResY: 404
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: 其他,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1,2,5,5,10,134
Style: 片头介绍,微软雅黑,20,&H00C2E0EC,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,134
Style: 正文,微软雅黑,26,&H00C2E0EC,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,5,134
Style: 人物介绍,微软雅黑,16,&H00C2E0EC,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.90,0:00:10.17,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs20\c&HC2E0EC&\b1\bord0\pos(360,300)}双语特效字幕\N{\b0}百度贴吧{\fs25\c&HFFFFFF&\b1}衣柜字幕组{\fs16\c&HC2E0EC&}\N专注GOT剧集 华语冰火最专业字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.74,0:00:12.48,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(457.315,206.567)}翻译{\fs22\b1} 艾莉娅的缝衣针
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.70,0:00:14.70,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(322.409,112.289)}翻译{\fs22\b1} 麻绳力攻
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.77,0:00:16.77,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(482.447,319.144)}翻译{\fs22\b1} 道朗马泰尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.20,0:00:20.60,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(320,250)\fs25\b1}君临{\fs12\b0} King's Landing
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.40,0:00:22.38,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(468.119,112.289)}翻译{\fs22\b1} imzxz1051
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.67,0:00:26.76,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\move(425,245,425,235)\fad(300,500)\fs25\b1}红堡{\fs12\b0} Red Keep
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.20,0:00:29.24,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(451,308)}校对{\fs22\b1} pksunking
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.26,0:00:31.13,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,0)\fs15\b1\frz10\frx40\t(\fs25\frz20)\move(551,190,527,226)}龙石岛{\fscx50\fscy50\b0} Dragonstone
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.13,0:00:31.93,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,0)\fs25\b1\frz20\frx40\t(\fs45\frz27)\move(527,226,478,311)}龙石岛{\fscx50\fscy50\b0} Dragonstone
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.93,0:00:32.59,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,0)\fs45\frz27\frx40\b1\t(\fs50\frz30)\move(478,311,461.965,360)}龙石岛{\fscx50\fscy50\b0} Dragonstone
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.59,0:00:36.85,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fs25\b1\pos(561,323)}龙石岛{\fscx50\fscy50\b0} Dragonstone
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.20,0:00:39.44,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(162,175)}校对{\fs22\b1} 小魔女透明子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.62,0:00:44.82,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,0)\frx22\move(170,150,300,150)\fs25\b1}孪河城
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.62,0:00:44.82,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,0)\frx22\move(490,150,360,150)\fs18\b0}The Twins
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.82,0:00:47.72,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\frx22\fry0\frz0\t(200,2750,\fry-80)\t(200,2750,\frz-15)}{\fad(0,700)}{\fs25\b1}{\pos(330,150)}孪河城{\fs18\b0} The Twins
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.72,0:00:49.42,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\frx22\fry80\frz15\t(0,2000,\fry14)\t(0,2000,\frz3)}{\fad(400,500)}{\fs25\b1}{\pos(375,145)}孪河城{\fs18\b0} The Twins
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.36,0:00:52.03,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(405,302)}监制{\fs22\b1} 临冬城的狮子 旧镇老翁
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.19,0:00:53.24,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,0)\frx60\fs15\b1\t(\fs25\frx50)\move(400,180,400,221)}临冬城{\fscx50\fscy50\b0} Winterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.24,0:00:55.08,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,200)\frx50\fs25\b1\t(1.5,\fs100\frx30)\move(400,221,385,390)}临冬城{\fscx50\fscy50\b0} Winterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.18,0:00:57.96,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,300)\fs25\b1\pos(461,261)}临冬城{\fscx50\fscy50\b0} Winterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.66,0:01:00.41,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(420,110)}后期{\fs22\b1} poplar
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.85,0:01:02.60,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(169,303)}后期{\fs22\b1} 窝鹏偏逢连夜雪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.84,0:01:09.70,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(327,173)}策划{\fs22\b1} baozhenyuawabi
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.10,0:01:12.10,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(218,310)}特别鸣谢{\fs22\b1} 屈畅CCXX（@史诗图书）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.76,0:01:13.84,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,0)\b1\move(399,223,415,212)\fscx50\fscy50\frx346\fry26\frz6.917\t(\fscx100\fscy100\frx342\fry20\frz7.349)}绝境长城{\fs12\b0} the Wall
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.84,0:01:15.51,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,200)\b1\fscx100\fscy100\frx342\fry20\frz7.349\t(\fscx180\fscy180\frx340\fry2\frz4)\move(415,212,368.421,200)}绝境长城{\fs12\b0} the Wall
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.51,0:01:18.64,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,300)\fs25\b1\pos(232.287,236.705)\frx-60\t(\frx-10)}绝境长城{\fs12\b0} the Wall
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.10,0:01:25.50,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(360,300)\fs25\c&HC2E0EC&}最专业的华语冰火资料站：冰与火之歌中文维基\N\N{\fs20\c&HFFFFFF&}http://zh.asoiaf.wikia.com/
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.50,0:01:28.54,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs20\pos(354,360)} 百度冰与火之歌贴吧 & 百度权力的游戏贴吧 {\fs12} 联合出品
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.50,0:01:30.30,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\move(348,240,320,400,1200,1800)\fad(200,200)\frx70\fs25\b1\t(\fs60\frx30)}阿斯塔波{\fs12\b0}Astapor
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.91,0:01:32.13,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,200)\frz25\frx60\t(\frx45\fscx200\fscy200\frz37)\fs25\b1\move(450.378,202.746,570,370,4,1199)}渊凯{\fscx50\fscy50\b0} Yunkai
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.33,0:01:33.78,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,0)\frz10\fry60\fs40\t(\frz5\fry30\fs38)\b1\move(509.749,184,418.49,193,29,1448)}渊凯{\fscx50\fscy50\b0} Yunkai
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.74,0:01:35.88,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,200)\frz5\fry30\fs38\t(\fry-90\frz-15\fs30)\b1\move(418.49,193,83.9,186,0,2123)}渊凯{\fscx50\fscy50\b0} Yunkai
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.60,0:01:36.60,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs12\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(484,57)}根据长篇小说
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.60,0:01:36.60,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs24\pos(558,82)}《{\b1}冰与火之歌{\b0}》{\fs12} 改编
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.60,0:01:36.60,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs12\pos(639,110)} 原著 {\fs20} 乔治·R·R·马丁
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.82,0:01:49.38,正文,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.46,0:01:47.71,其他,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs24\c&H24EFFF&\b1\pos(360,300)}权力的游戏\N{\fs14}第三季 第十集\N{\fs20\c&HFFFFFF&}衣柜字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.05,0:01:53.30,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs12\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(360,250)}第十集 {\fs18} "Mhysa"\N{\fs12}弥莎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.00,0:02:01.29,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(229,179.023)}卢斯·波顿\N{\b0\fs12}恐怖堡伯爵
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.92,0:02:30.82,正文,,0,0,0,,驾！驾！\N{\fs16}Yah! Yah!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.10,0:02:37.00,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(563,199)}桑铎·克里冈\N{\b0\fs12}“猎狗”
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.66,0:02:45.06,正文,,0,0,0,,- 走 撤！ - 北境之王！\N{\fs16}- Go, move out! - The King in the North!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.10,0:02:48.27,正文,,0,0,0,,北境之王！\N{\fs16}The King in the North!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.30,0:02:50.50,正文,,0,0,0,,北境之王！北境之王！\N{\fs16}The King in the North! The King in the North!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.54,0:02:52.90,正文,,0,0,0,,北境之王！北境之王！\N{\fs16}The King in the North! The King in the North!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.70,0:02:52.90,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(269,162)}罗柏·史塔克{\b0}\N{\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.90,0:02:55.40,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(621,328)}艾莉亚·史塔克
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.94,0:02:56.34,正文,,0,0,0,,北境之王驾到！\N{\fs16}Here comes the King in the North!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.38,0:02:58.61,正文,,0,0,0,,北境之王驾到！\N{\fs16}Here comes the King in the North!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.64,0:03:00.58,正文,,0,0,0,,北境之王！北境之王！\N{\fs16}The King in the North! The King in the North!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.61,0:03:04.48,正文,,0,0,0,,北境……\N{\fs16}Here comes...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.68,0:03:33.60,正文,,0,0,0,,哈哈\N{\fs16}Hmm.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.04,0:03:36.58,正文,,0,0,0,,艾尔德瑞克·萨斯菲尔德爵士和戴斯蒙·克雷赫大人\N{\fs16}Ser Eldrick Sarsfield and Lord Desmond Crakehall.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.30,0:03:36.30,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\move(160,264,465,271,1,1961)}雪伊{\b0}\N{\fs12}珊莎的侍女 小恶魔的情人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.61,0:03:39.11,正文,,0,0,0,,艾尔德瑞克·萨斯菲尔德爵士和戴斯蒙·克雷赫大人\N{\fs16}Ser Eldrick Sarsfield and Lord Desmond Crakehall.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.00,0:03:43.00,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(156,315)}提利昂·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}“小恶魔” 财政大臣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.15,0:03:40.72,正文,,0,0,0,,你怎么了？\N{\fs16}What are you doing?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.75,0:03:42.62,正文,,0,0,0,,我有个清单\N{\fs16}I have a list.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.65,0:03:44.69,正文,,0,0,0,,杀人清单？\N{\fs16}A list of people you mean to kill?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.00,0:03:47.00,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(435,178)}珊莎·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}提利昂的夫人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.72,0:03:45.99,正文,,0,0,0,,就因为他们嘲笑我？\N{\fs16}For laughing at me?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.02,0:03:48.12,正文,,0,0,0,,在你眼中我和乔佛里没两样是吗？\N{\fs16}Do I look like Joffrey to you?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.16,0:03:50.09,正文,,0,0,0,,不 杀人这种做法是有点极端\N{\fs16}No, death seems a bit extreme.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.13,0:03:52.16,正文,,0,0,0,,应该说是 死亡带来的恐惧…\N{\fs16}Fear of death, on the other hand...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.19,0:03:53.80,正文,,0,0,0,,你该学会视而不见\N{\fs16}You should learn to ignore them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.83,0:03:55.96,正文,,0,0,0,,夫人 人们嘲笑我\N{\fs16}My lady, people have been laughing at me{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.00,0:03:57.83,正文,,0,0,0,,要比嘲笑你久远多了\N{\fs16}far longer than they've been laughing at you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.87,0:03:59.80,正文,,0,0,0,,我是半人\N{\fs16}I'm the Halfman,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.83,0:04:01.87,正文,,0,0,0,,小魔猴 小恶魔\N{\fs16}the Demon Monkey, the Imp.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.90,0:04:03.44,正文,,0,0,0,,你是兰尼斯特家的人\N{\fs16}You're a Lannister.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.47,0:04:07.01,正文,,0,0,0,,而我却是叛徒奈德·史塔克的女儿\N{\fs16}I am the disgraced daughter of the traitor Ned Stark.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.04,0:04:09.71,正文,,0,0,0,,叛徒的女儿和小魔猴\N{\fs16}The disgraced daughter and the Demon Monkey.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.74,0:04:12.14,正文,,0,0,0,,我们真是天生一对\N{\fs16}We're perfect for each other.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.11,0:04:17.32,正文,,0,0,0,,那我们该怎么教训他们？\N{\fs16}So how should we punish them?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.35,0:04:18.92,正文,,0,0,0,,谁？谁要教训谁？\N{\fs16}Who? Whom?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.95,0:04:22.02,正文,,0,0,0,,艾尔德瑞克·萨斯菲尔德爵士和戴斯蒙·克雷赫大人\N{\fs16}Ser Eldrick Sarsfield and Lord Desmond Crakehall.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.06,0:04:23.69,正文,,0,0,0,,啊\N{\fs16}Ah.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.72,0:04:27.19,正文,,0,0,0,,我可以和瓦里斯大人谈谈 打听一下他们有什么变态嗜好\N{\fs16}I could speak to Lord Varys and learn their perversions.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.23,0:04:30.70,正文,,0,0,0,,取名叫“戴斯蒙·克雷赫”的人一定是个变态\N{\fs16}Anyone named Desmond Crakehall must be a pervert.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.73,0:04:33.13,正文,,0,0,0,,我听说你就是个变态\N{\fs16}I hear that you're a pervert.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.17,0:04:34.47,正文,,0,0,0,,我是小恶魔\N{\fs16}I am the Imp.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.50,0:04:36.23,正文,,0,0,0,,我有自己的一套规矩\N{\fs16}I have certain standards to maintain.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.07,0:04:41.77,正文,,0,0,0,,我们可以拿戴斯蒙大人的床玩塞羊进去的把戏\N{\fs16}We could sheep shift Lord Desmond's bed.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.47,0:04:44.61,正文,,0,0,0,,在他的床垫上开一个洞\N{\fs16}You cut a little hole in his mattress{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.64,0:04:46.38,正文,,0,0,0,,把羊粪塞进去\N{\fs16}and you stuff sheep dung inside.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.41,0:04:49.38,正文,,0,0,0,,然后把洞缝好 把床重新整理好\N{\fs16}Then you sew up the hole and make his bed again.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.41,0:04:51.85,正文,,0,0,0,,他的房间会很臭 而他找不到臭味是从哪儿来的\N{\fs16}His room will stink, but he won't know where it's coming from.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.97,0:04:53.47,正文,,0,0,0,,珊莎夫人！\N{\fs16}Lady Sansa!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.50,0:04:55.93,正文,,0,0,0,,我妹妹跟我闹别扭时就这么整过我\N{\fs16}My sister used to do that when she was angry with me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.97,0:04:58.47,正文,,0,0,0,,她经常跟我闹别扭\N{\fs16}And she was always angry with me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.50,0:05:00.47,正文,,0,0,0,,为什么叫“塞羊”？\N{\fs16}Why sheep shift?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.51,0:05:04.01,正文,,0,0,0,,大粪听起来太粗俗了\N{\fs16}That's the vulgar word for dung.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.04,0:05:05.98,正文,,0,0,0,,夫人呐……\N{\fs16}My lady...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.01,0:05:07.31,正文,,0,0,0,,是你问我的\N{\fs16}Well, you asked me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.35,0:05:08.71,正文,,0,0,0,,哦！\N{\fs16}Oh!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.75,0:05:10.32,正文,,0,0,0,,是他！\N{\fs16}That's him!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.45,0:05:13.45,正文,,0,0,0,,大人 夫人\N{\fs16}My lord, my lady.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.70,0:05:15.80,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(356,219)}波德瑞克·派恩\N{\b0\fs12}提利昂的侍从
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.49,0:05:15.79,正文,,0,0,0,,令尊传您去参加御前会议\N{\fs16}Your father has called a meeting of the small council.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.36,0:05:26.20,正文,,0,0,0,,今天又杀了几只小狗仔？\N{\fs16}Killed a few puppies today?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.23,0:05:28.17,正文,,0,0,0,,给他看\N{\fs16}Show him.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.40,0:05:28.40,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(321,285)}乔佛里·拜拉席恩{\b0}\N{\fs12}铁王座上的王
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.20,0:05:30.17,正文,,0,0,0,,快 给他看\N{\fs16}Come on, show him.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.10,0:05:34.50,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(321,285)}派席尔{\b0}\N{\fs12}大学士
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.37,0:05:37.44,正文,,0,0,0,,哦 抱歉 大人\N{\fs16}Oh, apologies, my lord.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.47,0:05:39.41,正文,,0,0,0,,老了 手指不听使唤\N{\fs16}Old fingers.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.08,0:05:50.59,正文,,0,0,0,,“萝丝琳套住一条肥美鳟鱼\N{\fs16}"Roslin caught a fine fat trout.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.62,0:05:54.62,正文,,0,0,0,,她的兄弟们为婚礼献上两张狼皮为礼\N{\fs16}Her brothers gave her a pair of wolf pelts for her wedding.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.66,0:05:57.46,正文,,0,0,0,,署名 瓦德·佛雷”\N{\fs16}Signed Walder Frey."{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.26,0:06:01.20,正文,,0,0,0,,这文掉得还真蹩脚呢\N{\fs16}Is that bad poetry{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.23,0:06:03.30,正文,,0,0,0,,到底是什么意思？\N{\fs16}or is it supposed to mean something?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.33,0:06:05.17,正文,,0,0,0,,罗柏·史塔克死啦！\N{\fs16}Robb Stark is dead.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.20,0:06:08.50,正文,,0,0,0,,他的贱人老娘也死啦！\N{\fs16}And his bitch mother.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.00,0:06:11.37,正文,,0,0,0,,快回信给瓦德大人\N{\fs16}Write back to Lord Frey.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.41,0:06:14.07,正文,,0,0,0,,感谢他的效力 命令他\N{\fs16}Thank him for his service and command him{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.11,0:06:16.84,正文,,0,0,0,,送回罗柏·史塔克的人头\N{\fs16}to send Robb Stark's head.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.88,0:06:20.08,正文,,0,0,0,,等我结婚时 要亲手把这个交给珊莎\N{\fs16}I'm going to serve it to Sansa at my wedding feast.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.11,0:06:23.58,正文,,0,0,0,,陛下 珊莎夫人可是您舅妈\N{\fs16}Your Grace, Lady Sansa is your aunt by marriage.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.00,0:06:24.70,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(527,228)}瓦里斯{\b0}\N{\fs12}“八爪蜘蛛” 情报总管
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.62,0:06:26.15,正文,,0,0,0,,小乔在开玩笑 他不是认真的\N{\fs16}A joke. Joffrey did not mean it.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.70,0:06:26.30,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(91,181)}瑟曦·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}摄政太后
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.19,0:06:27.75,正文,,0,0,0,,我当然是认真的\N{\fs16}Yes, I did.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.79,0:06:30.72,正文,,0,0,0,,等我结婚时 要亲手把这个交给珊莎\N{\fs16}I'm going to have it served to Sansa at my wedding feast.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.76,0:06:32.29,正文,,0,0,0,,不行\N{\fs16}No.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.33,0:06:34.99,正文,,0,0,0,,你休想再折磨她\N{\fs16}She is no longer yours to torment.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.80,0:06:38.66,正文,,0,0,0,,我想整谁就整谁\N{\fs16}Everyone is mine to torment.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.13,0:06:42.93,正文,,0,0,0,,你给我记住 小怪物\N{\fs16}You'd do well to remember that, you little monster.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.97,0:06:44.80,正文,,0,0,0,,哦 我是怪物\N{\fs16}Oh, I'm a monster.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.84,0:06:48.34,正文,,0,0,0,,那你更应该对我礼貌些\N{\fs16}Perhaps you should speak to me more softly, then.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.37,0:06:50.61,正文,,0,0,0,,怪物可是很危险的\N{\fs16}Monsters are dangerous{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.64,0:06:54.75,正文,,0,0,0,,而且这世道 杀个国王跟摁死只苍蝇差不多\N{\fs16}and just now kings are dying like flies.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.05,0:07:04.29,正文,,0,0,0,,如此口出狂言\N{\fs16}I could have your tongue out{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.32,0:07:05.82,正文,,0,0,0,,我要拔了你的舌头\N{\fs16}for saying that.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.86,0:07:08.76,正文,,0,0,0,,就让他威胁吧\N{\fs16}Let him make his threats.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.79,0:07:11.76,正文,,0,0,0,,哼 他不过是个满腹牢骚的小可怜虫罢了\N{\fs16}Hmm? He's a bitter little man.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.80,0:07:14.96,正文,,0,0,0,,提利昂大人应该立即道歉\N{\fs16}Lord Tyrion should apologize immediately.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.00,0:07:18.07,正文,,0,0,0,,让人忍无可忍 目无尊长\N{\fs16}Unacceptable, disrespectful,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.10,0:07:20.20,正文,,0,0,0,,而且非常低俗\N{\fs16}and in very bad taste.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.24,0:07:23.07,正文,,0,0,0,,我是国王！\N{\fs16}I am the king!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.11,0:07:24.57,正文,,0,0,0,,我要惩罚你\N{\fs16}I will punish you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.61,0:07:27.18,正文,,0,0,0,,任何大声声明“我是国王”的人\N{\fs16}Any man who must say, "I am the king"{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.70,0:07:29.10,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(285,199)}泰温·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}凯岩城公爵 国王之手
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.21,0:07:29.85,正文,,0,0,0,,根本当不了真正的王者\N{\fs16}is no true king.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.88,0:07:31.78,正文,,0,0,0,,等我替你赢下这场战争\N{\fs16}I'll make sure you understand that{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.81,0:07:33.35,正文,,0,0,0,,我会教你明白这一点的\N{\fs16}when I've won your war for you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.38,0:07:36.05,正文,,0,0,0,,我的父亲才赢下了真正的战争\N{\fs16}My father won the real war.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.09,0:07:39.15,正文,,0,0,0,,他亲手杀掉雷加王子 赢得王冠\N{\fs16}He killed Prince Rhaegar. He took the crown{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.19,0:07:41.96,正文,,0,0,0,,而这时候呢 你却躲在凯岩城里不敢出来\N{\fs16}while you hid under Casterly Rock!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.70,0:07:56.57,正文,,0,0,0,,国王累了\N{\fs16}The king is tired.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.60,0:07:58.77,正文,,0,0,0,,护送他回房\N{\fs16}See him to his chambers.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.81,0:08:01.04,正文,,0,0,0,,- 来吧 - 我不累\N{\fs16}- Come along. - I'm not tired.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.08,0:08:03.78,正文,,0,0,0,,我们有很多值得庆贺的事\N{\fs16}We have so much to celebrate.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.81,0:08:06.88,正文,,0,0,0,,还有一场婚礼要策划 你必须休息了\N{\fs16}A wedding to plan. You must rest.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.48,0:08:11.75,正文,,0,0,0,,大学士 也许弄点安眠酒\N{\fs16}Grand Maester, perhaps some essence of nightshade{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.79,0:08:14.22,正文,,0,0,0,,以帮助他入睡\N{\fs16}to help him sleep.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.25,0:08:17.69,正文,,0,0,0,,我不累！\N{\fs16}I'm not tired!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.23,0:08:21.13,正文,,0,0,0,,来吧\N{\fs16}Come.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.25,0:08:43.35,正文,,0,0,0,,你留下\N{\fs16}Not you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.39,0:08:52.96,正文,,0,0,0,,你刚把维斯特洛最有权势的人\N{\fs16}You just sent the most powerful man in Westeros{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.99,0:08:55.33,正文,,0,0,0,,空着肚子送上床\N{\fs16}to bed without his supper.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.36,0:08:58.93,正文,,0,0,0,,如果你认为他是维斯特洛最有权势的人 你就是个傻瓜\N{\fs16}You're a fool if you believe he's the most powerful man in Westeros.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.96,0:09:01.90,正文,,0,0,0,,叛国言论 乔佛里可是国王\N{\fs16}A treasonous statement. Joffrey is king.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.93,0:09:04.93,正文,,0,0,0,,你真认为王冠能带来权力？\N{\fs16}You really think a crown gives you power?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.74,0:09:08.54,正文,,0,0,0,,不\N{\fs16}No.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.57,0:09:11.37,正文,,0,0,0,,我认为军队才能带来权力\N{\fs16}I think armies give you power.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.41,0:09:14.21,正文,,0,0,0,,- 嗯 - 罗柏·史塔克有支军队\N{\fs16}- Mm- hmm. - Robb Stark had one,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.24,0:09:16.18,正文,,0,0,0,,从没输过一场战役\N{\fs16}never lost a battle,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.21,0:09:18.45,正文,,0,0,0,,还不是被你给打败了\N{\fs16}and you defeated him all the same.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.48,0:09:21.65,正文,,0,0,0,,- 嗯 - 哦 我知道了\N{\fs16}- Mm- hmm. - Oh, I know.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.68,0:09:24.55,正文,,0,0,0,,我猜 这次瓦德·佛雷是非功过\N{\fs16}Walder Frey gets all the credit.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.59,0:09:26.56,正文,,0,0,0,,一肩挑了\N{\fs16}Or the blame, I suppose,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.59,0:09:28.46,正文,,0,0,0,,就看你是否支持他\N{\fs16}depending on your allegiance.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.76,0:09:31.73,正文,,0,0,0,,瓦德·佛雷这人个性很复杂\N{\fs16}Walder Frey is many things,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.76,0:09:33.86,正文,,0,0,0,,但要说他勇敢？\N{\fs16}but a brave man?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.90,0:09:35.26,正文,,0,0,0,,算不上\N{\fs16}No.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.50,0:09:38.63,正文,,0,0,0,,若非别人作出承诺\N{\fs16}He never would have risked such an action{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.67,0:09:41.17,正文,,0,0,0,,谅他没胆子单独行动\N{\fs16}if he didn't have certain assurances.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.20,0:09:43.94,正文,,0,0,0,,我给了他承诺\N{\fs16}Which he got from me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.97,0:09:45.87,正文,,0,0,0,,你有意见吗？\N{\fs16}Do you disapprove?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.91,0:09:47.87,正文,,0,0,0,,兵不厌诈 这就是战争\N{\fs16}I'm all for cheating. This is war.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.91,0:09:50.04,正文,,0,0,0,,但在婚宴上大开杀戒……\N{\fs16}But to slaughter them at a wedding...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.08,0:09:52.88,正文,,0,0,0,,我倒是不明白\N{\fs16}Explain to me why it is more noble{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.91,0:09:54.98,正文,,0,0,0,,在战场上屠杀一万士兵\N{\fs16}to kill 10,000 men in battle{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.02,0:09:56.32,正文,,0,0,0,,与在餐桌边干掉十来个人相比 前者有何高尚之处\N{\fs16}than a dozen at dinner.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.35,0:09:58.35,正文,,0,0,0,,所以您这么干？\N{\fs16}So that's why you did it?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.39,0:09:59.95,正文,,0,0,0,,为了拯救苍生？\N{\fs16}To save lives?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.99,0:10:03.09,正文,,0,0,0,,为了结束战争 为了保护族人\N{\fs16}To end the war. To protect the family.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.12,0:10:05.99,正文,,0,0,0,,你想为死去的史塔克一族写首歌吗？\N{\fs16}Do you want to write a song for the dead Starks?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.03,0:10:08.86,正文,,0,0,0,,写啊\N{\fs16}Go ahead, write one.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.90,0:10:12.33,正文,,0,0,0,,我在这世上保卫兰尼斯特家族 保护亲人\N{\fs16}I'm in this world a little while longer{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.37,0:10:16.17,正文,,0,0,0,,的时间比你长些\N{\fs16}to defend the Lannisters, to defend my blood.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.20,0:10:18.84,正文,,0,0,0,,北方人绝不会忘了这事\N{\fs16}The northerners will never forget.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.87,0:10:20.24,正文,,0,0,0,,很好\N{\fs16}Good.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.27,0:10:21.97,正文,,0,0,0,,等他们向南方行军时\N{\fs16}Let them remember what happens{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.01,0:10:24.34,正文,,0,0,0,,务必记得这一切\N{\fs16}when they march on the south.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.81,0:10:29.08,正文,,0,0,0,,史塔克家族的人都死了\N{\fs16}All the Stark men are dead.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.11,0:10:31.92,正文,,0,0,0,,临冬城成了废墟\N{\fs16}Winterfell is a ruin.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.95,0:10:35.85,正文,,0,0,0,,卢斯·波顿将被册封为北境守护\N{\fs16}Roose Bolton will be named Warden of the North{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.89,0:10:40.89,正文,,0,0,0,,直到你和珊莎的儿子长大成人\N{\fs16}until your son by Sansa comes of age.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.80,0:10:47.36,正文,,0,0,0,,那方面你还得加把劲\N{\fs16}I believe you still have some work to do on that score.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.90,0:10:51.87,正文,,0,0,0,,那您觉得珊莎会乖乖配合吗？\N{\fs16}Do you think she'll open her legs for me{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.90,0:10:55.30,正文,,0,0,0,,在我告诉她我们谋杀了她的母亲和哥哥之后?\N{\fs16}after I tell her how we murdered her mother and brother?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.34,0:10:58.67,正文,,0,0,0,,不管怎样 你得让那姑娘怀孕\N{\fs16}One way or another, you will get that girl pregnant.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.71,0:11:01.21,正文,,0,0,0,,我不会强暴她\N{\fs16}I will not rape her.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.71,0:11:05.65,正文,,0,0,0,,要我简短地给你上一课 教你如何看清这世道吗？\N{\fs16}Shall I explain to you in one easy lesson how the world works?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.68,0:11:08.68,正文,,0,0,0,,劳烦您说简单点 我可没您聪明\N{\fs16}Use small words. I'm not as bright as you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.72,0:11:11.85,正文,,0,0,0,,将家人放在首位的家族\N{\fs16}The house that puts family first will always defeat{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.89,0:11:14.29,正文,,0,0,0,,总会击败那些\N{\fs16}the house that puts the whims and wishes{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.32,0:11:17.56,正文,,0,0,0,,任由子女胡作非为的家族\N{\fs16}of its sons and daughters first.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.59,0:11:19.99,正文,,0,0,0,,一个称职的人会竭尽所能\N{\fs16}A good man does everything in his power{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.03,0:11:23.16,正文,,0,0,0,,为亲人谋福祉\N{\fs16}to better his family's position{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.20,0:11:26.77,正文,,0,0,0,,而非出于个人私欲\N{\fs16}regardless of his own selfish desires.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.54,0:11:31.94,正文,,0,0,0,,你觉得好笑吗？\N{\fs16}Does that amuse you?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.97,0:11:34.84,正文,,0,0,0,,不 这是很好的一课\N{\fs16}No, it's a very good lesson.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.88,0:11:38.18,正文,,0,0,0,,这个家是由您一个人说了算的\N{\fs16}Only it's easy for you to preach utter devotion to family{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.21,0:11:40.78,正文,,0,0,0,,您当然希望每个人都一心一意服务于这个家\N{\fs16}when you're making all the decisions.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.81,0:11:42.62,正文,,0,0,0,,我希望？\N{\fs16}Easy for me, is it?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.65,0:11:46.02,正文,,0,0,0,,您什么时候做事不是出于个人私欲\N{\fs16}When have you ever done something that wasn't in your interest{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.05,0:11:48.39,正文,,0,0,0,,什么时候又是纯为了家人的利益着想？\N{\fs16}but solely for the benefit of the family?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.42,0:11:51.26,正文,,0,0,0,,你出生的那一天\N{\fs16}The day that you were born.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.53,0:11:57.53,正文,,0,0,0,,我想把你扔进海里\N{\fs16}I wanted to carry you into the sea{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.56,0:11:59.93,正文,,0,0,0,,让海浪把你冲走\N{\fs16}and let the waves wash you away.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.17,0:12:04.74,正文,,0,0,0,,但我却让你活了下来\N{\fs16}Instead, I let you live.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.84,0:12:08.31,正文,,0,0,0,,作为儿子养大\N{\fs16}And I brought you as my son.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.31,0:12:14.11,正文,,0,0,0,,因为你还算是个兰尼斯特\N{\fs16}Because you're a Lannister.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.79,0:12:31.43,正文,,0,0,0,,珊莎\N{\fs16}Sansa.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.20,0:12:56.70,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,100)\pos(295,189)}梅拉·黎德
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.40,0:13:02.40,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(60,248)}夏天{\b0}\N{\fs12}布兰·史塔克的冰原狼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.92,0:13:02.06,正文,,0,0,0,,里面没人\N{\fs16}It's empty.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.09,0:13:03.72,正文,,0,0,0,,我们找个地方睡觉\N{\fs16}Let's find a place to sleep.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.40,0:13:03.90,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(228,273)}玖健·黎德{\b0}\N{\fs12}拥有绿之视野的男孩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.50,0:13:15.50,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,100)\pos(294,292)}阿多{\b0}\N{\fs12}临冬城的马僮
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.27,0:13:15.44,正文,,0,0,0,,阿多\N{\fs16}Hodor.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.84,0:13:18.34,正文,,0,0,0,,阿多\N{\fs16}Hodor.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.37,0:13:21.07,正文,,0,0,0,,别这样 阿多\N{\fs16}Don't, Hodor.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.50,0:13:21.20,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(463,188)}布兰·史塔克\N{\fs12}异形者
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.76,0:13:27.59,正文,,0,0,0,,也许我们不该待在这儿\N{\fs16}Maybe we shouldn't stay.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.62,0:13:30.26,正文,,0,0,0,,你情愿待在外面？\N{\fs16}You'd rather be out there?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.29,0:13:33.23,正文,,0,0,0,,关于这地方 流传着很多故事\N{\fs16}There are a lot of stories about this place.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.50,0:13:35.96,正文,,0,0,0,,恐怖的故事\N{\fs16}Horrible stories.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.00,0:13:38.13,正文,,0,0,0,,我总喜欢听恐怖故事\N{\fs16}I always quite liked the horrible stories.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.17,0:13:40.00,正文,,0,0,0,,我也是\N{\fs16}So did I.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.12,0:13:42.30,正文,,0,0,0,,从前\N{\fs16}Once.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.61,0:13:46.54,正文,,0,0,0,,你听过鼠厨师的故事吗？\N{\fs16}You ever heard about the Rat Cook?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.57,0:13:48.78,正文,,0,0,0,,没有 他是谁\N{\fs16}No. Who's he?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.81,0:13:52.05,正文,,0,0,0,,他只是守夜人中的一名厨师\N{\fs16}Just a cook in the Night's Watch.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.08,0:13:54.52,正文,,0,0,0,,他因为什么事生国王的气\N{\fs16}He was angry at the king for something,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.55,0:13:56.45,正文,,0,0,0,,我不记得了\N{\fs16}I don't remember.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.48,0:13:59.25,正文,,0,0,0,,国王访问长夜堡时\N{\fs16}When the king was visiting the Nightfort,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.29,0:14:01.72,正文,,0,0,0,,厨师杀死了国王的儿子\N{\fs16}the cook killed the king's son,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.76,0:14:03.66,正文,,0,0,0,,和洋葱 胡萝卜 蘑菇 培根一起\N{\fs16}cooked him into a big pie{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.69,0:14:07.26,正文,,0,0,0,,做成了一个大馅饼\N{\fs16}with onions, carrots, mushrooms and bacon.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.30,0:14:11.26,正文,,0,0,0,,那天夜里他将馅饼呈给国王\N{\fs16}That night he served the pie to the king.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.30,0:14:13.97,正文,,0,0,0,,国王津津有味地吃着自己亲儿子的肉\N{\fs16}He liked the taste of his son so much,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.03,0:14:16.44,正文,,0,0,0,,并叫厨师再来一块\N{\fs16}he asked for a second slice.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.54,0:14:21.64,正文,,0,0,0,,后来 诸神把厨师变成一只巨大的白老鼠\N{\fs16}The gods turned the cook into a giant white rat{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.67,0:14:23.98,正文,,0,0,0,,只能吃自己的小孩\N{\fs16}who could only eat his own young.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.01,0:14:27.38,正文,,0,0,0,,从此以后 他就在长夜堡内游荡\N{\fs16}He's been roaming the Nightfort ever since,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.41,0:14:29.71,正文,,0,0,0,,吞食子孙\N{\fs16}devouring his own babies.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.72,0:14:33.88,正文,,0,0,0,,但无论如何\N{\fs16}But no matter what he does,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.92,0:14:35.89,正文,,0,0,0,,饥饿感却永远无法满足\N{\fs16}he's always hungry.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.02,0:14:39.16,正文,,0,0,0,,要是诸神把所有的杀人犯\N{\fs16}If the gods turned every killer{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.19,0:14:40.49,正文,,0,0,0,,都变成大白老鼠…\N{\fs16}into a giant white rat--{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.53,0:14:42.86,正文,,0,0,0,,诸神不是因为谋杀而诅咒鼠厨师\N{\fs16}It wasn't for murder the gods cursed the Rat Cook{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.89,0:14:45.23,正文,,0,0,0,,也不是因为给国王吃自己儿子做的馅饼\N{\fs16}or for serving the king's son in a pie.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.26,0:14:47.60,正文,,0,0,0,,但是杀害自家屋檐下的宾客\N{\fs16}He killed a guest beneath his roof.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.63,0:14:52.04,正文,,0,0,0,,践踏宾客权利 诸神绝不原谅\N{\fs16}That's something the gods can't forgive.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.70,0:14:56.50,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(290,222)}瓦德·佛雷\N{\b0\fs12}孪河城侯爵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.40,0:15:08.90,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\an8}篡夺者战争时期 佛雷家族是徒利家族的封臣 在三叉戟河之役（劳勃与雷加的决斗）\N佛雷侯爵在战争结束后方才带着人马姗姗来迟 不禁让人怀疑他原本打算为哪一边效力\N 从此霍斯特·徒利改口称他为“迟到的佛雷侯爵”
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.51,0:15:03.25,正文,,0,0,0,,老徒利曾经称呼我“迟到的瓦德·佛雷”\N{\fs16}"The late Walder Frey," old Tully called me{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.28,0:15:07.05,正文,,0,0,0,,因为我没有及时出兵到三叉戟河\N{\fs16}because I didn't get my men to the Trident in time for battle.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.08,0:15:09.42,正文,,0,0,0,,他自以为精明\N{\fs16}He thought he was witty.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.45,0:15:11.65,正文,,0,0,0,,而如今呢 老徒利\N{\fs16}Look at us now, Tully.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.69,0:15:14.69,正文,,0,0,0,,你已经死了 你女儿也死了\N{\fs16}You're dead, your daughter's dead,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.72,0:15:16.29,正文,,0,0,0,,你的外孙也死了\N{\fs16}your grandson's dead,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.33,0:15:19.49,正文,,0,0,0,,你儿子在地牢里度过了新婚之夜\N{\fs16}your son spent his wedding night in a dungeon{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.53,0:15:22.33,正文,,0,0,0,,而我 成了奔流城公爵\N{\fs16}and I'm Lord of Riverrun.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.10,0:15:26.03,正文,,0,0,0,,“黑鱼”逃走了\N{\fs16}The Blackfish escaped.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.57,0:15:29.74,正文,,0,0,0,,不过是个流亡的老头子\N{\fs16}An old man on the run{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.77,0:15:32.21,正文,,0,0,0,,孤立无援\N{\fs16}with no allies.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.24,0:15:34.24,正文,,0,0,0,,我有泰温·兰尼斯特撑腰\N{\fs16}I have Tywin Lannister backing me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.28,0:15:37.28,正文,,0,0,0,,- 他还有谁？ - 言之有理\N{\fs16}- Who does he have? - As you say.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.31,0:15:38.95,正文,,0,0,0,,他们都嘲笑我\N{\fs16}They all laughed at me,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.98,0:15:40.91,正文,,0,0,0,,那些个高高在上的领主们\N{\fs16}all those high lords.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.95,0:15:43.92,正文,,0,0,0,,一个个都自以为比我强\N{\fs16}They all thought they were better than me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.95,0:15:46.69,正文,,0,0,0,,奈德·史塔克 霍斯特·徒利\N{\fs16}Ned Stark, Hoster Tully.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.72,0:15:50.22,正文,,0,0,0,,我娶个年轻姑娘他们也笑话\N{\fs16}People snigger when I marry a young girl,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.26,0:15:53.73,正文,,0,0,0,,当年琼恩·艾林娶徒利家的小骚货时 他们怎么不去叽歪\N{\fs16}but who said a word when Jon Arryn married the little Tully bitch?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.76,0:15:55.79,正文,,0,0,0,,你得再娶个年轻姑娘咯\N{\fs16}You'll be needing a new young girl.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.83,0:15:57.93,正文,,0,0,0,,是啊\N{\fs16}Yeah.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.96,0:16:00.63,正文,,0,0,0,,咱得合计合计这事儿\N{\fs16}Got that to look forward to.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.00,0:16:03.47,正文,,0,0,0,,而你\N{\fs16}And you,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.50,0:16:05.64,正文,,0,0,0,,成了北境守护\N{\fs16}the Warden of the North.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.67,0:16:09.01,正文,,0,0,0,,再也不用向史塔克们俯首称臣了\N{\fs16}No more Starks to bow and scrape to.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.04,0:16:10.71,正文,,0,0,0,,真是苦了你了\N{\fs16}Must have been torture{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.74,0:16:12.81,正文,,0,0,0,,一路跟着那个傻小子征战\N{\fs16}following that stupid boy all over the country.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.85,0:16:15.91,正文,,0,0,0,,他从来没有听从我的建议\N{\fs16}He ignored my advice at every turn.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.95,0:16:18.08,正文,,0,0,0,,假如当初他稍微收敛一点…\N{\fs16}If he'd been a trifle less arrogant...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.12,0:16:20.62,正文,,0,0,0,,竟然自称少狼主\N{\fs16}Calling himself the Young Wolf.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.65,0:16:22.39,正文,,0,0,0,,瞧给他得瑟的\N{\fs16}How's that for pomposity?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.96,0:16:27.29,正文,,0,0,0,,敬少狼主\N{\fs16}Well, here's to the Young Wolf!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.33,0:16:30.06,正文,,0,0,0,,永远年少\N{\fs16}Forever young.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.67,0:16:38.40,正文,,0,0,0,,战争已经结束了 你会搬去临冬城住么\N{\fs16}Will you move to Winterfell now that the war's over?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.44,0:16:41.00,正文,,0,0,0,,总归是会的吧\N{\fs16}At some point perhaps.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.04,0:16:43.17,正文,,0,0,0,,然而临冬城已经成了一片废墟\N{\fs16}But Winterfell's in ruins.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.21,0:16:46.04,正文,,0,0,0,,是啊\N{\fs16}Yeah.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.08,0:16:47.84,正文,,0,0,0,,那里究竟发生了什么\N{\fs16}What happened up there?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.88,0:16:50.91,正文,,0,0,0,,听说被那个葛雷乔伊家的儿子占领了\N{\fs16}I heard the Greyjoy boy seized the place.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.95,0:16:53.52,正文,,0,0,0,,他宰了所有的信鸦\N{\fs16}I heard he killed all the ravens.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.55,0:16:55.95,正文,,0,0,0,,那以后就没信儿了\N{\fs16}And after that, nothing.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.99,0:16:58.95,正文,,0,0,0,,我派了私生子拉姆斯去讨伐他\N{\fs16}I sent my bastard Ramsay to root him out.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.99,0:17:02.56,正文,,0,0,0,,罗柏·史塔克对那些铁民给予特赦\N{\fs16}Robb Stark offered amnesty for the ironborn{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.59,0:17:04.43,正文,,0,0,0,,只要他们把席恩交出来\N{\fs16}if they gave us Theon.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.46,0:17:06.40,正文,,0,0,0,,噢 然后呢？\N{\fs16}Oh. And?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.43,0:17:08.03,正文,,0,0,0,,拉姆斯把话带过去了\N{\fs16}Ramsay delivered the terms.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.06,0:17:12.20,正文,,0,0,0,,铁民交出了席恩 预料之中的事\N{\fs16}The ironborn turned on Theon as we knew they would.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.23,0:17:15.40,正文,,0,0,0,,五花大绑地交了出来\N{\fs16}They handed him over trussed and hooded.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.44,0:17:19.51,正文,,0,0,0,,不过呢 拉姆斯…\N{\fs16}But Ramsay--well...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.54,0:17:22.14,正文,,0,0,0,,他有他自己的行事方式\N{\fs16}Ramsay has his own way of doing things.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.30,0:17:25.81,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(249,176)}拉姆斯·雪诺\N{\b0\fs12}卢斯·波顿的私生子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.11,0:17:25.08,正文,,0,0,0,,看来 姑娘们句句属实啊\N{\fs16}Well, the girls weren't lying.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.11,0:17:27.01,正文,,0,0,0,,你那话儿还真不小\N{\fs16}You had a good- sized cock.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.91,0:17:31.01,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(164,231)}席恩·葛雷乔伊{\b0}\N{\fs12}铁群岛继承人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.46,0:17:37.16,正文,,0,0,0,,咋了？\N{\fs16}What?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.19,0:17:38.59,正文,,0,0,0,,不是啦\N{\fs16}No.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.76,0:17:43.30,正文,,0,0,0,,猪肉肠而已\N{\fs16}Pork sausage.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.33,0:17:45.70,正文,,0,0,0,,你以为我是哪来的野人么？\N{\fs16}You think I'm some sort of savage?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.11,0:18:00.61,正文,,0,0,0,,人们说起幻肢\N{\fs16}People talk about phantom limbs.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.65,0:18:04.05,正文,,0,0,0,,一个人就算被砍掉了脚 他也会感觉到原先有脚的地方会痒\N{\fs16}An amputee might have an itch where his foot used to be.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.08,0:18:06.48,正文,,0,0,0,,所以 我就纳闷了…\N{\fs16}So I've always wondered...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.46,0:18:12.96,正文,,0,0,0,,太监是不是也有“幻鸡巴”？\N{\fs16}do eunuchs have a phantom cock?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.86,0:18:16.96,正文,,0,0,0,,当你以后想到裸女\N{\fs16}Next time you think about naked girls,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.99,0:18:19.56,正文,,0,0,0,,你的幻鸡巴会不会有点痒？\N{\fs16}would you feel an itch?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.91,0:18:29.51,正文,,0,0,0,,不好意思\N{\fs16}Sorry.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.64,0:18:32.44,正文,,0,0,0,,我不该开玩笑\N{\fs16}I shouldn't make jokes.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.01,0:18:37.01,正文,,0,0,0,,妈妈教过我不要对残废扔石头\N{\fs16}My mother taught me not to throw stones at cripples.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.58,0:18:44.12,正文,,0,0,0,,但是我父亲说 瞄准脑袋再扔\N{\fs16}But my father taught me to aim for their head.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.15,0:18:46.19,正文,,0,0,0,,杀了我\N{\fs16}Kill me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.22,0:18:48.16,正文,,0,0,0,,抱歉 什么？\N{\fs16}Sorry, what?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.53,0:18:51.29,正文,,0,0,0,,杀了我\N{\fs16}Kill me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.96,0:18:54.53,正文,,0,0,0,,再大点声\N{\fs16}A little louder.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.56,0:18:57.63,正文,,0,0,0,,杀了我吧！\N{\fs16}Kill me!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.24,0:19:01.57,正文,,0,0,0,,你死了对我又没什么好处\N{\fs16}You're no good to me dead.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.60,0:19:04.04,正文,,0,0,0,,我们需要你\N{\fs16}We need you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.86,0:19:27.49,正文,,0,0,0,,你看起来都不像“席恩·葛雷乔伊”了\N{\fs16}You don't look like a Theon Greyjoy anymore.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.90,0:19:31.06,正文,,0,0,0,,那是贵族的名字\N{\fs16}That's a name for a lord.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.27,0:19:34.33,正文,,0,0,0,,而你不是什么贵族\N{\fs16}But you're not a lord,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.37,0:19:36.54,正文,,0,0,0,,是吧\N{\fs16}are you?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.57,0:19:39.50,正文,,0,0,0,,你只是块肉\N{\fs16}You're just meat.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.07,0:19:44.91,正文,,0,0,0,,一块烂肉\N{\fs16}Stinking meat.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.05,0:19:50.45,正文,,0,0,0,,你散发着臭气\N{\fs16}You reek.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.48,0:19:53.25,正文,,0,0,0,,臭佬！\N{\fs16}Reek!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.29,0:19:55.49,正文,,0,0,0,,这名字蛮适合你啊\N{\fs16}That's a good name for you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.69,0:19:59.29,正文,,0,0,0,,你叫什么名字？\N{\fs16}What's your name?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.32,0:20:01.56,正文,,0,0,0,,席恩·葛雷乔伊\N{\fs16}Theon Greyjoy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.63,0:20:08.73,正文,,0,0,0,,你叫什么名字？\N{\fs16}What's your name?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.83,0:20:12.60,正文,,0,0,0,,席 --\N{\fs16}Th--{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.64,0:20:15.10,正文,,0,0,0,,席恩·葛雷乔伊\N{\fs16}Theon Greyjoy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.21,0:20:23.35,正文,,0,0,0,,求求你\N{\fs16}Please.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.38,0:20:28.38,正文,,0,0,0,,你叫什么名字？！\N{\fs16}What is your name?!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.89,0:20:31.39,正文,,0,0,0,,臭佬\N{\fs16}Reek.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.79,0:20:36.26,正文,,0,0,0,,我的名字是…\N{\fs16}My name is...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.09,0:20:40.19,正文,,0,0,0,,臭佬\N{\fs16}Reek.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.12,0:21:09.56,正文,,0,0,0,,阿多\N{\fs16}Hodor.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.00,0:21:41.40,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(643,319)}山姆威尔·塔利{\b0}\N{\fs12}守夜人事务官
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.49,0:21:42.09,正文,,0,0,0,,- 别杀我！ - 什么人？\N{\fs16}- Don't kill me! - Who are you?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.12,0:21:44.82,正文,,0,0,0,,- 山姆！山姆！ - 你是什么人？！\N{\fs16}- Sam! Sam! - Who are you?!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.86,0:21:47.76,正文,,0,0,0,,我叫吉莉 不要伤害我们\N{\fs16}Gilly. Don't hurt us.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.79,0:21:49.56,正文,,0,0,0,,你们要去哪？\N{\fs16}Where are you going?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.59,0:21:53.10,正文,,0,0,0,,去黑城堡 我是一名守夜人\N{\fs16}To Castle Black. I'm a brother of the Night's Watch.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.13,0:21:55.47,正文,,0,0,0,,- 我哥哥 他也在守… - 嘘\N{\fs16}- My brother, he's in the Night's--- Shush.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.50,0:21:57.23,正文,,0,0,0,,- 你哥哥是谁？ - 那不重要\N{\fs16}- Who's your brother? - Doesn't matter.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.41,0:22:08.61,正文,,0,0,0,,你是琼恩的弟弟\N{\fs16}You're Jon's brother.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.64,0:22:10.58,正文,,0,0,0,,那个从窗户坠下去的\N{\fs16}The one who fell from the window.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.61,0:22:12.75,正文,,0,0,0,,我不是\N{\fs16}No, I'm not.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.78,0:22:17.32,正文,,0,0,0,,我认识白灵 知道冰原狼长什么样\N{\fs16}I've been around Ghost enough to know a direwolf when I see one.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.20,0:22:18.51,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(639,331)}吉莉{\b0}\N{\fs12}卡斯特的女儿与妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.35,0:22:19.49,正文,,0,0,0,,我也听说过阿多\N{\fs16}And I've heard all about Hodor.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.52,0:22:21.39,正文,,0,0,0,,阿多\N{\fs16}Hodor.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.19,0:22:26.49,正文,,0,0,0,,要不是琼恩 我早没命了\N{\fs16}I'd be dead if it wasn't for Jon.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.53,0:22:28.56,正文,,0,0,0,,如果你是他的弟弟 那么你也是我的兄弟\N{\fs16}If you're his brother, you're my brother, too.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.60,0:22:30.93,正文,,0,0,0,,我会尽我所能帮助你\N{\fs16}And anything I can do to help you, I will.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.97,0:22:33.33,正文,,0,0,0,,带我们去长城以北\N{\fs16}Take us north of the Wall.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.64,0:22:39.97,正文,,0,0,0,,什么？\N{\fs16}What?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.01,0:22:41.94,正文,,0,0,0,,你怎么会想去…\N{\fs16}Why in the world would you want to go--{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.98,0:22:44.31,正文,,0,0,0,,我不是想去 我必须去\N{\fs16}I don't want to. I have to.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.34,0:22:45.62,正文,,0,0,0,,你们是怎么穿过长城的？\N{\fs16}How did you get through the Wall?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.74,0:22:49.05,正文,,0,0,0,,那口井是不是通向地下河？ 你们是从那儿过来的么？\N{\fs16}Does the well lead to an underground river? Is that how you came here?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.08,0:22:51.52,正文,,0,0,0,,跟我们走吧\N{\fs16}Come with us.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.55,0:22:55.06,正文,,0,0,0,,长城南面刻有阶梯\N{\fs16}There are steps carved into the south side of the Wall.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.18,0:22:56.92,正文,,0,0,0,,阿多可以背你上去\N{\fs16}Hodor can carry you to the top.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.96,0:22:59.12,正文,,0,0,0,,我们直接回到黑城堡\N{\fs16}We'll walk straight to Castle Black.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.16,0:23:02.59,正文,,0,0,0,,跟我们走吧 长城以北只有死路一条\N{\fs16}Come with us. There's nothing north but death.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.63,0:23:04.90,正文,,0,0,0,,琼恩如果还活着\N{\fs16}If Jon is alive,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.93,0:23:06.70,正文,,0,0,0,,他会回黑城堡去的\N{\fs16}then Castle Black's where he'll be.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.73,0:23:08.67,正文,,0,0,0,,你们在那里最安全\N{\fs16}It's the safest place for you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.70,0:23:11.34,正文,,0,0,0,,现在不管哪里都不在安全 你知道的\N{\fs16}There's nowhere safe any longer. You know that.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.37,0:23:14.91,正文,,0,0,0,,我亲眼见到过\N{\fs16}What I know is what I saw.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.94,0:23:16.84,正文,,0,0,0,,如果你也见到了 你绝不会往那儿走\N{\fs16}And if you saw it, too, you'd run the other way.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.88,0:23:20.41,正文,,0,0,0,,你见到异鬼和亡者大军\N{\fs16}You saw the white walkers and the army of the dead.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.38,0:23:22.85,正文,,0,0,0,,你怎么知道的？\N{\fs16}How do you know all that?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.88,0:23:25.45,正文,,0,0,0,,守夜人抵挡不了它们\N{\fs16}The Night's Watch can't stop them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.48,0:23:29.09,正文,,0,0,0,,维斯特洛所有的国王和他们的军队都抵挡不了\N{\fs16}The kings of Westeros and all their armies can't stop them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.10,0:23:40.23,正文,,0,0,0,,你们这是要去抵挡它们？\N{\fs16}But you're going to stop them?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.26,0:23:42.97,正文,,0,0,0,,让我们去吧 山姆\N{\fs16}Please, Sam.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.00,0:23:45.03,正文,,0,0,0,,我必须去北边\N{\fs16}I have to go north.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.60,0:23:48.47,正文,,0,0,0,,必须去\N{\fs16}I have to.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.91,0:24:03.50,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(68,260)}巴隆·葛雷乔伊\N{\fs12}铁群岛大王
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.53,0:24:19.67,正文,,0,0,0,,“巴隆·葛雷乔伊 铁群岛公爵\N{\fs16}"Balon Greyjoy, Lord of the Iron Islands{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.70,0:24:21.94,正文,,0,0,0,,和北境的入侵者\N{\fs16}and invader of the North.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.97,0:24:23.97,正文,,0,0,0,,限你在满月之前\N{\fs16}I give you until the full moon{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.01,0:24:27.17,正文,,0,0,0,,令麾下所有的铁种杂碎们离开北境\N{\fs16}to order all ironborn scum out of the North{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.21,0:24:30.34,正文,,0,0,0,,滚回你们沾满臭粪的石头上\N{\fs16}and back to those shit- stained rocks{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.38,0:24:32.55,正文,,0,0,0,,你们所谓的老家\N{\fs16}you call a home.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.70,0:24:33.91,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(495,193)}亚拉·葛雷乔伊\N{\fs12}席恩的姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.58,0:24:35.35,正文,,0,0,0,,然后到了满月的那一夜\N{\fs16}On the first night of the full moon,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.38,0:24:37.95,正文,,0,0,0,,我会捉住每一个\N{\fs16}I will hunt down every islander{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.99,0:24:42.52,正文,,0,0,0,,留在我们地盘的岛民 活剥了他们的皮\N{\fs16}still in our lands and flay them living{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.56,0:24:46.02,正文,,0,0,0,,就像我剥了临冬城的那\N{\fs16}the way I flayed the 20 ironborn scum{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.06,0:24:47.74,正文,,0,0,0,,二十个铁民渣滓的皮一样\N{\fs16}I found at Winterfell.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.86,0:24:51.50,正文,,0,0,0,,盒子里有一份送给你们的小礼物\N{\fs16}In the box you'll find a special gift--{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.50,0:24:55.63,正文,,0,0,0,,席恩最爱的玩具\N{\fs16}Theon's favorite toy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.67,0:24:59.00,正文,,0,0,0,,我给他割下来的时候他还哭了\N{\fs16}He cried when I took it away from him.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.12,0:25:23.39,正文,,0,0,0,,立刻从北境撤军 否则我会送更多盒子过来\N{\fs16}Leave the North now or more boxes will follow{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.43,0:25:26.00,正文,,0,0,0,,每个盒子里都有你们的席恩\N{\fs16}with more Theon.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.00,0:25:28.33,正文,,0,0,0,,署名 拉姆斯·雪诺\N{\fs16}Signed Ramsay Snow,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.37,0:25:30.00,正文,,0,0,0,,恐怖堡公爵 北境守护\N{\fs16}natural- born son of Roose Bolton,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.03,0:25:33.00,正文,,0,0,0,,卢斯·波顿的亲生儿子\N{\fs16}Lord of the Dreadfort and Warden of the North."{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.01,0:25:38.21,正文,,0,0,0,,把那玩意儿拿走\N{\fs16}Get that out of my sight.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.81,0:25:47.48,正文,,0,0,0,,席恩不听我的指挥\N{\fs16}Theon disobeyed my orders.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.99,0:25:53.35,正文,,0,0,0,,那小子是个白痴\N{\fs16}The boy is a fool.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.79,0:25:59.03,正文,,0,0,0,,他没法给葛雷乔伊家传宗接代了\N{\fs16}He cannot further the Greyjoy line.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.33,0:26:03.73,正文,,0,0,0,,我不会放弃已经占领的地盘\N{\fs16}I will not give up the lands I have seized,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.77,0:26:05.93,正文,,0,0,0,,拿下的要塞\N{\fs16}the strongholds I have taken.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.97,0:26:07.73,正文,,0,0,0,,快拿走\N{\fs16}Get this away from me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.67,0:26:10.17,正文,,0,0,0,,他是你的儿子\N{\fs16}He's your son.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.20,0:26:13.04,正文,,0,0,0,,儿子？\N{\fs16}Son?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.07,0:26:15.84,正文,,0,0,0,,他连个男人都不是了\N{\fs16}He's not a man anymore.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.88,0:26:17.44,正文,,0,0,0,,他是你的儿子\N{\fs16}He's your son.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.48,0:26:20.91,正文,,0,0,0,,是我的弟弟\N{\fs16}He's my brother.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.95,0:26:22.21,正文,,0,0,0,,是葛雷乔伊家的人\N{\fs16}He's a Greyjoy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.25,0:26:24.48,正文,,0,0,0,,注意自己的言行\N{\fs16}Watch yourself.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.52,0:26:26.85,正文,,0,0,0,,我决心已定\N{\fs16}I've made my decision.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.79,0:26:33.93,正文,,0,0,0,,我也是\N{\fs16}And I've made mine.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.83,0:26:40.10,正文,,0,0,0,,我要乘舰队里最快的船\N{\fs16}I'm going to pick the fastest ship in our fleet.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.33,0:26:45.70,正文,,0,0,0,,我要挑选铁群岛上最厉害的五十个杀手\N{\fs16}I'm going to choose the 50 best killers on the Iron Islands.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.74,0:26:48.17,正文,,0,0,0,,拿着绳子！\N{\fs16}Get those ropes!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.21,0:26:50.24,正文,,0,0,0,,我要沿着狭海北上\N{\fs16}I'm going to sail up the Narrow Sea{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.28,0:26:52.61,正文,,0,0,0,,驶入泪江\N{\fs16}all the way to the Weeping Water.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.81,0:26:56.95,正文,,0,0,0,,我要向恐怖堡进发\N{\fs16}I'm going to march on the Dreadfort.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.98,0:26:59.72,正文,,0,0,0,,我要找到我的弟弟\N{\fs16}I'm going to find my little brother{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.75,0:27:02.65,正文,,0,0,0,,然后 我要带他回家\N{\fs16}and I'm going to bring him home.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.29,0:27:09.93,正文,,0,0,0,,这是什么？\N{\fs16}What is it?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.96,0:27:11.46,正文,,0,0,0,,龙晶\N{\fs16}Dragonglass.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.49,0:27:13.30,正文,,0,0,0,,是我们在拳峰发现的\N{\fs16}We found them at the Fist.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.33,0:27:16.90,正文,,0,0,0,,很久以前 有人埋在那里\N{\fs16}Someone buried them a long time ago.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.93,0:27:19.10,正文,,0,0,0,,希望被我们找到\N{\fs16}Someone wanted us to find them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.14,0:27:22.97,正文,,0,0,0,,为什么？它们有什么用？\N{\fs16}Why? What are they for?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.41,0:27:29.14,正文,,0,0,0,,能杀死异鬼\N{\fs16}Killing white walkers.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.18,0:27:30.65,正文,,0,0,0,,你怎么知道？\N{\fs16}How do you know that?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.68,0:27:33.31,正文,,0,0,0,,那个异鬼冲着我的孩子走来\N{\fs16}The walker came for my baby.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.18,0:27:35.72,正文,,0,0,0,,然后山姆…\N{\fs16}And Sam...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.75,0:27:38.95,正文,,0,0,0,,但是几千年来都没有人杀死过异鬼\N{\fs16}But no one's killed a white walker in thousands of years.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.99,0:27:42.96,正文,,0,0,0,,总归有人第一个吃螃蟹吧\N{\fs16}Well, I suppose someone had to be the first.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.99,0:27:45.19,正文,,0,0,0,,拿着 阿多\N{\fs16}Take it, Hodor.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.87,0:27:53.73,正文,,0,0,0,,弓箭手也用得到\N{\fs16}And the archer.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.44,0:28:01.81,正文,,0,0,0,,我面对一个异鬼\N{\fs16}I got lucky{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.84,0:28:04.08,正文,,0,0,0,,侥幸逃生\N{\fs16}with one of them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.11,0:28:05.75,正文,,0,0,0,,他们还有更多\N{\fs16}There are more.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.78,0:28:09.32,正文,,0,0,0,,多得很\N{\fs16}Many more.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.35,0:28:11.85,正文,,0,0,0,,而且每一个异鬼\N{\fs16}And for every one of them,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.89,0:28:14.42,正文,,0,0,0,,伴随着的尸鬼\N{\fs16}the dead men,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.45,0:28:16.35,正文,,0,0,0,,数不胜数\N{\fs16}more than you could count.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.86,0:28:22.06,正文,,0,0,0,,真希望你们能跟我们走\N{\fs16}I wish you'd come with us.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.10,0:28:24.56,正文,,0,0,0,,我也希望可以\N{\fs16}I wish I could.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.33,0:28:28.27,正文,,0,0,0,,可惜情非所愿\N{\fs16}I really do.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.90,0:29:19.40,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(296,170)}戴佛斯·席渥斯\N{\b0\fs12}“洋葱骑士” 史坦尼斯的首相
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.71,0:29:18.45,正文,,0,0,0,,身体还好么？\N{\fs16}How are you keeping?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.48,0:29:20.28,正文,,0,0,0,,棒极了\N{\fs16}Great.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.40,0:29:21.70,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(482,267)}詹德利\N{\b0\fs12}“大牛” 劳勃·拜拉席恩的私生子
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.32,0:29:21.75,正文,,0,0,0,,好得不能再好\N{\fs16}Never better.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.78,0:29:24.39,正文,,0,0,0,,只是一点血罢了\N{\fs16}It was just a bit of blood.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.25,0:29:27.19,正文,,0,0,0,,我早该想到了\N{\fs16}I should have known.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.22,0:29:29.86,正文,,0,0,0,,只要有出身名门的人打听我的名字 准没好事\N{\fs16}Every time a highborn asks my name, it's trouble.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.06,0:29:32.66,正文,,0,0,0,,在你们看来 我们就不算做人 是么\N{\fs16}We're not really people to you, are we?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.69,0:29:34.49,正文,,0,0,0,,只是你们达成目的的各种手段而已\N{\fs16}Just a million different ways to get what you want.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.53,0:29:37.20,正文,,0,0,0,,- 我并非出身名门 - 她管你叫“爵士”\N{\fs16}- I'm not a highborn. - She called you Ser.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.23,0:29:39.10,正文,,0,0,0,,我听到了\N{\fs16}I heard it.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.90,0:29:43.64,正文,,0,0,0,,那是后来的事了\N{\fs16}A recent state of affairs.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.11,0:29:50.64,正文,,0,0,0,,我和你一样 也是在跳蚤窝出生的\N{\fs16}I was born in Flea Bottom just like you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.68,0:29:52.85,正文,,0,0,0,,可不是嘛\N{\fs16}Sure, you were.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.88,0:29:54.58,正文,,0,0,0,,你是我的朋友 来救我的咯\N{\fs16}You're my friend. You're here to help.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.61,0:29:56.65,正文,,0,0,0,,我在面粉街下面一带住过\N{\fs16}I lived below the Street of Flour.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.68,0:29:58.08,正文,,0,0,0,,离面粉街多远？\N{\fs16}How far below?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.12,0:30:00.29,正文,,0,0,0,,离红堡又有多近？\N{\fs16}How close to the Red Keep were you?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.69,0:30:04.16,正文,,0,0,0,,从红堡下水道涌出的屎尿\N{\fs16}The shit that poured from their privy pipes{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.19,0:30:07.93,正文,,0,0,0,,沿着制革道流向伊耿高丘的一端\N{\fs16}flowed down the side of Aegon's Hill{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.96,0:30:12.00,正文,,0,0,0,,恰好从我门前经过\N{\fs16}along Tanner's Row and right in front of my front door{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.03,0:30:14.17,正文,,0,0,0,,那是在...松酒巷\N{\fs16}- on Gin Alley. - Gin Alley.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.84,0:30:18.80,正文,,0,0,0,,钢铁街\N{\fs16}The Street of Steel,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.84,0:30:22.14,正文,,0,0,0,,整天与你的盔甲和骑士在一起？ 噗\N{\fs16}with your armor and your knights? Pfft.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:22.17,0:30:24.61,正文,,0,0,0,,你可在城镇最热闹的地方住过\N{\fs16}You lived in the fancy part of town.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.61,0:30:31.45,正文,,0,0,0,,但我们现在却在这里\N{\fs16}And here we are now.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.48,0:30:35.05,正文,,0,0,0,,两个跳蚤窝出身的男孩身处于国王的城堡之中\N{\fs16}Two boys from Flea Bottom in the castle of a king.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.09,0:30:37.52,正文,,0,0,0,,是啊 我们走了好长一段路\N{\fs16}Yeah, we've come a long way.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.56,0:30:40.79,正文,,0,0,0,,我们是一路人 真的\N{\fs16}We're all the same, really.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.82,0:30:43.79,正文,,0,0,0,,她费尽心机向我指出这一点\N{\fs16}She went to great pains to point that out to me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.83,0:30:46.20,正文,,0,0,0,,既然你都不信任那些衣冠楚楚的人\N{\fs16}If you mistrust fancy people so much,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.23,0:30:49.37,正文,,0,0,0,,为什么会轻信她的鬼话？\N{\fs16}why were you in such a hurry to trust her?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.73,0:30:53.14,正文,,0,0,0,,如果你是我的话\N{\fs16}You're me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.17,0:30:54.50,正文,,0,0,0,,从来没亲近过女人\N{\fs16}Never been with a woman.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.54,0:30:57.37,正文,,0,0,0,,连话都没跟女人说过 真的\N{\fs16}Never talked to a woman, really.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.41,0:30:58.97,正文,,0,0,0,,然后她来到了你面前 --\N{\fs16}And then she comes at you--{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.01,0:31:02.11,正文,,0,0,0,,一番大话 一丝不挂\N{\fs16}big words, no clothes.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.14,0:31:03.91,正文,,0,0,0,,换了是你你会怎么做？\N{\fs16}What would you have done?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.58,0:31:09.22,正文,,0,0,0,,她懂得如何操纵一个男人 这确实不假\N{\fs16}She does know her way around a man's head, I'll give her that.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.86,0:31:17.56,正文,,0,0,0,,话说 你是怎么成为贵族的？\N{\fs16}So how'd you become a lord?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.59,0:31:19.26,正文,,0,0,0,,哦 那个说来话长\N{\fs16}Oh, that's a long story.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.29,0:31:22.40,正文,,0,0,0,,那就长话短说，我可不想听长篇大论\N{\fs16}Better not, then. I'm a bit busy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.73,0:31:27.57,正文,,0,0,0,,许多年前我帮助史坦尼斯国王\N{\fs16}Many years ago I helped King Stannis{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.60,0:31:30.04,正文,,0,0,0,,渡过难关\N{\fs16}out of a difficult situation.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.07,0:31:33.44,正文,,0,0,0,,他赐予我贵族头衔\N{\fs16}He rewarded me with a lordship.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.47,0:31:35.74,正文,,0,0,0,,还有这个\N{\fs16}And this.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.51,0:31:39.84,正文,,0,0,0,,你瞧？\N{\fs16}You see?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.88,0:31:42.05,正文,,0,0,0,,贵族们\N{\fs16}Highborns.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.39,0:31:48.12,正文,,0,0,0,,我本不想成为贵族\N{\fs16}I didn't want to be a lord.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.15,0:31:49.92,正文,,0,0,0,,我差点就拒绝了\N{\fs16}I nearly didn't accept.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.96,0:31:51.42,正文,,0,0,0,,那为何又接受了？\N{\fs16}Why did you?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.46,0:31:54.43,正文,,0,0,0,,为了我儿子\N{\fs16}I did it for my son.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.46,0:31:56.89,正文,,0,0,0,,我不想他每次都要趟着屎尿\N{\fs16}I didn't want him to step over a river of shit{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.93,0:31:59.43,正文,,0,0,0,,进家门\N{\fs16}every time he stepped through his front door{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.97,0:32:03.17,正文,,0,0,0,,我希望他能过得好一点\N{\fs16}I wanted him to have a better life.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.14,0:32:06.77,正文,,0,0,0,,那么他现在过得好么？\N{\fs16}Does he?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:08.01,0:32:09.71,正文,,0,0,0,,他死了\N{\fs16}He's dead.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.31,0:32:16.75,正文,,0,0,0,,怎么死的？\N{\fs16}How'd he die?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.32,0:32:20.12,正文,,0,0,0,,追随我而死\N{\fs16}Following me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.96,0:32:34.40,正文,,0,0,0,,你是什么时候来到这个陌生的国度的？\N{\fs16}When did you come to this strange country?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.17,0:32:37.60,正文,,0,0,0,,13岁的时候\N{\fs16}When I was 13.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.63,0:32:39.60,正文,,0,0,0,,你那时还是个孩子\N{\fs16}You were only a child.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.77,0:32:43.14,正文,,0,0,0,,我九岁时就不再是孩子了\N{\fs16}I stopped being a child when I was nine.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.17,0:32:45.97,正文,,0,0,0,,我母亲可以为此作证\N{\fs16}My mother made sure of that.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.71,0:32:49.38,正文,,0,0,0,,要知道 你给我俩的朋友带来了\N{\fs16}You've been a good influence{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.50,0:32:51.70,正文,,0,0,0,,正面的影响\N{\fs16}on our mutual friend, you know.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.74,0:32:53.81,正文,,0,0,0,,他曾酗酒 从日落到日出\N{\fs16}He used to drink from sundown to sunup,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.84,0:32:55.51,正文,,0,0,0,,一晚上光顾三座妓院\N{\fs16}visit three brothels a night,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.54,0:32:58.08,正文,,0,0,0,,赌输他父亲的钱\N{\fs16}gamble away his father's money.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.11,0:33:00.04,正文,,0,0,0,,而现在他仅仅是酗酒而已\N{\fs16}Now it's just the drinking.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.08,0:33:03.45,正文,,0,0,0,,而现在我则是他夫人的女仆\N{\fs16}And now I'm his wife's servant.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.48,0:33:05.42,正文,,0,0,0,,我为她梳头 帮她修指甲\N{\fs16}I brush her hair and clip her nails{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.45,0:33:06.92,正文,,0,0,0,,替她倒尿壶\N{\fs16}and empty her chamber pot.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.95,0:33:08.42,正文,,0,0,0,,她是个年轻的小甜心\N{\fs16}She is a sweet young thing.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.45,0:33:09.92,正文,,0,0,0,,这一切都不是她的错\N{\fs16}None of this is her fault.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.96,0:33:12.89,正文,,0,0,0,,我爱那个女孩 为了她我不惜杀人\N{\fs16}I love that girl. I would kill for her.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:12.93,0:33:14.86,正文,,0,0,0,,你认为这样就能让我好过一点？\N{\fs16}Do you think that makes it easier for me?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.89,0:33:17.96,正文,,0,0,0,,不 我知道不会\N{\fs16}No, I expect not.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.80,0:33:23.77,正文,,0,0,0,,她年轻 漂亮 血统高贵\N{\fs16}She's young and she's beautiful and highborn.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.80,0:33:25.57,正文,,0,0,0,,我们与他们一同进餐\N{\fs16}We break bread with them,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.60,0:33:28.17,正文,,0,0,0,,却不足以使我们与他们成为一家人\N{\fs16}but that doesn't make us family.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.21,0:33:29.67,正文,,0,0,0,,我们学习他们的语言\N{\fs16}We've learned their language,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.71,0:33:32.24,正文,,0,0,0,,却从不是他们的同胞\N{\fs16}but we'll never be their countrymen.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.04,0:33:36.98,正文,,0,0,0,,如果你能让自己相信\N{\fs16}If you let yourself believe{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.01,0:33:39.22,正文,,0,0,0,,一个无名的外来女孩\N{\fs16}that a foreign girl with no name{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.25,0:33:41.58,正文,,0,0,0,,能和泰温·兰尼斯特的儿子共度一生\N{\fs16}could spend her life with the son of Tywin Lannister--{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.62,0:33:44.39,正文,,0,0,0,,我有名字 你是有名字\N{\fs16}- I have a name. - You have one name.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.42,0:33:45.96,正文,,0,0,0,,我也有\N{\fs16}As do I.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.99,0:33:48.92,正文,,0,0,0,,但在这儿姓氏决定一切\N{\fs16}Here only the family name matters.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.96,0:33:51.26,正文,,0,0,0,,你想从我这儿得到什么 瓦里斯大人？\N{\fs16}What do you want from me, Lord Varys?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.73,0:33:56.67,正文,,0,0,0,,这些钻石\N{\fs16}Diamonds.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.70,0:33:59.53,正文,,0,0,0,,我会告诉你 携带那么多财宝要时刻提防\N{\fs16}I'd tell you to beware carrying so much wealth,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.57,0:34:02.04,正文,,0,0,0,,不过你知道如何保护自己\N{\fs16}but you know how to protect yourself.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:03.01,0:34:04.71,正文,,0,0,0,,登上那些船中的一艘\N{\fs16}Get on one of those ships.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.74,0:34:07.44,正文,,0,0,0,,去潘托斯 或是里斯 密尔也行\N{\fs16}Sail to Pentos or Lys or Myr.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:07.48,0:34:10.68,正文,,0,0,0,,你可以用这些钻石买一栋房子\N{\fs16}You can buy a house with these diamonds,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.71,0:34:12.68,正文,,0,0,0,,一栋很大的房子\N{\fs16}a very large house.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.71,0:34:14.55,正文,,0,0,0,,雇很多仆人\N{\fs16}Hire servants.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.58,0:34:15.98,正文,,0,0,0,,开始新生活\N{\fs16}Start a new life,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.02,0:34:18.45,正文,,0,0,0,,远离这里的 美好生活\N{\fs16}a good life, far from here.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.49,0:34:21.55,正文,,0,0,0,,神秘的异国漂亮妞\N{\fs16}The mysterious foreign beauty.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.59,0:34:23.56,正文,,0,0,0,,会有成群结队的求婚者向你示爱\N{\fs16}You'll have suitors lining up.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.59,0:34:25.89,正文,,0,0,0,,为什么你要我离开\N{\fs16}Why do you want me to leave?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.93,0:34:28.60,正文,,0,0,0,,提利昂·兰尼斯特是仅存的几位\N{\fs16}Tyrion Lannister is one of the few people alive{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.63,0:34:30.70,正文,,0,0,0,,能让这个国家摆脱窘境的人之一\N{\fs16}who could make this country a better place.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.73,0:34:32.43,正文,,0,0,0,,他有思想 他有决心\N{\fs16}He has the mind for it, he has the will,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.47,0:34:33.90,正文,,0,0,0,,他有个杰出的姓氏\N{\fs16}he has the right last name.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.93,0:34:36.00,正文,,0,0,0,,而你\N{\fs16}And you--{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.04,0:34:39.20,正文,,0,0,0,,你是个难题\N{\fs16}you are a complication.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.37,0:34:42.54,正文,,0,0,0,,我知道你爱着他\N{\fs16}I know you love him.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.58,0:34:46.61,正文,,0,0,0,,我也知道这是真爱 而非由金银所构筑的爱\N{\fs16}And I know it's true love not bought by gold and silver.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.65,0:34:49.11,正文,,0,0,0,,我不是让你为了钱离开他\N{\fs16}I'm not asking you to leave him for money.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.15,0:34:51.78,正文,,0,0,0,,只是单纯地请你离开\N{\fs16}I'm asking you to leave{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:51.82,0:34:54.82,正文,,0,0,0,,因为在君临 你的存在\N{\fs16}because your presence in the capital{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.85,0:34:57.22,正文,,0,0,0,,将使他陷入危险的境地\N{\fs16}endangers him.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.39,0:35:00.79,正文,,0,0,0,,这里从来就不是你的家 我的女士\N{\fs16}This will never be your home, my lady.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.83,0:35:05.27,正文,,0,0,0,,远离此处 去寻找一个真正意义上的家\N{\fs16}Find a true home somewhere far from here...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.06,0:35:08.26,正文,,0,0,0,,趁现在还来得及\N{\fs16}while there's still time.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.40,0:35:12.07,正文,,0,0,0,,瓦里斯大人\N{\fs16}Lord Varys.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.37,0:35:19.04,正文,,0,0,0,,如果是他要我离开 他可以亲自和我说\N{\fs16}If he wants me to leave, he can tell me himself.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.96,0:35:29.46,正文,,0,0,0,,再来点\N{\fs16}Keep up.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.50,0:35:32.16,正文,,0,0,0,,我想我不胜酒力了 大人\N{\fs16}I don't think I can, my lord.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.17,0:35:36.70,正文,,0,0,0,,想喝醉从来就不是一件容易的事\N{\fs16}It's not easy being drunk all the time.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.84,0:35:41.14,正文,,0,0,0,,要是容易的话每个人都这么干了\N{\fs16}Everyone would do it if it were easy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.61,0:35:45.61,正文,,0,0,0,,退下\N{\fs16}Leave.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.95,0:35:58.26,正文,,0,0,0,,那么 新婚生活还满意么？\N{\fs16}So, enjoying married life?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.19,0:36:05.76,正文,,0,0,0,,郁郁寡欢的妻子是酒贩子最好的朋友\N{\fs16}An unhappy wife is a wine merchant's best friend.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.80,0:36:08.13,正文,,0,0,0,,她不该受到如此对待\N{\fs16}She doesn't deserve this.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.17,0:36:09.70,正文,,0,0,0,,不该？\N{\fs16}Deserve?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.73,0:36:12.63,正文,,0,0,0,,小心这个想法\N{\fs16}Be careful with that.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.67,0:36:15.84,正文,,0,0,0,,谁又应该受苦呢？ 一旦你开始思考这个问题\N{\fs16}Start trying to work out who deserves what{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.87,0:36:18.31,正文,,0,0,0,,用不了多久 你就要把余生\N{\fs16}and before long you'll spend the rest of your days{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.34,0:36:21.58,正文,,0,0,0,,用来为世上的每一个人悲伤了\N{\fs16}weeping for each and every person in the world.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.61,0:36:25.21,正文,,0,0,0,,还有什么比大器晚成的“哲学家”更糟的\N{\fs16}There's nothing worse than a late- blooming philosopher.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.58,0:36:28.88,正文,,0,0,0,,你能用同样的哲学理念让自己接受\N{\fs16}Will you be facing your marriage to Ser Loras{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.92,0:36:32.02,正文,,0,0,0,,和洛拉斯爵士的婚姻么？\N{\fs16}with the same philosophical spirit?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.05,0:36:33.55,正文,,0,0,0,,我不会嫁给洛拉斯爵士\N{\fs16}I won't be marrying Ser Loras.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.59,0:36:36.52,正文,,0,0,0,,我记得对于自己的婚姻\N{\fs16}I seem to remember saying something similar{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.56,0:36:38.53,正文,,0,0,0,,我也说过类似的话\N{\fs16}about my own marriage.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.56,0:36:40.83,正文,,0,0,0,,你不能和我比\N{\fs16}You're not me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.06,0:36:43.96,正文,,0,0,0,,你真想为珊莎好？\N{\fs16}You want to make things better for Sansa?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.00,0:36:45.73,正文,,0,0,0,,那就给她一个孩子\N{\fs16}Give her a child.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.77,0:36:47.67,正文,,0,0,0,,这样你就可以告诉父亲\N{\fs16}So you can tell Father it was you{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.70,0:36:49.97,正文,,0,0,0,,最终说服了我的鸡巴的人是你？\N{\fs16}who finally talked me into it?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.00,0:36:53.11,正文,,0,0,0,,这样她就能在生命中获得一些快乐\N{\fs16}So she can have some happiness in her life.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.14,0:36:54.77,正文,,0,0,0,,你有孩子\N{\fs16}You have children.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.81,0:36:57.98,正文,,0,0,0,,说说看你有多快乐？\N{\fs16}How happy would you say you are?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.81,0:37:02.58,正文,,0,0,0,,不是很多\N{\fs16}Not very.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:05.64,0:37:07.78,正文,,0,0,0,,但如果不是为了我的孩子\N{\fs16}But if it weren't for my children,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.81,0:37:10.71,正文,,0,0,0,,我肯定已经从红堡最高的窗户跳下去了\N{\fs16}I'd have thrown myself from the highest window in the Red Keep.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.58,0:37:15.12,正文,,0,0,0,,他们是我活着的理由\N{\fs16}They're the reason I'm alive.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.15,0:37:17.22,正文,,0,0,0,,即便是乔佛里？\N{\fs16}Even Joffrey?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.25,0:37:20.12,正文,,0,0,0,,没错 即便是乔佛里\N{\fs16}Even Joffrey.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.76,0:37:26.19,正文,,0,0,0,,在弥赛拉出生前\N{\fs16}He was all I had once.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.23,0:37:28.90,正文,,0,0,0,,他曾经是我的一切\N{\fs16}Before Myrcella was born.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.40,0:37:35.00,正文,,0,0,0,,我曾经连续几小时\N{\fs16}I used to spend hours{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.03,0:37:37.47,正文,,0,0,0,,就这样看着他\N{\fs16}looking at him.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:37.50,0:37:39.61,正文,,0,0,0,,看着他那一撮撮的头发\N{\fs16}His wisps of hair.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.71,0:37:43.41,正文,,0,0,0,,看着他娇小的手脚\N{\fs16}His tiny little hands and feet.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:44.44,0:37:46.91,正文,,0,0,0,,他是一个如此活泼快乐的小宝贝\N{\fs16}He was such a jolly little fellow.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.95,0:37:53.18,正文,,0,0,0,,人们常说 坏人从小就是坏胚\N{\fs16}You always hear the terrible ones were terrible babies.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.22,0:37:55.99,正文,,0,0,0,,“我们早该知道 从小我们就该看出来了”\N{\fs16}"We should have known. Even then we should have known."{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.02,0:37:58.12,正文,,0,0,0,,真是无稽之谈\N{\fs16}It's nonsense.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.79,0:38:02.46,正文,,0,0,0,,和我在一起的时候 他始终是那么快乐\N{\fs16}Whenever he was with me, he was happy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.43,0:38:08.13,正文,,0,0,0,,没人能夺走这一切\N{\fs16}And no one can take that away from me,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.17,0:38:09.93,正文,,0,0,0,,即便是乔佛里\N{\fs16}not even Joffrey--{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.97,0:38:12.57,正文,,0,0,0,,这就是当你拥有\N{\fs16}how it feels to have someone.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.57,0:38:16.07,正文,,0,0,0,,一个属于自己的人时的感觉\N{\fs16}Someone of your own.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.79,0:38:28.42,正文,,0,0,0,,还要持续多久？\N{\fs16}How long does it go on?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.82,0:38:33.49,正文,,0,0,0,,直到我们解决所有的敌人\N{\fs16}Until we've dealt with all our enemies.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.06,0:38:37.79,正文,,0,0,0,,每当我们击败一个敌人\N{\fs16}Every time we deal with an enemy,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.83,0:38:39.89,正文,,0,0,0,,就创造出两个新的\N{\fs16}we create two more.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.46,0:38:44.80,正文,,0,0,0,,那我想这得需要很长一段时间\N{\fs16}Then I suppose it will go on for quite a long time.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.67,0:38:52.17,正文,,0,0,0,,和你说 当时她是这样的\N{\fs16}I'm telling you, that's what she did.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.48,0:38:57.48,正文,,0,0,0,,听起来像是一头发情的母牛\N{\fs16}Sounded like a cow in heat.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.51,0:38:59.81,正文,,0,0,0,,- 哈 没持续多久 - 是的\N{\fs16}- Aye, not for long. - That's right.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:38:59.85,0:39:02.15,正文,,0,0,0,,黑瓦德很快让她闭了嘴\N{\fs16}Black Walder shut her up right quick.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.18,0:39:05.39,正文,,0,0,0,,那顿饭过后 史塔克们的嘴里再也吐不出一个字了\N{\fs16}None of the Starks had much to say about the end of that meal.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.42,0:39:06.95,正文,,0,0,0,,尽管这样 我还是要说\N{\fs16}I'll tell you what, though.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.99,0:39:10.29,正文,,0,0,0,,最困难的事还是把狼头钉在身体上\N{\fs16}The hardest thing was getting that wolf's head to stay on the body.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.32,0:39:12.83,正文,,0,0,0,,是你缝上去的？ - 是我干的\N{\fs16}- You sewed it on? - I did.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.86,0:39:15.96,正文,,0,0,0,,我打赌有1000个人会这么说\N{\fs16}I bet there were 1,000 men claiming they were the one.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:16.00,0:39:17.73,正文,,0,0,0,,真的是我\N{\fs16}It was me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.77,0:39:20.70,正文,,0,0,0,,还有马可和塔波特\N{\fs16}And Malcolm and Talbott.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:20.73,0:39:23.47,正文,,0,0,0,,听我讲 那玩意儿太重 一开始掉了下来\N{\fs16}Well, the thing was so heavy, it fell off the first time.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.50,0:39:25.07,正文,,0,0,0,,还带着皮\N{\fs16}Took the skin right with it.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.10,0:39:28.07,正文,,0,0,0,,最后我们不得不用针\N{\fs16}What we ended up having to do was hook the needle{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.11,0:39:29.68,正文,,0,0,0,,勾住锁骨下方\N{\fs16}right under the collarbone.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.71,0:39:32.51,正文,,0,0,0,,这样能有个不错的固定点 然后\N{\fs16}Give it a nice firm mooring and--{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.72,0:39:37.08,正文,,0,0,0,,你想干什么\N{\fs16}What do you want?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.12,0:39:40.38,正文,,0,0,0,,我能烤烤火么？ 滚开\N{\fs16}- Mind if I keep warm? - Fuck off.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.42,0:39:42.79,正文,,0,0,0,,我很饿\N{\fs16}But I'm hungry.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.82,0:39:46.22,正文,,0,0,0,,让你滚听不懂么？\N{\fs16}Does fuck off mean something different where you're from?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.26,0:39:48.39,正文,,0,0,0,,我有钱\N{\fs16}I've got money.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.66,0:39:54.47,正文,,0,0,0,,那是什么硬币？\N{\fs16}What kind of coin is that?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.50,0:39:56.33,正文,,0,0,0,,它值很多钱\N{\fs16}It's worth a lot.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.94,0:40:00.27,正文,,0,0,0,,抱歉\N{\fs16}Sorry.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.30,0:40:02.31,正文,,0,0,0,,小混蛋\N{\fs16}Little shit.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.01,0:40:08.74,正文,,0,0,0,,蠢材！\N{\fs16}Fool!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.63,0:40:26.19,正文,,0,0,0,,你从哪儿搞到的小刀？\N{\fs16}Where did you get the knife?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.23,0:40:27.93,正文,,0,0,0,,从你那儿\N{\fs16}From you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.30,0:40:33.93,正文,,0,0,0,,杀的第一个人？\N{\fs16}Is that the first man you've killed?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.97,0:40:36.07,正文,,0,0,0,,第一个人\N{\fs16}The first man.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.34,0:40:39.71,正文,,0,0,0,,下次要干类似的活\N{\fs16}Next time you're going to do something like that,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.74,0:40:41.88,正文,,0,0,0,,先跟我说\N{\fs16}tell me first.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.49,0:40:55.92,正文,,0,0,0,,Valar morghulis\N{\fs16}Valar morghulis.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:08.41,0:41:11.71,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(100,278)}琼恩·雪诺\N{\b0\fs12}叛逃的乌鸦
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.00,0:41:18.90,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(643,272)}耶哥蕊特\N{\b0\fs12}“火吻而生” 野人
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.05,0:41:27.75,正文,,0,0,0,,耶哥蕊特 你明白我别无选择\N{\fs16}Ygritte, you know I didn't have a choice.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.96,0:41:33.76,正文,,0,0,0,,一直以来你都知道我是谁\N{\fs16}You always knew who I was,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.79,0:41:35.63,正文,,0,0,0,,是什么人\N{\fs16}what I am.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:38.17,0:41:40.84,正文,,0,0,0,,我必须得回去\N{\fs16}I have to go home now.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.90,0:41:45.33,正文,,0,0,0,,我知道你不会伤害我\N{\fs16}I know you won't hurt me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.87,0:41:48.94,正文,,0,0,0,,你什么都不知道 琼恩·雪诺\N{\fs16}You know nothing, Jon Snow.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:52.58,0:41:55.04,正文,,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\fs16}I do know some things.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.25,0:41:57.88,正文,,0,0,0,,我知道我爱你\N{\fs16}I know I love you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:00.55,0:42:02.88,正文,,0,0,0,,我知道你也爱我\N{\fs16}I know you love me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.52,0:42:08.36,正文,,0,0,0,,但现在我必须回去\N{\fs16}But I have to go home now.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:47.30,0:42:49.90,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(505,319)}伊蒙·坦格利安{\b0}\N{\fs12}守夜人的学士
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.00,0:42:51.46,正文,,0,0,0,,我知道这看起来不妥\N{\fs16}I know how this must look.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.03,0:42:57.24,正文,,0,0,0,,我的意思是 - 我向您保证 大人\N{\fs16}- What I meant was--- I swear to you, my lord--{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:57.27,0:42:59.77,正文,,0,0,0,,我不是大人 亲爱的\N{\fs16}I'm not a lord, my dear.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:59.81,0:43:02.51,正文,,0,0,0,,很多很多年前就不是了\N{\fs16}Not for many, many years.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:02.54,0:43:05.88,正文,,0,0,0,,一旦加入了守夜人\N{\fs16}Every man who joins the Night's Watch{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.91,0:43:09.98,正文,,0,0,0,,就得放弃过去所有的头衔\N{\fs16}renounces all former titles.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:11.65,0:43:13.89,正文,,0,0,0,,此外\N{\fs16}Among other things.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:16.79,0:43:18.69,正文,,0,0,0,,你叫什么名字\N{\fs16}What is your name?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:18.72,0:43:20.39,正文,,0,0,0,,吉莉\N{\fs16}Gilly.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.42,0:43:23.73,正文,,0,0,0,,啊 以紫罗兰花之名\N{\fs16}Ah, for the gillyflower.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:23.76,0:43:25.19,正文,,0,0,0,,真可爱\N{\fs16}Lovely.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:25.23,0:43:27.63,正文,,0,0,0,,是的 大——\N{\fs16}Yes, my--{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:29.70,0:43:31.33,正文,,0,0,0,,学士\N{\fs16}Maester.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:32.27,0:43:33.45,正文,,0,0,0,,邪士\N{\fs16}Master.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:33.57,0:43:36.07,正文,,0,0,0,,是学士\N{\fs16}Maester.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:36.11,0:43:38.07,正文,,0,0,0,,这孩子？\N{\fs16}And the child?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:39.51,0:43:41.71,正文,,0,0,0,,她尚未取名\N{\fs16}She hasn't chosen a name yet.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:41.75,0:43:44.05,正文,,0,0,0,,他叫山姆\N{\fs16}His name is Sam.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:47.52,0:43:49.65,正文,,0,0,0,,塔利\N{\fs16}Tarly...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:49.69,0:43:53.15,正文,,0,0,0,,你是否还记得你发过的誓\N{\fs16}do you remember the oath you swore{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.19,0:43:55.76,正文,,0,0,0,,在你加入守夜人时许下的？\N{\fs16}when you joined this order?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:55.79,0:43:58.96,正文,,0,0,0,,他不是我的孩子 伊蒙学士\N{\fs16}He's not my child, Maester Aemon.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:00.30,0:44:02.20,正文,,0,0,0,,他是卡斯特众多妻子中的一位\N{\fs16}She's one of Craster's wives.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:06.97,0:44:10.57,正文,,0,0,0,,我谨记誓言\N{\fs16}I remember every word of the oath.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:11.67,0:44:14.21,正文,,0,0,0,,长夜将至 我从今开始守望\N{\fs16}Night gathers and my watch begins.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:14.24,0:44:18.24,正文,,0,0,0,,我是守护王国人民的坚盾\N{\fs16}I am the shield that guards the realms of men.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.28,0:44:22.88,正文,,0,0,0,,王国的人民\N{\fs16}The realms of men.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:24.75,0:44:27.55,正文,,0,0,0,,意味着她和我们都在其中\N{\fs16}That means her as well as us.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:27.59,0:44:30.96,正文,,0,0,0,,我们造五百里长\N{\fs16}We didn't build 500 miles of ice walls,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:30.99,0:44:33.69,正文,,0,0,0,,七百尺高的冰墙 不是为了把自己人挡在城外\N{\fs16}700 feet high to keep out men.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:35.70,0:44:38.03,正文,,0,0,0,,长夜将至 伊蒙学士\N{\fs16}The night is gathering, Maester Aemon.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:38.07,0:44:40.13,正文,,0,0,0,,我亲眼看见\N{\fs16}I've seen it.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:40.13,0:44:42.67,正文,,0,0,0,,它冲着我们所有人来了\N{\fs16}It's coming for all of us.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:45.27,0:44:48.44,正文,,0,0,0,,吉莉 你和你的儿子\N{\fs16}Gilly, you and your son{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:48.47,0:44:51.54,正文,,0,0,0,,就暂且做我们的客人吧\N{\fs16}will be our guests for the time being.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:51.58,0:44:56.48,正文,,0,0,0,,我们肯定不会将你们\N{\fs16}We certainly cannot send you back{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:56.51,0:44:58.48,正文,,0,0,0,,送回长城外的\N{\fs16}beyond the Wall.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:44:58.52,0:45:01.02,正文,,0,0,0,,谢谢您\N{\fs16}Thank you...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:01.05,0:45:03.32,正文,,0,0,0,,学士\N{\fs16}Maester.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:03.35,0:45:05.52,正文,,0,0,0,,我能做饭 能打扫 还能 --\N{\fs16}I can cook and clean and I can--{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:05.56,0:45:07.22,正文,,0,0,0,,很好\N{\fs16}Good.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:07.26,0:45:11.79,正文,,0,0,0,,山姆威尔 拿羽毛笔和墨水来\N{\fs16}Samwell, fetch a quill and inkwell.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:15.90,0:45:19.50,正文,,0,0,0,,希望你的书法比你的剑术强一点儿\N{\fs16}I hope your penmanship is better than your swordplay.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:19.54,0:45:21.64,正文,,0,0,0,,强多了\N{\fs16}Miles better.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:23.31,0:45:27.11,正文,,0,0,0,,上回清点时我们还有四十四只渡鸦\N{\fs16}We had 44 ravens at last count.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:27.14,0:45:30.71,正文,,0,0,0,,确保它们全都吃饱喝足\N{\fs16}Make sure they're all fed.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:30.75,0:45:34.02,正文,,0,0,0,,今晚将它们全数送出\N{\fs16}Every one of them flies tonight.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:42.99,0:45:45.46,正文,,0,0,0,,致国王\N{\fs16}"To His Grace{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:45.49,0:45:48.20,正文,,0,0,0,,史坦尼斯·拜拉席恩陛下\N{\fs16}King Stannis Baratheon.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:49.26,0:45:52.63,正文,,0,0,0,,要情 --邀 --邀清 --邀请您\N{\fs16}Invaded--inv--invit--invited{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:52.67,0:45:56.44,正文,,0,0,0,,出席瑞林·佛罗伦的\N{\fs16}to the name day celebration{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:45:52.70,0:45:55.00,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(389,274)}希琳·拜拉席恩\N{\b0\fs12}史坦尼斯·拜拉席恩的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:45:56.47,0:46:01.78,正文,,0,0,0,,命名日庆典\N{\fs16}for Rylene Florent{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:01.81,0:46:04.04,正文,,0,0,0,,时间为第一耶\N{\fs16}on the first nigit--"{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:04.08,0:46:05.98,正文,,0,0,0,,夜\N{\fs16}Night.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:06.01,0:46:08.35,正文,,0,0,0,,满月后的第一夜\N{\fs16}"First night of the full moon."{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:08.38,0:46:09.78,正文,,0,0,0,,夜晚这个词里干嘛还要有个 "G"？\N{\fs16}Why is there a G in night?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:09.82,0:46:11.89,正文,,0,0,0,,我不知道 反正就这么写\N{\fs16}I don't know. There just is.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:13.09,0:46:15.15,正文,,0,0,0,,反正 你父亲不会参加的\N{\fs16}Well, your father's not going to go to that.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:16.59,0:46:19.09,正文,,0,0,0,,我的书本比这些乏味的卷轴有趣\N{\fs16}My books are better than these boring scrolls.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:19.13,0:46:21.13,正文,,0,0,0,,你能读到黑死神贝勒里恩的故事呢\N{\fs16}You could read about Balerion the Dread.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:21.16,0:46:24.66,正文,,0,0,0,,他们说在红堡下的地牢里你还能看到它的颅骨\N{\fs16}They say you can still see his skull in the dungeons beneath the\NRed Keep.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:24.70,0:46:27.00,正文,,0,0,0,,有天能去看看就好了\N{\fs16}I'd like to see that someday.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:27.03,0:46:30.34,正文,,0,0,0,,我这辈子都不想再进地牢了\N{\fs16}I've been trying to stay out of those dungeons my whole life.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:30.37,0:46:34.01,正文,,0,0,0,,它的尖牙和巨剑一样长 "\N{\fs16}"His fangs were as long as bastard swords."{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:35.34,0:46:37.37,正文,,0,0,0,,是啊 老贝勒里恩肯定比\N{\fs16}Aye, old Balerion's definitely better{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:37.41,0:46:40.44,正文,,0,0,0,,你表亲蕾拉妮的那些烂事有意思的多\N{\fs16}than anything your cousin Rylene's got on offer.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:40.48,0:46:42.95,正文,,0,0,0,,但既然我又当上了你父亲的首相\N{\fs16}But now that I'm your father's Hand again,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:42.98,0:46:45.25,正文,,0,0,0,,我就得让他消息畅通\N{\fs16}I have to keep him informed.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:46.14,0:46:48.82,正文,,0,0,0,,国王没空处理这等琐事\N{\fs16}The king does not have time for this drudgery.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:50.69,0:46:54.83,正文,,0,0,0,,致维斯特洛的所有领主和归族们\N{\fs16}"To all the lords and knobble men of Westeros."{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:54.86,0:46:57.63,正文,,0,0,0,,- 是贵族啦 - 贵族们\N{\fs16}- Noblemen. - "Noblemen of Westeros,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:46:57.66,0:47:02.17,正文,,0,0,0,,收夜…守夜人\N{\fs16}the Nig--the Night's Watch...{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:05.24,0:47:07.30,正文,,0,0,0,,在此恳求\N{\fs16}implores..."{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:07.34,0:47:08.97,正文,,0,0,0,,怎么了？\N{\fs16}What is it?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:13.38,0:47:15.28,正文,,0,0,0,,他们干嘛鸣钟？\N{\fs16}Why are they ringing the bells?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:15.31,0:47:17.15,正文,,0,0,0,,我们遇袭了吗？\N{\fs16}Are we being attacked?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:17.18,0:47:19.65,正文,,0,0,0,,待在这儿\N{\fs16}Stay here.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:19.68,0:47:21.82,正文,,0,0,0,,拴好门\N{\fs16}Bar the door.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:29.21,0:47:31.40,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(119,215)}梅丽珊卓{\b0}\N{\fs12}光之王的“红袍祭司”
Dialogue: 0,0:47:31.40,0:47:33.60,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(472,268)}史坦尼斯·拜拉席恩\N{\b0\fs12}狭海中的王
Dialogue: 0,0:47:40.20,0:47:42.57,正文,,0,0,0,,篡夺者罗柏·史塔克已经死了\N{\fs16}The usurper Robb Stark is dead.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:42.60,0:47:46.01,正文,,0,0,0,,被手下封臣背叛\N{\fs16}Betrayed by his bannerman.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:46.04,0:47:49.84,正文,,0,0,0,,你想说这是你的功劳？就因为你往火盆里扔了条水蛭？\N{\fs16}And you take credit because you dropped a leech into the fire?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:49.88,0:47:51.48,正文,,0,0,0,,我无需居功\N{\fs16}I take no credit.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:51.51,0:47:54.55,正文,,0,0,0,,我有信仰 而我的虔诚得到了回应\N{\fs16}I have faith and my faith has been rewarded.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:57.75,0:48:02.02,正文,,0,0,0,,陛下 这世道已然光怪陆离\N{\fs16}Your Grace, the world has got so far bent.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:02.06,0:48:04.96,正文,,0,0,0,,我也见识过噩梦中的种种怪物成为现实\N{\fs16}I've seen things crawl out of nightmares,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:04.99,0:48:06.69,正文,,0,0,0,,但我仍能明辨是非\N{\fs16}but my eyes were open.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:06.73,0:48:09.56,正文,,0,0,0,,我虽不知罗柏·史塔克的死是因为红袍女的巫术\N{\fs16}I don't know if Robb Stark died because of the Red Woman's sorcery{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:09.60,0:48:11.80,正文,,0,0,0,,还是因为打起仗来 人命就朝不保夕\N{\fs16}or because at war men die all the time,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:11.83,0:48:15.00,正文,,0,0,0,,但我明白 用血魔法来\N{\fs16}but I do know that uniting the Seven Kingdoms{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:15.03,0:48:16.67,正文,,0,0,0,,一统七大王国大错特错\N{\fs16}with blood magic is wrong.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:16.70,0:48:17.90,正文,,0,0,0,,这是邪恶之举\N{\fs16}It is evil.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:17.94,0:48:20.01,正文,,0,0,0,,而您绝非邪恶之人\N{\fs16}And you are not an evil man.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:20.04,0:48:22.84,正文,,0,0,0,,你知道谁雕刻油漆了这张桌子吧 戴佛斯爵士？\N{\fs16}Do you know who had this table carved and painted, Ser Davos?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:23.78,0:48:25.04,正文,,0,0,0,,是伊耿·坦格利安\N{\fs16}Aegon Targaryen.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:25.08,0:48:27.71,正文,,0,0,0,,那你知道伊耿·坦格利安是怎么征服维斯特洛的吗？\N{\fs16}And do you know how Aegon Targaryen conquered Westeros?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:27.75,0:48:29.81,正文,,0,0,0,,靠他的巨龙黑死神贝勒里恩\N{\fs16}On the back of his dragon Balerion the Dread.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:29.85,0:48:33.75,正文,,0,0,0,,他的舰队和军队\N{\fs16}He had a smaller fleet than the kings he faced{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:33.79,0:48:36.45,正文,,0,0,0,,都比他的敌人少得多 但他拥有三条龙\N{\fs16}and a smaller army, but he had three dragons.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:36.49,0:48:38.52,正文,,0,0,0,,巨龙就是魔法 戴佛斯爵士\N{\fs16}Dragons are magic, Ser Davos.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:38.56,0:48:42.09,正文,,0,0,0,,我的敌人让我的王国流血了\N{\fs16}My enemies have made my kingdom bleed.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:44.03,0:48:46.06,正文,,0,0,0,,这点我不会忘记\N{\fs16}I will not forget that.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:46.10,0:48:48.73,正文,,0,0,0,,这点我不会宽恕\N{\fs16}I will not forgive that.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:50.27,0:48:53.07,正文,,0,0,0,,我会不择手段\N{\fs16}I will punish them with any arms{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:53.10,0:48:54.37,正文,,0,0,0,,惩罚他们\N{\fs16}at my disposal.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:54.40,0:48:57.24,正文,,0,0,0,,您没有必要烧死那个男孩\N{\fs16}You do not need to burn the boy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:48:57.27,0:49:00.58,正文,,0,0,0,,如果您所言为真\N{\fs16}If what you say is true,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:00.61,0:49:03.61,正文,,0,0,0,,他的一滴血就能杀掉罗柏·史塔克 --\N{\fs16}a drop of his blood killed Robb Stark--{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:03.65,0:49:06.48,正文,,0,0,0,,我们的国王并未离铁王座更近一步\N{\fs16}And our king is still no closer to the Iron Throne.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:09.22,0:49:12.59,正文,,0,0,0,,而伟大的恩赐需要伟大的牺牲\N{\fs16}A great gift requires a great sacrifice.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:29.24,0:49:31.60,正文,,0,0,0,,他的名字是詹德利\N{\fs16}His name is Gendry.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:31.64,0:49:33.27,正文,,0,0,0,,他是个好小子\N{\fs16}He's a good lad.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:34.41,0:49:36.48,正文,,0,0,0,,出身于跳蚤窝的穷小子\N{\fs16}A poor lad from Flea Bottom{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:36.51,0:49:39.18,正文,,0,0,0,,还恰好是您的侄子\N{\fs16}who happens to be your nephew.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:44.28,0:49:47.99,正文,,0,0,0,,一个私生子的性命相对于一个王国的前途又算什么呢？\N{\fs16}What is the life of one bastard boy against a kingdom?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:49.76,0:49:51.52,正文,,0,0,0,,一切\N{\fs16}Everything.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:49:52.46,0:49:54.66,正文,,0,0,0,,这男孩必须死\N{\fs16}The boy must die.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:02.00,0:50:03.97,正文,,0,0,0,,你在做什么？ - 你现在就动身\N{\fs16}- What are you doing? - You're leaving.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:04.00,0:50:06.84,正文,,0,0,0,,这是什么把戏吗？\N{\fs16}Is this some kind of trick?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:06.87,0:50:09.54,正文,,0,0,0,,没错 但不是针对你\N{\fs16}Yes, but not on you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:13.48,0:50:16.41,正文,,0,0,0,,冲着那颗星星划 别停\N{\fs16}Aim for that star. Don't stop.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:16.45,0:50:18.68,正文,,0,0,0,,有面包和水 吃慢点儿\N{\fs16}There's bread and water. Go slow with it.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:18.72,0:50:20.38,正文,,0,0,0,,如果吃完了\N{\fs16}If you finish it off,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:20.42,0:50:23.75,正文,,0,0,0,,不管有多渴\N{\fs16}no matter how thirsty you get,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:23.79,0:50:25.72,正文,,0,0,0,,都别喝海水\N{\fs16}don't drink seawater.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:25.76,0:50:27.76,正文,,0,0,0,,我知道不能喝海水\N{\fs16}I know not to drink seawater.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:27.79,0:50:31.46,正文,,0,0,0,,划上一整天再一整夜后你就能到达鸦栖堡\N{\fs16}Row for a full day and night and you'll reach Rook's Rest.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:31.49,0:50:34.23,正文,,0,0,0,,那时你一定累得想停在那儿 千万别 她会找到你的\N{\fs16}You'll want to stop there. Don't. She'll find you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:34.26,0:50:35.60,正文,,0,0,0,,那我该去哪？\N{\fs16}Where should I go?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:35.63,0:50:37.03,正文,,0,0,0,,继续向前 保持海岸线在你左手边\N{\fs16}You must keep the coast on your left side{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:37.07,0:50:38.60,正文,,0,0,0,,一直划到君临\N{\fs16}until you reach King's Landing.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:38.64,0:50:40.50,正文,,0,0,0,,金袍子还在搜我呢\N{\fs16}The gold cloaks are looking for me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:40.54,0:50:42.24,正文,,0,0,0,,他们已经搜了我二十年\N{\fs16}They were looking for me for 20 years.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:42.27,0:50:44.17,正文,,0,0,0,,他们知道你相貌了？没\N{\fs16}- Do they know your face? - No.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:44.21,0:50:46.01,正文,,0,0,0,,我会更提防红袍女\N{\fs16}I'd worry more about the Red Woman.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:53.05,0:50:54.68,正文,,0,0,0,,转过来\N{\fs16}The other way.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:50:59.22,0:51:01.06,正文,,0,0,0,,你以前乘过船吗？\N{\fs16}You ever been in a boat before?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:01.09,0:51:02.62,正文,,0,0,0,,没\N{\fs16}No.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:02.66,0:51:03.99,正文,,0,0,0,,会游泳吗？\N{\fs16}You know how to swim?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:04.03,0:51:05.23,正文,,0,0,0,,不会\N{\fs16}No.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:05.26,0:51:06.69,正文,,0,0,0,,那就别掉下水\N{\fs16}Don't fall out.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:06.73,0:51:09.23,正文,,0,0,0,,出发吧\N{\fs16}Go on.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:11.20,0:51:12.57,正文,,0,0,0,,你为什么这么做？\N{\fs16}Why are you doing this?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:12.60,0:51:15.07,正文,,0,0,0,,因为这么做是对的\N{\fs16}Because it's right.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:15.10,0:51:16.97,正文,,0,0,0,,还因为我就是不吸取教训\N{\fs16}And because I'm a slow learner.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:19.64,0:51:23.18,正文,,0,0,0,,等你到了跳蚤窝 为我干一碗褐汤\N{\fs16}When you get to Flea Bottom, have a bowl of brown for me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:27.91,0:51:29.68,正文,,0,0,0,,马来了！\N{\fs16}Horse approaching!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:29.72,0:51:32.88,正文,,0,0,0,,停下！停下！\N{\fs16}Halt! Halt!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:50.67,0:51:52.47,正文,,0,0,0,,琼恩！琼恩！\N{\fs16}Jon! Jon!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:52.50,0:51:54.21,正文,,0,0,0,,琼恩 是我们啊\N{\fs16}Jon, it's us.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:54.24,0:51:56.54,正文,,0,0,0,,我觉得他瞅不见我们\N{\fs16}I don't think he can see us.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:51:54.70,0:51:56.40,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(214,328)}派普尔{\b0}\N{\fs12}“派普” 守夜人
Dialogue: 0,0:52:00.34,0:52:03.55,正文,,0,0,0,,派普？\N{\fs16}Pyp?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:03.58,0:52:05.78,正文,,0,0,0,,山姆？\N{\fs16}Sam?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:05.82,0:52:09.19,正文,,0,0,0,,好了 别说话 你到家了\N{\fs16}Hush, now. You're home.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:10.82,0:52:13.89,正文,,0,0,0,,把他抬进去 动作轻点\N{\fs16}Carry him inside. Gently.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:32.20,0:52:35.21,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(357,264)}詹姆·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}“弑君者” 御林铁卫队长
Dialogue: 0,0:52:35.91,0:52:40.41,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(539,202)}布蕾妮·塔斯{\b0\fs12}\N“美人”
Dialogue: 0,0:52:39.21,0:52:41.55,正文,,0,0,0,,别挡道\N{\fs16}Out of the way.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:41.58,0:52:43.22,正文,,0,0,0,,站一边去 乡巴佬\N{\fs16}Step aside, country boy.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:52:41.90,0:52:45.70,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(357,264)}科本\N{\b0\fs12}被剥夺项链的学士
Dialogue: 0,0:52:43.25,0:52:45.12,正文,,0,0,0,,我们在干活呢\N{\fs16}People working here.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:53:30.20,0:53:32.33,正文,,0,0,0,,瑟曦\N{\fs16}Cersei.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:53:50.88,0:53:53.02,正文,,0,0,0,,你不否认这点？\N{\fs16}You don't deny it?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:53:53.05,0:53:55.05,正文,,0,0,0,,不\N{\fs16}No.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:53:56.12,0:53:58.19,正文,,0,0,0,,我放他走了\N{\fs16}I let him go.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:53:58.22,0:54:01.29,正文,,0,0,0,,你心慈手软救了这男孩一命\N{\fs16}Your mercy saved the boy's life.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:01.33,0:54:03.13,正文,,0,0,0,,你感觉很好？\N{\fs16}You feel good about that?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:03.16,0:54:04.53,正文,,0,0,0,,是的 很好\N{\fs16}Aye, I do.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:04.56,0:54:07.06,正文,,0,0,0,,你救了一个无辜的人\N{\fs16}You saved one innocent.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:07.10,0:54:10.83,正文,,0,0,0,,可是却给多少万生灵带来厄运？\N{\fs16}How many tens of thousands have you doomed?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:14.00,0:54:16.44,正文,,0,0,0,,一定有别的法子的\N{\fs16}There has got to be another way.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:16.47,0:54:17.91,正文,,0,0,0,,什么别的法子？\N{\fs16}What other way?!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:17.94,0:54:19.74,正文,,0,0,0,,你倒是说说看啊\N{\fs16}Tell us about this other way.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:19.78,0:54:21.38,正文,,0,0,0,,我不知道 陛下\N{\fs16}I don't know, Your Grace.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:21.41,0:54:24.01,正文,,0,0,0,,我无法在火焰中看见未来\N{\fs16}I can't see the future in the fire.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:28.52,0:54:30.58,正文,,0,0,0,,很好 戴佛斯席沃斯爵士\N{\fs16}Very well, Ser Davos Seaworth.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:31.85,0:54:34.42,正文,,0,0,0,,我 身为拜拉席恩家族的\N{\fs16}I, Stannis of the House Baratheon,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:34.46,0:54:36.89,正文,,0,0,0,,史坦尼斯一世 安达尔和先民之王\N{\fs16}First of My Name, Rightful King of the Andals and the First Men,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:36.92,0:54:38.83,正文,,0,0,0,,在此判处你死刑 - 我明白\N{\fs16}- sentence you to die. - I understand.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:38.86,0:54:41.13,正文,,0,0,0,,但既然您尚未免除我首相的职务\N{\fs16}But since you haven't yet unnamed me Hand of the King,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:41.16,0:54:43.63,正文,,0,0,0,,我仍有职责谏言您不要这样做\N{\fs16}it is my duty to advise you against it.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:43.66,0:54:46.30,正文,,0,0,0,,您会需要我的辅佐 - 带他下去\N{\fs16}You're gonna need me. - Take him away.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:47.70,0:54:49.47,正文,,0,0,0,,我为何需要你的辅佐？\N{\fs16}Why am I gonna need you?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:53.77,0:54:55.21,正文,,0,0,0,,陛下\N{\fs16}My king.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:54:59.08,0:55:01.51,正文,,0,0,0,,这是守夜人的伊蒙学士送来的\N{\fs16}It's from Maester Aemon of the Night's Watch.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:55:01.55,0:55:03.32,正文,,0,0,0,,他们的总司令去世了\N{\fs16}Their Lord Commander is dead.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:55:03.35,0:55:05.95,正文,,0,0,0,,带游骑兵北上后再未归来\N{\fs16}Took a ranging party north and never made it back.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:55:05.99,0:55:08.25,正文,,0,0,0,,但有一个小伙子活着回来了\N{\fs16}One lad did, though.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:55:08.29,0:55:10.92,正文,,0,0,0,,他在长城外看到的东西\N{\fs16}What he saw beyond the Wall--{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:55:10.96,0:55:13.39,正文,,0,0,0,,冲我们大家来了\N{\fs16}it's coming for all of us.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:55:27.54,0:55:29.37,正文,,0,0,0,,你何时学会阅读的？\N{\fs16}When did you learn to read?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:55:29.41,0:55:30.87,正文,,0,0,0,,马索斯生前教过我\N{\fs16}Matthos taught me before he died{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:55:30.91,0:55:32.98,正文,,0,0,0,,这样我能更好地辅佐您\N{\fs16}so I could be of better service to you.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:55:40.48,0:55:43.99,正文,,0,0,0,,这场五王之战已毫无意义\N{\fs16}This War of Five Kings means nothing.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:55:45.22,0:55:48.52,正文,,0,0,0,,真正的战争在北方 陛下\N{\fs16}The true war lies to the north, my king.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:55:49.63,0:55:51.93,正文,,0,0,0,,死亡正向长城进军\N{\fs16}Death marches on the Wall.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:55:51.96,0:55:54.60,正文,,0,0,0,,只有您能力挽狂澜\N{\fs16}Only you can stop him.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:55:54.63,0:55:56.70,正文,,0,0,0,,只靠您一个人不行\N{\fs16}You can't stop him alone.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:55:56.73,0:55:59.33,正文,,0,0,0,,您需要人来为您重建军队\N{\fs16}You need someone to rebuild your army for you,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:55:59.37,0:56:02.00,正文,,0,0,0,,游说领主 让他们为您而战\N{\fs16}someone to convince this lord and that lord to fight for you,{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:56:02.04,0:56:04.11,正文,,0,0,0,,将佣兵和海盗聚于您靡下\N{\fs16}to bring sellswords and pirates to your side.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:56:04.14,0:56:06.51,正文,,0,0,0,,我决心已定\N{\fs16}I've made my decision.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:56:07.91,0:56:11.11,正文,,0,0,0,,他是对的 您需要他\N{\fs16}He's right. You need him.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:56:11.15,0:56:13.78,正文,,0,0,0,,在即将到来的战争中他还有用武之地\N{\fs16}He has a part to play in the war to come.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:56:22.76,0:56:25.23,正文,,0,0,0,,看见了吗 戴佛斯爵士？\N{\fs16}You see, Ser Davos?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:56:25.26,0:56:28.63,正文,,0,0,0,,你喜欢嘲弄的火神倒是救了你一命\N{\fs16}You've been saved by that fire god you like to mock.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:56:32.30,0:56:34.40,正文,,0,0,0,,你也在为他而战了\N{\fs16}You're in his army now.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:56:51.70,0:56:54.50,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(609,301)}丹妮莉丝·坦格利安\N{\b0\fs12}风暴降生 龙之母
Dialogue: 0,0:56:57.00,0:57:00.91,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,100)\pos(262,235)}巴利斯坦·赛尔弥\N{\fs12}“无畏的”女王铁卫
Dialogue: 0,0:56:57.26,0:56:59.76,正文,,0,0,0,,他们会出来的 陛下\N{\fs16}They will come, Your Grace.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:56:59.79,0:57:01.66,正文,,0,0,0,,只要他们准备好了\N{\fs16}When they're ready.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:57:01.69,0:57:03.53,正文,,0,0,0,,或许他们不想被征服\N{\fs16}Perhaps they didn't want to be conquered.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:57:03.56,0:57:06.06,正文,,0,0,0,,您并未征服他们\N{\fs16}You didn't conquer them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:57:03.91,0:57:07.91,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(649,304)}乔拉·莫尔蒙\N{\b0\fs12}“大熊” 熊老之子
Dialogue: 0,0:57:06.10,0:57:08.23,正文,,0,0,0,,您解放了他们\N{\fs16}You liberated them.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:57:09.33,0:57:10.90,正文,,0,0,0,,枷锁戴久了 也会有人爱上它\N{\fs16}People learn to love their chains.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:57:53.35,0:57:58.41,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(139,268)}达里奥·纳哈里斯\N{\b0\fs12}次子团成员
Dialogue: 0,0:57:58.41,0:58:01.21,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(418,159)}弥桑黛\N{\b0\fs12}丹妮莉丝·坦格利安的侍女
Dialogue: 0,0:58:00.05,0:58:01.30,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(360,333)}这位就是丹妮莉丝·坦格利安
Dialogue: 0,0:58:01.65,0:58:04.20,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(359,333)}风暴降生 不焚者
Dialogue: 0,0:58:04.75,0:58:07.40,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(348,332)}维斯特洛七大王国的女王
Dialogue: 0,0:58:07.75,0:58:09.90,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(356,332)}龙之母
Dialogue: 0,0:58:10.95,0:58:13.40,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(357,332)}是她给了你们自由
Dialogue: 0,0:58:13.46,0:58:15.46,正文,,0,0,0,,不\N{\fs16}No.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:58:24.25,0:58:26.95,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(355,332)}你们的自由不是我给的
Dialogue: 0,0:58:28.75,0:58:31.05,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(363,333)}我不能把它给你们
Dialogue: 0,0:58:32.60,0:58:34.70,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(358,332)}你们的自由 我无权给予
Dialogue: 0,0:58:35.57,0:58:37.70,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(362,334)}自由从来只属于你们自己
Dialogue: 0,0:58:38.85,0:58:42.50,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(356,332)}想要夺回自由你们必须亲自去争取
Dialogue: 0,0:58:42.50,0:58:45.20,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(359,331)}自由掌握在你们每一个人手中
Dialogue: 0,0:58:53.40,0:58:55.70,正文,,0,0,0,,- 弥莎！ - 弥莎！\N{\fs16}- Mhysa! - Mhysa!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:58:55.73,0:58:58.50,正文,,0,0,0,,弥莎！弥莎！\N{\fs16}Mhysa! Mhysa!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:58:58.54,0:59:00.84,正文,,0,0,0,,弥莎！弥莎！弥莎！\N{\fs16}Mhysa! Mhysa! Mhysa!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:59:01.74,0:59:03.81,正文,,0,0,0,,这是什么意思？\N{\fs16}What does it mean?{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:59:03.84,0:59:06.74,正文,,0,0,0,,这是古吉斯语 卡丽熙\N{\fs16}It is old Ghiscari, khaleesi.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:59:06.78,0:59:09.15,正文,,0,0,0,,意思是 "母亲 "\N{\fs16}It means "mother."{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:59:14.48,0:59:17.22,正文,,0,0,0,,没事的\N{\fs16}It's all right.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:59:17.25,0:59:18.95,正文,,0,0,0,,他们不会伤害我\N{\fs16}These people won't hurt me.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:59:21.46,0:59:24.13,正文,,0,0,0,,弥莎！弥莎！\N{\fs16}Mhysa! Mhysa!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:59:29.91,0:59:34.91,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(373,336)}卓耿\N{\b0\fs12}丹妮莉丝·坦格利安的龙
Dialogue: 0,0:59:29.91,0:59:34.91,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(179,342)}雷哥\N{\b0\fs12}丹妮莉丝·坦格利安的龙
Dialogue: 0,0:59:29.91,0:59:34.91,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(639,339)}韦赛利昂\N{\b0\fs12}丹妮莉丝·坦格利安的龙
Dialogue: 0,0:59:40.48,0:59:42.05,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(359,329)}飞翔吧
Dialogue: 0,1:00:01.80,1:00:03.35,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(359,329)}让我过去
Dialogue: 0,1:00:12.91,1:00:16.07,正文,,0,0,0,,弥莎\N{\fs16}Mhysa.{\r}
Dialogue: 0,1:00:27.59,1:00:30.19,正文,,0,0,0,,弥莎！ 弥莎！弥莎！\N{\fs16}Mhysa! Mhysa! Mhysa!{\r}
Dialogue: 0,1:01:21.13,1:11:21.40,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\an8}{\fad(500,500)\fs18\c&HFFFFFF&\b1}衣柜字幕组出品
Dialogue: 0,1:01:21.13,1:01:40.90,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,衣柜字幕组成员巡礼（排名不分先后）\N{\fs12}翻译组：北落师门 Barrosa 天银石 泰温公爵 卖力杀猪 FuriousFurion 盗墓奸尸 Bran的夏天 凯冯·兰尼斯特 波隆·史铎克渥斯 Rucle 艾莉娅的缝衣针 为万世开百事 非42 电影控孟老师 守誓剑 杰诺斯·史林特 唐朝栗子 小愤青菜 麻绳力攻 道朗马泰尔 imzxz1051
Dialogue: 0,1:01:40.90,1:02:00.90,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,衣柜字幕组成员巡礼（排名不分先后）\N{\fs12}校对组：屈畅(ccxx) 赵琳（@史诗图书）旧镇老翁 临冬城的狮子 托曼·兰尼斯特 守誓剑 艾莉娅的缝衣针 FuriousFurion 龙的命根子 pksunking Barrosa 泰温公爵 imzxz1051 加文·维斯特林 夏大猫子 Rhine 道朗马泰尔 Rucle 北落师门 盗墓奸尸 麻绳力攻 电影控孟老师 小魔女透明子
Dialogue: 0,1:02:00.90,1:02:10.90,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,衣柜字幕组成员巡礼（排名不分先后）\N{\fs12}特效组：窝鹏偏逢连夜雪 YBL_poplar 麻绳力攻 旧镇老翁 加文·维斯特林
Dialogue: 0,1:02:10.90,1:02:20.90,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,衣柜字幕组成员巡礼（排名不分先后）\N{\fs12}监制组：临冬城的狮子 北落师门\N{\fs12}总策划：baozhenyuawabi
Dialogue: 0,1:02:20.90,1:02:43.55,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,感谢又一季大家对于衣柜组的支持，衣柜字幕组与您相约第四季！
