[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: Default Aegisub file
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 358
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: 其他,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1,2,5,5,10,134
Style: 片头介绍,微软雅黑,20,&H00C2E0EC,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,134
Style: 正文,微软雅黑,26,&H00C2E0EC,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,5,134
Style: 人物介绍,微软雅黑,16,&H00C2E0EC,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.03,0:00:10.30,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs20\c&HC2E0EC&\b1\bord0\pos(320,278)}双语特效字幕\N{\b0}百度贴吧{\fs25\c&HFFFFFF&\b1}衣柜字幕组{\fs16\c&HC2E0EC&}\N专注GOT剧集 华语冰火最专业字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.77,0:00:12.61,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(410,188)}翻译{\fs22\b1}  凯冯·兰尼斯特
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.83,0:00:14.83,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(320,102)}翻译{\fs22\b1}  FuriousFurion
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.90,0:00:16.90,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(428,283)}翻译{\fs22\b1}  卖力杀猪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.33,0:00:20.73,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(320,250)\fs25\b1}君临{\fs12\b0}  King's Landing
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.53,0:00:22.45,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(387,99)}翻译{\fs22\b1}  泰温公爵
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.33,0:00:27.33,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\move(425,245,425,235)\fad(300,500)\fs25\b1}红堡{\fs12\b0}  Red Keep
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.37,0:00:30.37,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(363,99)}校对{\fs22\b1}  守誓剑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.73,0:00:34.53,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\t(\fry-90)\fs25\b1\pos(439.653,198.441)}赫伦堡{\fs12\b0}  Harrenhal
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.42,0:00:35.96,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(125,281)}校对{\fs22\b1}  夏小猫子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.03,0:00:41.01,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)\fs20\frx40\t(0,2000,\fs40\frx30\frz23)\b1\move(306.918,126,461.887,308,2,1962)}奔流城{\fs18\b0}  Riverrun
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.13,0:00:43.23,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fs25\b1\move(372,290,372,180)}奔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.13,0:00:44.23,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fs25\b1\move(392,290,392,180)}流
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.13,0:00:45.60,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fs25\b1\move(412,290,412,180)}城
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.13,0:00:45.60,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\move(450,290,450,180)\t(\fry720)\fs12\b0}Riverrun
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:45.60,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fs25\b1\pos(372,180)}奔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.23,0:00:45.60,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fs25\b1\pos(392,180)}流
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.35,0:00:47.98,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\an1\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(303,245)}复校{\fs22\b1}  艾莉亚的缝衣针\N{\fs14\b0}复校{\fs22\b1}  rucle\N{\fs14\b0}复校{\fs22\b1}  道朗马泰尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.63,0:00:49.68,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,0)\frx60\fs15\b1\t(\fs25\frx50)\move(353.774,131,353.78,177,38,1039)}临冬城{\fscx50\fscy50\b0}  Winterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.68,0:00:51.52,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,200)\frx50\fs25\b1\t(1.5,\fs100\frx30)\move(353.78,177,336.918,358,0,1824)}临冬城{\fscx50\fscy50\b0}  Winterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.56,0:00:54.40,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,300)\fs25\b1\pos(420,252)}临冬城{\fscx50\fscy50\b0}  Winterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.65,0:00:56.44,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(123,276)}后期{\fs22\b1}  poplar
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.86,0:00:58.82,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(364,106)}后期{\fs22\b1}  窝鹏偏逢连夜雪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.41,0:01:05.20,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(397,108)}监制{\fs22\b1}  临冬城的狮子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.74,0:01:07.37,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(126,273)}监制{\fs22\b1}  北落师门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.79,0:01:09.71,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(461,127)}策划{\fs22\b1}  baozhenyuawabi
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:11.75,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs14\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(182,106)}特别顾问{\fs22\b1}  屈畅(ccxx)@史诗图书
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.83,0:01:14.33,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\move(340,240,340,240)\fad(300,0)\frx45\fs25\b1}绝境长城{\fs12\b0}  the Wall
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.33,0:01:20.33,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\move(340,240,340,180)\fs25\b1}绝境长城{\fs12\b0}  the Wall
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.96,0:01:24.21,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(320,270)\fs25\c&HC2E0EC&}最专业的华语冰火资料站：冰与火之歌中文维基\N{\fs20\c&HFFFFFF&}http://zh.asoiaf.wikia.com/
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.13,0:01:28.67,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs18\pos(475,269)} 百度冰与火之歌贴吧 & 百度权力的游戏贴吧 {\fs12} 联合出品
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.63,0:01:30.43,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\move(348,240,320,400,1200,1800)\fad(200,200)\frx70\fs25\b1\t(\frx0)}阿斯塔波{\fs12\b0}Astapor
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.72,0:01:31.94,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)\frz25\frx60\t(\frx45\fscx200\fscy200\frz37)\fs25\b1\move(410.755,185,521.635,330,31,1199)}渊凯{\fscx50\fscy50\b0}  Yunkai
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.14,0:01:33.59,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,0)\frz10\fry60\fs40\t(\frz5\fry30\fs38)\b1\move(509.749,184,418.49,193,29,1448)}渊凯{\fscx50\fscy50\b0}  Yunkai
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.55,0:01:35.69,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,200)\frz5\fry30\fs38\t(\fry-90\frz-15\fs30)\b1\move(418.49,193,83.9,186,0,2123)}渊凯{\fscx50\fscy50\b0}  Yunkai
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.52,0:01:36.48,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs12\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(481,271)}根据长篇小说
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.52,0:01:36.48,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs24\pos(535,298)}《{\b1}冰与火之歌{\b0}》{\fs12} 改编
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.52,0:01:36.48,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs12\pos(572,315)} 原著 {\fs20} 乔治·R·R·马丁
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.59,0:01:47.84,其他,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs24\c&H24EFFF&\b1\pos(320,278)}权力的游戏\N{\fs14}第三季 第六集\N{\fs20\c&HFFFFFF&}衣柜字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.43,0:01:53.83,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs12\c&HC2E0EC&\pos(320,234)}第六集 {\fs18} "The Climb"\N{\fs12}攀爬
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.19,0:02:07.93,正文,,0,0,0,,木头放太多了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You've got too much wood in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.89,0:02:10.93,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(302,184)}山姆威尔·塔利{\b0}\N{\fs12}守夜人事务官
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.96,0:02:11.60,正文,,0,0,0,,木柴越多 火就越旺嘛\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But the more wood, the bigger the fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.56,0:02:13.64,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(385,166)}吉莉{\b0}\N{\fs12}卡斯特的女儿与妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.63,0:02:13.74,正文,,0,0,0,,火也需要呼吸\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It needs to breathe.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.77,0:02:15.70,正文,,0,0,0,,把那块大的挪开\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Take off that big log.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.08,0:02:28.59,正文,,0,0,0,,哈 你还挺懂生火的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Huh. You know your fires.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.39,0:02:40.10,正文,,0,0,0,,你小时候就有人替你生火吗？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Someone built your fires for you growing up?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.13,0:02:43.00,正文,,0,0,0,,河湾地那边没有这么冷\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It doesn't get so cold down in the Reach.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.72,0:02:46.87,正文,,0,0,0,,仆人当然也有\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And there were servants, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.91,0:02:49.17,正文,,0,0,0,,我知道你是个贵族\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I knew you were highborn.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.71,0:02:56.58,正文,,0,0,0,,噢 我在先民拳峰找到些东西\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Oh, I found something at the Fist of the First Men.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.96,0:03:00.80,正文,,0,0,0,,埋在地里的宝藏\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Buried treasure.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.83,0:03:03.33,正文,,0,0,0,,我觉得吧\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Thousands of years old.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.37,0:03:04.97,正文,,0,0,0,,怎么也得埋了上千年\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I think.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.14,0:03:08.07,正文,,0,0,0,,这有什么用？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}What does it do?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.31,0:03:11.81,正文,,0,0,0,,我也不知道\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'm not sure that it does anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.84,0:03:14.04,正文,,0,0,0,,但是很好看啊\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It's beautiful, though, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.12,0:03:25.32,正文,,0,0,0,,- 还要多久才能到？ - 用不了多久\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- How much longer? - Not so far.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.36,0:03:27.52,正文,,0,0,0,,几天就到了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}A few more days.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.56,0:03:30.90,正文,,0,0,0,,长城真像传说中那么高大吗？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Is the Wall as big as they say?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.93,0:03:32.80,正文,,0,0,0,,更高大\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Bigger.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.07,0:03:37.04,正文,,0,0,0,,有时甚至看不到它的顶端\N{\fs16}{\fs16}So big you can't even see the top sometimes.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.07,0:03:39.07,正文,,0,0,0,,因为藏到云里边去了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It's hidden in clouds.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.94,0:03:42.44,正文,,0,0,0,,你在逗我吧\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're playing with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.48,0:03:46.65,正文,,0,0,0,,我可没有 有700尺高呢\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'm not. It's 700 feet high,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.68,0:03:48.98,正文,,0,0,0,,全部由冰筑成\N{\fs16}{\fs16}all made of ice.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.05,0:03:51.69,正文,,0,0,0,,天气暖和的时候 你可以看到它“流泪”\N{\fs16}{\fs16}On a warm day you can see it weeping.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.29,0:03:59.59,正文,,0,0,0,,黑城堡是个好地方\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Castle Black is nice enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.63,0:04:02.96,正文,,0,0,0,,大厅里无论日夜\N{\fs16}{\fs16}They keep a fire burning in the long hall
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.00,0:04:04.73,正文,,0,0,0,,都生着炉火\N{\fs16}{\fs16}day and night.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.77,0:04:08.90,正文,,0,0,0,,哈布会炖上鹿肉\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And Hobb makes venison stew
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.94,0:04:10.70,正文,,0,0,0,,加点儿洋葱\N{\fs16}{\fs16}with onions.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.74,0:04:12.14,正文,,0,0,0,,非常美味\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Very tasty.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.17,0:04:16.48,正文,,0,0,0,,有时候 有弟兄会唱歌\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Sometimes, one of the brothers will sing.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.51,0:04:19.05,正文,,0,0,0,,戴利恩唱得最好了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Dareon sings best.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.08,0:04:21.18,正文,,0,0,0,,- 你会唱歌吗？ - 不会\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- Do you sing? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.22,0:04:24.02,正文,,0,0,0,,不 不 不 我唱得不好\N{\fs16}{\fs16}No, no, no. Not very well.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.25,0:04:28.59,正文,,0,0,0,,给我唱首歌吧\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Sing me a song.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.62,0:04:32.23,正文,,0,0,0,,噢 那好吧\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Oh, all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.26,0:04:34.16,正文,,0,0,0,,我想想\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Let's see.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.00,0:04:38.93,正文,,0,0,0,,噢…… 咳咳\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Oh... ahem.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.04,0:04:45.14,正文,,0,0,0,,天父面容坚毅刚强\N{\fs16}{\fs16}? The father's face is stern and strong ?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.17,0:04:48.28,正文,,0,0,0,,裁决谬误主持公义\N{\fs16}{\fs16}? He sits and judges right from wrong ?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.31,0:04:51.58,正文,,0,0,0,,判定福寿长短高低\N{\fs16}{\fs16}? He weighs our lives, the short and long ?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.61,0:04:54.85,正文,,0,0,0,,慈祥喜爱小小孩童\N{\fs16}{\fs16}? And loves the little children ?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.88,0:04:58.79,正文,,0,0,0,,圣母带来生命之福\N{\fs16}{\fs16}? The mother gives the gift of life ?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.82,0:05:02.59,正文,,0,0,0,,守护照看每位人妇\N{\fs16}{\fs16}? And watches over every wife ?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.62,0:05:06.96,正文,,0,0,0,,她的笑容终斗止戈\N{\fs16}{\fs16}? Her gentle smile ends all strife ?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.99,0:05:10.73,正文,,0,0,0,,温柔呵护小小孩童\N{\fs16}{\fs16}? And she loves her little children. ?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.91,0:05:18.62,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(532,99)}欧莎{\b0}\N{\fs12}布兰与瑞肯的保护者
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.31,0:05:18.87,正文,,0,0,0,,兔子皮可不是这么剥的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}That's not how you skin a rabbit.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.62,0:05:20.54,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(306,119)}梅拉·黎德
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.91,0:05:20.37,正文,,0,0,0,,我知道怎么剥兔子皮\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I know how to skin a rabbit.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.41,0:05:22.74,正文,,0,0,0,,瞧着可不像\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Not by the looks of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.92,0:05:26.75,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(512,91)}布兰·史塔克
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.36,0:05:40.86,正文,,0,0,0,,如果你在长城以北长大\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You grow up north of the Wall,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.90,0:05:42.73,正文,,0,0,0,,就会知道该怎么处理猎物\N{\fs16}{\fs16}you learn the proper way to handle game.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.76,0:05:45.20,正文,,0,0,0,,来这之前我没处理过什么猎物\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I didn't see any game before I got here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.67,0:05:48.80,正文,,0,0,0,,如果我有弓 我能猎到一打兔子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}If I had a bow, I could have shot a dozen rabbits.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.84,0:05:50.37,正文,,0,0,0,,好吧 这弓可是我自己做的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Well, I made this bow myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.40,0:05:52.52,正文,,0,0,0,,我猜你在长城以北没学会这门手艺\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Guess you don't learn how to do that north of the Wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.54,0:05:54.67,正文,,0,0,0,,你倒是学会了怎么用拳头\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You learn how to use your fists, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.71,0:05:56.74,正文,,0,0,0,,哦 你打算用拳头把兔子锤死？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Oh, you're gonna punch the rabbits to death?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.78,0:05:58.24,正文,,0,0,0,,我想的可不是兔子 是别人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I had someone else in mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.28,0:05:59.75,正文,,0,0,0,,好吧 “别人”现在正在这儿坐着\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Well, someone else is sitting right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.78,0:06:02.25,正文,,0,0,0,,你们两位都很会剥兔子皮\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're both very good at skinning rabbits.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.28,0:06:05.12,正文,,0,0,0,,其中一位稍微剥得好点儿\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Some of us are just a little better.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.15,0:06:07.12,正文,,0,0,0,,是啊 当“别人”辛苦打猎 弄来早餐时\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Well, some of us would say thank you when someone else
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.15,0:06:09.22,正文,,0,0,0,,“其中一位”应该说声“谢谢”\N{\fs16}{\fs16}hunts down their breakfast for them.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.26,0:06:11.19,正文,,0,0,0,,也许在长城以北没人教过你？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Or don't they teach you to say thank you north of the Wall?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.22,0:06:14.86,正文,,0,0,0,,你嘴巴太大了 丫头 牙也太多了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You've got a big mouth, girl, and too many teeth.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.89,0:06:17.06,正文,,0,0,0,,- 停下！ - 阿多\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- Stop it! - Hodor.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.10,0:06:19.60,正文,,0,0,0,,你们从刚见面就一直吵个不休 拜托歇会儿吧\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You've been fighting since you met. Just stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.63,0:06:22.43,正文,,0,0,0,,黎德小姐的尾巴快翘到天上去了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Lady Reed here's got a stick so far up her ass,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.47,0:06:23.94,正文,,0,0,0,,她居然还能在地上站稳简直是个奇迹\N{\fs16}{\fs16}it's a wonder her feet touch the ground.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.97,0:06:26.31,正文,,0,0,0,,你每天都对她恶言相向\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You've been nasty to her every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.34,0:06:27.74,正文,,0,0,0,,她当然会以恶言针锋相对\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Of course she's nasty back.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.77,0:06:29.37,正文,,0,0,0,,我？ 这么说来是我的错了？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Me? It's my fault?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.41,0:06:31.58,正文,,0,0,0,,我第一次见她 她就把匕首搁我脖子上\N{\fs16}{\fs16}First time I met her, she put a knife to my throat.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.61,0:06:33.95,正文,,0,0,0,,我第一次见你 你也把匕首搁我脖子上\N{\fs16}{\fs16}First time I met you, you held a knife at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.08,0:06:37.82,正文,,0,0,0,,我们不能内讧\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We can't fight each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.85,0:06:40.12,正文,,0,0,0,,不然永远都别想到长城\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We'll never make it to the Wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.15,0:06:42.89,正文,,0,0,0,,我需要你们休战\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I want you both to make peace.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.97,0:06:54.07,正文,,0,0,0,,你剥兔子皮的方法的确比我更快\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Your way of skinning rabbits is quicker than mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.10,0:06:56.70,正文,,0,0,0,,- 我早就说了 不是么？ - 欧莎！\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- I said so, didn't I? - Osha!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.21,0:07:01.87,正文,,0,0,0,,你是个出色的小猎手\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're a good little hunter.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.91,0:07:03.34,正文,,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.38,0:07:04.81,正文,,0,0,0,,看？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}See?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.85,0:07:06.58,正文,,0,0,0,,没那么难 是吧？谢谢\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Not so hard, is it? Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.61,0:07:08.01,正文,,0,0,0,,别逼我\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Don't push me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.86,0:07:11.82,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(199,183)}玖健·黎德
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.89,0:07:20.43,正文,,0,0,0,,嘘\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Shh.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.46,0:07:22.49,正文,,0,0,0,,姐姐在这里\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'm right here with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.53,0:07:24.46,正文,,0,0,0,,发生什么了？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}What's happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.70,0:07:24.66,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(223,183)}阿多{\b0}\N{\fs12}临冬城的马僮
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.70,0:07:24.66,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(546,285)}瑞肯·史塔克
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.50,0:07:26.67,正文,,0,0,0,,姐姐在你身边\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'm right here with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.43,0:07:29.57,正文,,0,0,0,,他怎么了？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}What's wrong with him?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.01,0:07:35.77,正文,,0,0,0,,绿之视野需要付出代价\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The visions take their toll.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.38,0:07:39.11,正文,,0,0,0,,他又看到了么？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He's having one now?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.26,0:08:01.30,正文,,0,0,0,,我看到琼恩·雪诺了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I saw Jon Snow.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.27,0:08:04.30,正文,,0,0,0,,你看到他了？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You saw him?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.34,0:08:05.90,正文,,0,0,0,,在黑城堡？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}At Castle Black?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.14,0:08:09.61,正文,,0,0,0,,他在长城的另一边 相反的那边……\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He was on the wrong side of the Wall...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.74,0:08:12.24,正文,,0,0,0,,被敌人团团包围\N{\fs16}{\fs16}surrounded by enemies.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.69,0:08:25.42,正文,,0,0,0,,从前 长城附近一里内是找不到树的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Used to be you couldn't find a tree within a mile of the Wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.43,0:08:28.27,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(565,120)}托蒙德\N{\b0\fs12}“巨人克星” 野人掠袭者
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.46,0:08:28.59,正文,,0,0,0,,乌鸦们每天早晨都带着斧子过来砍树\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Crows would come out every morning with axes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.56,0:08:31.15,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(216,118)}琼恩·雪诺\N{\b0\fs12}叛逃的乌鸦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.69,0:08:34.94,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\fad(300,500)\pos(358,143)}欧瑞尔\N{\b0\fs12}“鹰眼” 易形者
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.86,0:08:35.33,正文,,0,0,0,,你们这群乌鸦每年都在减少\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Your flock gets smaller every year.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.77,0:08:43.44,正文,,0,0,0,,你以前有爬过吗？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You ever climbed it before?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.47,0:08:45.54,正文,,0,0,0,,没有\N{\fs16}{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.57,0:08:46.33,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(270,225)}耶哥蕊特\N{\b0\fs12}“火吻而生” 野人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.58,0:08:48.51,正文,,0,0,0,,但托蒙德爬过不下五十次\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But Tormund's done it half a hundred times.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.32,0:08:56.32,正文,,0,0,0,,你在害怕\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're afraid.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.12,0:09:00.56,正文,,0,0,0,,- 你呢？ - 我怕得紧\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- Aren't you? - Aye.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.59,0:09:03.33,正文,,0,0,0,,向上难于登天 往下万劫不复\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It's a long way up and a long way down.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.36,0:09:05.73,正文,,0,0,0,,可我已经等了一辈子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But I've waited my whole life
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.77,0:09:07.77,正文,,0,0,0,,想站在长城上看看这个世界\N{\fs16}{\fs16}to see the world from up there.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.21,0:09:15.27,正文,,0,0,0,,过来 坐下 我给你拿了一双\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Here, sit down. I brought a pair for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.64,0:09:19.58,正文,,0,0,0,,对你来说大了点 但是很好用\N{\fs16}{\fs16}They're too big for you, but they're good.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.61,0:09:21.45,正文,,0,0,0,,你为它们杀人了？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You kill someone for them?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.48,0:09:23.65,正文,,0,0,0,,没\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Nah.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.68,0:09:25.45,正文,,0,0,0,,我没杀他\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I didn't kill him,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.49,0:09:27.85,正文,,0,0,0,,但我敢打赌他的卵蛋还肿着\N{\fs16}{\fs16}but I bet his balls are still bruised.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.63,0:09:37.50,正文,,0,0,0,,他不像你这么对我好\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He wasn't good to me the way you're good to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.87,0:09:42.14,正文,,0,0,0,,也做不了你用舌头玩的花样\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He didn't do that thing you do with your tongue.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.27,0:09:44.94,正文,,0,0,0,,我们能不在这儿提这事吗？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Can we not talk about that here?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.97,0:09:47.44,正文,,0,0,0,,“我们能不在这儿提这事吗？”\N{\fs16}{\fs16}"Can we not talk about that here?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.48,0:09:49.28,正文,,0,0,0,,“我是琼恩·雪诺”\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'm Jon Snow.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.31,0:09:51.31,正文,,0,0,0,,“我灭过尸鬼也杀过断掌科林”\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I've killed dead men and Qhorin Halfhand,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.35,0:09:53.45,正文,,0,0,0,,“可我一见裸体的女孩就会吓坏了”\N{\fs16}{\fs16}but I'm scared of naked girls."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.48,0:09:54.98,正文,,0,0,0,,我那天看上去像吓坏的样子吗？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Did I seem scared the other day?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.02,0:09:56.65,正文,,0,0,0,,你抖得像片叶子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You were trembling like a leaf.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.69,0:09:58.22,正文,,0,0,0,,只有开头是那样\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Only in the beginning.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.76,0:10:01.62,正文,,0,0,0,,只有开头是那样\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Only in the beginning.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.19,0:10:06.76,正文,,0,0,0,,你是个不错的情人 琼恩·雪诺\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're a proper lover, Jon Snow.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.80,0:10:09.67,正文,,0,0,0,,别担心\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And don't worry.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.70,0:10:11.77,正文,,0,0,0,,你的秘密在我这儿很安全\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Your secret's safe with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.80,0:10:14.24,正文,,0,0,0,,什么秘密？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}What secret?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.94,0:10:17.74,正文,,0,0,0,,你真以为我和你从小看到大的那些\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Do you think I'm as dumb as all those girls
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.77,0:10:21.71,正文,,0,0,0,,穿丝绸裙装的女孩一样蠢吗？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}in silk dresses you knew growing up?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.74,0:10:24.68,正文,,0,0,0,,你忠诚 你勇敢\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're loyal and you're brave.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.78,0:10:30.55,正文,,0,0,0,,从你走进曼斯·雷德的帐篷那天到现在\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You didn't stop being a crow
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.59,0:10:33.29,正文,,0,0,0,,你仍旧是个乌鸦\N{\fs16}{\fs16}the day you walked into Mance Rayder's tent.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.90,0:10:42.33,正文,,0,0,0,,但我是你的女人了 琼恩·雪诺\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But I'm your woman now, Jon Snow.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.43,0:10:47.84,正文,,0,0,0,,要对你的女人忠诚\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're going to be loyal to your woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.68,0:10:55.51,正文,,0,0,0,,守夜人不会在乎你的死活\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The Night's Watch don't care if you live or die.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.55,0:10:58.91,正文,,0,0,0,,曼斯·雷德也不会在乎我的死活\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Mance Rayder don't care if I live or die.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.95,0:11:00.52,正文,,0,0,0,,我们只是他们军队里的小卒\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We're just soldiers in their armies
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.55,0:11:02.85,正文,,0,0,0,,如果我们倒下了 还会有千千万万个小卒站起来\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and there's plenty more to carry on if we go down.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.49,0:11:13.06,正文,,0,0,0,,这是你我的事\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It's you and me
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.10,0:11:16.17,正文,,0,0,0,,只关乎你我\N{\fs16}{\fs16}that matters to me and you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.80,0:11:22.14,正文,,0,0,0,,永远不要背叛我\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Don't ever betray me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.55,0:11:30.95,正文,,0,0,0,,我不会的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I won't.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.98,0:11:34.05,正文,,0,0,0,,不然我会把你漂亮的鸡巴切下来\N{\fs16}{\fs16}'Cause I'll cut your pretty cock right off
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.09,0:11:36.39,正文,,0,0,0,,戴到脖子上\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and wear it 'round my neck.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.13,0:11:49.96,正文,,0,0,0,,迈出每一步之前\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Sink your metal deep
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.00,0:11:53.53,正文,,0,0,0,,都要确保你的铁刺插得够牢够深\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and make sure it holds before taking your next step.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.44,0:11:56.07,正文,,0,0,0,,如果你掉下来了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And if you fall,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.11,0:11:57.84,正文,,0,0,0,,不要尖叫\N{\fs16}{\fs16}don't scream.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.87,0:12:01.51,正文,,0,0,0,,你也不想给她留下这样的最后印象吧\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You don't want that to be the last thing she remembers.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.19,0:12:15.79,正文,,0,0,0,,乔佛里\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Joffrey.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.50,0:12:21.80,正文,,0,0,0,,瑟曦\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Cersei.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.83,0:12:23.70,正文,,0,0,0,,伊林·派恩\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Ilyn Payne.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.63,0:12:26.76,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(398,169)}艾莉亚·史塔克
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.63,0:12:26.76,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(248,114)}安盖{\b0}\N{\fs12}“射手” 来自风暴地的弓箭手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.97,0:12:26.84,正文,,0,0,0,,你还不错\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're good.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.04,0:12:34.18,正文,,0,0,0,,但没有你自以为那么好\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're not as good as you think you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.88,0:12:38.51,正文,,0,0,0,,脸 胸 蛋\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Face, tits, balls--
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.55,0:12:40.12,正文,,0,0,0,,我本来就想射这三个地方\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I hit 'em right where I wanted to.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.15,0:12:43.89,正文,,0,0,0,,嗯 不过你太磨蹭了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Aye, but you took your sweet time of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.98,0:12:44.02,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(258,114)}密尔的索罗斯\N{\fs12\b0}无旗兄弟会的红袍僧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.92,0:12:47.42,正文,,0,0,0,,你的对手可不是稻草人 小淑女\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You won't be fighting straw men, little lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.36,0:12:51.69,正文,,0,0,0,,摆开姿势看看\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Show me your position.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.46,0:12:56.26,正文,,0,0,0,,抬高肘部\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Keep your elbow high.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.30,0:12:59.27,正文,,0,0,0,,你得用背部发力\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You want your back doing the hard labor.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.24,0:13:03.20,正文,,0,0,0,,你定住了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're holding.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.24,0:13:04.97,正文,,0,0,0,,永远不要定住\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Never hold.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.01,0:13:07.94,正文,,0,0,0,,- 什么？ - 定住的时候肌肉会紧张\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- What? - Your muscles tense up when you hold.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.98,0:13:10.24,正文,,0,0,0,,将弓弦向后拉到下巴中央\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Pull the string back to the center of your chin
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.28,0:13:11.74,正文,,0,0,0,,然后立刻松手\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and release.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.78,0:13:13.68,正文,,0,0,0,,永远不要定住\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Never hold.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.71,0:13:15.75,正文,,0,0,0,,但我需要瞄准\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But I have to aim.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.78,0:13:17.45,正文,,0,0,0,,永远不要瞄准\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Never aim.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.48,0:13:19.05,正文,,0,0,0,,永远不要瞄准？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Never aim?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.09,0:13:22.82,正文,,0,0,0,,你的眼睛知道你想射向什么地方\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Your eye knows where it wants the arrow to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.86,0:13:25.06,正文,,0,0,0,,相信你的眼睛\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Trust your eye.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.13,0:13:31.26,正文,,0,0,0,,那边有人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}There's someone out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.25,0:13:52.32,正文,,0,0,0,,停下 别再靠近了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}That's about far enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.30,0:13:59.43,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(267,117)}梅丽珊卓{\b0}\N{\fs12}光之王的“红袍祭司”
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.09,0:13:58.46,正文,,0,0,0,,我们是朋友\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We come as friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.49,0:14:00.29,正文,,0,0,0,,抱歉 夫人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Begging your pardon, m'lady,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.33,0:14:02.43,正文,,0,0,0,,这由我们说了算\N{\fs16}{\fs16}but we'll be the judge of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.73,0:14:06.40,正文,,0,0,0,,Valar morghulis.\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Valar morghulis
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.43,0:14:08.47,正文,,0,0,0,,Valar dohaeris.\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Valar dohaeris
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.70,0:14:13.24,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,268)}我在河间地可没见过拉赫洛的女祭司
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.24,0:14:16.53,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,293)}你是密尔的索罗斯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.95,0:14:20.95,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,293)}至高牧师给了你一个任务
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.41,0:14:25.21,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,268)}让劳勃国王放弃旧信仰皈依光之王
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.79,0:14:27.09,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,293)}结果如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.34,0:14:28.92,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,293)}我失败了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.46,0:14:31.51,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,293)}你放弃了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.92,0:14:35.26,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,268)}异教徒们继续相互残杀而你酗酒度日
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.59,0:14:40.60,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,268)}你以你的方式侍奉真主 而我有我的方式
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.31,0:14:44.35,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,293)}你会说通用语吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.34,0:14:47.27,正文,,0,0,0,,我的这些朋友不懂高等瓦雷利亚语\N{\fs16}{\fs16}My friends here don't speak High Valyrian.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.91,0:14:51.04,正文,,0,0,0,,请问夫人为何而来？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Why are you here, my lady?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.19,0:14:57.24,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(130,297)}贝里·唐德利恩\N{\b0\fs12}“闪电大王” 无旗兄弟会的领袖
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.66,0:15:05.76,正文,,0,0,0,,抱歉失礼了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Forgive my manners.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.86,0:15:08.79,正文,,0,0,0,,最近我没怎么见过女士\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I don't see many ladies these days.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.83,0:15:10.69,正文,,0,0,0,,这是女士们的好运\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Lucky for the ladies.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.16,0:15:42.26,正文,,0,0,0,,真主已经救活他多少次了？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}How many times has the Lord brought him back?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.29,0:15:44.13,正文,,0,0,0,,六次\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Six.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.75,0:15:48.67,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,293)}这不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.71,0:15:51.96,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,293)}真主眷顾了我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.26,0:15:55.13,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,293)}你不该有这种法力
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.34,0:15:57.34,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,293)}我没有法力
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.26,0:16:00.85,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,293)}我请求真主的帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.01,0:16:02.93,正文,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,293)}而真主回应了我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.62,0:16:12.02,正文,,0,0,0,,我一直是一个糟糕的僧侣\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I've always been a terrible priest.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.33,0:16:15.93,正文,,0,0,0,,喝了太多酒\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Drank too much rum.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.96,0:16:18.06,正文,,0,0,0,,上遍君临所有的妓女\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Fucked all the whores in King's Landing.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.10,0:16:20.80,正文,,0,0,0,,承认这点很糟糕\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It's a terrible thing to say,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.83,0:16:24.73,正文,,0,0,0,,当我来到维斯特洛时 我已经不信奉我们的真主了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}but by the time I came to Westeros, I didn't believe in our Lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.47,0:16:30.24,正文,,0,0,0,,我觉得他跟其余神祗一样\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I decided that He, that all the gods,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.27,0:16:33.81,正文,,0,0,0,,是我们为了让孩子听话而编的故事\N{\fs16}{\fs16}were stories we told the children to make them behave.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.61,0:16:38.58,正文,,0,0,0,,所以我时不时穿上红袍吟诵祷辞\N{\fs16}{\fs16}So I wore the robes and every now and then I'd recite the prayers,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.62,0:16:41.69,正文,,0,0,0,,却只是演戏罢了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}but it was just for show.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.46,0:16:46.42,正文,,0,0,0,,就当给人奉上精彩表演\N{\fs16}{\fs16}A spectacle for the locals.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.46,0:16:49.89,正文,,0,0,0,,直到魔山将长枪刺入他的心脏\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Until the Mountain drove a lance through this one's heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.13,0:16:57.44,正文,,0,0,0,,我跪在他冰冷的躯体前\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I knelt beside his cold body
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.47,0:16:59.27,正文,,0,0,0,,吟诵那些古老的辞句\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and said the old words.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.31,0:17:02.01,正文,,0,0,0,,倒不是因为我相信它们 但……\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Not because I believed in them, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.38,0:17:07.28,正文,,0,0,0,,他是我的朋友\N{\fs16}{\fs16}he was my friend
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.31,0:17:09.62,正文,,0,0,0,,可他死了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and he was dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.82,0:17:12.75,正文,,0,0,0,,那是我唯一会说的祷辞\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And they were the only words I knew.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.29,0:17:17.29,正文,,0,0,0,,此生第一次 真主回应了我\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And for the first time in my life, the Lord replied.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.53,0:17:21.63,正文,,0,0,0,,贝里的眼睛睁开了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Beric's eyes opened
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.66,0:17:24.40,正文,,0,0,0,,于是我明白了真理\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and I knew the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.43,0:17:27.43,正文,,0,0,0,,我们的神才是唯一的真神\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Our god is the one true god.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.77,0:17:32.17,正文,,0,0,0,,凡人皆需侍奉\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And all men must serve Him.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.25,0:17:42.25,正文,,0,0,0,,你去过另一个世界\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You've been to the other side.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.12,0:17:45.25,正文,,0,0,0,,另一个世界？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The other side?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.35,0:17:49.16,正文,,0,0,0,,没有另一个世界\N{\fs16}{\fs16}There is no other side.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.26,0:17:52.86,正文,,0,0,0,,我曾经步入黑暗 夫人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I have been to the darkness, my lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.83,0:17:59.67,正文,,0,0,0,,真主派你来一定自有深意\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He sent you to us for a reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.14,0:18:03.47,正文,,0,0,0,,你手下有他想要的人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You have someone He needs.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.91,0:18:07.34,正文,,0,0,0,,锥形箭头\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Bodkin point.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.76,0:18:08.39,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(361,234)}詹德利\N{\b0\fs12}“大牛” 铁匠学徒
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.38,0:18:10.28,正文,,0,0,0,,可以在200尺的距离射穿板甲\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Penetrates plate at 200 yards.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.12,0:18:16.15,正文,,0,0,0,,你会打造这种吗？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Can you make 'em?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.19,0:18:18.55,正文,,0,0,0,,能 这没啥难的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Yeah, nothing tricky about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.59,0:18:20.89,正文,,0,0,0,,只是需要上好的钢\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Just need decent steel.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.92,0:18:22.22,正文,,0,0,0,,我帮你找钢材\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'll get you the steel.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.26,0:18:24.49,正文,,0,0,0,,来\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.03,0:18:27.76,正文,,0,0,0,,我不喜欢那个女人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I don't like that woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.07,0:18:32.64,正文,,0,0,0,,因为你是个女孩\N{\fs16}{\fs16}That's 'cause you're a girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.67,0:18:34.40,正文,,0,0,0,,那跟这有啥关系？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}What does that have to do with anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.68,0:18:42.28,正文,,0,0,0,,抱歉 小子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Forgive me, lad.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.38,0:18:49.15,正文,,0,0,0,,你们在干什么？放开他\N{\fs16}{\fs16}What are you doing? Let go of him.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.19,0:18:50.82,正文,,0,0,0,,- 让他们住手  - 过来\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- Tell them to stop. - Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.85,0:18:52.65,正文,,0,0,0,,他想成为你们中的一员\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He wants to be one of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.69,0:18:54.96,正文,,0,0,0,,他想加入兄弟会 阻止他们！\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He wants to join the Brotherhood. Stop them!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.99,0:18:57.16,正文,,0,0,0,,我们侍奉光之王\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We serve the Lord of Light
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.19,0:18:59.39,正文,,0,0,0,,而光之王需要这个男孩\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and the Lord of Light needs this boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.43,0:19:02.03,正文,,0,0,0,,是光之王告诉你的还是她告诉你的？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Did the Lord of Light tell you that or did she?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.04,0:19:11.14,正文,,0,0,0,,你们不是为了你们的神\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're not doing this for your god.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.17,0:19:12.84,正文,,0,0,0,,你们是为了金子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're doing it for gold.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.87,0:19:15.04,正文,,0,0,0,,我们既为神也为金子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We're doing it for both, girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.41,0:19:18.25,正文,,0,0,0,,没有武器 马匹和食物\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We can't defend the people without weapons
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.28,0:19:20.55,正文,,0,0,0,,我们没法保护人民\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and horses and food.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.58,0:19:24.25,正文,,0,0,0,,没有金子 我们就没法获得武器 马匹和食物\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And we can't get weapons and horses and food without gold.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.29,0:19:27.22,正文,,0,0,0,,你说过这是个兄弟会\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You told me this was a Brotherhood.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.26,0:19:29.73,正文,,0,0,0,,你说过我可以成为你们中的一员\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You told me I could be one of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.20,0:19:38.37,正文,,0,0,0,,你能派上的用处比留在这里要大得多\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You are more than they can ever be.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.40,0:19:41.27,正文,,0,0,0,,他们不过是大战中的小卒\N{\fs16}{\fs16}They're just foot soldiers in the great war.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.31,0:19:43.94,正文,,0,0,0,,你却能决定国王的崛起和陨落\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You will make kings rise and fall.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.72,0:19:58.89,正文,,0,0,0,,你是个女巫 你想要伤害他\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're a witch. You're going to hurt him.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.96,0:20:06.16,正文,,0,0,0,,我在你身上看到了黑暗\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I see a darkness in you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.80,0:20:10.63,正文,,0,0,0,,在那黑暗中有数双眼睛凝视着我\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And in that darkness, eyes staring back at me--
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.67,0:20:12.67,正文,,0,0,0,,棕色\N{\fs16}{\fs16}brown eyes,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.70,0:20:15.97,正文,,0,0,0,,蓝色 绿色\N{\fs16}{\fs16}blue eyes, green eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.01,0:20:19.18,正文,,0,0,0,,你将永远阖上那些眼睛\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Eyes you'll shut forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.62,0:20:24.72,正文,,0,0,0,,我们会再见面的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We will meet again.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.00,0:21:42.66,正文,,0,0,0,,你在盯着我的屁股 琼恩·雪诺？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You staring at my ass, Jon Snow?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.77,0:21:54.44,正文,,0,0,0,,你没事吧？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.91,0:22:00.41,正文,,0,0,0,,只想看看你抗不抗打 小子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Just seeing if you can take a hit, lad.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.03,0:22:17.13,正文,,0,0,0,,抱歉 你在睡觉吗？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Sorry. Were you sleeping?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.16,0:22:19.23,正文,,0,0,0,,十……\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Wa--
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.22,0:22:20.23,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(521,272)}席恩·葛雷乔伊{\b0}\N{\fs12}铁群岛继承人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.87,0:22:24.30,正文,,0,0,0,,十……？十……？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Wa--? Wa--?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.44,0:22:27.24,正文,,0,0,0,,水？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Water?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.28,0:22:29.31,正文,,0,0,0,,你想喝水\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You want some water.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.85,0:22:34.38,正文,,0,0,0,,真希望能有点给你\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I wish I had some for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.37,0:22:50.77,正文,,0,0,0,,好 我们来玩一个游戏吧\N{\fs16}{\fs16}So let's play a game.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.94,0:22:55.17,正文,,0,0,0,,你身体的哪个部分是你最不需要的？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Which body part do you need the least?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.77,0:23:00.24,正文,,0,0,0,,- 求求你  - “求求你”不是身体的一部分\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- Please. - Please is not a body part.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.28,0:23:02.58,正文,,0,0,0,,我什么都告诉你 求你了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'll tell you everything, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.61,0:23:07.15,正文,,0,0,0,,但你已经全都告诉我了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But you've already told me everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.19,0:23:09.69,正文,,0,0,0,,忘了吗？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.72,0:23:12.16,正文,,0,0,0,,你老爸对你很苛刻\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Your daddy was mean to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.19,0:23:15.53,正文,,0,0,0,,史塔克家族不接纳你\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The Starks didn't appreciate you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.59,0:23:19.16,正文,,0,0,0,,有点倒还不错\N{\fs16}{\fs16}One good bit, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.20,0:23:21.40,正文,,0,0,0,,史塔克家的孩子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The Stark boys,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.43,0:23:24.13,正文,,0,0,0,,还活着\N{\fs16}{\fs16}they're still alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.27,0:23:29.27,正文,,0,0,0,,会不会是一次难忘的狩猎？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Wouldn't that be a hunt to remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.31,0:23:33.24,正文,,0,0,0,,你失败了 但我是一个更优秀的猎手\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You failed, but I'm a better hunter than you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.98,0:23:36.98,正文,,0,0,0,,现在\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Now...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.01,0:23:38.98,正文,,0,0,0,,小拇指怎么样？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}how about your little finger?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.02,0:23:40.85,正文,,0,0,0,,你不怎么用它 对吧？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You don't use that for much, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.88,0:23:44.05,正文,,0,0,0,,对？好的 我们就从这儿开始\N{\fs16}{\fs16}No? Good. Let's start with that.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.10,0:23:56.77,正文,,0,0,0,,你肯定在想你为什么在这里\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You've been wondering why you're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.80,0:23:59.30,正文,,0,0,0,,对吧？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Haven't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.34,0:24:01.17,正文,,0,0,0,,你在哪\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Where you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.21,0:24:02.97,正文,,0,0,0,,我是谁\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Who I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.01,0:24:05.81,正文,,0,0,0,,我为什么要这样对你\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Why I'm doing this to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.41,0:24:09.65,正文,,0,0,0,,猜猜看吧\N{\fs16}{\fs16}So guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.68,0:24:11.92,正文,,0,0,0,,如果你猜对了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}If you guess right,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.95,0:24:13.52,正文,,0,0,0,,我就告诉你\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'll tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.55,0:24:16.52,正文,,0,0,0,,我以新旧诸神之名起誓\N{\fs16}{\fs16}By the old gods and the new, I swear it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.46,0:24:19.96,正文,,0,0,0,,如果你能弄清楚我是谁\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You win the game
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.99,0:24:22.06,正文,,0,0,0,,我为什么折磨你\N{\fs16}{\fs16}if you can figure out who I am
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.09,0:24:23.63,正文,,0,0,0,,游戏就算你赢\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and why I'm torturing you
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.66,0:24:27.00,正文,,0,0,0,,而如果你求我砍掉你的指头 就算我赢\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and I win the game if you beg me to cut off your finger.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.90,0:24:32.67,正文,,0,0,0,,如果我赢了 你会放我走吗？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}If I win, you'll let me go?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.71,0:24:37.47,正文,,0,0,0,,如果你认为这会有一个美好结局\N{\fs16}{\fs16}If you think this has a happy ending,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.51,0:24:40.51,正文,,0,0,0,,你刚才一定听得不够仔细\N{\fs16}{\fs16}you haven't been paying attention.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.54,0:24:42.18,正文,,0,0,0,,求求你\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.21,0:24:46.15,正文,,0,0,0,,再说一遍“求求你” 包你后悔的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You say please again and you'll wish you hadn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.59,0:24:51.75,正文,,0,0,0,,你先来\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You first.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.79,0:24:53.89,正文,,0,0,0,,我们在哪儿？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Where are we?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.89,0:24:57.49,正文,,0,0,0,,- 北境  - 太模糊了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- The North. - Too vague.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.53,0:24:59.16,正文,,0,0,0,,深林堡\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Deepwood Motte.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.40,0:25:03.63,正文,,0,0,0,,猜得糟透了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Terrible guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.31,0:25:13.84,正文,,0,0,0,,好了 在哪？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Now, where?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.78,0:25:16.85,正文,,0,0,0,,最后壁炉城\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Last Hearth.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.88,0:25:19.95,正文,,0,0,0,,我他妈的看起来像一个安柏家族的人吗？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Do I look like a fucking Umber to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.05,0:25:25.15,正文,,0,0,0,,卡霍城！\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Karhold!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.96,0:25:33.70,正文,,0,0,0,,卡霍城？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Karhold?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.50,0:25:38.43,正文,,0,0,0,,你怎么知道的？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}How did you know that?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.84,0:25:42.87,正文,,0,0,0,,我们进来的时候你看见旗帜了？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Did you see any banners flying when we came in?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.91,0:25:44.51,正文,,0,0,0,,没\N{\fs16}{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.54,0:25:47.11,正文,,0,0,0,,只是猜的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It was just a guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.14,0:25:50.65,正文,,0,0,0,,很好 席恩大人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Very good, Lord Theon.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.18,0:25:54.58,正文,,0,0,0,,那么我是谁？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And who am I?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.82,0:25:57.79,正文,,0,0,0,,托伦·卡史塔克\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Torrhen Karstark.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.82,0:25:59.72,正文,,0,0,0,,他死了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.76,0:26:02.36,正文,,0,0,0,,被弑君者勒死了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Strangled by the Kingslayer.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.16,0:26:06.70,正文,,0,0,0,,他是你的兄弟\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He was your brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.03,0:26:15.47,正文,,0,0,0,,你父亲是瑞卡德·卡史塔克伯爵\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Your father is Lord Rickard Karstark.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.01,0:26:27.25,正文,,0,0,0,,- 你发誓会告诉我如果我…… - 你猜对了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- You swore to tell me if I-- - You're right.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.08,0:26:32.92,正文,,0,0,0,,瑞卡德·卡史塔克伯爵是罗柏·史塔克的封臣\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Lord Rickard Karstark is Robb Stark's bannerman.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.95,0:26:34.89,正文,,0,0,0,,而我背叛了罗柏\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I betrayed Robb.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.92,0:26:38.53,正文,,0,0,0,,这就是你为什么折磨我\N{\fs16}{\fs16}That's why you're torturing me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.70,0:26:42.50,正文,,0,0,0,,没错\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.97,0:26:47.67,正文,,0,0,0,,你赢了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You win.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.05,0:27:01.72,正文,,0,0,0,,当然 你忘了问一个问题\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Of course, you forgot to ask one question.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.75,0:27:05.25,正文,,0,0,0,,你忘了问我是不是个骗子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You forgot to ask if I'm a liar.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.03,0:27:13.66,正文,,0,0,0,,恐怕我是的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'm afraid I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.63,0:27:18.87,正文,,0,0,0,,我告诉你的每一个字都是谎言\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Everything I told you is a lie.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.57,0:27:24.37,正文,,0,0,0,,发生在你身上的这些不需要什么理由\N{\fs16}{\fs16}This isn't happening to you for a reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.41,0:27:28.14,正文,,0,0,0,,好吧 有一个理由—— 我乐在其中\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Well, one reason-- I enjoy it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.18,0:27:31.41,正文,,0,0,0,,求你了 砍掉它！砍掉它！砍掉它！\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Please, cut it off! Cut it off! Cut it off!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.55,0:27:39.16,正文,,0,0,0,,我赢了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I win.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.19,0:27:41.86,正文,,0,0,0,,感谢你们这么快就赶来了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Thank you for riding here so quickly.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.89,0:27:44.39,正文,,0,0,0,,我明白这年头行路可不再轻松愉快\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I know travel isn't easy in these times.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.43,0:27:47.16,正文,,0,0,0,,路上到处是土匪和强盗\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The roads are crawling with cutthroats and bandits.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.88,0:27:48.93,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(220,186)}罗索·佛雷{\b0}\N{\fs12}“跛子罗索”
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.88,0:27:48.93,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(394,199)}瓦德·佛雷{\b0}\N{\fs12}“黑瓦德”
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.20,0:27:50.67,正文,,0,0,0,,然而北境之王召唤的时候 我们来了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But when the King of the North summons us, we come.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.70,0:27:53.10,正文,,0,0,0,,父亲让我们告诉您\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Our father has instructed us to tell you
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.14,0:27:55.87,正文,,0,0,0,,他将继续维持盟约\N{\fs16}{\fs16}that his alliance with the North can continue
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.91,0:27:58.58,正文,,0,0,0,,如果您能满足他的条件的话\N{\fs16}{\fs16}if his terms are met.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.98,0:28:00.81,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(362,155)}罗柏·史塔克{\b0}\N{\fs12}北境之王
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.98,0:28:00.81,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(149,191)}凯特琳·徒利\N{\b0\fs12}艾德·史塔克的遗孀
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.61,0:28:01.54,正文,,0,0,0,,佛雷大人要求一个正式的道歉\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Lord Frey requires a formal apology
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.85,0:28:03.11,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(248,154)}艾德慕·徒利\N{\b0\fs12}奔流城公爵 凯特琳·徒利之弟
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.85,0:28:03.11,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(572,162)}布林登·徒利\N{\b0\fs12}“黑鱼” 凯特琳·徒利之叔
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.58,0:28:03.58,正文,,0,0,0,,为您打破神圣誓言\N{\fs16}{\fs16}for your violation of your sacred oath
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.61,0:28:04.95,正文,,0,0,0,,没能娶他的一位女儿而道歉\N{\fs16}{\fs16}to marry one of his daughters.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.98,0:28:08.08,正文,,0,0,0,,当然 这是他应得的 是我的错\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Of course. He deserves as much. I was in the wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.12,0:28:10.55,正文,,0,0,0,,作为对这种背叛的赔偿\N{\fs16}{\fs16}As restitution for this betrayal,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.59,0:28:13.69,正文,,0,0,0,,他要求赫伦堡和其领地\N{\fs16}{\fs16}he demands Harrenhal and all its attendant lands.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.72,0:28:17.06,正文,,0,0,0,,- 我不认为这 - 我们在为北境战斗\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- I don't think that's-- - We are fighting for the North.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.10,0:28:20.06,正文,,0,0,0,,赫伦堡可不在北境\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Harrenhal is not in the North.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.10,0:28:23.77,正文,,0,0,0,,战争结束的时候就是了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It is his once the war is over
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.80,0:28:26.44,正文,,0,0,0,,它在战略上也不再有用了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and we have no further strategic need for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.37,0:28:30.27,正文,,0,0,0,,当然还有别的要求\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And there's something else.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.31,0:28:33.11,正文,,0,0,0,,我们会尽所能供其所需\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We will do whatever we can to give Lord Frey what he needs.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.14,0:28:36.71,正文,,0,0,0,,我们要的是人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Not what, whom.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.28,0:28:40.12,正文,,0,0,0,,什么？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.02,0:28:47.09,正文,,0,0,0,,不\N{\fs16}{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.12,0:28:49.36,正文,,0,0,0,,我们父亲要求艾德慕大人迎娶\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Our father requires Lord Edmure to wed
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.39,0:28:51.33,正文,,0,0,0,,他的一位女儿—— 萝丝琳\N{\fs16}{\fs16}one of his daughters-- Roslin.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.36,0:28:53.20,正文,,0,0,0,,她多大了？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}How old is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.23,0:28:54.46,正文,,0,0,0,,19\N{\fs16}{\fs16}19.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.50,0:28:56.07,正文,,0,0,0,,我能先见她吗？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Could I see her first?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.10,0:28:57.23,正文,,0,0,0,,您想要数她有几颗牙不成？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You want to count her teeth?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.27,0:29:00.00,正文,,0,0,0,,我们明早出发前往孪河城\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We depart for the Twins in the morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.04,0:29:02.07,正文,,0,0,0,,在我们离开之前要得到一个答复\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We need an answer before we leave
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.11,0:29:03.81,正文,,0,0,0,,而婚礼将在半个月内举行\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and a wedding not more than a fortnight thereafter
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.84,0:29:05.87,正文,,0,0,0,,不然盟约就此解除\N{\fs16}{\fs16}or this alliance is at an end.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.91,0:29:08.48,正文,,0,0,0,,令尊大人当这还是和平时节？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Your father does realize we're in the middle of a war?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.51,0:29:11.18,正文,,0,0,0,,父亲老了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Father is old.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.21,0:29:13.21,正文,,0,0,0,,见证女儿嫁给一个好丈夫\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It will put his heart at peace
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.25,0:29:16.12,正文,,0,0,0,,能让他安心\N{\fs16}{\fs16}if he could see her wed to a good husband.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.15,0:29:18.99,正文,,0,0,0,,并且最近的经历让他对于\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And his recent experience has made him wary
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.05,0:29:20.92,正文,,0,0,0,,拖得太久的婚约没有信心\N{\fs16}{\fs16}of long engagements.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.96,0:29:22.76,正文,,0,0,0,,可以理解\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He has every right to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.79,0:29:26.09,正文,,0,0,0,,请允许我们商议一下\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Please excuse us while we discuss it.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.65,0:29:46.21,正文,,0,0,0,,为什么我要让那个老黄鼠狼为我挑新娘？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Why should I let that old ferret choose my bride for me?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.25,0:29:49.32,正文,,0,0,0,,至少我该和你有同样的选择权\N{\fs16}{\fs16}At the very least, I should be offered the same choice you were.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.35,0:29:50.79,正文,,0,0,0,,我是他的封君\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'm his liege lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.82,0:29:53.02,正文,,0,0,0,,他是个骄傲的老头 然而我们伤害了他\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He's a proud man and we've wounded him.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.06,0:29:55.02,正文,,0,0,0,,不是我干的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I didn't wound him.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.06,0:29:56.69,正文,,0,0,0,,我说不行\N{\fs16}{\fs16}My answer is no.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.96,0:30:02.66,正文,,0,0,0,,听我说\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Listen to me
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.70,0:30:05.67,正文,,0,0,0,,听好了 你——\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and listen very carefully. You--
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.70,0:30:08.40,正文,,0,0,0,,神谕和律法说得都很清楚\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The laws of gods and men are very clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.44,0:30:10.91,正文,,0,0,0,,没人能够强迫谁去结婚\N{\fs16}{\fs16}No man can compel another man to marry.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.94,0:30:13.51,正文,,0,0,0,,我的拳头倒是可以强迫你的牙齿离开嘴巴\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The laws of my fist are about to compel your teeth.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.54,0:30:16.75,正文,,0,0,0,,好了好了 你听见他说了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It's all right. You heard him.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.81,0:30:19.98,正文,,0,0,0,,如果你拒绝 我们和佛雷家的盟约就完蛋了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}If you refuse, our alliance with the Freys is dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.02,0:30:23.42,正文,,0,0,0,,从我12岁开始他就想要把他的女儿塞给我了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He's wanted me for one of his daughters since I was 12.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.45,0:30:26.22,正文,,0,0,0,,他到现在还没死心\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He's not gonna stop wanting it now.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.26,0:30:28.62,正文,,0,0,0,,如果我说不 他还会回来的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}When I say no, he will come back
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.66,0:30:30.66,正文,,0,0,0,,那时他就会让我挑一个女儿\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and offer me a daughter of my choosing.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.69,0:30:32.53,正文,,0,0,0,,你这是要赌上我们的自由\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're willing to risk our freedom
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.56,0:30:35.00,正文,,0,0,0,,和性命去换一个漂亮点的老婆？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and our lives for a chance at a prettier wife?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.03,0:30:37.37,正文,,0,0,0,,我有仗要打\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I have a war to fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.40,0:30:39.40,正文,,0,0,0,,没有他们我们赢不了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We can't win it without them.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.44,0:30:41.27,正文,,0,0,0,,没时间讨价还价了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I have no time to haggle.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.30,0:30:43.44,正文,,0,0,0,,你说过你想弥补石磨坊的过失\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You said you wanted to make amends for the Stone Mill.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.47,0:30:47.38,正文,,0,0,0,,你想起那次壮举了？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You recall that heroic engagement?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.78,0:30:54.32,正文,,0,0,0,,我说要补偿的时候没想到结婚这种事\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I had something less permanent in mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.35,0:30:56.79,正文,,0,0,0,,我每战必胜\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I've won every battle,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.82,0:30:58.66,正文,,0,0,0,,却赢不了这场战争\N{\fs16}{\fs16}but I'm losing this war.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.46,0:31:03.66,正文,,0,0,0,,一旦错过这次机会\N{\fs16}{\fs16}If we don't do this and do it now,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.70,0:31:05.76,正文,,0,0,0,,就彻底输了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}we're lost.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.17,0:31:13.04,正文,,0,0,0,,我会娶她的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'll marry her.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.07,0:31:15.97,正文,,0,0,0,,你在为我赎罪 舅舅\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're paying for my sins, Uncle.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.01,0:31:18.84,正文,,0,0,0,,这对你既不公平也不正确\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It's not fair or right.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.88,0:31:20.68,正文,,0,0,0,,我会记住的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'll remember it.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.65,0:31:28.32,正文,,0,0,0,,我发现我的人终于给你找了点\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I see my men have finally found you
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.35,0:31:30.42,正文,,0,0,0,,适合你穿的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}something appropriate to wear.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.46,0:31:34.36,正文,,0,0,0,,是的 感谢他们\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Yes. Most kind of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.39,0:31:36.46,正文,,0,0,0,,你是史塔克的封臣 波顿大人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're a Stark bannerman, Lord Bolton.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.49,0:31:39.13,正文,,0,0,0,,我奉史塔克夫人之命\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I am acting on Lady Stark's orders
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.16,0:31:41.16,正文,,0,0,0,,把詹姆·兰尼斯特押送回君临\N{\fs16}{\fs16}to return Jaime Lannister to King's Landing.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.28,0:31:41.45,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(359,166)}詹姆·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}“弑君者” 御林铁卫队长
Dialogue: 0,0:31:41.20,0:31:44.80,正文,,0,0,0,,罗柏国王离开赫伦堡的时候 他的母亲尚为阶下囚\N{\fs16}{\fs16}When King Robb left Harrenhal, his mother was his prisoner.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:41.45,0:31:44.54,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(237,244)}卢斯·波顿\N{\b0\fs12}恐怖堡伯爵
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.84,0:31:46.44,正文,,0,0,0,,如果她不是他母亲的话\N{\fs16}{\fs16}If she wasn't his mother,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.47,0:31:48.57,正文,,0,0,0,,他会以叛国罪绞死她\N{\fs16}{\fs16}he'd have hanged her for treason.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.66,0:31:49.50,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(370,168)}布蕾妮·塔斯{\b0\fs12}\N“美人” 詹姆的护卫
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.78,0:31:58.05,正文,,0,0,0,,我必须把你们交还给罗柏·史塔克\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I should send you back to Robb Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.08,0:32:00.31,正文,,0,0,0,,你是该这么做\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You should.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.35,0:32:02.78,正文,,0,0,0,,不过 你还是坐在这里\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But instead, you're sitting here
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.82,0:32:05.45,正文,,0,0,0,,看着我吃不了饭的样子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}watching me fail at dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.49,0:32:07.66,正文,,0,0,0,,这是为什么？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Why might that be?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.69,0:32:09.56,正文,,0,0,0,,战争是花钱的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Wars cost money.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.59,0:32:11.56,正文,,0,0,0,,很多人会为你出个好价钱\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Many people would pay a great deal for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.59,0:32:14.26,正文,,0,0,0,,我们都知道谁会出最高价\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We both know who would pay the most.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.80,0:32:17.37,正文,,0,0,0,,或者让你付出最多的代价\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Or make you pay the most
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.40,0:32:19.07,正文,,0,0,0,,如果让他发现你抓住我\N{\fs16}{\fs16}if he found out you had captured me
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.10,0:32:21.34,正文,,0,0,0,,并且送我回北境去服刑\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and sent me back up north for a summary execution.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.37,0:32:23.74,正文,,0,0,0,,你是对的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're right.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.77,0:32:27.58,正文,,0,0,0,,也许最保险的做法是杀了你们俩然后烧了尸体\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Perhaps the safest thing to do is to kill you both and burn your bodies.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.61,0:32:29.54,正文,,0,0,0,,也许是个不错的方法\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It would be,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.58,0:32:32.88,正文,,0,0,0,,如果你真的以为我父亲不会知道真相\N{\fs16}{\fs16}if you honestly believed my father would never find out about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.92,0:32:35.58,正文,,0,0,0,,罗柏国王让你的父亲忙着呢\N{\fs16}{\fs16}King Robb is keeping your father quite busy.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.62,0:32:37.95,正文,,0,0,0,,他没空管别的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He doesn't have time for anything else.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.99,0:32:40.16,正文,,0,0,0,,他会为你腾出时间来的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He'll make time for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.49,0:32:44.99,正文,,0,0,0,,一旦你能够上路了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}As soon as you're well enough to travel,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.03,0:32:47.83,正文,,0,0,0,,我会让你去君临的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I will allow you to go to King's Landing
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.86,0:32:51.37,正文,,0,0,0,,算是补偿我部下的所为\N{\fs16}{\fs16}as restitution for the mistakes my soldiers made.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.40,0:32:54.77,正文,,0,0,0,,你得发誓告诉你父亲真相\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And you will swear to tell your father the truth,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.81,0:32:57.34,正文,,0,0,0,,并不是我搞残你的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}that I had nothing to do with your maiming.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.11,0:33:06.78,正文,,0,0,0,,- 喝一杯？ - 我就算了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- Shall we drink on it? - I don't partake.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.62,0:33:12.32,正文,,0,0,0,,换做别人早就怀疑这里藏着什么乾坤了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You do understand how suspicious that is to ordinary people?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.79,0:33:15.79,正文,,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Very well.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.83,0:33:17.86,正文,,0,0,0,,小姐\N{\fs16}{\fs16}My lady,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:17.90,0:33:20.96,正文,,0,0,0,,祝我们的旅途不再节外生枝\N{\fs16}{\fs16}may our journey continue without further incident.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.00,0:33:22.73,正文,,0,0,0,,哦 她不会和你一起走的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Oh, she won't be going with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.77,0:33:25.47,正文,,0,0,0,,我负责带詹姆爵士到——\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I am charged with bringing Ser Jaime to--
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.50,0:33:28.27,正文,,0,0,0,,你受指控参与叛国\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You are charged with abetting treason.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.31,0:33:30.44,正文,,0,0,0,,恐怕我得要求她跟我走\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'm afraid I must insist.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.47,0:33:33.14,正文,,0,0,0,,你没权力要求任何事情\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're in no place to insist on anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.18,0:33:35.31,正文,,0,0,0,,我还以为你那些不自量力的往事\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I would have hoped you'd learned your lesson
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.34,0:33:39.18,正文,,0,0,0,,能给你点教训\N{\fs16}{\fs16}about overplaying your position.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.15,0:33:45.32,正文,,0,0,0,,- 没戏 - 为什么？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- Impossible. - Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.24,0:33:45.45,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(419,250)}泰温·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}凯岩城公爵 国王之手
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.35,0:33:47.69,正文,,0,0,0,,我孙子是高庭的骄傲\N{\fs16}{\fs16}My grandson is the pride of Highgarden.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.45,0:33:47.12,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(372,171)}奥莲娜夫人\N{\b0\fs12}玛格丽·提利尔的祖母
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.72,0:33:50.86,正文,,0,0,0,,七大王国最炙手可热的未婚男子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The most desirable bachelor in all seven kingdoms.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.89,0:33:53.50,正文,,0,0,0,,- 您的女儿—— - 很富有\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- Your daughter-- - Is rich,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:53.53,0:33:57.27,正文,,0,0,0,,并且是七大王国最美丽的女人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}the most beautiful woman in all seven kingdoms...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.50,0:34:00.30,正文,,0,0,0,,还是国王的母亲\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and the mother of the king.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.34,0:34:01.74,正文,,0,0,0,,太老了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Old.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.61,0:34:03.61,正文,,0,0,0,,太老了？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Old?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:03.64,0:34:06.71,正文,,0,0,0,,太老了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Old.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.74,0:34:09.21,正文,,0,0,0,,我算得上是这方面的专家了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'm something of an expert on the subject.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.24,0:34:11.85,正文,,0,0,0,,衰老很快就会体现在她的身上\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Her change will be upon her before long.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:11.88,0:34:15.38,正文,,0,0,0,,我懒得跟你解释还会发生什么变化\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'll spare you the details of what will happen then.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.42,0:34:18.12,正文,,0,0,0,,你们男人可能对嗜血杀戮挺有兴趣\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You men may have a stomach for bloodshed and slaughter,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.15,0:34:20.56,正文,,0,0,0,,但这方面就是另一回事了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}but this is another matter entirely.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.59,0:34:24.23,正文,,0,0,0,,岁月也在惩罚我们 我向你保证\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The years punish us as well, I promise you that.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.46,0:34:30.63,正文,,0,0,0,,我的胃口倒还挺不错的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}My stomach remains quite strong, however.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.67,0:34:32.50,正文,,0,0,0,,唯一会让我倒胃口的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The only thing that might turn it
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.54,0:34:36.24,正文,,0,0,0,,是你孙子那些臭名昭著的行为\N{\fs16}{\fs16}are details of your grandson's nocturnal activities.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.54,0:34:39.47,正文,,0,0,0,,- 你否认吗？ - 噢 当然不\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- Do you deny them? - Oh, not at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.51,0:34:41.54,正文,,0,0,0,,他就好这口\N{\fs16}{\fs16}A sword swallower through and through.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.58,0:34:43.34,正文,,0,0,0,,有这样丑闻的男孩\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And a boy with his affliction
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.38,0:34:45.38,正文,,0,0,0,,有机会娶到七国最美的女人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}should be grateful for the opportunity
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.41,0:34:48.45,正文,,0,0,0,,还能抹去身上的污点\N{\fs16}{\fs16}to marry the most beautiful woman in the kingdoms
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.52,0:34:50.35,正文,,0,0,0,,应该心怀感激\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and remove the stain from his name.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.39,0:34:53.62,正文,,0,0,0,,您有没有和表兄弟一同长大 泰温大人?\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Did you grow up with boy cousins, Lord Tywin?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.65,0:34:55.66,正文,,0,0,0,,您父亲封臣的儿子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Sons of your father's bannermen,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.69,0:34:57.52,正文,,0,0,0,,侍从 或者马房小弟?\N{\fs16}{\fs16}squires, stable boys?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.56,0:34:59.86,正文,,0,0,0,,当然\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.89,0:35:03.06,正文,,0,0,0,,你就从没……\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And you never...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.10,0:35:05.13,正文,,0,0,0,,没有\N{\fs16}{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.17,0:35:07.17,正文,,0,0,0,,一次都没有？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Not once?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.20,0:35:08.77,正文,,0,0,0,,怎样都没有？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Not in any way?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.80,0:35:10.67,正文,,0,0,0,,从来没有\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Never.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.70,0:35:13.64,正文,,0,0,0,,我真心称赞你的自制\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I congratulate you upon your restraint.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.71,0:35:15.94,正文,,0,0,0,,不过两个男孩在床上\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But it's a natural thing, two boys having a go
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.98,0:35:17.61,正文,,0,0,0,,“打打闹闹”再正常不过了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}at each other beneath the sheets.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.64,0:35:20.21,正文,,0,0,0,,也许“高”庭对于不正常的行为\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Perhaps Highgarden has a high tolerance
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.25,0:35:22.15,正文,,0,0,0,,也有比较高的容忍度\N{\fs16}{\fs16}for unnatural behavior.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.18,0:35:23.62,正文,,0,0,0,,我可不会这么说\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I wouldn't say that.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.65,0:35:25.92,正文,,0,0,0,,当然 我们不会为这点基情\N{\fs16}{\fs16}True, we don't tie ourselves in knots
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.95,0:35:29.12,正文,,0,0,0,,就自寻烦恼 不过\N{\fs16}{\fs16}over a discreet bit of buggery, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.79,0:35:32.89,正文,,0,0,0,,弟弟和姐姐——\N{\fs16}{\fs16}brothers and sisters--
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.26,0:35:36.46,正文,,0,0,0,,在我的家乡 可算是\N{\fs16}{\fs16}where I come from, that stain
Dialogue: 0,0:35:36.50,0:35:38.97,正文,,0,0,0,,难以抹消的污点\N{\fs16}{\fs16}would be very difficult to wash out.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.00,0:35:41.60,正文,,0,0,0,,我不想再讨论\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I will not breathe further life
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.64,0:35:44.04,正文,,0,0,0,,这种恶意的谎言\N{\fs16}{\fs16}into a malicious lie by discussing it.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.91,0:35:47.68,正文,,0,0,0,,无论是不是谎言\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Lie or not,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.71,0:35:50.85,正文,,0,0,0,,你得承认很多人都觉得它挺可信的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}you must admit many people find it quite convincing.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.88,0:35:53.42,正文,,0,0,0,,以至于执剑上阵\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Convincing enough to put swords in their hands
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.45,0:35:55.48,正文,,0,0,0,,杀向狮子和玫瑰\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and send them off to kill Lannisters
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.52,0:35:58.55,正文,,0,0,0,,这新联盟把我们也捎带上了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and Tyrells thanks to our new affiliation.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.59,0:36:00.66,正文,,0,0,0,,我不管人们相信什么\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I don't care what people believe.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.69,0:36:03.52,正文,,0,0,0,,你也不用管\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And neither do you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.56,0:36:07.13,正文,,0,0,0,,站在我的立场上 可不能不管\N{\fs16}{\fs16}As an authority on myself, I must disagree.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.20,0:36:11.33,正文,,0,0,0,,现在 如果关于我孩子的谣言是真的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Now, if the rumors about my children were true,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.37,0:36:14.27,正文,,0,0,0,,那么乔佛里根本就不是国王\N{\fs16}{\fs16}then Joffrey is no king at all
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.30,0:36:18.47,正文,,0,0,0,,提利尔家也就把他们的宝贝玫瑰插在了牛粪上\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and House Tyrell is throwing its prized flower into the dirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.51,0:36:22.21,正文,,0,0,0,,如果瑟曦太老 给不了洛拉斯孩子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And if Cersei is too old to give Loras children,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.25,0:36:26.42,正文,,0,0,0,,我们就又把另一朵鲜花插在了牛粪上\N{\fs16}{\fs16}we're throwing another prized flower into the dirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.45,0:36:29.99,正文,,0,0,0,,我们不能冒这个险\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It is a chance we simply cannot take.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.02,0:36:32.56,正文,,0,0,0,,不确定性让你很不舒服\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The uncertainty makes you uncomfortable.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.96,0:36:35.79,正文,,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fs16}{\fs16}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.83,0:36:38.36,正文,,0,0,0,,那我们就来“确定”一下\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'll remove it for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.40,0:36:41.20,正文,,0,0,0,,如果你拒绝洛拉斯和瑟曦的婚姻\N{\fs16}{\fs16}If you refuse to marry Loras to Cersei,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.23,0:36:44.10,正文,,0,0,0,,我会让他披上白袍\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I will name him to the Kingsguard.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.13,0:36:47.57,正文,,0,0,0,,我相信你很熟悉御林铁卫的誓言\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'm sure you're familiar with the Kingsguard vows.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.60,0:36:49.60,正文,,0,0,0,,他将不结婚\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He will never marry.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.64,0:36:51.44,正文,,0,0,0,,- 不生子 - 哦……\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- He will never have children. - Oh...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.47,0:36:53.37,正文,,0,0,0,,提利尔家族会逐渐消亡\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The Tyrell name will fade.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.41,0:36:56.08,正文,,0,0,0,,而高庭会传给\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And Highgarden will go to the children
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.11,0:36:57.61,正文,,0,0,0,,乔佛里和玛格丽的孩子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}of Joffrey and Margaery.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:57.65,0:37:00.11,正文,,0,0,0,,难道你会愿意让一个痛恨你的人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You would have your grandson protected
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.15,0:37:01.98,正文,,0,0,0,,保护你的外孙？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}by someone who disgusts you?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.02,0:37:05.62,正文,,0,0,0,,我会让一个谨守誓言\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I would have my grandson protected by a skilled warrior
Dialogue: 0,0:37:05.65,0:37:08.99,正文,,0,0,0,,武艺精湛的战士保护我的外孙\N{\fs16}{\fs16}who takes his vows seriously.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.03,0:37:11.86,正文,,0,0,0,,那么 要我起草这条命令呢？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}So, shall I draw up the order?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.40,0:37:15.80,正文,,0,0,0,,还是你同意这桩婚事？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Or do you consent to this marriage?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.47,0:37:22.50,正文,,0,0,0,,名副其实的人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It's a rare enough thing--
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.57,0:37:26.44,正文,,0,0,0,,这年头太少见了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}a man who lives up to his reputation.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.29,0:38:20.63,正文,,0,0,0,,不！\N{\fs16}{\fs16}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:40.21,0:38:42.02,正文,,0,0,0,,我们必须割断绳索！\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We've gotta cut them loose!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.05,0:38:44.32,正文,,0,0,0,,不行！\N{\fs16}{\fs16}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.80,0:39:31.57,正文,,0,0,0,,抓住我的手！\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Take my hand!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.44,0:40:09.51,正文,,0,0,0,,别针好漂亮\N{\fs16}{\fs16}That's a wonderful pin.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.54,0:40:13.04,正文,,0,0,0,,呃 这其实是胸针\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Oh, it's more of a brooch, really.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.62,0:40:13.34,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(376,85)}珊莎·史塔克
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.62,0:40:13.34,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(92,100)}洛拉斯·提利尔\N{\b0\fs12}“百花骑士”
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.31,0:40:19.75,正文,,0,0,0,,不过我想胸针应该也是一种别针 所以……\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Though I suppose a brooch is a sort of pin, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.92,0:40:28.46,正文,,0,0,0,,我很高兴听说我们的……\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'm very happy about...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.49,0:40:30.29,正文,,0,0,0,,啊 是的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Uh, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.33,0:40:32.49,正文,,0,0,0,,我……我也是\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I-I am as well.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.80,0:40:36.83,正文,,0,0,0,,感觉好像在做梦一样\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I feel like I'm in a dream.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.87,0:40:40.64,正文,,0,0,0,,对 我也是 梦一样\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Yes, me, too. Definitely.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.67,0:40:43.21,正文,,0,0,0,,很小的时候我就幻想过一场盛大的婚礼\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I've dreamed of a large wedding since I was quite young.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.24,0:40:44.44,正文,,0,0,0,,幻想着宾客们\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The guests,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.48,0:40:47.64,正文,,0,0,0,,美食 比武大会\N{\fs16}{\fs16}the food, the tournaments.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.72,0:40:53.25,正文,,0,0,0,,当然 还有新娘\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And the bride, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.06,0:40:59.69,正文,,0,0,0,,世上最美丽的新娘\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The most beautiful bride in the world
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.73,0:41:01.33,正文,,0,0,0,,身着美丽的金丝礼服\N{\fs16}{\fs16}in a beautiful gown of gold
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.36,0:41:03.93,正文,,0,0,0,,和流苏袖口的绿色织锦\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and green brocade with fringed sleeves.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.37,0:41:08.60,正文,,0,0,0,,你去过高庭吗 小姐？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Have you ever been to Highgarden, my lady?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.74,0:41:11.37,正文,,0,0,0,,没有 来君临之前\N{\fs16}{\fs16}No. I had never left Winterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.40,0:41:14.41,正文,,0,0,0,,我从来没有离开过临冬城\N{\fs16}{\fs16}before I came to King's Landing.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:14.44,0:41:16.01,正文,,0,0,0,,不过听说那里很美\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But it sounds wonderful.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.04,0:41:18.64,正文,,0,0,0,,我等不及想去看看\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I can't wait to see it.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.68,0:41:20.78,正文,,0,0,0,,还有离开这里\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And to leave this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:21.88,0:41:23.65,正文,,0,0,0,,这里很可怕 是吧？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It's terrible, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.15,0:41:28.65,正文,,0,0,0,,世界上最可怕的地方\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The most terrible place there is.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:38.17,0:41:41.40,正文,,0,0,0,,对这桩婚事我们恐怕无能为力\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I don't suppose there's anything we can do about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.43,0:41:43.70,正文,,0,0,0,,我们可以把他们两个都杀了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We can have them both killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.51,0:41:43.59,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(486,139)}瑟曦·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}摄政太后
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.01,0:41:46.85,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(127,207)}提利昂·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}“小恶魔” 财政大臣
Dialogue: 0,0:41:45.51,0:41:47.47,正文,,0,0,0,,这场包办婚姻里\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It's hard to say which of the four of us
Dialogue: 0,0:41:47.51,0:41:50.51,正文,,0,0,0,,很难说我们四个谁最惨\N{\fs16}{\fs16}is getting the worst of this arrangement.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.54,0:41:52.48,正文,,0,0,0,,大概是珊莎\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Probably Sansa.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:52.51,0:41:54.35,正文,,0,0,0,,虽然洛拉斯肯定也会陷入\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Though Loras will certainly come to know
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.38,0:41:57.15,正文,,0,0,0,,深深地痛苦之中\N{\fs16}{\fs16}a deep and singular misery.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:57.18,0:41:59.92,正文,,0,0,0,,父亲倒是一视同仁\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Father doesn't discriminate.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.95,0:42:02.79,正文,,0,0,0,,我们全都被送进了地狱\N{\fs16}{\fs16}We're all being shipped off to hell together.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:02.82,0:42:04.92,正文,,0,0,0,,还不是你造成的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}On a boat you built.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:04.96,0:42:08.00,正文,,0,0,0,,提利尔家族谋划要削弱我们\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The Tyrells were plotting to undermine our family.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.03,0:42:10.57,正文,,0,0,0,,我所做的都是为了保护家族\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I did what I did to protect our family.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:10.60,0:42:12.70,正文,,0,0,0,,我也是家族中的一分子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'm your family.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:13.64,0:42:15.67,正文,,0,0,0,,而且是为了家族的生存\N{\fs16}{\fs16}A member of your family
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.70,0:42:18.74,正文,,0,0,0,,做了积极贡献的一分子\N{\fs16}{\fs16}who has actively contributed to that family's survival.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:19.81,0:42:21.58,正文,,0,0,0,,不管你和父亲或者任何人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Whether or not you or Father
Dialogue: 0,0:42:21.61,0:42:23.61,正文,,0,0,0,,是不是承认这一点\N{\fs16}{\fs16}or anyone else wants to admit it.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.65,0:42:25.95,正文,,0,0,0,,我承认\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I do admit it.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:25.98,0:42:28.62,正文,,0,0,0,,如果不是你的野火把戏\N{\fs16}{\fs16}If it weren't for your trick with the wildfire,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:28.65,0:42:31.95,正文,,0,0,0,,史坦尼斯就会在父亲来到之前攻陷君临\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Stannis would have sacked the city before Father got here.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:31.99,0:42:35.06,正文,,0,0,0,,我们的头大概现在还在城门上烂着呢\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Our heads would still be rotting on the city gate.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:35.09,0:42:39.43,正文,,0,0,0,,那么叫人杀我真是个奇怪的感谢方式\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Trying to have me killed is an odd way of saying thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.56,0:42:43.63,正文,,0,0,0,,在君临仅有两人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}There are two people in King's Landing
Dialogue: 0,0:42:43.67,0:42:45.83,正文,,0,0,0,,有权指挥御林铁卫\N{\fs16}{\fs16}who can give an order to a Kingsguard.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:45.87,0:42:48.84,正文,,0,0,0,,是不是你命令曼登爵士\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Did you or did you not order Ser Mandon
Dialogue: 0,0:42:48.87,0:42:51.77,正文,,0,0,0,,在黑水河之战中趁乱杀死我?\N{\fs16}{\fs16}to kill me during the Battle of the Blackwater?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:01.35,0:43:03.78,正文,,0,0,0,,我理解他想杀我的冲动\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The impulse I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:04.99,0:43:07.92,正文,,0,0,0,,他恨我因为我是唯一一个告诉他\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He hates me because I'm the only one
Dialogue: 0,0:43:07.96,0:43:10.83,正文,,0,0,0,,他实际上是个什么货色的人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}who tells him what he really is.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:13.70,0:43:18.13,正文,,0,0,0,,所以 他想我死 很正常\N{\fs16}{\fs16}So, fair enough. He wants me dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:18.17,0:43:20.17,正文,,0,0,0,,但是他愚蠢的地方在哪?\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But his stupidity?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.20,0:43:24.21,正文,,0,0,0,,他本来可以将我毒死 没有人会发现\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He could have had me poisoned and no one would have known.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:24.24,0:43:27.71,正文,,0,0,0,,但是国王命令御林铁卫\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But the king orders a Kingsguard
Dialogue: 0,0:43:27.74,0:43:29.91,正文,,0,0,0,,在他自己的军队面前\N{\fs16}{\fs16}to murder the Hand of the King
Dialogue: 0,0:43:29.95,0:43:31.85,正文,,0,0,0,,杀死国王之手\N{\fs16}{\fs16}in full view of his own army.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:31.88,0:43:33.41,正文,,0,0,0,,那这孩子还真是个白痴\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The boy's an idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:33.45,0:43:34.85,正文,,0,0,0,,你想让我说什么？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}What do you want me to say?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:34.88,0:43:37.89,正文,,0,0,0,,我想让你告诉我 我是不是还没脱险境\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I want you to tell me if my life is still in danger.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:37.92,0:43:39.65,正文,,0,0,0,,可能吧\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Probably.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:39.69,0:43:41.39,正文,,0,0,0,,但危险不会来自乔佛里\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But not from Joffrey.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:41.42,0:43:43.59,正文,,0,0,0,,父亲在这里 他不敢造次\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He won't do anything now Father's here.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:45.26,0:43:47.86,正文,,0,0,0,,泰温·兰尼斯特震慑住了七大王国\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Seven kingdoms united in fear
Dialogue: 0,0:43:47.90,0:43:50.03,正文,,0,0,0,,统一在即\N{\fs16}{\fs16}of Tywin Lannister.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:50.07,0:43:52.43,正文,,0,0,0,,提利尔家族未必赞同\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Not the Tyrells.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:52.47,0:43:54.50,正文,,0,0,0,,不久之后他们就不必再害怕他\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Soon they won't need to be afraid of him.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:54.54,0:43:55.97,正文,,0,0,0,,乔佛里会被玛格丽征服\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Joffrey will belong to Margaery,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:56.01,0:43:57.91,正文,,0,0,0,,那婊子的眼神如雌鹿一般\N{\fs16}{\fs16}the little doe-eyed whore.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:57.94,0:44:00.94,正文,,0,0,0,,之后他的子孙也会如此\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And so will his children and their children.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:00.98,0:44:03.21,正文,,0,0,0,,历史将从我们手中被夺走\N{\fs16}{\fs16}History will be taken from our hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:05.22,0:44:07.78,正文,,0,0,0,,你至少还能逃\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You may escape, at least.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:07.82,0:44:09.45,正文,,0,0,0,,只要詹姆回来\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Once Jaime gets back,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:09.49,0:44:11.99,正文,,0,0,0,,洛拉斯爵士恐怕会被\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Ser Loras may come down with a terrible case
Dialogue: 0,0:44:12.02,0:44:15.22,正文,,0,0,0,,一剑穿肠的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}of sword through bowels.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:15.26,0:44:17.23,正文,,0,0,0,,如果詹姆回来的话 是的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}When Jaime gets back, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:17.26,0:44:18.93,正文,,0,0,0,,但是你觉得他什么时候才会回来？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But when do we think that's going to be?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:18.96,0:44:20.80,正文,,0,0,0,,我们都不知道他在哪\N{\fs16}{\fs16}He's out there somewhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:22.60,0:44:26.47,正文,,0,0,0,,詹姆回不回来 我都他妈的完蛋了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Jaime or not, I'm truly fucked.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:29.54,0:44:31.68,正文,,0,0,0,,谁去告诉她呢?\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Who's going to tell her?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:33.08,0:44:35.41,正文,,0,0,0,,你觉得人们会喜欢吗?\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Do you think people will like it?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:35.45,0:44:37.95,正文,,0,0,0,,我觉得根本不会有人注意\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I don't think they will even notice it.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:37.98,0:44:40.45,正文,,0,0,0,,你说得对 又不是我的婚礼\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're right. It's not my wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:39.73,0:44:42.69,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(113,201)}雪伊{\b0}\N{\fs12}珊莎的侍女 小恶魔的情人
Dialogue: 0,0:44:41.95,0:44:43.42,正文,,0,0,0,,总之 看得出来\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Anyway, from what I can tell,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:43.45,0:44:45.62,正文,,0,0,0,,高庭的裁缝比君临的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}the dressmakers in Highgarden will be far superior
Dialogue: 0,0:44:45.66,0:44:47.22,正文,,0,0,0,,手艺要好得多\N{\fs16}{\fs16}to the ones in King's Landing.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:47.26,0:44:50.59,正文,,0,0,0,,我的婚礼上肯定不会用这么呆板的东西\N{\fs16}{\fs16}They'd never make me anything as dull as this for my wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:51.80,0:44:54.50,正文,,0,0,0,,洛拉斯喜欢绿色和金色的锦缎\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Loras likes green and gold brocade.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.53,0:44:56.40,正文,,0,0,0,,他肯定会喜欢的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I'm sure he does.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:57.87,0:44:59.80,正文,,0,0,0,,他们会同意我邀请我的家人吗？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Will they let me invite my family?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:59.84,0:45:02.24,正文,,0,0,0,,他们可没问我的意见\N{\fs16}{\fs16}They haven't asked my opinion.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:02.27,0:45:04.64,正文,,0,0,0,,但你觉得会不会呢？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But do you think they will?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:04.68,0:45:06.28,正文,,0,0,0,,不会\N{\fs16}{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:13.22,0:45:14.92,正文,,0,0,0,,珊莎小姐 提利昂大人想见您\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Lady Sansa, Lord Tyrion to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:14.95,0:45:17.79,正文,,0,0,0,,- 我要不要……  - 不好意思 小姐\N{\fs16}{\fs16}- Should I-- - I beg your pardon, my lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:17.82,0:45:20.19,正文,,0,0,0,,下午好 提利昂大人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Good afternoon, Lord Tyrion.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:20.23,0:45:22.76,正文,,0,0,0,,我正在为乔佛里国王的婚礼试礼服\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I was just trying on a gown for King Joffrey's wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:24.23,0:45:28.70,正文,,0,0,0,,恩 那会是场盛大的婚礼\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Yes, it should be quite a wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:28.73,0:45:31.14,正文,,0,0,0,,我有话要跟你说 珊莎小姐\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I need to speak with you, Lady Sansa.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:31.17,0:45:32.67,正文,,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:32.70,0:45:35.37,正文,,0,0,0,,单独说 如果可以的话\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Alone, if I may.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:35.41,0:45:37.11,正文,,0,0,0,,有什么话非得单独说？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Why do you need to speak to her alone?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.14,0:45:38.94,正文,,0,0,0,,雪伊\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Shae.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:38.98,0:45:40.75,正文,,0,0,0,,请原谅她 提利昂大人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Please excuse her, Lord Tyrion.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:40.78,0:45:42.28,正文,,0,0,0,,她不是本地人\N{\fs16}{\fs16}She's not from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:42.32,0:45:43.52,正文,,0,0,0,,但是我信任她\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But I trust her,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:43.55,0:45:45.82,正文,,0,0,0,,虽然她告诉我别相信她\N{\fs16}{\fs16}even though she tells me not to.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:47.49,0:45:51.32,正文,,0,0,0,,有时我们总是急着听到消息\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Sometimes we think we want to hear something
Dialogue: 0,0:45:51.36,0:45:54.43,正文,,0,0,0,,但往往在知道之后\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and it's only afterwards when it's too late
Dialogue: 0,0:45:54.46,0:45:57.23,正文,,0,0,0,,才明白还不如\N{\fs16}{\fs16}that we realize we wished we'd heard it
Dialogue: 0,0:45:57.26,0:45:59.40,正文,,0,0,0,,在一个完全不同的情境下听到它\N{\fs16}{\fs16}under entirely different circumstances.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:59.43,0:46:01.27,正文,,0,0,0,,没关系 真的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It's all right, really.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:04.80,0:46:07.04,正文,,0,0,0,,从哪说起呢?\N{\fs16}{\fs16}How to begin?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:09.61,0:46:12.18,正文,,0,0,0,,这--这--\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It's-- this--
Dialogue: 0,0:46:12.21,0:46:15.85,正文,,0,0,0,,这--这事很尴尬\N{\fs16}{\fs16}this-- this is awkward.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:17.88,0:46:19.92,正文,,0,0,0,,1000柄剑\N{\fs16}{\fs16}1000 blades
Dialogue: 0,0:46:19.95,0:46:23.02,正文,,0,0,0,,来自伊耿的手下败将\N{\fs16}{\fs16}taken from the hands of Aegon's fallen enemies,
Dialogue: 0,0:46:23.04,0:46:27.08,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(415,106)}培提尔·贝里席\N{\b0\fs12}“小指头” 赫伦堡公爵
Dialogue: 0,0:46:23.04,0:46:27.08,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(198,241)}瓦里斯{\b0}\N{\fs12} “八爪蜘蛛” 情报总管
Dialogue: 0,0:46:23.06,0:46:26.46,正文,,0,0,0,,在“黑死神”贝勒里恩的龙焰下锻造而成\N{\fs16}{\fs16}forged in the fiery breath of Balerion the Dread.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:26.49,0:46:29.23,正文,,0,0,0,,没有1000柄\N{\fs16}{\fs16}There aren't 1,000 blades.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:29.26,0:46:31.83,正文,,0,0,0,,甚至没有200柄\N{\fs16}{\fs16}There aren't even 200.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:31.87,0:46:33.37,正文,,0,0,0,,我数过\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I've counted.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:33.40,0:46:36.04,正文,,0,0,0,,哈 我相信你数过\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Ha, I'm sure you have.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:36.07,0:46:38.81,正文,,0,0,0,,丑陋老旧的东西\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Ugly old thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:38.84,0:46:41.94,正文,,0,0,0,,却有着独特的吸引力\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Yet it has a certain appeal.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:41.98,0:46:44.41,正文,,0,0,0,,真可惜诸多选择中\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The Lysa Arryn of chairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:44.45,0:46:47.21,正文,,0,0,0,,你不得不向莱莎·艾林这个第二选择妥协了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Shame you had to settle for your second choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:47.25,0:46:49.52,正文,,0,0,0,,言之尚早 我的朋友\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Early days, my friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:49.55,0:46:52.49,正文,,0,0,0,,我很荣幸 真的……\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It is flattering, really...
Dialogue: 0,0:46:53.79,0:46:56.46,正文,,0,0,0,,你看起来如此害怕\N{\fs16}{\fs16}you feeling such dread
Dialogue: 0,0:46:56.49,0:46:58.96,正文,,0,0,0,,看到我将要得偿所愿\N{\fs16}{\fs16}at the prospect of me getting what I want.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:58.99,0:47:01.80,正文,,0,0,0,,打败你从来都不是我的首要目标\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Thwarting you has never been my primary ambition,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:01.83,0:47:03.66,正文,,0,0,0,,我向你保证\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I promise you.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:03.70,0:47:07.10,正文,,0,0,0,,不过谁不想看到自己的朋友不时受挫呢？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Although who doesn't like to see their friends fail now and then?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:07.13,0:47:08.40,正文,,0,0,0,,说的没错\N{\fs16}{\fs16}You're so right.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:08.44,0:47:10.24,正文,,0,0,0,,比如\N{\fs16}{\fs16}For instance,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:10.27,0:47:11.97,正文,,0,0,0,,当我破坏了你\N{\fs16}{\fs16}when I thwarted your plan
Dialogue: 0,0:47:12.01,0:47:14.07,正文,,0,0,0,,把珊莎·史塔克交给提利尔家的计划时\N{\fs16}{\fs16}to give Sansa Stark to the Tyrells.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:14.11,0:47:16.21,正文,,0,0,0,,如果让我说实话\N{\fs16}{\fs16}If I'm going to be honest,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:16.24,0:47:18.11,正文,,0,0,0,,我确实明显地感觉到\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I did feel an unmistakable sense
Dialogue: 0,0:47:18.15,0:47:21.61,正文,,0,0,0,,一种愉悦之情\N{\fs16}{\fs16}of enjoyment there.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:21.65,0:47:24.25,正文,,0,0,0,,不过你的心腹\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But your confidant,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:24.29,0:47:27.75,正文,,0,0,0,,一直在向你报告我的计划的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}the one who fed you information about my plans,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:27.79,0:47:30.52,正文,,0,0,0,,你想要保护的那个\N{\fs16}{\fs16}the one you swore to protect...
Dialogue: 0,0:47:31.86,0:47:34.46,正文,,0,0,0,,你没有给她带来任何好处\N{\fs16}{\fs16}you didn't bring her any enjoyment.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:35.63,0:47:39.10,正文,,0,0,0,,她也没有给我带来什么好处\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And she didn't bring me any enjoyment.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:39.13,0:47:42.34,正文,,0,0,0,,她是我的失败投资\N{\fs16}{\fs16}She was a bad investment on my part.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:44.04,0:47:47.17,正文,,0,0,0,,幸运的是 我有个朋友\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Luckily, I have a friend
Dialogue: 0,0:47:47.21,0:47:49.58,正文,,0,0,0,,想要玩点新花样\N{\fs16}{\fs16}who wanted to try something new.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:49.61,0:47:53.11,正文,,0,0,0,,玩点大胆的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Something daring.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:53.15,0:47:56.95,正文,,0,0,0,,他很感谢我为他提供\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And he was so grateful to me for providing
Dialogue: 0,0:47:56.98,0:48:00.25,正文,,0,0,0,,新鲜的体验\N{\fs16}{\fs16}this fresh experience.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:04.32,0:48:07.13,正文,,0,0,0,,我为了王国做了我该做的事情\N{\fs16}{\fs16}I did what I did for the good of the realm.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:07.16,0:48:09.79,正文,,0,0,0,,王国？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The realm?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:09.83,0:48:12.23,正文,,0,0,0,,你知道王国本来是什么吗？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Do you know what the realm is?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:14.00,0:48:17.20,正文,,0,0,0,,只不过是数千柄剑融成的王座\N{\fs16}{\fs16}It's the thousand blades of Aegon's enemies.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:17.24,0:48:22.17,正文,,0,0,0,,只不过是一个反反复复讲给别人的故事\N{\fs16}{\fs16}A story we agree to tell each other over and over
Dialogue: 0,0:48:22.21,0:48:24.68,正文,,0,0,0,,直到我们自己都忘了这是个谎言\N{\fs16}{\fs16}till we forget that it's a lie.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:24.71,0:48:29.28,正文,,0,0,0,,但是除去谎言之外我们还剩什么呢？\N{\fs16}{\fs16}But what do we have left once we abandon the lie?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:29.31,0:48:31.25,正文,,0,0,0,,只有混乱\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Chaos.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:31.28,0:48:33.99,正文,,0,0,0,,一个慢慢吞噬我们所有人的深渊\N{\fs16}{\fs16}A gaping pit waiting to swallow us all.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:34.02,0:48:37.56,正文,,0,0,0,,混乱不是深渊\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Chaos isn't a pit.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:37.59,0:48:39.96,正文,,0,0,0,,混乱是个阶梯\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Chaos is a ladder.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:39.97,0:48:42.89,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(264,145)}乔佛里·拜拉席恩{\b0}\N{\fs12}铁王座上的王
Dialogue: 0,0:48:42.13,0:48:44.63,正文,,0,0,0,,试图攀爬的人大多失败了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Many who try to climb it fail
Dialogue: 0,0:48:44.66,0:48:47.10,正文,,0,0,0,,之后再也不敢尝试\N{\fs16}{\fs16}and never get to try again.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:48.20,0:48:50.77,正文,,0,0,0,,失败摧毁了他们\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The fall breaks them.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:53.86,0:48:56.82,人物介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(172,180)}萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:48:59.21,0:49:02.91,正文,,0,0,0,,还有的人本来有机会攀爬\N{\fs16}{\fs16}And some are given a chance to climb,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:02.95,0:49:05.41,正文,,0,0,0,,但他们拒绝了\N{\fs16}{\fs16}but they refuse.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:05.45,0:49:08.78,正文,,0,0,0,,他们紧紧依附于王国\N{\fs16}{\fs16}They cling to the realm
Dialogue: 0,0:49:08.82,0:49:10.82,正文,,0,0,0,,或诸神\N{\fs16}{\fs16}or the gods
Dialogue: 0,0:49:10.85,0:49:13.29,正文,,0,0,0,,甚或爱\N{\fs16}{\fs16}or love.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:13.32,0:49:15.56,正文,,0,0,0,,这些都是幻觉\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Illusions.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:16.76,0:49:19.53,正文,,0,0,0,,只有那阶梯才是真实的\N{\fs16}{\fs16}Only the ladder is real.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:19.56,0:49:22.86,正文,,0,0,0,,努力攀爬才是一切\N{\fs16}{\fs16}The climb is all there is.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:01.05,0:53:15.66,片头介绍,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(320,120)\fs18\c&HFFFFFF&\b1}衣柜字幕组出品
