[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.2.2012.322
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: Game of Thrones S06E03
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 衣柜
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 衣柜
Script Updated By: 衣柜
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 720
PlayResY: 404
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Titles,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles_L,Microsoft YaHei,24,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Character_L,Microsoft YaHei,28,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,4,10,10,10,1
Style: Character_B,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Author,Microsoft YaHei,16,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,1,10,10,10,1
Style: QR code - BG,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000019FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,400,400,0,0,1,0,0,5,0,0,0,1
Style: QR code - code,Arial,20,&H00000000,&H000019FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,200,200,0,0,1,0,0,5,0,0,0,1
Style: Titles - 1,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,5,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles - 2,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Titles - 3 -,Microsoft YaHei,20,&H0001031B,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000429,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Subtitle,Microsoft YaHei,26,&H00C1DFED,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.50,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(1000,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx89\fscy89\p1\move(298,257,298,257,120,1400)}m -11 -35 l -11 39 l 63 39 l 63 -35{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.50,Titles - 2,,0,0,0,,{\fad(1000,500)\move(340,280,340,280,300,1400)\p1\fscx40\fscy40}m -86 -116 b -89 -117 -89 -117 -95 -119 l -97 -115 l -85 -105 l -116 -102 b -116 -100 -116 -98 -116 -97 l -108 -91 l -96 -91 l -116 -63 l -105 -69 l -96 -47 l -74 -63 l -77 -69 l -91 -63 l -91 -77 l -88 -80 l -66 -49 l -46 -63 l -58 -66 l -66 -74 l -49 -80 l -60 -91 l -74 -83 l -80 -91 l -77 -94 l -46 -94 l -52 -108 l -71 -105 b -69 -107 -67 -110 -66 -113 m -31 -119.875 l -33 -119 b -34 -113 -36 -107 -38 -102 l -46 -97 b -42 -93 -38 -89 -35 -85 l -44 -63 b -41 -64 -38 -65 -35 -66 l -35 -52 l -33 -47 l -27 -55 l -27 -69 l -21 -63 l -21 -69 l -19 -72 l -27 -88 l -21 -94 l -21 -99 l -27 -102 l -27 -102 l -30 -116 m -21 -113 l -21 -105 l -21 -99 l -21 -94 l -19 -85 l -19 -66 l -21 -49 l -19 -47 l -7 -52 l 26 -52 l 18 -66 l -7 -63 l -5 -69 l 6 -69 l 18 -69 l 20 -99 l -7 -94 l -7 -83 l 6 -85 l 6 -80 l -7 -77 l -7 -94 l -10 -99 l 23 -102 l 18 -116 l -10 -110 l -19 -116 m -105 -38 l -116 -41 l -110 -13 l -102 -19 l -102 -30 l -63 -33 l -55 -19 l -46 -41 l -49 -44 m -88 -33 l -91 -24 l -99 -24 l -105 -16 l -102 -13 l -85 -16 l -85 -10 l -94 -8 l -85 -16 l -102 -13 l -108 1 l -88 1 l -88 4 l -116 6 l -116 9 l -110 15 l -88 15 l -85 26 l -77 23 l -74 15 l -52 15 l -49 15 l -52 4 l -74 6 l -71 1 l -55 -2 l -60 -13 l -74 -10 l -74 -13 l -55 -16 l -63 -24 l -74 -24 l -80 -33 m -46 -41 l -38 -2 l -41 23 l -38 26 l 1 20 l 15 26 l 18 23 l 18 -8 l 20 -41 l 20 -44 l -24 -38 l -35 -41 l -35 -30 l -13 -30 l -19 -21 l -33 -19 l -33 -13 l -21 -13 l -33 6 l -33 15 l -13 -5 l -13 1 l -21 6 l -13 12 l -2 9 l -2 -8 l 9 -10 l 12 -19 l 1 -21 l -2 -27 l 9 -33 l 6 -16 l 6 -10 l 9 12 l -2 9 l -30 12 l -30 12 l -27 -2 l -27 -2 l -30 -16 l -27 -21 l -35 -41 m -126 -127 l -130 -130 l -129 38 l 34 37 l 35 -135 l -130 -131 l -127 -127 l 30 -129 l 31 32 l -124 34
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.50,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(386,224.2)\fad(1000,500)\b0\fs18\bord1} 最专业冰火字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.50,Titles - 1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(384,165.2)\fad(1000,500)}\N{\fs20}{\fs32.001\c&HFFFFFF&\b1}诚意奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:12.50,Titles - 1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(385,197.2)\fad(1000,500)\b000}专注GOT剧集{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.20,0:00:14.00,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(393.25,100.022)\fad(300,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}喵羽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.25,0:00:16.30,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.875,313.122)\fad(500,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}SaintHS
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.45,0:00:18.55,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(137.875,110.367)\fad(500,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}依依eva
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.55,0:00:29.95,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(176.708,104.159)\fad(500,500)}翻译{\fs24} {\b1}埃尔夫歪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.75,0:00:32.30,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(401.209,112.666)\fad(500,500)}校对{\fs24} {\b1}屈畅   赵琳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.20,0:00:35.90,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(158.417,137.016)\fad(500,500)}校对{\fs24} {\b1}运气哥
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:41.20,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(139.125,287.792)\fad(500,500)}后期{\fs24} {\b1}SerGawen@huiji.wiki
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.60,0:00:53.40,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(154,140.961)\fad(500,500)}监制{\fs24} {\b1}临冬城的狮子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.10,0:00:50.50,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(418.792,140.97)\fad(500,500)}监制{\fs24} {\b1}北落师门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.50,0:01:10.50,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(478.917,112.893)\fad(500,500)}策划{\fs24} {\b1}衣柜军团
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.10,0:01:18.10,Author,,0,0,0,,{\pos(120.792,141.05)\fad(500,500)}特别顾问{\fs24} {\b1}屈畅(ccxx)@史诗图书
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.26,0:00:23.66,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\t(\fscx150\fscy150,150)\p1\move(277,278,289,305,1,4381)}m -15 -18 l -15 -17 l -14 -16 l -13 -16 l -11 -15 l -6 -16 b -8 -15 -8 -15 -11 -13 l -14 -9 l -12 -9 l -10 -8 l -5 -9 b -4 -8 -2 -6 6 -7 l 7 -7 l 3 -8 l 1 -10 b 2 -14 5 -17 3 -19 l 2 -21 l 5 -21 l 3 -22 l 0 -23 l 0 -24 l 4 -26 l 8 -23 l 16 -21 b 20 -23 25 -24 28 -36 l 27 -35 b 26 -35 26 -35 22 -37 b 25 -34 25 -32 24 -32 l 17 -34 l 23 -30 b 22 -29 20 -27 19 -29 l 14 -33 b 15 -31 17 -29 16 -26 b 13 -25 11 -24 7 -27 l 11 -31 l 10 -36 b 10 -32 11 -32 8 -30 b 7 -30 5 -29 4 -29 b 3 -30 2 -31 0 -34 l 3 -28 l -1 -27 l -5 -30 l -7 -34 l -6 -30 l -3 -27 l -8 -28 l -15 -32 l -10 -27 l -6 -25 l -4 -25 l -7 -23 l -10 -21 l -3 -21 l -5 -20 l -7 -21 l -7 -22 l -8 -22 l -13 -19{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.26,0:00:23.66,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\pos(301.714,255.889)\fad(300,500)\frx360\t(20,200,\frx0)\fs25\b1}君临{\fs12\b0} King's Landing
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.31,0:00:27.73,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,50)\move(420,300,420,280)\fs25\p1}m -17 -23 l -10 -8 l -19 -15 l -12 -1 l -24 -9 l -14 6 l -25 1 l -16 9 l -13 17 l -15 24 l 18 24 l 13 19 l 15 12 l 22 4 l 13 10 l 25 -3 l 20 0 l 14 3 l 17 -3 l 22 -11 l 13 -4 l 18 -21 l 13 -15 l 10 -13 l 11 -26 l 7 -16 l 7 -28 l 3 -16 l 0 -32 l -2 -15 l -6 -22 l -8 -28 l -8 -11{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.31,0:00:27.73,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(380,230,380,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}红堡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.31,0:00:27.73,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(425,250,425,235)\fad(300,500)\fs12\b0} Red Keep
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.31,0:00:35.31,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(380,260,380,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}派
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.50,0:00:35.31,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(405,260,405,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}克
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.70,0:00:35.31,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(430,260,430,240)\fad(300,500)\fs28\b1}城
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.31,0:00:35.31,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(460,260,460,240)\fad(300,500)\fs12\b0}Pyke
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.50,0:00:47.01,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(334.667,176.333)\fad(1000,1000)\frx25\fs28\b1\frz-22\t(0,1800,\frz-0)}临冬城{\fs12\b0}\NWinterfell
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.59,0:01:38.59,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(338,265)\fad(1250,1000)\frx50\t(1200,2500,\frx0)\fs28} {\b1}弥林\N{\fs12\b0}Meereen
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.32,0:01:13.50,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\pos(337.5,157.549)\fad(500,500)\fs12.746} 联合出品
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.32,0:01:13.50,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\fad(500,500)\fs24} 史诗图书 | 冰火中文维基 | 黑城堡奇幻微刊\N{\fs20}\N{\fs20}\N{\fs20}{\fs12}\N{\fs20}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.32,0:01:13.50,Titles,,0,0,180,,{\pos(337.5,212.563)\fad(500,500)\fs14.997} Epic Books         ASOIAF.huiji.wiki          Heichengbao
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.20,0:01:15.50,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(516.25,319.545)\fad(500,500)} {\fs24\b1} 史诗图书 {\fs18\b0} 正统奇幻的圣殿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.52,0:01:07.02,Titles,,0,30,200,,{\fad(100,50)\frx75\t(0,3500,\frx-0)\fs28} {\b1}绝境长城{\fs12\b0} the Wall
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.43,0:01:26.22,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(355,250,370,250)\fs28\b1}维斯·多斯拉克
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.43,0:01:26.22,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\move(365,260,355,260)\fad(100,1000)\fs12\b0} Vaes Dothrak
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.30,0:01:00.28,Titles,,0,0,100,,{\fs25\fad(100,1000)} {\b0} 最专业的华语冰火资料站：        冰与火之歌{\b0\fs20}中文维基{\b0}\N{\fs20}\N{\fs20\c&HFFFFFF&}http://asoiaf.huiji.wiki
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.50,0:01:00.28,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(100,1000)\pos(410,285)\fs25\c&HC1DFED&} {\b1\p1\fscx60\fscy60}m 31 -6 l -21 40 l 34 22 m 29 -8 l -3 -12 l -24 40{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.28,0:01:02.38,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(516.25,119.545)\fad(500,500)} {\fs24\b1} 技术支持 {\fs18\b0}灰机T.R.A.N.S.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.60,0:01:38.80,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(462,310)\fad(500,500)\fs14} {\c&HC1DFED&}根据长篇小说
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.60,0:01:38.80,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(552,334)\fad(500,500)} {\fs24}《{\b1}冰与火之歌{\b0}》{\fs14} 改编
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.60,0:01:38.80,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(625,358)\fad(500,500)} {\fs12} 原著 {\fs20} 乔治·R·R·马丁
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.32,0:01:49.63,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(350,294.067)\fad(300,500)\fs56.267\fn宋体\b1}权力的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.32,0:01:49.63,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(348.667,322)\fad(300,500)\c&HFFFFFF&\b1\fs22}衣柜字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(428,118.44)\fad(500,500)\p1}m -18.625 0 l -18.625 0 l 281.25 0 l 281.25 1.125 l -18.625 1.125{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(231.125,202.841)\p1\fscx35\fscy35}m -86 -116 b -89 -117 -89 -117 -95 -119 l -97 -115 l -85 -105 l -116 -102 b -116 -100 -116 -98 -116 -97 l -108 -91 l -96 -91 l -116 -63 l -105 -69 l -96 -47 l -74 -63 l -77 -69 l -91 -63 l -91 -77 l -88 -80 l -66 -49 l -46 -63 l -58 -66 l -66 -74 l -49 -80 l -60 -91 l -74 -83 l -80 -91 l -77 -94 l -46 -94 l -52 -108 l -71 -105 b -69 -107 -67 -110 -66 -113 m -31 -119.875 l -33 -119 b -34 -113 -36 -107 -38 -102 l -46 -97 b -42 -93 -38 -89 -35 -85 l -44 -63 b -41 -64 -38 -65 -35 -66 l -35 -52 l -33 -47 l -27 -55 l -27 -69 l -21 -63 l -21 -69 l -19 -72 l -27 -88 l -21 -94 l -21 -99 l -27 -102 l -27 -102 l -30 -116 m -21 -113 l -21 -105 l -21 -99 l -21 -94 l -19 -85 l -19 -66 l -21 -49 l -19 -47 l -7 -52 l 26 -52 l 18 -66 l -7 -63 l -5 -69 l 6 -69 l 18 -69 l 20 -99 l -7 -94 l -7 -83 l 6 -85 l 6 -80 l -7 -77 l -7 -94 l -10 -99 l 23 -102 l 18 -116 l -10 -110 l -19 -116 m -105 -38 l -116 -41 l -110 -13 l -102 -19 l -102 -30 l -63 -33 l -55 -19 l -46 -41 l -49 -44 m -88 -33 l -91 -24 l -99 -24 l -105 -16 l -102 -13 l -85 -16 l -85 -10 l -94 -8 l -85 -16 l -102 -13 l -108 1 l -88 1 l -88 4 l -116 6 l -116 9 l -110 15 l -88 15 l -85 26 l -77 23 l -74 15 l -52 15 l -49 15 l -52 4 l -74 6 l -71 1 l -55 -2 l -60 -13 l -74 -10 l -74 -13 l -55 -16 l -63 -24 l -74 -24 l -80 -33 m -46 -41 l -38 -2 l -41 23 l -38 26 l 1 20 l 15 26 l 18 23 l 18 -8 l 20 -41 l 20 -44 l -24 -38 l -35 -41 l -35 -30 l -13 -30 l -19 -21 l -33 -19 l -33 -13 l -21 -13 l -33 6 l -33 15 l -13 -5 l -13 1 l -21 6 l -13 12 l -2 9 l -2 -8 l 9 -10 l 12 -19 l 1 -21 l -2 -27 l 9 -33 l 6 -16 l 6 -10 l 9 12 l -2 9 l -30 12 l -30 12 l -27 -2 l -27 -2 l -30 -16 l -27 -21 l -35 -41 m -126 -127 l -130 -130 l -129 38 l 34 37 l 35 -135 l -130 -131 l -127 -127 l 30 -129 l 31 32 l -124 34{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(293,112.813)\fad(500,500)\b1}协力制作
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(293,157.827)\fad(500,500)}史诗图书\N{\fs16}Epic Books
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(405.5,157.827)\fad(500,500)}冰火中文维基\N{\fs16}ASOIAF.huiji.wiki
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.70,0:01:55.26,Titles,,0,0,0,,{\pos(518,157.827)\fad(500,500)}黑城堡\N{\fs16}EPICASTLE
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.60,0:01:55.20,Titles_L,,260,0,163,,{\pos(310,300)\fad(500,500)\fs16\b0}第三集
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.60,0:01:55.20,Titles_L,,300,0,132,,{\pos(310,340)\fad(500,500)}破誓者\N{\fs16\b0}Oathbreaker
Dialogue: 0,0:50:50.00,0:52:08.00,Titles,,0,0,20,,{\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(360,390)}衣柜字幕组出品
Dialogue: 0,0:50:50.00,0:52:08.00,Titles,,0,0,40,,{\be1\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(357,372)}本集关键字：{\c&H5650F3\b0}极乐塔之战  欧莎  多希卡林
Dialogue: 0,0:50:50.00,0:52:08.00,Titles,,0,0,335,,{\bord1\c&HFFFFFF&\fs18\b1\pos(360,40)}剧情没看懂？ 典故不清楚？{\b0}\N维基新站网址：{\c&H00FF40}HTTP://AsoIaF.HuiJi.WiKi
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.50,0:02:15.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(157,278)\fad(300,500)}戴佛斯·席渥斯\N{\b0\fs12}洋葱骑士
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.30,0:02:28.30,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(128,262)\fad(300,500)}琼恩·雪诺\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.00,0:03:13.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(275,244)\fad(300,500)}梅丽珊卓\N{\b0\fs12}红袍祭祀
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.50,0:05:59.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(516,254)\fad(300,500)}忧郁的艾迪\N{\b0\fs12}守夜人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.70,0:06:48.70,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(63,312)\fad(300,500)}托蒙德\N{\b0\fs12}野人头领
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.00,0:07:59.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(236,269)\fad(300,500)}吉莉\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.01,0:08:16.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(357,312)\fad(300,500)}山姆威尔·塔利\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.00,0:12:20.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(85,262)\fad(300,500)}布兰·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.00,0:12:20.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(589,284)\fad(300,500)}三眼乌鸦\N{\b0\fs12}先知
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.19,0:18:22.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(109,211)\fad(300,500)}丹妮莉丝·坦格利安\N{\b0\fs12}龙之母
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.00,0:22:06.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(323,296)\fad(300,500)}瓦里斯\N{\b0\fs12}“八爪蜘蛛”
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.00,0:25:46.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(585,296)\fad(300,500)}提利昂·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}“小恶魔”
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.50,0:25:49.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(238,214)\fad(300,500)}灰虫子\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.50,0:25:49.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(524,227)\fad(300,500)}弥桑黛
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.70,0:29:12.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(315,207)\fad(100,100)}科本\N{\b0\fs12}学士
Dialogue: 0,0:30:17.00,0:30:19.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(135,254)\fad(100,100)}劳勃·斯壮\N{\b0\fs12}御林铁卫
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.50,0:30:27.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(607,274)\fad(100,100)}詹姆·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.00,0:30:30.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(497,274)\fad(100,100)}瑟曦·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}太后
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.00,0:31:50.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(208,241)\fad(100,100)}派席尔\N{\b0\fs12}学士
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.00,0:31:53.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(628,274)\fad(100,100)}奥莲娜·雷德温\N{\b0\fs12}荆棘女王
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.30,0:32:14.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(568,254)\fad(100,100)}梅斯·提利尔\N{\b0\fs12}王后之父
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.00,0:32:16.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(140,267)\fad(100,100)}凯冯·兰尼斯特\N{\b0\fs12}国王之手
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.00,0:34:21.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(388,304)\fad(300,500)}大麻雀\N{\b0\fs12}总主教
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.00,0:34:28.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(481,248)\fad(300,500)}拖曼·拜拉席恩一世\N{\b0\fs12}国王
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.00,0:38:05.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(508,241)\fad(300,500)}艾莉亚·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}无名之辈
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.00,0:41:44.10,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(600,216)\fad(300,500)}贾昆·赫加尔\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:43:08.50,0:43:11.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(108,250)\fad(300,500)}拉姆斯·波顿\N{\b0\fs12}临冬城城主
Dialogue: 0,0:43:12.00,0:43:16.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(209,220)\fad(300,500)}琼恩·安柏\N{\b0\fs12}小琼恩
Dialogue: 0,0:45:18.00,0:45:20.50,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(228,162)\fad(300,500)}欧莎\N{\b0\fs12}野人
Dialogue: 0,0:45:50.00,0:45:53.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(567,272)\fad(300,500)}瑞肯·史塔克\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:47:24.00,0:47:26.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(288,291)\fad(300,500)}波文·马尔锡\N{\b0\fs12}总务长
Dialogue: 0,0:47:29.00,0:47:32.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(288,241)\fad(300,500)}奥赛尔·亚威克\N{\b0\fs12}首席工匠
Dialogue: 0,0:47:46.00,0:47:49.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(313,247)\fad(300,500)}艾里沙·索恩\N{\b0\fs12}守夜人教头
Dialogue: 0,0:48:44.00,0:48:47.00,Character_B,,0,0,0,,{\pos(288,291)\fad(300,500)}奥利\N{\b0\fs12}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.70,0:03:06.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,慢点 慢点\N{\fs16}Easy, easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.24,0:03:07.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,慢点\N{\fs16}Easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.82,0:03:16.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你都记得什么？\N{\fs16}What do you remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.29,0:03:25.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们捅了我\N{\fs16}They stabbed me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.07,0:03:31.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奥利……\N{\fs16}Olly...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.54,0:03:36.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他一刀扎进我的心脏\N{\fs16}he put a knife in my heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.84,0:03:44.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我应该死了\N{\fs16}I shouldn't be here.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.05,0:03:48.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,红袍女士令你死而复生\N{\fs16}The lady brought you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.62,0:03:52.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,后来呢 他们捅了你之后\N{\fs16}Afterwards, after they stabbed you,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.46,0:03:54.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你死之后 去了什么地方？\N{\fs16}after you died, where did you go?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.72,0:03:56.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,看到了什么？\N{\fs16}What did you see?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.10,0:04:02.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没有\N{\fs16}Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.84,0:04:07.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,什么都没有\N{\fs16}There was nothing at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.94,0:04:14.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,真主带你回来必有原因\N{\fs16}The Lord let you come back for a reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.71,0:04:19.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,史坦尼斯并非预言中的王子\N{\fs16}Stannis was not the prince who was promised,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.45,0:04:21.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但总有人是\N{\fs16}but someone has to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.62,0:04:27.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,能让我俩单独待会儿么？\N{\fs16}Could you give us a moment?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.31,0:04:50.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你死了\N{\fs16}You were dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.98,0:04:52.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,现在又活了\N{\fs16}And now you're not.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.15,0:04:58.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,要我看 这件事疯狂到了极点\N{\fs16}That's completely fucking mad, seems to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.12,0:05:00.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我没法想象你自己怎么看\N{\fs16}I can only imagine how it seems to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.89,0:05:05.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我做了自认为正确的事\N{\fs16}I did what I thought was right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.63,0:05:09.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,结果被人谋害\N{\fs16}And I got murdered for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.47,0:05:12.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,现在我又复活了\N{\fs16}And now I'm back.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.80,0:05:14.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,为什么？\N{\fs16}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.30,0:05:15.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不知道\N{\fs16}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.01,0:05:18.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,或许我们永远不会知道\N{\fs16}Maybe we'll never know.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.51,0:05:20.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但这重要吗？\N{\fs16}What does it matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.68,0:05:24.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你继续前行\N{\fs16}You go on.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.05,0:05:28.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只要一息尚存 就去战斗\N{\fs16}You fight for as long as you can.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.65,0:05:31.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,尽可能摆平这些破事\N{\fs16}You clean up as much of the shit as you can.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.76,0:05:34.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不知道该怎么做\N{\fs16}I don't know how to do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.43,0:05:38.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我以为自己知道 可……\N{\fs16}I thought I did, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.27,0:05:44.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,可我失败了\N{\fs16}I failed.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.90,0:05:49.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很好\N{\fs16}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.27,0:05:50.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不妨多失败几次\N{\fs16}Now go fail again.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.26,0:06:49.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们以为你是神\N{\fs16}They think you're some kind of god.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.63,0:06:52.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所以才会死而复生\N{\fs16}The man who returned from the dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.54,0:06:54.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不是神\N{\fs16}I'm not a god.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.94,0:06:56.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\fs16}I know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.48,0:07:00.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我看了你的鸡鸡\N{\fs16}I saw your pecker.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.51,0:07:03.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,神的鸡鸡哪能那么小？\N{\fs16}What kind of god would have a pecker that small?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.17,0:07:31.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的眼睛还是棕色\N{\fs16}Your eyes are still brown.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.84,0:07:33.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但你还是你吗？\N{\fs16}Is that still you in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.71,0:07:35.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,应该还是\N{\fs16}I think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.15,0:07:40.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你得等等才能烧掉我了\N{\fs16}Hold off on burning my body for now.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.19,0:07:45.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,真好笑\N{\fs16}That's funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.32,0:07:49.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你确定你还是你？\N{\fs16}You sure that's still you in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.72,0:08:22.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你还好吗？\N{\fs16}You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.76,0:08:25.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好 好 我没事\N{\fs16}Yes. Yes, I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.43,0:08:32.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我有没有告诉过你 我曾以为大洋念做“扬”\N{\fs16}Did I ever tell you I used to think the sea was called the see
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.27,0:08:35.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为一眼望去全是水波扬起？\N{\fs16}because it was nothing but water as far as the eye could see?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.30,0:08:36.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没有吧\N{\fs16}I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.71,0:08:39.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,洋 扬\N{\fs16}Sea, see.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.21,0:08:42.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,它们写法不同 发音却一样\N{\fs16}They're spelled different, but they sound the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.41,0:08:45.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对 是啊\N{\fs16}Yeah, they do.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.21,0:08:48.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,当然 这是在我识字之前的事了\N{\fs16}It was before I learned how to read, obviously.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.39,0:08:54.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,山姆 你是不是病了？\N{\fs16}Sam, are you going to be sick?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.21,0:09:11.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,坚持一下 很快就到南方了\N{\fs16}Won't be long. We'll be in the south soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.04,0:09:14.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,想想能看到旧镇我就激动\N{\fs16}I'm excited to see Oldtown.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.18,0:09:19.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,船长说旧镇是维斯特洛最美的城市\N{\fs16}Captain says it's the most beautiful city in Westeros.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.68,0:09:23.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你又想吐？\N{\fs16}Are you going to vomit again?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.29,0:09:25.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不不不 只是……\N{\fs16}No. No, no, no. I'm...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.69,0:09:29.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,学城不准女人进\N{\fs16}The Citadel doesn't admit women.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.89,0:09:32.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你和小山姆不能住在那儿\N{\fs16}There won't be a place for you there or for Little Sam.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.06,0:09:36.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,黑城堡也不准女人进 我不也住了很久？\N{\fs16}I stayed at Castle Black. There's no women allowed there.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.60,0:09:38.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,学城跟黑城堡不一样\N{\fs16}The Citadel isn't Castle Black.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.77,0:09:43.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那儿没有琼恩·雪诺或伊蒙学士帮我行方便\N{\fs16}I don't have a Jon Snow or Maester Aemon to help me bend the rules.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.17,0:09:47.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那我住旧镇好了\N{\fs16}I'll stay in Oldtown, then.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.11,0:09:48.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你一个人？\N{\fs16}By yourself?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.88,0:09:50.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,带个孩子 身无分文？\N{\fs16}With a baby and no money?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.85,0:09:53.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不去旧镇的话\N{\fs16}So if we're not going to Oldtown,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.05,0:09:55.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你要带我去哪儿？\N{\fs16}where are you taking me?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.62,0:09:58.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去我家\N{\fs16}To my home.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.06,0:10:00.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,角陵\N{\fs16}Horn Hill.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.49,0:10:04.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我爹……算了 别指望他了\N{\fs16}My father's... well, my father,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.99,0:10:08.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不过我妈心肠很好 我妹妹人也不错\N{\fs16}but my mother's a kind woman and my sister's lovely.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.67,0:10:11.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她们会照顾你们母子\N{\fs16}They'll take care of you both.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.64,0:10:14.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,“不管你去哪儿 我都跟你一起”\N{\fs16}"Wherever you go, I go, too."
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.84,0:10:16.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这可是你说的\N{\fs16}That's what you said.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.96,0:10:36.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我这么说 是因为我希望你和小山姆平安\N{\fs16}I said that because I want you and Little Sam to be safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.33,0:10:38.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是我唯一的心愿\N{\fs16}That's all I want...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.70,0:10:42.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果我能当上学士 到时候就能辅助琼恩\N{\fs16}to become a maester so I can help Jon when the time comes
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.33,0:10:43.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们也就安全了\N{\fs16}so you'll be safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.07,0:10:45.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你要帮我们 还要帮世界上其他的……\N{\fs16}Us and everyone else in the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.77,0:10:47.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我才不在乎其他人\N{\fs16}I don't care about them.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.00,0:10:51.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好吧 我在乎 但不是特别在乎\N{\fs16}Well, no, I do, but I don't really.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.11,0:10:55.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我在乎的是你和他\N{\fs16}I care about you and him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.71,0:10:59.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我知道 山姆\N{\fs16}I know that, Sam.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.98,0:11:02.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他也知道\N{\fs16}And he does, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.42,0:11:07.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只有你真正在乎我们\N{\fs16}You're the only one who ever has.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.10,0:11:18.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果你觉得这么做最好\N{\fs16}If you think it's for the best,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.80,0:11:21.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们就听你的\N{\fs16}we trust you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.54,0:11:24.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我宁可你用东西砸我 然后跑掉\N{\fs16}I'd feel better if you threw something at me and stormed off.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.54,0:11:28.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我绝不会对我孩子的爹那么做\N{\fs16}I'd never do that to the father of my son.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.60,0:12:28.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那是我父亲\N{\fs16}That's my father.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.20,0:12:30.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他旁边是霍兰·黎德\N{\fs16}The man beside him is Howland Reed,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.71,0:12:32.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,梅拉的父亲\N{\fs16}Meera's father.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.92,0:12:45.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,亚瑟·戴恩爵士\N{\fs16}Ser Arthur Dayne.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.89,0:12:48.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,拂晓神剑\N{\fs16}The Sword of the Morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.12,0:12:50.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,父亲说亚瑟·戴恩是他见过最强的剑士\N{\fs16}Father said he was the best swordsman he ever saw.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.27,0:13:07.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,史塔克大人\N{\fs16}Lord Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.14,0:13:10.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我在三叉戟河上没见到你们\N{\fs16}I looked for you on the Trident.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.45,0:13:12.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们不在那里\N{\fs16}We weren't there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.51,0:13:14.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们在的话\N{\fs16}Your friend the usurper
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.18,0:13:17.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的篡夺者朋友就该入土了\N{\fs16}would lie beneath the ground if we had been.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.25,0:13:19.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,疯王已死\N{\fs16}The Mad King is dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.39,0:13:21.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,入土的则是雷加\N{\fs16}Rhaegar lies beneath the ground.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.56,0:13:23.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们为何不去守护你们的王子？\N{\fs16}Why weren't you there to protect your prince?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.06,0:13:25.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,王子命我们在此守护\N{\fs16}Our prince wanted us here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.64,0:13:35.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我妹妹呢？\N{\fs16}Where's my sister?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.84,0:13:40.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在未来的战争中 祝你们好运\N{\fs16}I wish you good fortune in the wars to come.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.62,0:13:50.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一切就从这里开始吧\N{\fs16}And now it begins.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.66,0:13:56.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不对\N{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.83,0:13:58.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一切将在这里结束\N{\fs16}Now it ends.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.92,0:15:37.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他比我父亲强\N{\fs16}He's better than my father.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.06,0:15:39.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,强得多\N{\fs16}Far better.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.70,0:15:46.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我父亲打败了他\N{\fs16}But Father beat him.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.77,0:15:48.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,真的？\N{\fs16}Did he?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.94,0:15:50.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我知道是真的\N{\fs16}I know he did.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.01,0:15:52.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这故事我都听一千遍了\N{\fs16}Heard the story a thousand times.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.76,0:16:12.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他在背后捅刀\N{\fs16}He stabbed him in the back.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.62,0:16:33.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谁在塔里？\N{\fs16}What's in the tower?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.45,0:16:35.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,今天看得差不多了\N{\fs16}That's enough for one day.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.25,0:16:36.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,改天继续\N{\fs16}We'll visit again another time.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.05,0:16:39.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 我只想看看他去了哪里  - 该走了\N{\fs16}- I want to see where he's going. - Time to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.19,0:16:42.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,父亲！\N{\fs16}Father!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.82,0:17:10.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你为何这么做？\N{\fs16}Why did you do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.59,0:17:12.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,带我回去那里 我要回去\N{\fs16}Take me back there. I want to go back.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.75,0:17:14.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不行\N{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.26,0:17:18.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 他听到我叫他了  - 也许吧\N{\fs16}- He heard me. - Maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.73,0:17:22.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 也许他只是听到了风声 - 他听到我了\N{\fs16}- Maybe he heard the wind. - He heard me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.13,0:17:25.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,过去已成过去 一切都已盖棺定论\N{\fs16}The past is already written. The ink is dry.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.23,0:17:27.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谁在塔里？\N{\fs16}What's in that tower?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.64,0:17:28.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我要回去看看\N{\fs16}I want to go back there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.07,0:17:31.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我告诉过你无数次\N{\fs16}I've told you many times, stay too long
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.94,0:17:34.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,在不属于你的时空停留过久 就回不来了\N{\fs16}where you don't belong and you will never return.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.48,0:17:36.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我干嘛回来？\N{\fs16}Why do I want to return?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.38,0:17:38.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就为继续当个残废？\N{\fs16}So I can be a cripple again?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.25,0:17:40.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,跟长在树里的老家伙闲扯淡？\N{\fs16}So I can talk to an old man in a tree?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.78,0:17:42.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你以为我愿意在这里坐上一千年\N{\fs16}You think I wanted to sit here for 1,000 years
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.92,0:17:44.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,极目远眺这个世界\N{\fs16}watching the world from a distance
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.89,0:17:46.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,任由树根长进我的身体？\N{\fs16}as the roots grew through me?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.39,0:17:48.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那你到底为什么？\N{\fs16}So why did you?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.23,0:17:50.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为我在等你\N{\fs16}I was waiting for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.06,0:17:52.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我可不想变成你这样\N{\fs16}I don't want to be you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.48,0:17:55.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不怪你\N{\fs16}I don't blame you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.90,0:17:59.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不会永远待在这儿\N{\fs16}You won't be here forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.24,0:18:01.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不会变成树里的老家伙\N{\fs16}You won't be an old man in a tree.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.94,0:18:04.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但离开之前\N{\fs16}But before you leave,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.47,0:18:07.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你必须学习\N{\fs16}you must learn.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.54,0:18:09.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,学什么？\N{\fs16}Learn what?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.48,0:18:12.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一切\N{\fs16}Everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.87,0:18:36.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,嘿 伟大的卡丽熙 动动你的屁股\N{\fs16}Hey, Great Khaleesi. Move your ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.64,0:19:14.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,欢迎回家 卡丽熙\N{\fs16}Welcome home, Khaleesi.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.96,0:19:40.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,退下\N{\fs16}Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.21,0:19:52.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们干嘛？！\N{\fs16}What are you doing?!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.34,0:19:53.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,把你们的手拿开！\N{\fs16}Take your hands off me!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.81,0:19:55.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我要砍你们的头！\N{\fs16}I will have your heads!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.70,0:20:18.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你犯了个大错\N{\fs16}You have made a mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.75,0:20:20.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你会后悔的\N{\fs16}One you will regret.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.85,0:20:22.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是伟大卡奥的妻子\N{\fs16}I am the wife of the Great Khal.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.64,0:20:24.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们知道你是谁\N{\fs16}We know who you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.09,0:20:27.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我还记得你当众吃下马心\N{\fs16}I remember you eating the stallion's heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.18,0:20:33.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,卓戈卡奥死后 你为什么不回来？\N{\fs16}Why didn't you come to us after Khal Drogo died?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.30,0:20:35.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为我是风暴降生丹妮莉丝\N{\fs16}Because I am Daenerys Stormborn,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.41,0:20:36.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,解放者\N{\fs16}the Breaker of Chains,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.95,0:20:39.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,弥林女王 龙之母\N{\fs16}the Queen of Meereen and the Mother of Dragons.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.22,0:20:41.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不会在这里陪你们终老\N{\fs16}My place is not here with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.25,0:20:43.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是伟大卡奥的妻子\N{\fs16}You were the wife of the Great Khal.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.74,0:20:48.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你以为自己会陪在他身边 陪他征服世界\N{\fs16}You thought he would conquer the world with you at his side.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.60,0:20:50.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他却死了\N{\fs16}He didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.43,0:20:53.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我也曾是伟大卡奥的妻子\N{\fs16}I was the wife of the Great Khal.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.01,0:20:55.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,萨沃卡奥\N{\fs16}Khal Savo
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.84,0:21:01.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我也以为自己会陪在他身边 陪他征服世界\N{\fs16}I thought he would conquer the world with me at his side.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.63,0:21:05.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你还太年轻\N{\fs16}You're young.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.74,0:21:08.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们都年轻过\N{\fs16}We were all young once.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.80,0:21:12.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但我们都接受了现实\N{\fs16}But we all understand the way things are.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.16,0:21:14.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你也学着接受吧\N{\fs16}You will learn as well,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.53,0:21:17.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果你足够幸运 能与我们终老的话\N{\fs16}if you are fortunate enough to stay with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.28,0:21:20.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我还能去哪儿呢？\N{\fs16}Where else would I go?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.64,0:21:23.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,每个卡丽熙最终都会成为多希卡林\N{\fs16}Every khaleesi become Dosh Khaleen.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.19,0:21:27.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,对 在她们的卡奥死后立刻成为\N{\fs16}Yes. Immediately after the death of their khal
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.20,0:21:29.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你却继续在外游荡\N{\fs16}But you went out into the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.32,0:21:30.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这可犯了大忌\N{\fs16}That is forbidden
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.81,0:21:36.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所有卡拉萨都会来参加卡拉萨大会\N{\fs16}All the khalasars have returned for the Khalar Vezhven.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.80,0:21:42.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一起决定洗劫哪些城市 奴役哪些部落\N{\fs16}They will decide which cities will be sacked and which tribes will be enslaved.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.60,0:21:46.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,现在他们必须决定如何处置卓戈卡奥的银发遗孀\N{\fs16}And now the must decide what to do with Khal Drogo's silver-haired widow.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.84,0:21:51.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,幸运的话 你会留下陪我们终老 龙之母\N{\fs16}With luck, your place will be here with us, Moter of Dragons.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.40,0:21:53.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是你最好的结局\N{\fs16}It is the best you can hope for, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.58,0:22:08.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,真搞不懂 你们居然还穿得住一身皮甲\N{\fs16}I don't know how you stand it in all that leather.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.76,0:22:17.66,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,能让我们单独谈谈吗\N{\fs16}If we could have the room.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.10,0:22:30.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你今天好美 亲爱的 真的\N{\fs16}You look lovely today, my dear. You really do.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.91,0:22:35.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你怎么做到汗都不流就爬完这些台阶的？\N{\fs16}How you climbed all those steps without breaking a sweat.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.38,0:22:36.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你要是想拷问我\N{\fs16}If you're going to torture me,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.65,0:22:38.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,叫他们回来动手就行\N{\fs16}just call them back and get on with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.85,0:22:40.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我可不是拷问者\N{\fs16}I am not a torturer.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.35,0:22:45.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,尽管很多时候有些人活该受虐\N{\fs16}Though it so often is what people deserve.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.99,0:22:49.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,拷打的确也能问出答案\N{\fs16}And it does provide answers.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:52.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不过通常都是错误答案罢了\N{\fs16}But they're usually the wrong answers.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.80,0:22:56.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的任务却是找到正确答案\N{\fs16}My job is to find the right answers.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.40,0:22:58.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,知道我会怎么做吗？\N{\fs16}Do you know how I do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.60,0:23:01.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我会让人开心\N{\fs16}I do it by making people happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.97,0:23:04.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我也想让你开心 瓦拉\N{\fs16}I'd like to make you happy, Vala.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.71,0:23:07.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是你的名字 对吧 瓦拉？\N{\fs16}That's your name, isn't it, Vala?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.01,0:23:10.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不说也没关系\N{\fs16}That's all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.41,0:23:13.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我知道你是谁 知道你做过什么\N{\fs16}I know who you are and what you've done.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.42,0:23:16.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你还真做了不少呢\N{\fs16}You've done a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.82,0:23:19.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你为达目的献出了你的身体\N{\fs16}You've sacrificed your body for a cause,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.39,0:23:22.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这就已经比大部分人做得多了\N{\fs16}which is more than most people do.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.83,0:23:25.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你还帮助鹰身女妖之子\N{\fs16}And you've helped the Sons of the Harpy
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.03,0:23:28.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谋杀无垢者和次子团的人\N{\fs16}murder the Unsullied and the Second Sons.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.90,0:23:32.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,无垢者和次子团是外国的战士\N{\fs16}The Unsullied and the Second Sons are foreign soldiers
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.33,0:23:34.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,由外国的女王带领\N{\fs16}brought here by a foreign queen
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.47,0:23:37.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,毁掉了我们的城市与历史\N{\fs16}to destroy our city and our history.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.27,0:23:40.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我明白了\N{\fs16}I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.21,0:23:42.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,从你的立场看\N{\fs16}Well, that makes perfect sense
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.98,0:23:45.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的行为无可指责\N{\fs16}from your perspective.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.81,0:23:49.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,当然了 你我立场不同\N{\fs16}I have a different perspective, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.69,0:23:53.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我觉得 重点是你应该站在我的立场上想想问题\N{\fs16}I think it's important that you try to see things from my perspective
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.25,0:23:55.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,正如我也会试着换位思考\N{\fs16}just as I will try to see them from yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.72,0:23:57.92,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为这是我让你和多姆都开心\N{\fs16}Because that is the only way
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.03,0:24:00.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,的唯一办法\N{\fs16}that I can make you and Dom happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.03,0:24:07.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是这么发音吧 多姆？\N{\fs16}That is how you pronounce it... Dom?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.94,0:24:10.94,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很抱歉我不太擅长这种语言\N{\fs16}I'm afraid I don't really speak the language.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.47,0:24:14.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,多么帅气的男孩\N{\fs16}Such a handsome boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.48,0:24:18.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那双棕色的大眼睛 希望不要太招女生喜欢\N{\fs16}Those big, brown eyes. Good luck keeping the ladies away.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.11,0:24:22.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,呵 你还真是个解放者 对吗？\N{\fs16}Yes, you're a true liberator, aren't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.35,0:24:25.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不会拷问我 只会用我儿子作要挟\N{\fs16}You won't torture me, you'll just threaten my son.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.32,0:24:27.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,孩子是无辜的\N{\fs16}Children are blameless.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.79,0:24:30.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我从没伤害过他们\N{\fs16}I have never hurt them.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.09,0:24:33.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你儿子目前没危险\N{\fs16}Your boy is in no immediate danger,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.53,0:24:35.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我向你发誓\N{\fs16}this I swear to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.07,0:24:38.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,至于你呢 亲爱的\N{\fs16}But between us, dear,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.07,0:24:42.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你曾密谋杀害女王的士兵\N{\fs16}you did conspire to kill the queen's soldiers.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.30,0:24:44.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们都明白你将面临何种刑罚\N{\fs16}We both know the penalty for that crime.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.98,0:24:53.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没了母亲 可怜的多姆该怎么活？\N{\fs16}How will poor Dom get on without his mother?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.75,0:24:55.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他还有气喘病\N{\fs16}And with his breathing problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.88,0:24:58.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哪怕我招了一个字 他们都会杀了我\N{\fs16}If I tell you anything, they'll kill me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.32,0:25:00.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就算你不杀我 他们也会\N{\fs16}So either you kill me or they do.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.59,0:25:04.12,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是啊 站在你的立场 这是个问题\N{\fs16}Yes, from your perspective, this is a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.66,0:25:07.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但你还有第三个选择\N{\fs16}There is a third option, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.80,0:25:11.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,明天有艘船去潘托斯\N{\fs16}A ship leaving tomorrow for Pentos.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.10,0:25:15.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我已经帮一个女人和她儿子订了位置\N{\fs16}I've already booked passage for a woman and her young son.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.84,0:25:19.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还留下一袋银币帮你们重新开始\N{\fs16}I'll even throw in a bag of silver to help you start again.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.37,0:25:21.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不过 恐怕我得\N{\fs16}Though I'm afraid we'll have to ask
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.24,0:25:24.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,喊一个穿皮甲的朋友帮你扛出去\N{\fs16}one of our leather-clad friends back in to carry it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.05,0:25:26.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我觉得袋子太沉了\N{\fs16}Far too heavy for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.12,0:25:29.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,明天天一亮就开船\N{\fs16}The boat sails at dawn.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.09,0:25:32.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你必须马上做决定\N{\fs16}You need to decide now.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.96,0:25:35.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是你和多姆开始新的生活\N{\fs16}A new life for you and Dom
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.82,0:25:37.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还是……\N{\fs16}or...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.51,0:25:55.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就这么干等？\N{\fs16}What should we do while we wait?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.41,0:25:57.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不如干点什么打发时间吧？\N{\fs16}To pass the time, what should we do?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.31,0:25:59.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不聊点什么？\N{\fs16}What should we talk about?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.98,0:26:03.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你会说十九种语言\N{\fs16}You speak 19 languages.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.85,0:26:07.19,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,偶尔用它们聊聊天总可以吧\N{\fs16}You must occasionally use some of them to talk about things.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.29,0:26:10.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们俩 总是待在一起\N{\fs16}You two, you spend a great deal of time together.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.63,0:26:13.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不在的话 你们会聊什么？\N{\fs16}What would you be talking about if I weren't here?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.86,0:26:16.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,巡逻\N{\fs16}Patrol.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.93,0:26:19.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,聊我带领无垢者一起巡逻的事\N{\fs16}When I am going on patrol with the Unsullied.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.67,0:26:22.24,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们巡逻时看到了什么\N{\fs16}What we see on patrol.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.34,0:26:24.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,巡逻时抓住了谁\N{\fs16}Who we captured on patrol.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.37,0:26:26.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,很好 非常好\N{\fs16}That's good. That's very good.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.94,0:26:31.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但这只是报告\N{\fs16}But that's a report.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.45,0:26:33.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我觉得聊天不止如此\N{\fs16}I was thinking more of a conversation.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.75,0:26:36.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有位智者说过 真正的世界历史\N{\fs16}A wise man once said the true history of the world
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.89,0:26:40.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,由豪华房间里发生的伟大聊天组成\N{\fs16}is the history of great conversations in elegant rooms.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.39,0:26:42.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谁说的？\N{\fs16}Who said this?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.39,0:26:44.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我\N{\fs16}Me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.86,0:26:46.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,刚说完\N{\fs16}Just now.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.17,0:26:55.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好吧 不聊天\N{\fs16}All right, no conversations.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.50,0:26:57.37,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那就玩个游戏\N{\fs16}Let's play a game.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.24,0:27:02.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你俩不玩游戏吗 从没玩过？\N{\fs16}You don't play games, either one of you, ever?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.11,0:27:03.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,游戏是小孩玩的\N{\fs16}Games are for children.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.44,0:27:07.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我曾经的主人克拉兹尼有时会让我们玩游戏\N{\fs16}My master Kraznys would sometimes make us play games.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.45,0:27:09.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,看 一个好的开始\N{\fs16}There, that's a start.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.28,0:27:12.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 但只有女孩能玩 - 不不不\N{\fs16}- Only the girls. - No, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.06,0:27:15.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不是 当然不是那种游戏\N{\fs16}Not that. Of course not that.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.39,0:27:18.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是说 纯洁又好玩的游戏\N{\fs16}Innocent games. Fun games.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.73,0:27:20.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,喝酒游戏\N{\fs16}Drinking games.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.33,0:27:22.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们不喝酒\N{\fs16}We do not drink.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.63,0:27:24.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,直到你们破戒\N{\fs16}Until you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.37,0:27:28.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好吧 不喝酒\N{\fs16}All right. No drinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.60,0:27:30.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不喝也能玩\N{\fs16}We can play without drinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.24,0:27:32.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是个很棒的游戏 我发明的\N{\fs16}It's a wonderful game. I invented it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.51,0:27:34.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,规则如下\N{\fs16}Here's how it works.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.11,0:27:36.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我猜你们的过去\N{\fs16}I make a statement about your past.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:36.18,0:27:37.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果我猜错了 罚酒\N{\fs16}If I'm wrong, I drink.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.91,0:27:41.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果我猜对了……\N{\fs16}And if I'm right...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.12,0:27:44.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不喝酒可能就玩不下去了\N{\fs16}maybe we can't play without drinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.29,0:27:48.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哦 你真够准时的\N{\fs16}Oh, you took your time.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.86,0:27:50.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不好意思\N{\fs16}Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.93,0:27:54.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我忙着打听究竟是谁资助鹰身女妖之子\N{\fs16}I was busy learning who funds the Sons of the Harpy.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.66,0:27:56.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 有些事情你急不得 - 你找到了吗？\N{\fs16}- Some things you can't rush. - You found out?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.80,0:27:58.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,阿斯塔波的善主\N{\fs16}The Good Masters of Astapor
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.03,0:28:01.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有渊凯的贤主\N{\fs16}and the Wise Masters of Yunkai.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.30,0:28:04.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,以及他们的瓦兰提斯朋友\N{\fs16}With help from their friends in Volantis.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.41,0:28:05.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你看？\N{\fs16}You see?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.94,0:28:08.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你根本不用担心本地的叛乱\N{\fs16}You don't even have to worry about the local rebellion.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.54,0:28:10.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们只需要担心\N{\fs16}We only have to worry about
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.18,0:28:12.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,三个资助他们的富有城邦\N{\fs16}the three rich foreign cities paying for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.48,0:28:14.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们曾经征服过阿斯塔波和渊凯\N{\fs16}We conquered Astapor and Yunkai once.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.22,0:28:16.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们可再次征服他们 并处决那些奴隶主\N{\fs16}We will do it again and execute the Masters.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.15,0:28:19.55,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,若无垢者出兵重夺阿斯塔波和渊凯\N{\fs16}If the Unsullied march off to reconquer Astapor and Yunkai,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.65,0:28:21.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谁留下保卫弥林的自由民？\N{\fs16}who will remain to defend the free people of Meereen?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.26,0:28:23.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果不出兵 如何阻止流血\N{\fs16}If we do not fight them, how can we stop them?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.89,0:28:25.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们阻止不了\N{\fs16}We cannot.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.69,0:28:28.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,奴隶主只说一种语言\N{\fs16}The Masters speak only one language.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.56,0:28:30.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,多年来他们一直对我说这种语言\N{\fs16}They spoke it to me for many years.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.33,0:28:32.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我了解它更胜母语\N{\fs16}I know it better than my mother tongue.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.20,0:28:35.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,想让他们听话 我们必须用这种语言回敬\N{\fs16}If we want them to hear us, we must speak it back to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.97,0:28:38.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让这些话为他们送终\N{\fs16}May it be the last thing they ever hear.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.24,0:28:40.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也许只能如此\N{\fs16}You may be right.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.41,0:28:42.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所以要打了？\N{\fs16}So we will fight them?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:42.48,0:28:44.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 可能 - 可能？\N{\fs16}- Possibly. - Possibly?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.51,0:28:47.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这就是聊天\N{\fs16}It's a conversation.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.52,0:28:49.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,告诉我 你的小小鸟儿能把消息传到\N{\fs16}Tell me, can your little birds get a message
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.92,0:28:53.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,阿斯塔波的善主 渊凯的贤主\N{\fs16}to the Good Masters of Astapor, the Wise Masters of Yunkai,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.26,0:28:55.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,以及瓦兰提斯仁慈的奴隶贩子那里去么？\N{\fs16}and benevolent enslavers of Volantis?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.92,0:28:58.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,当然 人无常善变\N{\fs16}Of course. Men can be fickle,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.66,0:29:01.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但小小鸟们永远值得信任\N{\fs16}but birds I always trust.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.10,0:29:11.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,亚瑟 你的眼睛看起来好多了\N{\fs16}Your eye looks much better, Arthur.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.11,0:29:12.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你母亲的下巴怎么样了？\N{\fs16}How's your mother's jaw?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.54,0:29:14.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,好点了\N{\fs16}Better.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.18,0:29:15.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你父亲呢？\N{\fs16}And your father?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.61,0:29:18.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,再没人见过他\N{\fs16}No one's seen him.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.18,0:29:19.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,也不会有人再见到他\N{\fs16}And no one will.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.55,0:29:21.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这结果相当不错\N{\fs16}That worked out rather nicely.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.28,0:29:23.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,瓦里斯大人会回来吗？\N{\fs16}Will Lord Varys ever come back?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.42,0:29:25.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我觉得他不会了\N{\fs16}I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.59,0:29:27.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你很想他吗？\N{\fs16}Do you miss him?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.49,0:29:30.06,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他人很好\N{\fs16}He was nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.16,0:29:32.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他管我们叫小小鸟儿\N{\fs16}He called us his little birds.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.56,0:29:34.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他给我们糖吃\N{\fs16}He gave us sweets.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.40,0:29:39.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,说起这个可就有意思了\N{\fs16}It's funny you should mention that.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.87,0:29:44.80,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,猜猜我今天碰巧找到了什么\N{\fs16}Guess what I happened to find today.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.91,0:29:48.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,多恩的梅子蜜饯\N{\fs16}Candied plums from Dorne.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.05,0:29:54.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,记住 如果你们的伙伴\N{\fs16}Now remember, if any of your friends
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.28,0:29:57.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,喜欢吃糖果 或者需要帮助 尽管来找我\N{\fs16}like sweets or need help, they can always come to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.62,0:30:02.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,只需跟我说说悄悄话\N{\fs16}All I need in return are whispers.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.46,0:30:11.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不用害怕\N{\fs16}No need to be afraid.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.37,0:30:13.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这位是格雷果爵士\N{\fs16}This is Ser Gregor.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.37,0:30:15.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的朋友就是他的朋友\N{\fs16}He's friends with all my friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.44,0:30:23.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,快走吧\N{\fs16}Run along now.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.12,0:30:29.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,瓦里斯的小小鸟吗？\N{\fs16}Varys's little birds?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.92,0:30:31.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,现在是您的小小鸟 陛下\N{\fs16}Your little birds now, Your Grace.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.52,0:30:33.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你到底对他做了什么？\N{\fs16}What did you do to him exactly?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.55,0:30:35.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我一直没能弄清楚\N{\fs16}I haven't been able to get a clear answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.32,0:30:37.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哦 我做了很多事情\N{\fs16}Oh, a number of things.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.46,0:30:38.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他能明白我们在说什么吗？\N{\fs16}Does he understand what we're saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.06,0:30:41.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是说 可以像以前那样\N{\fs16}I mean, to the extent that he ever understood
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.40,0:30:43.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,理解完整句子吗？\N{\fs16}complete sentences in the first place.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.40,0:30:47.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,完全可以\N{\fs16}He understands well enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.60,0:30:49.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那就告诉他杀去圣堂\N{\fs16}So tell him to march into the sept
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.74,0:30:52.34,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,把大麻雀的脑袋瓜捏碎\N{\fs16}and crush the High Sparrow's head like a melon.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:52.44,0:30:55.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,大麻雀有数百人的教团武装保护他\N{\fs16}The High Sparrow has hundreds of Faith Militant surrounding him.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.94,0:30:58.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,格雷果爵士没办法对付他们所有人\N{\fs16}Ser Gregor can't face them all.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.31,0:31:00.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他也不需要\N{\fs16}And he won't have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.35,0:31:02.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他只需要对付一个\N{\fs16}He'll only have to face one.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.49,0:31:06.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,教会提出正式的指控了吗？\N{\fs16}Has the Faith leveled official charges yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.99,0:31:08.65,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还没有\N{\fs16}Not yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.76,0:31:11.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我真期待见证这场比武审判\N{\fs16}That is one trial by combat I look forward to watching.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.03,0:31:13.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,别局限于君临\N{\fs16}Don't stop at the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.03,0:31:16.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我要小小鸟去多恩\N{\fs16}I want little birds in Dorne,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.43,0:31:19.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去高庭 去北境\N{\fs16}in Highgarden, in the North.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.20,0:31:22.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果有人想看我们的笑话 坐收渔利\N{\fs16}If someone is planning on making our losses their gains,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.37,0:31:24.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我要知道\N{\fs16}I want to hear it.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.31,0:31:26.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果有人敢嘲笑他们的太后\N{\fs16}If someone is laughing at the queen
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.01,0:31:29.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,说她赤身游街 满身污垢\N{\fs16}who walked naked through the streets covered in shit,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.74,0:31:31.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我要知道\N{\fs16}I want to hear.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.61,0:31:34.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我要知道他们是谁\N{\fs16}I want to know who they are.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.48,0:31:36.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们人在何处\N{\fs16}I want to know where they are.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.86,0:31:45.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 和瓦里斯大人一样坏 - 科本还要更坏\N{\fs16}- As bad as Lord Varys was, - Qyburn is worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.93,0:31:48.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我跟他们都说了 我说了\N{\fs16}I told them all. I told them.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.43,0:31:50.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他傲慢 危险\N{\fs16}He's arrogant, dangerous.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.43,0:31:53.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他不会无缘无故地就被赶出学城\N{\fs16}You don't get thrown out of the Citadel without good reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.57,0:31:55.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但没有人听我的话\N{\fs16}And no one listened to my advice.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.40,0:31:57.50,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所以才成了今天这样\N{\fs16}So here we are.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.61,0:32:02.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他在格雷果·克里冈身上做的事是邪恶的\N{\fs16}And what he's done to Gregor Clegane is an abomination.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.04,0:32:05.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们从未同意这个实验\N{\fs16}We never sanctioned this experiment.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.25,0:32:07.81,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我个人认为我们最好\N{\fs16}I for one think it will be in our best interest
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.92,0:32:09.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,把这个野兽杀……\N{\fs16}to have the beast dest...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.46,0:32:16.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 有什么可以效劳的吗？ - 你怎么在这？\N{\fs16}- Can I help you? - Why are you here?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.09,0:32:19.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,- 我的母亲…… - 亲爱的 我被邀请来\N{\fs16}- My mother... - I was invited, my dear,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.56,0:32:22.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,帮助解决一些棘手的问题\N{\fs16}to help deal with several troublesome issues,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.33,0:32:24.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,譬如王后被监禁\N{\fs16}such as the queen's imprisonment.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.73,0:32:27.17,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,亏你还提起这个\N{\fs16}Thank you for bringing it up.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.27,0:32:30.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们早就该讨论如何应对我所受的侮辱了\N{\fs16}It's well past time we addressed the abuses I endured.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.07,0:32:33.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,玛格丽才是王后\N{\fs16}Margaery is the queen.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.38,0:32:35.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不是\N{\fs16}You are not the queen
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.24,0:32:37.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为你没有嫁给国王\N{\fs16}because you're not married to the king.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.38,0:32:39.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我能明白你们家族里\N{\fs16}I do appreciate these things
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.18,0:32:42.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这些事情搞得有点混乱\N{\fs16}can get a bit confusing in your family.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.88,0:32:45.05,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这里是御前会议\N{\fs16}This is a small council meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.15,0:32:47.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你无权出席御前会议\N{\fs16}You have no position on the small council.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.39,0:32:49.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是御林铁卫队长\N{\fs16}I'm the Lord Commander of the Kingsguard.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.26,0:32:50.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,御林铁卫队长\N{\fs16}The Lord Commander of the Kingsguard
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.79,0:32:52.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有权出席御前会议\N{\fs16}does have a position on the small council.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:52.63,0:32:55.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,派席尔大学士 你认可吗？\N{\fs16}Grand Maester Pycelle, would you sanction that statement?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.26,0:32:57.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,呃……\N{\fs16}Well...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.47,0:33:00.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,杰洛·海塔尔爵士\N{\fs16}I would say Ser Gerold Hightower
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.54,0:33:02.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,曾在疯王的御前会议有一席之地\N{\fs16}had a seat on the Mad King's council.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.70,0:33:05.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但当然了 那是疯王\N{\fs16}Of course, that was the Mad King.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.37,0:33:06.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,劳勃国王认为不可\N{\fs16}King Robert saw things differently.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.08,0:33:08.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而乔……\N{\fs16}And King...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:12.08,0:33:14.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,弥赛菈的死怎么说 叔叔？\N{\fs16}What about Myrcella's death, Uncle?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.02,0:33:17.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您认为血亲被谋杀\N{\fs16}Do you consider the murder of your own blood
Dialogue: 0,0:33:17.29,0:33:19.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是一个棘手的问题么？\N{\fs16}a troublesome issue?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.39,0:33:21.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,谋杀弥赛菈的那个女人\N{\fs16}The same women who murdered Myrcella
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.32,0:33:23.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,推翻了马泰尔家族 控制了多恩\N{\fs16}have overthrown House Martell and taken control of Dorne.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.89,0:33:25.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们需要讨论的问题太多了\N{\fs16}We've got a lot to discuss.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.69,0:33:28.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们所有人 一起\N{\fs16}All of us together.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.20,0:33:31.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,既然你们无法让我们离开 就继续吧\N{\fs16}And seeing as you cannot make us leave, we best get on with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.04,0:33:36.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,的确 我们无法让你们离开\N{\fs16}No, we cannot make you leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.67,0:33:39.77,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而你们也无法强迫我们留在这\N{\fs16}And you cannot make us stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.87,0:33:43.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,除非你让那东西把我们都杀了\N{\fs16}Not unless you're gonna have that thing murder us all.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.58,0:34:24.85,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.85,0:34:26.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,陛下\N{\fs16}Your Grace.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.79,0:34:29.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我母亲想来看望她女儿最后的安息之地\N{\fs16}My mother would like to see her daughter's final resting place.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.06,0:34:32.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,抱歉 陛下\N{\fs16}I'm sorry, Your Grace.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.73,0:34:34.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这不可以 现在还不行\N{\fs16}That's not possible. Not yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.70,0:34:36.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那何时可以？\N{\fs16}When will it be possible?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.46,0:34:38.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,直到她赎清罪孽\N{\fs16}When she's fully atoned for her sins.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.83,0:34:41.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你已斩下她的头发\N{\fs16}You cut off her hair and marched her naked
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.54,0:34:43.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,令她在众目睽睽之下赤裸游行\N{\fs16}through the streets in front of the whole city.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.07,0:34:45.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这还不够赎罪吗？\N{\fs16}That wasn't the full atonement?!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.84,0:34:47.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不\N{\fs16}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.68,0:34:50.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她必须在七位修士面前接受审判\N{\fs16}She must stand trial before seven septons
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.95,0:34:53.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,让我们了解她的全部罪行\N{\fs16}so we can learn the true extent of her sins.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.18,0:34:57.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我要你打开大门 让她来看望弥赛菈的安息之地\N{\fs16}I want you to let her see Myrcella's resting place.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.45,0:34:59.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我是国王\N{\fs16}I am the king.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.12,0:35:00.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,没错\N{\fs16}You are.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.62,0:35:04.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那么这对你意味着什么？\N{\fs16}And what does that mean to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.59,0:35:05.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这对我意义非凡\N{\fs16}It means a great deal to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.06,0:35:07.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,王权与信仰\N{\fs16}The Crown and the Faith
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.06,0:35:10.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,乃是世界的两大支柱\N{\fs16}are the twin pillars of the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.30,0:35:12.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您知道这话是谁告诉我的？\N{\fs16}Do you know who told me that?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.70,0:35:15.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您母亲\N{\fs16}Your mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.14,0:35:17.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我那个“不洁”的母亲？\N{\fs16}My mother who is unclean?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.74,0:35:21.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我那个经受你种种折磨 却仍需赎罪的母亲？\N{\fs16}My mother who still needs to atone after all you've put her through?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.43,0:35:43.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您认为圣母首度降临是何情形？\N{\fs16}How do you think the Mother Above first came to us?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.73,0:35:46.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,世上的男男女女\N{\fs16}How did men and women
Dialogue: 0,0:35:46.63,0:35:50.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如何首度感受到圣母的存在？\N{\fs16}first come to feel the Mother's presence?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.54,0:35:53.31,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是通过自己的母亲\N{\fs16}It was through their own mothers.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.04,0:35:59.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,瑟曦非常虚伪 这点您心知肚明\N{\fs16}There's a great deal of falsehood in Cersei. You know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.51,0:36:03.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但当她谈及您时 母爱胜过了一切\N{\fs16}But when she speaks of you, the Mother's love outshines it all.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.75,0:36:08.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她对您的爱\N{\fs16}Her love for you is more real
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.79,0:36:10.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,比世上任何东西都要真实\N{\fs16}than anything else in this world
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.79,0:36:13.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,因为这种爱并非来自这个世界\N{\fs16}because it doesn't come from this world.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.89,0:36:15.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这点其实您也知道\N{\fs16}But you know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.93,0:36:18.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您亲身感受过\N{\fs16}You've felt it.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.63,0:36:20.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她对您说话的时候 您看见了圣母的影子\N{\fs16}You've seen her when she talks to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.94,0:36:24.70,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fs16}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:24.81,0:36:27.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是一件无与伦比的礼物\N{\fs16}It's a great gift.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.11,0:36:29.11,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我从未得到过\N{\fs16}One I never had.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.71,0:36:32.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,嫉妒\N{\fs16}Envy.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.85,0:36:35.28,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,又一项我应当忏悔的罪孽\N{\fs16}One more thing for me to atone for.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.75,0:36:38.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,哦陛下 您……我可以坐下吗？\N{\fs16}Your Grace, do you... may I?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.72,0:36:40.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您介意吗？\N{\fs16}Do you mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.39,0:36:41.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的膝盖不太中用了\N{\fs16}It's my knees.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.82,0:36:43.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你坐吧\N{\fs16}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.03,0:36:52.93,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,您的母亲踏上赎罪之行\N{\fs16}When your mother made her walk of atonement,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.03,0:36:55.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是为了回到您身边\N{\fs16}she did it to get back to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.34,0:36:58.10,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我还是不明白你为什么不依不饶\N{\fs16}I still don't understand why you want to put her
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.21,0:36:59.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还要让她承受更多折磨\N{\fs16}through any more than she's already endured.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.07,0:37:03.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,并不是我要这样做 是诸神\N{\fs16}It's not what I want. It's what the gods want.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.54,0:37:06.15,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,诸神向我们传达旨意\N{\fs16}They make their will known to us and it's up to us
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.25,0:37:08.68,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是否遵从则取决于我们\N{\fs16}to either accept or reject it.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.79,0:37:12.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,请坐\N{\fs16}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.76,0:37:20.99,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果我们一心向善 追求公正\N{\fs16}If we're to be just and good,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.10,0:37:23.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那所有人都得遵从诸神的旨意 包括国王在内\N{\fs16}then we accept it, all of us, even kings.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.93,0:37:28.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,真正的领袖会让最睿智者来辅佐他\N{\fs16}A true leader avails himself of the wisest counsel he can.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.30,0:37:30.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而没有谁比诸神更睿智\N{\fs16}And no one is wiser than the gods.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.31,0:37:36.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我祖父和我说过类似的话\N{\fs16}My grandfather once said something similar.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.58,0:37:38.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但他并没提到诸神的部分\N{\fs16}Except for the part about the gods.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.51,0:37:42.42,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,诸神透过他的嘴教诲你 无论他自己有没有意识到\N{\fs16}The gods worked through him whether he knew it or not.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.69,0:37:45.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,正如诸神也透过您的母亲\N{\fs16}As they work through your mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.99,0:37:50.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,每个人的内心都充满善意\N{\fs16}There's so much good in all of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.12,0:37:53.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而我们能做的是引导他人向善\N{\fs16}The best we can do is to help each other bring it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.06,0:38:23.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是谁？\N{\fs16}Who are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.92,0:38:25.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,无名之辈\N{\fs16}No one.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.23,0:38:29.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你在来这里之前是谁？\N{\fs16}Who were you before you came here?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.83,0:38:31.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,艾莉亚·史塔克\N{\fs16}Arya Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.47,0:38:36.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,跟我讲讲艾莉亚·史塔克的家庭\N{\fs16}Tell me about Arya Stark's family.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.14,0:38:39.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她的父亲是艾德·史塔克\N{\fs16}Her father was Eddard Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.11,0:38:41.64,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她的母亲是凯特琳·史塔克\N{\fs16}Her mother was Catelyn Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.74,0:38:45.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她有一个姐姐 珊莎\N{\fs16}She had one sister, Sansa,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.18,0:38:47.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有四个兄弟\N{\fs16}and four brothers.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:56.79,0:38:58.56,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,三个兄弟\N{\fs16}Three brothers.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.66,0:39:01.46,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,罗柏 布兰 瑞肯\N{\fs16}Robb, Bran, Rickon.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.43,0:39:06.33,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,以及同父异母的哥哥琼恩\N{\fs16}And a half-brother Jon.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.50,0:39:09.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他们现在何处？\N{\fs16}And where are they now?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.94,0:39:12.91,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,就女孩所知 他们可能已经死了\N{\fs16}They may be dead for all a girl knows.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.18,0:39:24.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,跟我讲讲猎狗的事\N{\fs16}Tell me about the Hound.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:26.52,0:39:28.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他也死了\N{\fs16}Also dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.43,0:39:41.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,艾莉亚·史塔克丢下他等死 他在她的名单上\N{\fs16}Arya Stark left him to die. He was on her list.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.10,0:39:47.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他不在她的名单上\N{\fs16}He was not on her list anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.31,0:39:49.04,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她把他从里面去掉了\N{\fs16}She had taken him off it.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.14,0:39:53.21,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,为什么？她不想让他死了吗？\N{\fs16}Why? Didn't she want him dead any longer?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.05,0:39:59.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她既想又不想\N{\fs16}She did and she did not.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.82,0:40:05.96,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,她听起来很困惑\N{\fs16}She sounds confused.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.60,0:40:14.47,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,是的 她很困惑\N{\fs16}Yes, she was.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.67,0:40:21.41,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有谁在艾莉亚·史塔克可笑的小名单上？\N{\fs16}Who else was on Arya Stark's funny little list?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.42,0:40:24.51,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,瑟曦·兰尼斯特\N{\fs16}Cersei Lannister.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.08,0:40:27.25,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,格雷果·克里冈\N{\fs16}Gregor Clegane.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:29.18,0:40:30.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,瓦德·佛雷\N{\fs16}Walder Frey.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.36,0:40:37.09,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这名单挺短的\N{\fs16}That's a short list.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.96,0:40:43.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想杀的人肯定不止这些\N{\fs16}That can't be everyone you want to kill.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.27,0:40:48.90,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你确定自己没有忘记谁吗？\N{\fs16}Are you sure you're not forgetting someone?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:51.91,0:40:55.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你想让女孩说出哪个名字？\N{\fs16}Which name would you like a girl to speak?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.95,0:41:33.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果女孩告诉某人她的名字\N{\fs16}If a girl tells me her name,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.18,0:41:35.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,某人会把眼睛还给她\N{\fs16}I will give her eyes back.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:38.52,0:41:40.49,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,女孩没有名字\N{\fs16}A girl has no name.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.19,0:41:45.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,过来\N{\fs16}Come.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.76,0:42:20.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果女孩真的是无名之辈\N{\fs16}If a girl is truly no one,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:21.00,0:42:23.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那她应当无所畏惧\N{\fs16}she has nothing to fear.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:48.76,0:42:50.89,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你是谁？\N{\fs16}Who are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.29,0:42:56.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,无名之辈\N{\fs16}No one.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.74,0:43:08.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,安柏家族可是以忠诚著称\N{\fs16}The Umbers are a famously loyal house.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:08.98,0:43:11.44,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,以忠诚于史塔克著称\N{\fs16}Famously loyal to the Starks.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:11.55,0:43:14.58,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,而你 卡史塔克大人\N{\fs16}And you, Lord Karstark.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.68,0:43:17.48,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的家族与史塔克有共同的血脉 不是吗？\N{\fs16}Your people share blood with the Starks, don't they?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:17.58,0:43:20.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们却都来到这里 世易时移\N{\fs16}But here we are. Times change.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.32,0:43:22.62,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,当我父亲成为北境守护的时候\N{\fs16}When my father became Warden of the North,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:22.72,0:43:24.72,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你的家族拒绝向他效忠\N{\fs16}your house refused to pledge their banners.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:24.83,0:43:26.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你父亲是个混蛋\N{\fs16}Your father was a cunt.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:29.80,0:43:32.03,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我亲爱的父亲 北境守护……\N{\fs16}My beloved father, the Warden...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:32.13,0:43:35.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你父亲是个混蛋 所以你杀了他\N{\fs16}Your father was a cunt and that's why you killed him.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:35.37,0:43:38.20,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,想来我大概也会这么对付我父亲\N{\fs16}I might have done the same to my father
Dialogue: 0,0:43:38.31,0:43:40.87,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果他没有行行好自己死掉的话\N{\fs16}if he hadn't have done me the favor of dying on his own.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:40.98,0:43:43.78,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我父亲是被我们的敌人毒害的\N{\fs16}My father was poisoned by our enemies.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:45.71,0:43:49.01,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你来临冬城做什么 安柏大人？\N{\fs16}Why have you come to Winterfell, Lord Umber?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:49.12,0:43:52.95,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,那个野种琼恩·雪诺率领一支野人军队过了长城\N{\fs16}The bastard Jon Snow led an army of wildlings past the Wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.05,0:43:55.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们的领地比你们这帮混球更靠北\N{\fs16}We're farther north than any of you fuckers.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:55.56,0:43:58.82,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,每当野人南下 我们总是首先拿起武器\N{\fs16}Wildlings come down, we always have to fight them first.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:58.93,0:44:02.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我喜欢打野人 我一辈子都在干这事\N{\fs16}I like fighting wildlings. Been doing it all my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:02.26,0:44:05.00,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,但他们人太多了 我们没法单干\N{\fs16}But there are too many of them for us to beat back alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:05.10,0:44:07.97,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,所以你现在是来求助？\N{\fs16}So now you've come seeking help?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:08.07,0:44:10.40,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们得互相帮助\N{\fs16}We need to help each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:10.50,0:44:14.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,天气越冷 那些操山羊的蛮子就会越往南迁徙\N{\fs16}The colder it gets, the farther south those goat fuckers will roam.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:14.18,0:44:16.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,过不了多久就会到这儿\N{\fs16}Won't take them long to get here.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:16.24,0:44:19.08,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你觉得一群野人能攻占临冬城？\N{\fs16}You think a horde of wildlings can take Winterfell?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:19.18,0:44:20.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果有琼恩·雪诺作他们的头儿 那可说不准\N{\fs16}If they get Jon Snow leading them, maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.85,0:44:23.32,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他远比我们中的任何人更了解这里\N{\fs16}He knows this place better than we ever will.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:26.45,0:44:28.59,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,向波顿家族宣誓效忠\N{\fs16}Pledge your banners to House Bolton.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:28.69,0:44:31.22,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,承认我为北境守护\N{\fs16}Swear loyalty to me as Warden of the North
Dialogue: 0,0:44:31.33,0:44:33.83,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我就与你并肩作战 除掉那个野种\N{\fs16}and we will fight together to destroy the bastard
Dialogue: 0,0:44:33.93,0:44:35.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,外加他所有的野人朋友\N{\fs16}and all his wildling friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:35.53,0:44:37.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我不会吻你的脏手\N{\fs16}I'm not kissing your fucking hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:37.83,0:44:40.43,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,按传统 封臣应向封君下跪\N{\fs16}Traditionally a bannerman kneels before his lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:40.53,0:44:42.57,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我也不会这么做\N{\fs16}I'm not doing that either.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:42.67,0:44:45.60,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我凭什么要相信一个不尊重传统的人？\N{\fs16}Why would I trust a man who won't honor tradition?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:45.71,0:44:48.54,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你父亲尊重传统\N{\fs16}Your father honored tradition.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:48.64,0:44:50.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,他向罗柏·史塔克下跪\N{\fs16}Knelt for Robb Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:50.95,0:44:53.35,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,拥戴其为北境之王\N{\fs16}Called him King of the North.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:53.45,0:44:55.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,罗柏·史塔克应当相信你父亲吗？\N{\fs16}Was Robb Stark right to trust your father?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:55.72,0:44:57.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,看来 我们陷入了一个小小的僵局\N{\fs16}Then it appears we're at a bit of an impasse.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:57.62,0:45:00.75,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,去他妈的下跪 去他妈的宣誓\N{\fs16}Fuck kneeling and fuck oaths.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:00.86,0:45:02.45,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我有个礼物给你\N{\fs16}I've got a gift for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:05.39,0:45:08.16,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,希望是个姑娘 我喜欢红发的\N{\fs16}A girl, I hope. I prefer redheads.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:08.26,0:45:11.23,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,姑娘 有的\N{\fs16}A girl, aye.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:12.60,0:45:14.63,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一个女野人\N{\fs16}A wild one.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:22.31,0:45:24.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我喜欢带野性的\N{\fs16}I like them wild.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:25.21,0:45:28.71,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,还有个男孩 年轻又健康\N{\fs16}And the boy, nice and young.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:28.82,0:45:30.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,卡史塔克大人肯定喜欢\N{\fs16}The way Karstark likes them.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:36.79,0:45:38.26,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这是谁？\N{\fs16}Who's this?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:38.36,0:45:40.73,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,瑞肯·史塔克\N{\fs16}Rickon Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:47.84,0:45:50.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你怎么证明这是瑞肯·史塔克？\N{\fs16}How do I know that's Rickon Stark?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:20.80,0:46:23.67,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,欢迎回家 史塔克大人\N{\fs16}Welcome home, Lord Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:35.12,0:46:36.88,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,时间到了\N{\fs16}It's time.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:14.29,0:47:17.39,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,有什么遗言 现在说吧\N{\fs16}If you have any last words, now is the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:17.49,0:47:19.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你不该活着\N{\fs16}You shouldn't be alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:19.86,0:47:21.79,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,这不该发生\N{\fs16}It's not right.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:22.96,0:47:24.76,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你们也不该谋杀我\N{\fs16}Neither was killing me.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:29.10,0:47:31.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我母亲还住在白港\N{\fs16}My mother's still living at White Harbor.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:31.84,0:47:33.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你能写信给她吗？\N{\fs16}Could you write her?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:33.84,0:47:36.14,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,告诉她我死在与野人的战斗中\N{\fs16}Tell her I died fighting the wildlings.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:44.55,0:47:48.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我有过选择 总司令大人\N{\fs16}I had a choice, Lord Commander.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:48.39,0:47:52.36,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,背叛你或背叛守夜人\N{\fs16}Betray you or betray the Night's Watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:52.46,0:47:55.53,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你将一支野人军队带到了我们的土地上\N{\fs16}You brought an army of wildlings into our lands.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:57.40,0:48:00.27,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,一支杀人犯和掠袭者组成的军队\N{\fs16}An army of murderers and raiders.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:00.37,0:48:04.07,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,如果让我知道结局 再重来一次\N{\fs16}If I had to do it all over knowing where I'd end up,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:04.17,0:48:07.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我祈祷自己能再次做出正确的选择\N{\fs16}I pray I'd make the right choice again.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:07.71,0:48:09.74,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我确信你会的 艾里沙爵士\N{\fs16}I'm sure you would, Ser Alliser.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:09.84,0:48:12.84,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我战斗过 我失败了\N{\fs16}I fought, I lost.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:14.68,0:48:16.61,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我可以安心休息\N{\fs16}Now I rest.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:17.62,0:48:21.52,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,可是你 雪诺大人\N{\fs16}But you, Lord Snow,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:21.62,0:48:24.02,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你将永世不得翻身\N{\fs16}you'll be fighting their battles forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:11.20,0:50:13.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我们应该烧掉这些尸体\N{\fs16}We should burn the bodies.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:14.63,0:50:16.13,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,不 是你应该\N{\fs16}You should.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:24.88,0:50:27.18,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,你干嘛把这个给我？\N{\fs16}What do you want me to do with this?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:27.28,0:50:28.98,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,穿上它\N{\fs16}Wear it.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:29.08,0:50:31.38,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,或者烧了它\N{\fs16}Burn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:31.49,0:50:33.69,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,想怎样都行\N{\fs16}Whatever you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:33.79,0:50:35.29,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,黑城堡是你的了\N{\fs16}You have Castle Black.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:42.10,0:50:44.30,Subtitle,,0,0,0,,我的守望于斯结束\N{\fs16}My watch is ended.

