[Script Info]
;  Script generated by PySubs
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2013-11-11 19:23:11
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: Guilty Crown OP x ED
Original Script: dlnm x cooKIe
Original Translation: bigo × dgwxx
Original Editing: zwc
Original Timing: zwc
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,文泉驿等宽微米黑,45,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00323232,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: IN,@TT-JTCウインM5P,39,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,98,100,0,270.00,1,0,3,3,10,45,10,1
Style: op_sc,方正中雅宋_GBK,37,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00B1CEA0,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,4,2,10,10,10,1
Style: SCREEN,文泉驿等宽微米黑,45,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H009CA353,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: ed_jp,DFPHSMincho-W9,33,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H78000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,8,20,20,20,128
Style: ed_sc,方正大标宋_GBK,37,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H78000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,20,20,20,1
Style: op_jp,DFPHSMincho-W9,33,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00B1CEA0,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,8,20,20,20,128
Style: isong_jp,DFPHSMincho-W9,33,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H78000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,9,20,20,20,128
Style: isong_sc,方正大标宋_GBK,37,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H78000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,9,20,20,64,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.06,0:01:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真名会吞噬祈 重生世间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.37,0:01:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们失去的夏娃将复活
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.49,0:01:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你晚了一步
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.97,0:01:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.79,0:01:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.13,0:01:59.96,SCREEN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3\pos(1058,700)\3c&HA6A43C&}祈 祷
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.76,0:02:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这到底是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.10,0:02:07.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这道光芒…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.53,0:02:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要出事了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.11,0:02:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.76,0:02:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了 我们守住这里
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.74,0:02:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们快去上面
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.28,0:02:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绫瀬 掩护我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.97,0:02:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解 但…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.48,0:02:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们可真是屡次坏了我的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.92,0:02:26.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这次不一样了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.33,0:02:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这台Gespenst！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.28,0:02:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鶫 还没夺回来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.82,0:02:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,防御突然加强了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.65,0:02:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管我怎么删除 还是跟僵尸一样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.01,0:02:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟鶫不相伯仲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.91,0:02:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,研二…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.93,0:02:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.96,0:03:19.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早啊 特里同
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.99,0:03:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你醒了 真名
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.14,0:03:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.60,0:03:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.43,0:03:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.91,0:03:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烦啊 有个讨厌的女人总碍姐姐的事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.60,0:03:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在没事了 我把她碾碎了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.52,0:03:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这身体已经是姐姐的了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.38,0:03:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙也太任性了 明明只是个被造出来的怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.27,0:03:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住嘴！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.73,0:03:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.97,0:04:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祈不是什么怪物 她为了我而哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.97,0:04:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音和外表虽然一样 但和你不同…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.08,0:04:05.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是个人类
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.30,0:04:11.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好过分啊 集
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.22,0:04:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐最喜欢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.04,0:04:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体四分五裂都还深爱着你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.43,0:04:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你却要再次拒绝我 集
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.88,0:04:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此为止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.77,0:04:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.20,0:04:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来交给我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.39,0:05:02.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐好受伤 集
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.76,0:05:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤害了别人 自己也要做好受伤的准备
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.42,0:05:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算道歉…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.31,0:05:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不会原谅你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.44,0:05:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.17,0:05:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始了吧 涯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.59,0:06:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.16,0:06:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,24区发出了远高于「迷失的圣诞节」的高功率基因共鸣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.65,0:06:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,End Rave的远程共鸣系统也受到了干扰！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.57,0:06:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.28,0:06:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第四次默示录开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.72,0:06:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个星球的生命将开始进化和淘汰！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.63,0:06:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谷寻！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.36,0:07:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丢弃脆弱的肉体 在结晶中获得永恒的思考
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.94,0:07:08.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是下一阶段
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.02,0:07:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Void就是一个前兆
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.44,0:07:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预示着内心物质化的新世界
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.61,0:07:23.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁让你用普通装备
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.30,0:07:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来来 这就踩扁你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.87,0:07:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休想得逞！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.18,0:07:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别瞧不起人 混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.58,0:07:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绫瀬 用有线连接！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.76,0:07:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鶫 使用回避程序！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.82,0:07:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鶫？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.78,0:07:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭女人！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.75,0:07:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.80,0:08:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔少尉 Void基因模拟器还在试验阶段
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.47,0:08:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用过量了！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.30,0:08:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡说些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.27,0:08:17.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不杀光他们怎么能停呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.54,0:08:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,颯太
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.00,0:08:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涯 那个时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.41,0:08:29.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在六本木的地下层你说要救真名
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.53,0:08:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说为了救她让我刺你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.32,0:08:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么会变成这样！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.46,0:08:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不会明白的 集！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.36,0:08:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是被选中 却又任性地撒手
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.29,0:08:52.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是绝对不会明白的！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.47,0:09:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 黑周
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.47,0:09:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想救的女儿就要毁灭世界了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.29,0:09:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.39,0:09:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为此把全世界…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.91,0:09:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和集卷进来了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.02,0:09:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不否认了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.58,0:09:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会开枪吗 春夏
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.66,0:09:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能让你们过去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.76,0:09:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要将他保护到底
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.89,0:09:39.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太烦人了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.88,0:09:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好 这样下去…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.38,0:09:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鶫
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.04,0:09:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请坚持到我给信号的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.55,0:09:52.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能做到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.30,0:09:54.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当我是谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.92,0:10:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是以前的你 我会把真名…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.97,0:10:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有亚当的位置让给你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.99,0:10:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在的你不值得我这样做
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.71,0:10:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧 集
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.55,0:10:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体好重
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.22,0:10:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样结束了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.85,0:10:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带着大家的Void…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.00,0:10:48.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别放弃 集
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.80,0:10:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的身体还能动
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.68,0:10:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都在等你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.56,0:11:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 大家
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.03,0:11:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用我吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.79,0:11:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.78,0:11:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.33,0:11:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,研二 将军了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.82,0:11:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人信任我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.47,0:11:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并将生命托付给了我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.71,0:12:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还不能死 一定要夺回祈
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.78,0:12:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁现在
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.77,0:12:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绫姐 久等了～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.43,0:12:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要上了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.80,0:12:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,座舱操纵交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.69,0:12:30.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涯 你要是挡我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.80,0:12:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会全力打倒你！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.02,0:12:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那声音 你果然在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.76,0:12:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小矮子！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.52,0:12:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鶫
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.32,0:12:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.63,0:12:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.75,0:12:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干掉你们 我才是我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.32,0:12:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个杀人狂 达里尔！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.56,0:12:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.67,0:12:59.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是个小屁孩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.26,0:13:14.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祈？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.11,0:13:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要——
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.26,0:13:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.70,0:13:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.99,0:13:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后取胜的既不是我 也不是黑周
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.05,0:13:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 春夏
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.41,0:14:05.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.72,0:14:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就好 集
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.60,0:14:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…这样就好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.42,0:14:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.03,0:14:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淘汰的终点
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.16,0:14:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,默示录尽头的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.42,0:14:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.93,0:14:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是达特所谓的乌有之乡
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.50,0:14:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这星球的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.43,0:14:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…将会成为结晶中的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.48,0:15:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被推上王座的我 也终究会…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.31,0:15:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直害怕遭到淘汰
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.18,0:15:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以选择反抗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.44,0:15:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以希望得到夏娃——真名
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.43,0:15:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在六本木的地下层被你刺穿时
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.46,0:15:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为这样就可以解放真名
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.82,0:15:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但达特 也就是生物淘汰的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.31,0:15:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不允许真名的死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.17,0:15:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使她的肉体消亡 也要让她复活
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.43,0:15:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她解脱的方法只有一个
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.51,0:15:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是结束她的使命
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.39,0:15:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我决定赌一把
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.56,0:15:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赌自己成为魔王 能让灾难降临
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.16,0:16:01.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赌你一定会出现
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.52,0:16:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的使命就到此为止了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.28,0:16:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.89,0:16:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就靠你去救祈了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.39,0:16:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.93,0:16:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.71,0:16:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要责备自己
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.62,0:16:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集让我体会到了很多
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.13,0:16:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都多亏了你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.92,0:16:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集 你在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.42,0:17:01.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.80,0:17:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.53,0:17:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远陪我好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.17,0:17:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我永远在你身边
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.71,0:17:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祈 一起走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.47,0:17:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.01,0:18:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉到樱满同学了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.66,0:18:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集 你想成为救世主吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.33,0:18:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基因结晶构成的框架整体正在崩溃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.77,0:18:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这栋设施马上就要垮掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.62,0:18:25.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.37,0:18:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱满博士 您没事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.64,0:18:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.57,0:18:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是能活下来 以后对人温柔一点
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.31,0:18:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你其实很善良吧 达里尔少爷
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.66,0:18:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家的心灵在流淌进来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.79,0:18:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连着回忆一起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.40,0:19:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算那些对我持有恶意的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.55,0:19:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是在他人的爱中降生的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.78,0:19:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祈…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.63,0:19:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿着
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.20,0:19:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祈！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.98,0:19:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 集还没出来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.83,0:19:55.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道 但我也不能看着你们死
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.10,0:20:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.37,0:21:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谷寻
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.68,0:21:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你挺快嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.83,0:21:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作忙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.86,0:21:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.49,0:21:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过今天提早下班了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.02,0:21:16.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里可以坐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.33,0:21:18.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.78,0:21:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绫姐 格雷伯爵茶可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.52,0:21:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真温柔啊 鶫
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.03,0:21:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有今天哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.02,0:21:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就要教师考试了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.19,0:21:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到家可就原形毕露了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.02,0:21:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙还没到？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.39,0:21:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会来的 他可是很期待的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.35,0:21:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.82,0:21:41.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久没见大家了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.42,0:21:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.38,0:21:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么今年也要好运
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.51,0:21:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干杯！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.82,0:00:14.77,op_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}崩壊の　Symphonyが鳴り響いて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.97,0:00:25.23,op_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}狂う雨はまるで涙の音色
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.22,0:00:28.25,op_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}気づいて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.25,0:00:33.44,op_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}その目は互いを認めるため
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.45,0:00:39.18,op_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}その声は想いを伝えるため
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.19,0:00:49.16,op_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}その手は大事な人とつなぐためにある
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.30,0:00:53.20,op_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}この歌が聴こえてる？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.21,0:00:56.85,op_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}命ある全てのものよ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.86,0:01:01.45,op_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}真実はあなたの胸の中にある
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.47,0:01:04.45,op_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}嵐の海を行く時も　
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.46,0:01:16.88,op_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}決して臆することのない強さを　くれるから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.82,0:00:14.77,op_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}崩坏的交响不断回荡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.97,0:00:25.23,op_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}倾泻的雨仿佛眼泪的音色
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.22,0:00:28.25,op_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}看看我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.25,0:00:33.44,op_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}双眼的存在是为了相互确认对方
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.45,0:00:39.18,op_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}声音的存在是为了相互传达思念
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.19,0:00:49.16,op_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}双手的存在是为了与心爱的人手牵手  心连心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.30,0:00:53.20,op_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}能听到这歌声吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.21,0:00:56.85,op_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}万物生灵啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.86,0:01:01.45,op_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}真相就在你的心中
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.47,0:01:04.45,op_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}即使前往阴风怒号的海洋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.46,0:01:16.88,op_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}也无所畏惧  这首歌将给你这样的勇猛刚强
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.80,0:21:25.85,isong_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}もうあなたから愛されることも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.80,0:21:25.85,isong_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}已经不再被你爱护着
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.47,0:21:32.52,isong_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}必要とされることもない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.47,0:21:32.52,isong_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}也不再被你所需要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.81,0:21:39.16,isong_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}そして私は　こうして一人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.81,0:21:39.16,isong_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}我就这样 独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.80,0:21:41.60,isong_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}落ちて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.80,0:21:41.60,isong_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}坠落
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.06,0:21:49.13,isong_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}あの時あなたはなんて言ったの
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.06,0:21:49.13,isong_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}那时的你说了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.75,0:21:55.82,isong_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}届かない言葉は宙を舞う
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.75,0:21:55.82,isong_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}无法传达的言语早已飘逝
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.24,0:22:02.49,isong_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}分かってるのに　今日もしてしまう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.24,0:22:02.49,isong_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}虽然心里明白  却又一如从前
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.05,0:22:09.13,isong_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}叶わぬ 願いことを
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.05,0:22:09.13,isong_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}许下那  无法实现的愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.24,0:22:15.84,isong_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}はなさないで　ぎゅっと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.24,0:22:15.84,isong_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}请不要放手 紧紧地
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.41,0:22:19.22,isong_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}手を握ってて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.41,0:22:19.22,isong_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}握住我的手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.79,0:22:26.06,isong_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}あなたと二人つづくと言って
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.79,0:22:26.06,isong_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}说好了两人将携手同行
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.31,0:22:35.05,isong_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}繋いだ　その手は暖かくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.31,0:22:35.05,isong_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}牵着我的那双手是如此温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.06,0:22:43.17,isong_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}優しかった
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.06,0:22:43.17,isong_sc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur0.75}如此柔和


