1
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:05,000
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

2
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:05,000
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

3
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:05,000
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

4
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
m 50 0 l 179 0 b 208 0 229 21 229 50 l 229 179 b 229 208 208 228 179 228 l 50 228 b 21 228 0 208 0 179 l 0 50 b 0 21 21 0 50 0

5
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
m 0 0 b 1 -1 2 -2 4 -1 b 7 1 3 2 5 5 b 6 7 8 7 9 5 l 15 -6 b 18 -7 20 -6 20 -3 b 19 -1 17 2 17 4 b 16 7 20 7 21 6 b 22 4 23 2 25 -1 b 27 -2 29 -1 29 1 b 29 2 28 3 29 5 b 30 7 32 7 33 6 b 34 5 34 4 35 3 b 37 2 39 3 39 5 b 39 6 38 8 37 9 b 34 13 29 13 25 9 b 22 13 17 13 13 9 b 10 13 3 13 0 8

6
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

7
00:00:06,000 --> 00:00:46,510
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

8
00:00:05,500 --> 00:00:46,510
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

9
00:00:06,790 --> 00:00:08,390
The news never ends.

10
00:00:08,390 --> 00:00:10,420
This is ten eighty GCR,

11
00:00:10,430 --> 00:00:13,330
you get all the news you need, all day long.

12
00:00:18,790 --> 00:00:21,360
I'm Standale Brodston. Here's what's happening.

13
00:00:21,360 --> 00:00:23,590
It's day eighteen of the garbage stall,

14
00:00:23,590 --> 00:00:26,590
with 10,000 tons of garbage piling up every day,

15
00:00:26,590 --> 00:00:29,920
even the nicest sections of the city are looking like swamps.

16
00:00:29,930 --> 00:00:31,560
Health commissioner Edward O'Roark

17
00:00:31,560 --> 00:00:33,490
is declaring a citywide state of emergency

18
00:00:33,490 --> 00:00:35,220
for the first time in decades.

19
00:00:35,230 --> 00:00:37,420
There's no need to wait until somebody dies

20
00:00:37,430 --> 00:00:39,320
or comes down with typhoid fever.

21
00:00:39,320 --> 00:00:41,390
It's already a serious situation.

22
00:00:41,390 --> 00:00:43,820
It's something that affects almost everyone in the city,

23
00:00:43,820 --> 00:00:46,090
no matter who they are or where they live.

24
00:00:46,090 --> 00:00:48,060
You can't go down no one avenue

25
00:00:48,060 --> 00:00:50,520
without seeing nothing but garbage and rats.

26
00:00:50,530 --> 00:00:51,920
It's starting to affect my business

27
00:00:51,930 --> 00:00:54,760
when customers can't get in here because of garbage situation.

28
00:00:54,760 --> 00:00:56,560
When out there, not just smell it,

29
00:00:56,560 --> 00:00:58,990
but I think to look at it, it's terrible.

30
00:00:58,990 --> 00:01:00,660
It don't affect me, except for the

31
00:01:00,660 --> 00:01:03,220
the very bad smell, it's horrific.

32
00:01:03,220 --> 00:01:04,060
The mess.

33
00:01:04,060 --> 00:01:05,960
I've been in this country for 50 years

34
00:01:05,960 --> 00:01:07,660
and I've never seen anything like it.

35
00:01:07,660 --> 00:01:09,160
What is this world coming to?

36
00:01:09,460 --> 00:01:10,720
Put them in the room

37
00:01:10,720 --> 00:01:11,860
and sit there and talk 'till they got it over with.

38
00:01:11,860 --> 00:01:14,620
24 hours, 48 hours, how long it takes.

39
00:01:14,720 --> 00:01:17,120
The idea of the National Guard pulling in and cleaning up,

40
00:01:17,130 --> 00:01:18,390
it's good idea!

41
00:01:18,430 --> 00:01:20,880
In other news, the Building Industry and Landlords

42
00:01:20,880 --> 00:01:24,760
today expressed concern over the latest increase in heating oil prices.

43
00:01:24,760 --> 00:01:27,530
Renters in the Metro area are certain to...

44
00:02:01,160 --> 00:02:02,220
Let's get it.

45
00:02:03,020 --> 00:02:05,420
- Yo, what's up with your shoes, bro? - Nice outfit, huh?

46
00:02:05,430 --> 00:02:06,260
If you're gonna be a clown,

47
00:02:06,260 --> 00:02:08,290
at least you can be a bill-boy, you know that, right?

48
00:02:09,660 --> 00:02:10,220
Stop it!

49
00:02:10,220 --> 00:02:11,860
Go! Go! Go!

50
00:02:14,260 --> 00:02:17,490
Come on, Kyle, let's go! We've got the sign!

51
00:02:18,190 --> 00:02:18,760
Let's go!

52
00:02:18,760 --> 00:02:20,720
Stop there! Come on!

53
00:02:20,730 --> 00:02:21,960
Watch your go! Watch your go!

54
00:02:24,160 --> 00:02:25,560
Make me stop, clown.

55
00:02:31,890 --> 00:02:33,760
C'mon clown, you are not catching up.

56
00:02:33,760 --> 00:02:34,660
Stop them!

57
00:02:34,660 --> 00:02:35,490
Come on!

58
00:02:36,520 --> 00:02:38,830
Come on! Get out of the way!

59
00:02:40,360 --> 00:02:41,760
Stop them!

60
00:02:48,060 --> 00:02:49,460
You bastards.

61
00:02:55,990 --> 00:02:58,290
Come on, beat his ass up.

62
00:02:58,360 --> 00:03:00,360
Come on, this guy's weak, can't do nothing.

63
00:03:00,360 --> 00:03:01,990
Harder! Harder!

64
00:03:02,360 --> 00:03:03,820
Beat him up. Take his stuff.

65
00:03:03,830 --> 00:03:05,290
Let's go, let's go! Come on, come on, come on!

66
00:03:05,290 --> 00:03:06,390
Let's go, let's go, let's go!

67
00:04:50,190 --> 00:04:51,660
Is it just me,

68
00:04:52,690 --> 00:04:54,720
or is it getting crazier out there?

69
00:04:58,890 --> 00:05:00,830
It is certainly tense.

70
00:05:02,190 --> 00:05:03,660
People are upset.

71
00:05:04,390 --> 00:05:05,430
They're struggling.

72
00:05:05,490 --> 00:05:06,690
Looking for work.

73
00:05:07,190 --> 00:05:08,930
These are tough times.

74
00:05:11,530 --> 00:05:12,460
How 'bout you?

75
00:05:14,730 --> 00:05:16,520
Have you been keeping up with your journal?

76
00:05:18,560 --> 00:05:19,560
Yes, Ma'am.

77
00:05:21,790 --> 00:05:22,690
Great.

78
00:05:24,090 --> 00:05:25,090
Did you bring it with you?

79
00:05:30,190 --> 00:05:31,130
Arthur...

80
00:05:31,560 --> 00:05:34,160
last time I asked you to bring your journal with you

81
00:05:34,160 --> 00:05:35,560
for these appointments.

82
00:05:36,230 --> 00:05:37,460
Can I see it?

83
00:05:49,620 --> 00:05:52,830
I've been using it as a-as a journal,

84
00:05:54,430 --> 00:05:56,390
but also as a joke diary.

85
00:05:56,990 --> 00:06:00,560
Funny thoughts or observations.

86
00:06:01,660 --> 00:06:05,690
I think I told you I'm pursuing a career in stand-up comedy.

87
00:06:09,530 --> 00:06:10,690
No, you didn't.

88
00:06:12,590 --> 00:06:13,860
I think I did.

89
00:06:23,190 --> 00:06:26,560
"I just hope my death makes more cents than my life."

90
00:06:43,190 --> 00:06:45,060
How does it feel to have to come here?

91
00:06:45,760 --> 00:06:48,390
Does it help to have someone to talk to?

92
00:06:52,590 --> 00:06:55,460
I think I felt better when I was locked up in a hospital.

93
00:06:58,020 --> 00:06:59,590
And having thought more about

94
00:07:00,560 --> 00:07:02,260
why you were locked up?

95
00:07:07,760 --> 00:07:09,360
Who knows?

96
00:07:16,660 --> 00:07:18,220
I was wondering if you could ask the doctor

97
00:07:18,230 --> 00:07:20,260
to increase my medication?

98
00:07:26,160 --> 00:07:28,860
Arthur, you're on seven different medications.

99
00:07:30,120 --> 00:07:32,160
Surely, they must be doing something.

100
00:07:35,260 --> 00:07:37,490
I just don't want to feel so bad anymore.

101
00:08:14,730 --> 00:08:16,420
Can you please stop bothering my kid?

102
00:08:19,520 --> 00:08:20,590
- Sit! - I wasn't bothering him...

103
00:08:20,590 --> 00:08:22,160
- Just stop! - I was...

104
00:08:30,640 --> 00:08:32,130
What, you think that's funny?

105
00:08:40,990 --> 00:08:42,530
I'm sorry, I have a co...

106
00:08:59,090 --> 00:09:00,160
I'm sorry.

107
00:10:38,990 --> 00:10:41,690
Happy? Did you check the mail before you came up?

108
00:10:41,990 --> 00:10:43,290
Yeah, mom.

109
00:10:44,290 --> 00:10:45,260
Nothing.

110
00:10:49,160 --> 00:10:51,490
And finally tonight, just when you thought

111
00:10:51,490 --> 00:10:53,290
it couldn't get any worse.

112
00:10:53,290 --> 00:10:56,990
Authorities are saying the city is under siege by scores of rats.

113
00:10:56,990 --> 00:11:00,460
And not just any rats. Super rats. More hard to kill.

114
00:11:00,460 --> 00:11:02,360
He must not be getting any of my letters.

115
00:11:03,990 --> 00:11:06,290
It's Thomas Wayne, mom.

116
00:11:06,590 --> 00:11:09,120
- He is a busy man. - Oh, please.

117
00:11:09,390 --> 00:11:11,660
I worked for that family for years.

118
00:11:11,820 --> 00:11:13,490
The least he could do is write back.

119
00:11:15,430 --> 00:11:18,160
Here, all worked up. Eat.

120
00:11:18,720 --> 00:11:21,160
- You need to eat. - You need to eat.

121
00:11:21,590 --> 00:11:23,260
How skinny you are.

122
00:11:29,160 --> 00:11:31,890
He will make a great mayor. Everybody says so.

123
00:11:32,390 --> 00:11:34,790
Oh, yeah? Everybody who?

124
00:11:34,820 --> 00:11:38,030
- Who do you talk to? - Well, everybody on the news.

125
00:11:38,690 --> 00:11:40,860
He is the only one who could save the city.

126
00:11:41,190 --> 00:11:42,660
He owes it to us.

127
00:11:45,720 --> 00:11:47,220
Come, sit. It's starting.

128
00:11:47,560 --> 00:11:49,060
Oh, my!

129
00:11:49,890 --> 00:11:53,490
From NCB studios in Gotham city!

130
00:11:53,490 --> 00:11:56,660
It's Live with Murray Franklin!

131
00:11:57,790 --> 00:12:00,120
Tonight Murray welcomes, Sandra Winger,

132
00:12:00,130 --> 00:12:05,460
comedian Skip Byron and the piano styling of Yeldon & Chantel!

133
00:12:00,890 --> 00:12:03,220
Sandra Winger's on it.

134
00:12:05,660 --> 00:12:08,060
Joining Murray as always,

135
00:12:08,060 --> 00:12:10,690
Ellis Drane and his Jazz Orchestra.

136
00:12:10,690 --> 00:12:13,220
And now, without further ado,

137
00:12:13,460 --> 00:12:16,720
Murray Franklin!

138
00:12:28,630 --> 00:12:29,530
Thank you.

139
00:12:31,590 --> 00:12:32,660
Thank you.

140
00:12:33,430 --> 00:12:35,490
We've got a great looking audience today.

141
00:12:37,890 --> 00:12:39,330
Thank you. Thank you.

142
00:12:39,960 --> 00:12:40,690
Thank you.

143
00:12:41,430 --> 00:12:42,990
So, everybody's heard about

144
00:12:42,990 --> 00:12:45,760
the super rats stutter in Gotham now, right?

145
00:12:46,690 --> 00:12:50,060
Well, today, the mayor said he has a solution.

146
00:12:50,060 --> 00:12:51,260
You ready for this?

147
00:12:51,660 --> 00:12:53,190
Super cats.

148
00:12:57,590 --> 00:12:59,120
But no, serious it is, I mean these guys are...

149
00:12:59,130 --> 00:13:00,560
I love you, Murray!

150
00:13:02,460 --> 00:13:03,590
I love you, too.

151
00:13:05,530 --> 00:13:07,220
Hey, Bobby, will you put the lights on?

152
00:13:07,690 --> 00:13:09,290
Who is that? Was that you?

153
00:13:09,430 --> 00:13:10,820
You wanna stand up, please?

154
00:13:10,820 --> 00:13:12,530
Stand. Stand up for me.

155
00:13:12,990 --> 00:13:13,930
There.

156
00:13:19,190 --> 00:13:20,190
What's your name?

157
00:13:21,460 --> 00:13:23,660
Hi, Murray. Arthur.

158
00:13:23,660 --> 00:13:25,190
- Arthur? - My name is Arthur.

159
00:13:25,190 --> 00:13:27,490
Okay, well, there is something special about you, Arthur.

160
00:13:27,490 --> 00:13:28,460
I could tell.

161
00:13:28,460 --> 00:13:31,360
- Where are you from? - I live right here in the city.

162
00:13:31,360 --> 00:13:32,860
With my m--mother.

163
00:13:34,530 --> 00:13:36,860
Okay, hold on. Hold on. There is nothing funny about that.

164
00:13:36,860 --> 00:13:39,690
I lived with my mother before I made it. Just me and her.

165
00:13:39,690 --> 00:13:42,530
I'm that kid who's father went out for a pack of cigarettes.

166
00:13:42,760 --> 00:13:44,190
And he never came back.

167
00:13:45,030 --> 00:13:46,690
I know what that's like, Murray.

168
00:13:46,990 --> 00:13:49,830
I've been the man of the house for as long as I can remember.

169
00:13:49,990 --> 00:13:51,690
I take good care of my mother.

170
00:13:56,090 --> 00:13:59,060
All that sacrifice, she must love you very much.

171
00:13:59,060 --> 00:14:00,090
She does.

172
00:14:00,460 --> 00:14:04,360
She always tells me to smile and put on a happy face.

173
00:14:04,620 --> 00:14:07,430
She says I was put here to spread joy and laughter.

174
00:14:15,160 --> 00:14:18,090
I like that. I like that a lot! Come on down.

175
00:14:18,160 --> 00:14:20,020
Come on! For that, you've got to come down.

176
00:14:21,030 --> 00:14:22,360
Come on! Come on!

177
00:14:30,460 --> 00:14:31,220
Come on!

178
00:14:46,620 --> 00:14:48,260
Okay, we've got a big show tonight.

179
00:14:48,260 --> 00:14:50,660
Stay tuned. We will be right back.

180
00:14:51,560 --> 00:14:53,190
That was great, Arthur. Thank you.

181
00:14:53,190 --> 00:14:55,990
I mean, I loved hearing what you had to say, it made my day.

182
00:14:56,430 --> 00:14:57,620
Thanks, Murray.

183
00:14:57,930 --> 00:14:59,890
You see all this, the lights, the show,

184
00:14:59,890 --> 00:15:01,160
the audience, all that stuff?

185
00:15:01,160 --> 00:15:02,540
I'd give it all up in a heartbeat

186
00:15:02,540 --> 00:15:03,930
to have a kid like you.

187
00:15:44,530 --> 00:15:46,060
You're such a jerk.

188
00:15:46,090 --> 00:15:48,390
- What's up, ladies? - Hey, Randall. What's up?

189
00:15:48,390 --> 00:15:50,020
Another day in chuckle town.

190
00:15:54,690 --> 00:15:55,590
You okay?

191
00:15:57,790 --> 00:15:59,860
I heard about the beat-down you took.

192
00:16:00,990 --> 00:16:02,290
Fucking savages.

193
00:16:03,590 --> 00:16:06,660
It was just a bunch of kids. I should've left them alone.

194
00:16:06,660 --> 00:16:09,430
No, they'll take everything from you if you do that.

195
00:16:09,820 --> 00:16:12,660
All the crazy shit out there? They're animals.

196
00:16:17,820 --> 00:16:18,690
You know what?

197
00:16:24,530 --> 00:16:25,360
Here.

198
00:16:27,190 --> 00:16:28,060
What is it?

199
00:16:28,820 --> 00:16:29,560
Take it.

200
00:16:30,790 --> 00:16:31,720
It's for you.

201
00:16:36,460 --> 00:16:38,260
You gotta protect yourself out there,

202
00:16:39,090 --> 00:16:40,620
otherwise you're gonna get fucked.

203
00:16:42,220 --> 00:16:43,160
Randall.

204
00:16:44,790 --> 00:16:47,360
I'm not supposed to have a gun.

205
00:16:48,990 --> 00:16:50,560
Don't sweat it, Art.

206
00:16:51,220 --> 00:16:52,490
No one has to know.

207
00:16:52,590 --> 00:16:54,660
And you can pay me back some other time.

208
00:16:55,190 --> 00:16:56,560
You know you're my boy.

209
00:16:58,790 --> 00:17:02,020
Arthur... Hoyt wants to see you in his office.

210
00:17:02,460 --> 00:17:05,120
Hey, Garry, you know what I've always wondered?

211
00:17:05,120 --> 00:17:06,190
No idea.

212
00:17:06,490 --> 00:17:10,060
Do you people call it miniature golf, or is it just golf to you?

213
00:17:15,130 --> 00:17:16,620
Punch him in the dick, Garry.

214
00:17:33,490 --> 00:17:34,560
Hello, Hoyt.

215
00:17:35,220 --> 00:17:37,590
Garry said you wanted to see me?

216
00:17:38,020 --> 00:17:39,070
How's the comedy career?

217
00:17:39,270 --> 00:17:40,920
You're a famous stand-up yet?

218
00:17:41,130 --> 00:17:42,190
Not quite.

219
00:17:42,360 --> 00:17:44,360
Just been working on my material.

220
00:17:44,360 --> 00:17:46,290
No, don't sit. This will be quick.

221
00:17:46,460 --> 00:17:48,620
Look. I like you, Arthur.

222
00:17:48,630 --> 00:17:50,460
You know, lot of the guys here think you're a freak,

223
00:17:50,460 --> 00:17:51,620
but I like you.

224
00:17:52,190 --> 00:17:53,760
I don't even know why I like you.

225
00:17:54,290 --> 00:17:55,790
But I got another complaint.

226
00:17:56,860 --> 00:17:59,390
And it's starting to piss me off. Kenny's Music.

227
00:17:59,720 --> 00:18:01,490
The guy said you disappeared.

228
00:18:01,890 --> 00:18:03,620
Never even returned his sign.

229
00:18:04,090 --> 00:18:06,190
Because I got jumped.

230
00:18:06,190 --> 00:18:07,460
Didn't you hear?

231
00:18:08,130 --> 00:18:09,160
For a sign?

232
00:18:09,990 --> 00:18:12,390
It's bullshit. It doesn't make sense,

233
00:18:12,660 --> 00:18:14,390
just give him his sign back.

234
00:18:14,490 --> 00:18:16,960
He's going out of business for God's sake, Arthur.

235
00:18:17,090 --> 00:18:18,920
Why would I keep that sign?

236
00:18:19,160 --> 00:18:21,660
How the fuck do I know? Why does anybody do anything?

237
00:18:23,130 --> 00:18:25,060
If you don't return the sign,

238
00:18:25,160 --> 00:18:27,330
I got to take it out of your pay check.

239
00:18:28,490 --> 00:18:29,560
Are we clear?

240
00:18:31,130 --> 00:18:34,520
Listen, I'm trying to help you. Okay?

241
00:18:34,520 --> 00:18:36,060
Now I tell you something else.

242
00:18:36,060 --> 00:18:39,660
The other guys, they don't feel comfortable around you, Arthur.

243
00:18:39,720 --> 00:18:42,220
Because people think you're weird, okay?

244
00:18:42,220 --> 00:18:44,190
And I can't have that around me.

245
00:18:44,190 --> 00:18:46,620
I want it-I want it to work out---

246
00:19:34,090 --> 00:19:36,260
Wait, wait, wait! Wait!

247
00:19:39,860 --> 00:19:40,620
Thank you.

248
00:20:02,960 --> 00:20:05,230
This building is so awful, isn't it?

249
00:20:07,430 --> 00:20:10,220
This building is so awful, right, mommy?

250
00:20:10,220 --> 00:20:12,620
Yeah, sweetie. I hear you, GiGi.

251
00:20:12,690 --> 00:20:15,330
It's so awful, mommy.

252
00:20:16,790 --> 00:20:18,230
Right, mommy?

253
00:20:25,630 --> 00:20:27,760
- Goodnight. - This building's so awful, isn't it?

254
00:20:41,660 --> 00:20:42,460
Come on.

255
00:21:02,160 --> 00:21:02,920
Head up.

256
00:21:03,520 --> 00:21:05,460
Maybe the mailman is throwing them away.

257
00:21:05,790 --> 00:21:07,890
Mom, why are these letters so important to you?

258
00:21:09,520 --> 00:21:12,090
- What do you think he's gonna do? - He's gonna help us.

259
00:21:13,160 --> 00:21:15,060
You worked for them, what?

260
00:21:15,830 --> 00:21:17,360
30 years ago?

261
00:21:17,390 --> 00:21:18,920
Why would he help us?

262
00:21:19,430 --> 00:21:21,860
Because Thomas Wayne is a good man.

263
00:21:22,990 --> 00:21:24,990
If he knew how we were living,

264
00:21:25,690 --> 00:21:28,620
if he saw this place, it would make him sick.

265
00:21:30,490 --> 00:21:32,660
I can't explain it to you any better than that.

266
00:21:35,130 --> 00:21:37,190
I don't want you worrying about money.

267
00:21:38,220 --> 00:21:39,260
Or me.

268
00:21:39,860 --> 00:21:43,960
Everybody's telling me that my stand-up is ready for the big clubs.

269
00:21:44,990 --> 00:21:47,660
But, Happy, what makes you think you could do that?

270
00:21:48,090 --> 00:21:49,590
- What do you mean? - I mean...

271
00:21:51,060 --> 00:21:53,060
don't you have to be funny to be a comedian?

272
00:22:56,930 --> 00:22:58,360
Hey, what's your name?

273
00:22:59,360 --> 00:23:00,360
Arthur.

274
00:23:01,330 --> 00:23:02,360
Hey, Arthur.

275
00:23:02,660 --> 00:23:04,330
You're a really good dancer.

276
00:23:05,260 --> 00:23:06,120
I know.

277
00:23:06,990 --> 00:23:07,990
And who is not?

278
00:23:08,660 --> 00:23:09,390
Him.

279
00:23:14,830 --> 00:23:16,960
Happy! What was that? Are you okay?

280
00:23:16,960 --> 00:23:18,160
Mom, what?

281
00:23:18,160 --> 00:23:20,320
That noise! Did you hear that noise?

282
00:23:20,330 --> 00:23:22,830
I'm-I'm watching an old war movie!

283
00:23:22,960 --> 00:23:24,490
Turn it down!

284
00:23:30,660 --> 00:23:31,960
Sorry, mom.

285
00:23:45,430 --> 00:23:46,190
You good?

286
00:24:53,690 --> 00:24:56,190
It's nice to see these couples are at my show.

287
00:24:57,060 --> 00:24:59,330
I have a wife, we love to role play.

288
00:24:59,790 --> 00:25:02,230
Yes. Yes, very sexy.

289
00:25:02,330 --> 00:25:03,920
My favorite one right now is...

290
00:25:03,930 --> 00:25:08,530
professor and senior who really needs to pass my class to graduate.

291
00:25:09,490 --> 00:25:10,590
Yes.

292
00:25:12,220 --> 00:25:13,720
So I tell you how I operate.

293
00:25:13,720 --> 00:25:16,560
I'm a professor at a prestigious New England university.

294
00:25:18,020 --> 00:25:21,860
And my wife is a senior in my intro to western civ.

295
00:25:23,960 --> 00:25:27,290
I know, I know, why is she-why is she a senior in intro?

296
00:25:27,290 --> 00:25:28,830
I didn't buy it either.

297
00:25:29,560 --> 00:25:31,690
So she comes to me during my office hours,

298
00:25:32,560 --> 00:25:34,290
Monday and Wednesday 3:00 to 5:00,

299
00:25:34,290 --> 00:25:36,490
and she says, "Excuse me, Professor Lewis."

300
00:25:36,660 --> 00:25:38,810
I can't use my real last name at this collage

301
00:25:38,810 --> 00:25:40,360
'cause they don't hire Jews.

302
00:25:42,220 --> 00:25:45,160
Something I'll address once I have a tenure, but for now...

303
00:25:46,130 --> 00:25:47,660
She says, "Excuse me, Professor Lewis.

304
00:25:47,660 --> 00:25:50,290
I think I might be in danger of failing intro to western civ,

305
00:25:50,290 --> 00:25:53,460
and I just want you to know I'm willing to do anything to pass."

306
00:25:53,860 --> 00:25:57,620
I said "anything?", and she says "Aah".

307
00:27:07,160 --> 00:27:08,530
Were you following me today?

308
00:27:12,220 --> 00:27:13,030
Yeah.

309
00:27:15,790 --> 00:27:17,120
I thought that was you.

310
00:27:18,590 --> 00:27:20,790
I was hoping you'd come in and rob the place.

311
00:27:23,020 --> 00:27:24,260
I have a gun.

312
00:27:24,690 --> 00:27:25,890
I'll come by tomorrow.

313
00:27:29,690 --> 00:27:31,220
You're so funny, Arthur.

314
00:27:33,560 --> 00:27:34,360
Yeah...

315
00:27:34,960 --> 00:27:37,460
You know, I--I do stand-up comedy.

316
00:27:37,760 --> 00:27:40,390
You should maybe come and see a show sometime.

317
00:27:41,060 --> 00:27:42,190
I could do that.

318
00:27:42,690 --> 00:27:43,460
Yeah?

319
00:27:43,960 --> 00:27:45,690
Yeah. You let me know when?

320
00:27:45,890 --> 00:27:46,590
Yeah.

321
00:27:53,820 --> 00:27:58,490
♪ If you're happy and you know it, wiggle your ears ♪

322
00:27:58,490 --> 00:28:02,990
♪ If you're happy and you know it, wiggle your ears ♪

323
00:28:02,990 --> 00:28:05,120
♪ If you're happy and you know it, ♪

324
00:28:05,130 --> 00:28:07,590
♪  and you feel it, well, just show it ♪

325
00:28:07,590 --> 00:28:12,320
♪ If you're happy and you know it, wiggle your ears ♪

326
00:28:12,320 --> 00:28:16,760
♪ If you're happy and you know it, stomp your feet ♪

327
00:28:16,760 --> 00:28:21,390
♪ If you're happy and you know it, stomp your feet ♪

328
00:28:21,390 --> 00:28:23,820
♪ If you're happy and you know it, ♪

329
00:28:23,820 --> 00:28:26,220
♪ and you feel it, well, just show it ♪

330
00:28:26,220 --> 00:28:30,690
♪ If you're happy and you know it, stomp your feet ♪

331
00:28:30,690 --> 00:28:35,320
♪ If you're happy and you know it, shout "Hooray" ♪

332
00:28:35,320 --> 00:28:39,990
♪ If you're happy and you know it, shout "Hooray" ♪

333
00:28:39,990 --> 00:28:43,860
♪ If you're happy and you know it, and you feel it,--♪

334
00:28:43,860 --> 00:28:45,830
Hoyt, please.

335
00:28:45,990 --> 00:28:47,420
I love this job.

336
00:28:47,430 --> 00:28:52,060
Arthur, I need to know why you brought a gun into a kids hospital.

337
00:28:52,060 --> 00:28:55,030
It's a prop. It's part of my act now.

338
00:28:55,190 --> 00:28:57,190
That's bullshit! Bullshit!

339
00:28:57,190 --> 00:28:59,530
What kind of a clown carries a fucking gun?

340
00:28:59,990 --> 00:29:04,300
Besides, Randall told me you tried to buy a .38 off him last week.

341
00:29:04,830 --> 00:29:07,240
- Randall told you that? - You're a fuck-up, Arthur.

342
00:29:07,480 --> 00:29:08,530
And a liar.

343
00:29:09,190 --> 00:29:10,210
You're fired!

344
00:29:42,100 --> 00:29:43,860
I'm telling you, she wanted my number.

345
00:29:43,860 --> 00:29:45,050
We should have just stayed.

346
00:29:45,050 --> 00:29:47,880
You're dreaming, man. She wasn't interested... at all.

347
00:29:47,880 --> 00:29:50,290
Are you nuts? Did you see how close we were dancing!?

348
00:29:50,290 --> 00:29:51,380
She was in love, bro.

349
00:29:51,380 --> 00:29:53,010
She couldn't wait to get away from you.

350
00:29:53,010 --> 00:29:55,710
Ryan. Ryan, am I crazy? Tell him what you saw.

351
00:29:57,790 --> 00:29:59,420
You want some french fries?

352
00:30:02,540 --> 00:30:04,710
Hello....?

353
00:30:05,730 --> 00:30:08,540
- I'm talking to you. Hey. - No, thank you.

354
00:30:11,460 --> 00:30:12,170
You sure?

355
00:30:14,470 --> 00:30:15,520
They're really good.

356
00:30:18,440 --> 00:30:21,520
Don't ignore him. He's being nice to you.

357
00:30:48,160 --> 00:30:49,760
Is something funny, asshole?

358
00:30:53,950 --> 00:30:55,420
Bitch!

359
00:31:02,130 --> 00:31:04,840
♪ Isn't it rich? ♪

360
00:31:05,800 --> 00:31:08,250
♪ Are we a pair? ♪

361
00:31:10,640 --> 00:31:13,700
♪ Me here, at last on the ground ♪

362
00:31:13,700 --> 00:31:16,340
♪ You in mid-air ♪

363
00:31:16,820 --> 00:31:20,610
♪ Send in the clowns. ♪

364
00:31:24,070 --> 00:31:26,330
♪ Isn't it bliss? ♪

365
00:31:27,160 --> 00:31:29,120
♪ Don't you approve? ♪

366
00:31:29,120 --> 00:31:30,510
Please. Don't.

367
00:31:30,510 --> 00:31:33,130
♪ One who keeps tearing around, ♪

368
00:31:33,130 --> 00:31:35,670
♪ One who can't move. ♪

369
00:31:35,670 --> 00:31:38,320
♪ Where are the clowns? ♪

370
00:31:38,660 --> 00:31:43,720
♪ There ought to be clowns. ♪

371
00:31:52,530 --> 00:31:55,420
So, buddy, tell us. What's so fucking funny?

372
00:31:55,580 --> 00:31:57,130
Nothing. I---

373
00:32:01,080 --> 00:32:02,960
I have a--- I have a condition.

374
00:32:02,960 --> 00:32:05,280
I'll tell you what you have, asshole.

375
00:32:08,840 --> 00:32:10,220
Please, stop!

376
00:32:12,070 --> 00:32:15,530
We've got a kicker, huh? Hey, hold him steady, hold him steady.

377
00:32:17,600 --> 00:32:19,110
Stay down, freak!

378
00:32:31,140 --> 00:32:33,810
No! No!

379
00:32:38,400 --> 00:32:41,180
Hey! Help! Help!

380
00:33:12,230 --> 00:33:13,800
Stay clear of the closing doors.

381
00:33:50,950 --> 00:33:51,640
Shit.

382
00:33:53,130 --> 00:33:53,970
Shit.

383
00:36:46,830 --> 00:36:48,910
I read it was a guy in full make-up.

384
00:36:48,910 --> 00:36:51,730
No, it says right here it was a mask.

385
00:36:51,730 --> 00:36:53,900
Either way, I think it's good for business.

386
00:36:53,900 --> 00:36:56,250
They got clowns in front of every newspaper.

387
00:36:56,400 --> 00:36:58,050
Big man, what's the good word?

388
00:37:01,920 --> 00:37:04,260
Hey, Arthur. I heard what happened.

389
00:37:04,560 --> 00:37:05,490
Sorry, mate.

390
00:37:06,210 --> 00:37:08,840
Yeah, it doesn't seem fair,

391
00:37:08,890 --> 00:37:10,490
you get fired like that.

392
00:37:11,770 --> 00:37:14,400
Did you really bring a gun to the children's hospital, Arty?

393
00:37:15,660 --> 00:37:17,170
What the fuck would you do that for?

394
00:37:17,240 --> 00:37:18,630
Is that part of your new act, Arthur?

395
00:37:18,630 --> 00:37:19,830
If your dancing doesn't do the trick,

396
00:37:19,830 --> 00:37:21,190
you just gonna shoot yourself?

397
00:37:22,540 --> 00:37:24,390
Why don't you ask Randall about it?

398
00:37:24,900 --> 00:37:26,190
It was his gun.

399
00:37:26,410 --> 00:37:29,420
- What? - I still owe you for that, don't I?

400
00:37:29,420 --> 00:37:31,120
What the fuck are you talking about?

401
00:37:31,620 --> 00:37:33,680
Stop talking outta your ass, Art!

402
00:37:38,790 --> 00:37:39,870
Oh, no!

403
00:37:41,710 --> 00:37:43,290
I forgot to punch out.

404
00:38:13,570 --> 00:38:17,330
And as our city tries to make sense of the brutal

405
00:38:17,330 --> 00:38:19,600
triple murder on the subway last week.

406
00:38:19,770 --> 00:38:21,370
We're joined by Thomas Wayne.

407
00:38:21,380 --> 00:38:23,460
- Happy, look. Thomas Wayne's on TV. - He has a personal connection

408
00:38:23,460 --> 00:38:25,280
- this tragedy. - Yes, mother.

409
00:38:25,280 --> 00:38:26,460
Thanks for having me on show.

410
00:38:26,460 --> 00:38:29,330
They're asking him about those horrible subway murders.

411
00:38:29,560 --> 00:38:32,800
Thank you, Thomas. I know this is a difficult time for you.

412
00:38:32,800 --> 00:38:34,680
- Why him? - These young men all were...

413
00:38:34,680 --> 00:38:36,130
Looks like his compaign.

414
00:38:36,940 --> 00:38:39,170
Yes, all three of them worked for Wayne Investments.

415
00:38:39,260 --> 00:38:40,920
Good, decent, educated,

416
00:38:40,920 --> 00:38:44,160
although, I didn't know any of them personally.

417
00:38:45,220 --> 00:38:47,310
Like all the Wayne employees, past and present,

418
00:38:48,380 --> 00:38:49,330
they were family.

419
00:38:49,330 --> 00:38:51,470
- You hear that! I told you. We're family. - There now seems to be a

420
00:38:51,470 --> 00:38:55,180
groundswell of anti-rich sentiment in the city.

421
00:38:55,180 --> 00:38:57,690
It's almost as if our less fortunate residents

422
00:38:57,690 --> 00:38:59,530
are taken the side of the killer.

423
00:38:59,530 --> 00:39:01,030
Yes and it's a shame.

424
00:39:01,350 --> 00:39:04,280
It's one of the reasons why I'm considering a run for mayor.

425
00:39:04,770 --> 00:39:06,530
Gotham has lost its way.

426
00:39:07,210 --> 00:39:08,670
What about the eyewitness report

427
00:39:08,680 --> 00:39:11,650
of the suspect being a man in a clown mask?

428
00:39:11,940 --> 00:39:13,700
Well, it makes total sense to me.

429
00:39:14,070 --> 00:39:16,470
What kind of a coward would do something that cold-blooded ?

430
00:39:16,470 --> 00:39:18,850
Someone who hides behind a mask.

431
00:39:18,870 --> 00:39:23,840
Someone who is envious of those more fortunate than themselves,

432
00:39:24,510 --> 00:39:26,850
yet they're too scared to show their own face.

433
00:39:27,460 --> 00:39:30,110
And until all those kind of people change for the better..

434
00:39:30,520 --> 00:39:34,350
those of us who've made something of our lives,

435
00:39:34,360 --> 00:39:36,230
will always look at those who haven't

436
00:39:36,790 --> 00:39:38,600
as nothing but clowns.

437
00:39:40,710 --> 00:39:43,310
Thomas Wayne, thank you for coming in this morning.

438
00:39:43,310 --> 00:39:44,480
It's not funny.

439
00:40:05,950 --> 00:40:08,490
I heard this song on the radio the other day.

440
00:40:11,000 --> 00:40:12,540
And the guy was singing,

441
00:40:13,150 --> 00:40:15,140
that his name was Carnival.

442
00:40:16,120 --> 00:40:18,710
- Arthur. - It's just crazy,

443
00:40:21,040 --> 00:40:23,550
because that's my clown name. At work.

444
00:40:25,150 --> 00:40:27,010
But until a while ago

445
00:40:28,760 --> 00:40:30,970
it was like nobody ever saw me.

446
00:40:33,350 --> 00:40:35,610
Even I didn't know if I really existed.

447
00:40:36,120 --> 00:40:37,770
Arthur, I have some bad news for you.

448
00:40:41,870 --> 00:40:43,280
You don't listen, do you?

449
00:40:44,990 --> 00:40:46,760
I don't think you ever

450
00:40:47,480 --> 00:40:49,100
really hear me.

451
00:40:50,120 --> 00:40:52,750
You just ask the same questions every week:

452
00:40:52,990 --> 00:40:54,160
"How's your job?"

453
00:40:54,390 --> 00:40:56,570
"Are you having any negative thoughts?"

454
00:40:57,370 --> 00:41:00,700
All I have are negative thoughts.

455
00:41:01,190 --> 00:41:03,710
But you don't listen, anyway.

456
00:41:04,260 --> 00:41:05,330
I said,

457
00:41:05,750 --> 00:41:07,460
for my whole life

458
00:41:07,860 --> 00:41:10,980
I didn't know if I even really existed.

459
00:41:12,350 --> 00:41:13,680
But I do.

460
00:41:15,360 --> 00:41:18,690
And people are starting to notice.

461
00:41:21,090 --> 00:41:22,230
They've cut our funding.

462
00:41:22,990 --> 00:41:24,930
We're closing down our offices next week.

463
00:41:26,360 --> 00:41:28,340
The city's cut funding across the board,

464
00:41:28,340 --> 00:41:30,260
social services is part of that.

465
00:41:30,470 --> 00:41:32,340
This is the last time we will be meeting.

466
00:41:33,490 --> 00:41:34,210
Okay.

467
00:41:38,820 --> 00:41:41,230
They don't give a shit about people like you, Arthur.

468
00:41:43,130 --> 00:41:46,210
And they really don't give a shit about people like me, either.

469
00:41:49,870 --> 00:41:50,650
Oh, fuck.

470
00:41:59,330 --> 00:42:01,600
How am I supposed to get my medication now?

471
00:42:04,970 --> 00:42:05,980
Who do I talk to?

472
00:42:08,920 --> 00:42:10,460
I'm sorry, Arthur.

473
00:42:13,140 --> 00:42:17,080
I think, uh-- I think most women look at sex like buying a car.

474
00:42:17,660 --> 00:42:20,050
You know, like, "Can I see myself in this long term?"

475
00:42:20,520 --> 00:42:23,890
Is it safe? Is it reliable?

476
00:42:24,080 --> 00:42:25,530
Could it kill me?

477
00:42:26,620 --> 00:42:28,700
Most guys look at sex like parking a car.

478
00:42:28,700 --> 00:42:30,240
We're like "There's a spot".

479
00:42:31,220 --> 00:42:33,230
"There is another spot, that would work."

480
00:42:33,700 --> 00:42:36,150
"Oh, I have to pay? Never mind."

481
00:42:37,900 --> 00:42:40,770
"Handicapped? Hope no one sees us."

482
00:42:43,510 --> 00:42:45,820
Alright that's my time. Thank you very much, guys.

483
00:42:50,830 --> 00:42:52,670
One more time, Sam Mohr, ya' all.

484
00:42:54,140 --> 00:42:55,790
Alright, this next comic

485
00:42:55,790 --> 00:42:58,380
describes himself as a lifelong Gotham resident

486
00:42:58,380 --> 00:43:00,890
who from a young age was always told that:

487
00:43:00,890 --> 00:43:02,200
"His purpose in life was to

488
00:43:02,200 --> 00:43:06,030
bring laughter and joy into this cold, dark world."

489
00:43:06,920 --> 00:43:07,780
Okay.

490
00:43:08,110 --> 00:43:11,850
Please help me welcome Arthur Fleck, ya'all. Arthur Fleck.

491
00:43:35,920 --> 00:43:38,110
Hello, it's good to be here---

492
00:43:50,200 --> 00:43:51,110
I hate--

493
00:44:02,330 --> 00:44:04,650
I---I hated

494
00:44:04,650 --> 00:44:06,250
school as a kid.

495
00:44:21,650 --> 00:44:25,500
I hated school as a-- as a kid.

496
00:44:27,700 --> 00:44:29,200
But my mother would always say,

497
00:44:29,510 --> 00:44:33,470
"You should enjoy it. One day you'll have to work for a living."

498
00:44:34,530 --> 00:44:37,990
"No I won't, Ma. I'm gonna be a comedian!"

499
00:44:50,240 --> 00:44:50,920
Here is one.

500
00:44:52,820 --> 00:44:56,090
You know, I was just thinking the other day,

501
00:44:56,460 --> 00:44:59,420
why are the rich people so---

502
00:45:38,340 --> 00:45:39,670
Do you believe that shit?

503
00:45:41,760 --> 00:45:42,460
Fuck 'em!

504
00:45:44,670 --> 00:45:46,620
I think the guy that did it is a hero.

505
00:45:49,240 --> 00:45:53,040
Three less pricks in Gotham city, only a million more to go.

506
00:46:23,240 --> 00:46:25,060
I know what you're gonna be thinking.

507
00:46:25,160 --> 00:46:28,110
And buddy, as always thanks for the laughs.

508
00:46:28,150 --> 00:46:31,660
Sure, will see you again. You will be here, right? I hope.

509
00:46:32,480 --> 00:46:35,160
Tomorrow night, we have Diana Hudson,

510
00:46:35,160 --> 00:46:39,220
Grieg Gordon, and animal expert Hugh Little.

511
00:46:39,750 --> 00:46:40,990
Thanks for watching.

512
00:46:41,280 --> 00:46:43,280
Good night. And always remember

513
00:46:43,720 --> 00:46:45,210
"That's Life".

514
00:46:49,520 --> 00:46:50,510
That's life.

515
00:46:55,560 --> 00:46:58,630
Mom, time to wake up. We go to bed.

516
00:47:02,290 --> 00:47:04,000
No, Happy.

517
00:47:06,380 --> 00:47:08,350
I wrote him a new letter.

518
00:47:08,500 --> 00:47:10,080
Come on, dance with me.

519
00:47:11,150 --> 00:47:13,730
For Thomas Wayne. That's important.

520
00:47:22,320 --> 00:47:23,780
You smell like cologne.

521
00:47:24,500 --> 00:47:26,460
Because I just had a big date.

522
00:47:31,230 --> 00:47:33,310
Just don't forget to mail it.

523
00:47:58,890 --> 00:48:01,110
The Murray Franklin show is taking alive

524
00:48:01,110 --> 00:48:04,550
before a studio audience in beautiful downtown Gotham city.

525
00:49:06,550 --> 00:49:09,570
You're gonna kill me! You're gonna give me a heart attack!

526
00:49:09,570 --> 00:49:12,470
- Don't give me your-- - No! No!

527
00:49:12,970 --> 00:49:15,950
I'm not talking to you until you stop being angry!

528
00:49:15,950 --> 00:49:16,910
Okay.

529
00:49:17,540 --> 00:49:18,250
Okay.

530
00:49:23,020 --> 00:49:24,350
I'm not angry, mom.

531
00:49:25,420 --> 00:49:26,460
I'm not angry.

532
00:49:27,840 --> 00:49:28,800
Please.

533
00:49:30,100 --> 00:49:33,070
Mom, is this real?

534
00:49:36,480 --> 00:49:39,340
He is an extraordinary man, Happy.

535
00:49:39,950 --> 00:49:41,960
He is a very powerful man.

536
00:49:43,750 --> 00:49:45,110
We were in love.

537
00:49:46,710 --> 00:49:48,820
He said it was best if we would not be together

538
00:49:48,820 --> 00:49:50,490
because of appearances.

539
00:49:53,280 --> 00:49:56,500
And I couldn't tell anyone because,

540
00:49:57,560 --> 00:49:58,270
well,

541
00:49:59,120 --> 00:50:00,680
I signed some papers.

542
00:50:02,400 --> 00:50:05,710
And besides, you can imagine what people would say about

543
00:50:06,330 --> 00:50:08,190
Thomas and me and...

544
00:50:10,120 --> 00:50:11,620
what they'd say about you.

545
00:50:15,870 --> 00:50:17,570
What would they say, mom?

546
00:52:55,030 --> 00:52:56,070
What's your name?

547
00:52:57,730 --> 00:52:58,520
I'm Bruce.

548
00:53:00,390 --> 00:53:01,480
Bruce.

549
00:53:03,480 --> 00:53:04,500
I'm Arthur.

550
00:53:26,790 --> 00:53:28,030
That's better.

551
00:53:28,870 --> 00:53:31,070
Bruce! Bruce!

552
00:53:32,220 --> 00:53:35,000
- Get away from that man. - It's okay. I'm a good guy.

553
00:53:35,380 --> 00:53:36,620
What are you doing? Who are you?

554
00:53:37,570 --> 00:53:39,180
I'm here to see Mr. Wayne.

555
00:53:39,440 --> 00:53:42,090
Well, you shouldn't be speaking to his son.

556
00:53:43,330 --> 00:53:46,330
- Why did you give him these flowers? - No, they're not real.

557
00:53:47,630 --> 00:53:49,390
It's...magic.

558
00:53:50,150 --> 00:53:51,850
I was just trying to make him smile.

559
00:53:51,850 --> 00:53:53,370
Well, It's not funny, is it?

560
00:53:54,490 --> 00:53:55,820
Do I need to call the police?

561
00:53:55,960 --> 00:53:57,700
No, please.

562
00:53:58,610 --> 00:54:00,240
My mother's name is Penny.

563
00:54:00,490 --> 00:54:01,700
Penny Fleck.

564
00:54:01,900 --> 00:54:03,240
She used to work here years ago.

565
00:54:03,250 --> 00:54:05,380
Can you please tell Mr. Wayne I need to see him?

566
00:54:06,580 --> 00:54:07,730
You're her son?

567
00:54:08,220 --> 00:54:08,890
Yeah.

568
00:54:09,840 --> 00:54:10,960
Did you know her?

569
00:54:15,170 --> 00:54:17,130
I know about the two of them.

570
00:54:18,010 --> 00:54:19,480
She told me everything.

571
00:54:22,460 --> 00:54:23,930
There's nothing to know.

572
00:54:25,260 --> 00:54:26,930
There is no "Them".

573
00:54:28,120 --> 00:54:29,790
Your mother was delusional.

574
00:54:31,080 --> 00:54:33,100
- She was a sick woman. - Don't

575
00:54:33,710 --> 00:54:34,610
say that.

576
00:54:35,600 --> 00:54:36,510
Just go.

577
00:54:38,330 --> 00:54:40,070
Before you make a fool of yourself.

578
00:54:42,230 --> 00:54:44,740
Thomas Wayne is my father.

579
00:54:50,200 --> 00:54:51,220
He left me!

580
00:54:53,650 --> 00:54:54,670
Let go!

581
00:55:21,400 --> 00:55:23,350
Keep respirations at 15.

582
00:55:23,350 --> 00:55:25,620
Slow, there're some stairs coming up.

583
00:55:26,820 --> 00:55:27,460
Mom?

584
00:55:29,140 --> 00:55:30,570
- What happened? - Who are you?

585
00:55:30,570 --> 00:55:32,210
- I'm her son. - Oh, great.

586
00:55:32,210 --> 00:55:33,990
- What happened? - You can probably help us out to decide.

587
00:55:33,990 --> 00:55:34,700
We don't know what happened yet.

588
00:55:34,700 --> 00:55:36,240
Hop in the back of the ambulance.

589
00:55:36,730 --> 00:55:38,670
Come on. We have one more left.

590
00:55:38,670 --> 00:55:39,910
I'm getting a little resistence here, Mike.

591
00:55:39,910 --> 00:55:41,950
Come on, give her a lift.

592
00:55:41,950 --> 00:55:43,180
Position her head.

593
00:55:43,180 --> 00:55:43,840
Lift.

594
00:55:49,880 --> 00:55:50,780
I'm here.

595
00:55:51,710 --> 00:55:52,620
Excuse me, sir.

596
00:55:53,080 --> 00:55:55,140
- Does your mother take any medications? - No.

597
00:55:55,140 --> 00:55:56,310
- Excuse me, I can't hear you. - No.

598
00:55:56,310 --> 00:55:58,970
- Sir, what was the last time you spoke to her? - I don't know.

599
00:56:44,080 --> 00:56:45,280
Mr. Fleck.

600
00:56:46,660 --> 00:56:48,670
Sorry to bother you. I'm detective Garrity.

601
00:56:48,670 --> 00:56:50,790
This is my partner detective Burke.

602
00:56:51,380 --> 00:56:54,110
We had a few questions for you, but you weren't home.

603
00:56:54,250 --> 00:56:56,940
So... we spoke with your mother.

604
00:57:01,140 --> 00:57:02,570
What did you say to her?

605
00:57:02,700 --> 00:57:04,480
- Did you do this? - What?

606
00:57:04,590 --> 00:57:07,360
No. No, no. No, we just asked her some questions.

607
00:57:07,630 --> 00:57:08,990
And she got hysterical..

608
00:57:09,270 --> 00:57:10,710
hyperventilating,

609
00:57:10,710 --> 00:57:12,000
then collapsed and hit her head pretty hard.

610
00:57:12,010 --> 00:57:14,680
Yeah, the doctor said she had a stroke.

611
00:57:15,290 --> 00:57:16,880
We're sorry to hear about that.

612
00:57:17,910 --> 00:57:20,480
But like I said, I still has some questions for you.

613
00:57:20,910 --> 00:57:23,510
They're about the subway killings that happened last week.

614
00:57:23,510 --> 00:57:25,760
- You've heard about them, right? - Yeah.

615
00:57:26,290 --> 00:57:28,180
- It's horrible. - Right.

616
00:57:29,460 --> 00:57:32,900
So with spoke with your boss over at...Ha-Ha's.

617
00:57:32,900 --> 00:57:34,120
He said you were fired for

618
00:57:34,120 --> 00:57:36,560
bringing a gun into the children's hospital.

619
00:57:37,950 --> 00:57:39,690
- Is that true, Mr. Fleck? - It was a prop.

620
00:57:40,060 --> 00:57:41,370
It was part of my act.

621
00:57:42,070 --> 00:57:43,300
I'm a party clown.

622
00:57:43,610 --> 00:57:45,490
Alright, so why were you fired?

623
00:57:48,810 --> 00:57:51,140
They said I wasn't funny enough.

624
00:57:51,530 --> 00:57:52,780
Can you imagine that?

625
00:57:53,610 --> 00:57:54,800
If you don't mind,

626
00:57:55,410 --> 00:57:57,050
I have to go and take care of my mother.

627
00:57:57,700 --> 00:58:00,380
Your boss also gave us one of your cards.

628
00:58:02,150 --> 00:58:04,230
This condition of yours, laughing.

629
00:58:05,440 --> 00:58:08,270
Is it real, or some sort of a clown thing?

630
00:58:08,980 --> 00:58:11,340
- "A clown thing?" - Yeah.

631
00:58:11,910 --> 00:58:14,370
I mean, part of your act?

632
00:58:16,880 --> 00:58:17,940
What do you think?

633
00:58:24,140 --> 00:58:25,700
It's exit only.

634
00:58:49,770 --> 00:58:51,570
She's gonna be okay.

635
00:58:56,440 --> 00:58:57,970
I'll get a coffee.

636
00:58:58,610 --> 00:59:00,500
- You want one? - Yeah.

637
00:59:13,880 --> 00:59:16,840
So, the other night I told my youngest son, Billy,

638
00:59:16,840 --> 00:59:19,870
you know, the new one, the-- not so bright one,

639
00:59:20,270 --> 00:59:23,240
I-- I told him the garbage strike is still going on, Billy,..

640
00:59:23,240 --> 00:59:25,370
and he says, and I'm not kidding, Billy says,

641
00:59:25,380 --> 00:59:27,730
"So where are we gonna get all our garbage from?"

642
00:59:34,940 --> 00:59:36,130
And finally,

643
00:59:36,170 --> 00:59:38,870
in a world where everyone thinks they could do my job,

644
00:59:38,880 --> 00:59:41,140
we got this video tape from Pogo's comedy club

645
00:59:41,140 --> 00:59:42,410
right here in Gotham.

646
00:59:42,410 --> 00:59:44,970
Here's a guy who thinks if you just keep laughing,

647
00:59:44,980 --> 00:59:46,670
it'll somehow make you funny.

648
00:59:46,840 --> 00:59:48,300
Check out this joker.

649
00:59:53,670 --> 00:59:54,530
Oh, no!

650
00:59:54,540 --> 00:59:58,400
I hated school as a kid.

651
00:59:58,940 --> 01:00:01,470
But my mother would always say,

652
01:00:02,140 --> 01:00:03,710
"You know, you should enjoy it.

653
01:00:03,710 --> 01:00:06,340
One day you'll have to work for a living."

654
01:00:06,770 --> 01:00:10,270
"No I won't, Ma. I'm gonna be a comedian!"

655
01:00:16,740 --> 01:00:18,370
You should have listened to your mother.

656
01:00:20,740 --> 01:00:22,440
And one more. One more, Bobby.

657
01:00:22,440 --> 01:00:24,630
Let's see one more. I love this guy.

658
01:00:25,940 --> 01:00:27,130
It's funny.

659
01:00:27,440 --> 01:00:29,270
When I was a little boy

660
01:00:29,540 --> 01:00:32,470
and told people I was gonna be a comedian,

661
01:00:32,810 --> 01:00:34,730
everyone laughed at me.

662
01:00:35,270 --> 01:00:37,030
Well, no one's laughing now.

663
01:00:41,380 --> 01:00:43,100
You can say that again, pal.

664
01:00:49,040 --> 01:00:50,100
Alright,

665
01:00:50,270 --> 01:00:53,530
We got a great show for you tonight. Chuck Cambie is here.

666
01:00:53,530 --> 01:00:55,340
Actress Joan Mulligan,

667
01:00:55,340 --> 01:00:59,600
and new music from Melruban and the stiff.

668
01:01:05,140 --> 01:01:08,040
As tensions mount around the metro area,

669
01:01:08,040 --> 01:01:11,570
Mayor Stokes has pleaded for cooler heads to prevail.

670
01:01:11,640 --> 01:01:13,540
City services have been affected

671
01:01:13,540 --> 01:01:18,340
and some businesses have decided to remain closed amid the unrest.

672
01:01:18,340 --> 01:01:20,940
Chuck Stevens filed this report.

673
01:01:21,140 --> 01:01:24,070
The anger and resentment that's been building in the city for weeks

674
01:01:24,070 --> 01:01:25,970
seems close to exploding.

675
01:01:25,980 --> 01:01:28,210
Protesters, many dressed as clowns,

676
01:01:28,210 --> 01:01:29,610
took the streets today

677
01:01:29,610 --> 01:01:33,110
in one of the several plan demonstrations taking on the city's elite,

678
01:01:33,110 --> 01:01:37,340
including a massive rally outside tomorrow night's benefit at Wayne home.

679
01:01:37,540 --> 01:01:39,070
What's the point of all this?

680
01:01:39,210 --> 01:01:41,470
Fuck the rich! Fuck Thomas Wayne.

681
01:01:41,510 --> 01:01:43,240
That's what this all fucking thing was about.

682
01:01:43,240 --> 01:01:44,470
Fuck all this system!

683
01:01:45,010 --> 01:01:47,470
Wayne, who recently announced his running for mayor

684
01:01:47,480 --> 01:01:49,270
will be attending the benefit.

685
01:01:49,310 --> 01:01:51,370
You might remember, it was Thomas Wayne

686
01:01:51,380 --> 01:01:55,500
who first referred to many of Gotam's residents as "clowns".

687
01:01:55,640 --> 01:01:58,670
Today, he offered little in way of an apology.

688
01:01:59,040 --> 01:02:00,210
Well, what I will say is,

689
01:02:00,210 --> 01:02:01,640
there's something wrong with those people.

690
01:02:01,640 --> 01:02:02,940
And I'm here to help them.

691
01:02:02,940 --> 01:02:04,110
I'm gonna lift them out of poverty,

692
01:02:04,110 --> 01:02:05,640
help make their lives better.

693
01:02:05,640 --> 01:02:07,010
That's why I'm running.

694
01:02:07,010 --> 01:02:09,940
They may not realize it, but I'm their only hope.

695
01:02:35,940 --> 01:02:38,400
Down with Wayne! Down with Wayne!

696
01:02:38,440 --> 01:02:40,970
Down with Wayne! Down with Wayne!

697
01:05:11,880 --> 01:05:13,130
Can I help you, pal?

698
01:05:15,340 --> 01:05:16,670
I don't know what to say.

699
01:05:20,540 --> 01:05:22,200
Do you want an autograph or something?

700
01:05:23,070 --> 01:05:23,840
No.

701
01:05:30,040 --> 01:05:31,300
My name is Arthur.

702
01:05:33,070 --> 01:05:34,800
Penny Fleck is my mother.

703
01:05:36,170 --> 01:05:37,200
Jesus.

704
01:05:38,210 --> 01:05:40,270
You're the guy that came to my house yesterday?

705
01:05:41,480 --> 01:05:42,370
Yes.

706
01:05:43,240 --> 01:05:45,210
I'm sorry I just showed up.

707
01:05:45,210 --> 01:05:47,030
But my mother told me everything.

708
01:05:47,140 --> 01:05:48,770
And I had to talk to you,

709
01:05:48,770 --> 01:05:50,710
- you know? - Look, pal, I'm not your father.

710
01:05:50,710 --> 01:05:52,300
What's wrong with you?

711
01:05:54,270 --> 01:05:55,340
Look at us.

712
01:05:57,380 --> 01:06:00,470
- I think you are. - Well, that's impossible.

713
01:06:01,070 --> 01:06:03,470
Because you were adopted and I never slept with your mother.

714
01:06:03,480 --> 01:06:05,140
- I wasn't adopted. - What do you want from me, money?

715
01:06:05,140 --> 01:06:06,270
No. I don't.

716
01:06:06,270 --> 01:06:07,450
I wasn't adopted.

717
01:06:07,450 --> 01:06:09,230
Jesus. She never told you?

718
01:06:09,610 --> 01:06:11,070
Told me what?

719
01:06:12,480 --> 01:06:14,640
Your mother adopted you while she was working for us.

720
01:06:14,640 --> 01:06:17,040
That's not true. Why are you saying that?

721
01:06:17,040 --> 01:06:19,810
Because she was arrested and committed to Arkham State Hospital

722
01:06:19,810 --> 01:06:21,340
when you were just a little boy.

723
01:06:21,340 --> 01:06:22,600
Why are you saying this?

724
01:06:22,810 --> 01:06:26,040
I don't need you to tell me lies. I know it seems strange.

725
01:06:26,040 --> 01:06:27,710
I don't mean to make you uncomfortable.

726
01:06:27,710 --> 01:06:29,570
I don't know why everyone is so rude,

727
01:06:29,570 --> 01:06:32,340
and I don't why you are, I don't want anything from you.

728
01:06:32,340 --> 01:06:34,910
Maybe a little bit of warmth, maybe a hug, dad!

729
01:06:34,910 --> 01:06:36,970
How much is a little bit of fucking decency?

730
01:06:36,980 --> 01:06:38,470
What is it with you people?!

731
01:06:38,480 --> 01:06:40,340
You say that staff about my mother?

732
01:06:40,740 --> 01:06:43,000
- She's crazy. - She's--

733
01:06:51,880 --> 01:06:53,970
- You think this is funny? - Yeah--

734
01:06:54,670 --> 01:06:56,700
Dad, it's me!

735
01:06:56,710 --> 01:06:57,780
Come on--

736
01:07:00,840 --> 01:07:03,400
You touch my son again, I'll fucking kill you!

737
01:07:23,340 --> 01:07:26,000
Hello, Mr. Fleck. This is detective Garrity.

738
01:07:26,110 --> 01:07:28,370
We met the other night at the Gotham General.

739
01:07:28,540 --> 01:07:31,070
My partner and I had a few more questions for you.

740
01:07:31,070 --> 01:07:33,900
We stopped by your apartment today, but you weren't at home.

741
01:07:34,140 --> 01:07:36,310
Please, give me a call when you've heard this message.

742
01:07:36,310 --> 01:07:38,310
Again, this is detective Garrity.

743
01:07:38,310 --> 01:07:42,770
My number is 212-- 99.

744
01:08:25,280 --> 01:08:27,240
This message is for Arthur Fleck.

745
01:08:27,240 --> 01:08:29,010
My name is Shirley Woods,

746
01:08:29,010 --> 01:08:31,200
I work on the Murray Franklin show.

747
01:08:31,310 --> 01:08:32,340
I don't know if you're aware,

748
01:08:32,340 --> 01:08:35,610
but Murray played a clip of your stand-up on the show recently

749
01:08:35,610 --> 01:08:38,810
and we've gotten an amazing response from our viewers.

750
01:08:38,810 --> 01:08:41,440
And Mr. Murray asked me to give you a call and see if you're---

751
01:08:45,440 --> 01:08:46,630
Who is this?

752
01:08:47,080 --> 01:08:48,840
Oh, hi. This is Shirley Woods.

753
01:08:48,840 --> 01:08:51,710
I'm the show-booker from Live With Murray Franklin.

754
01:08:51,710 --> 01:08:52,970
Is this Arthur?

755
01:08:54,810 --> 01:08:55,800
Yes.

756
01:08:56,080 --> 01:08:57,710
Hi, Arthur. Well, and as I was saying,

757
01:08:57,710 --> 01:09:02,010
we've gotten a lot of calls about your clip, amazing responses.

758
01:09:02,010 --> 01:09:04,140
And, Murray asked if I would reach out to you

759
01:09:04,140 --> 01:09:06,470
to see if you would come on as his guest.

760
01:09:11,370 --> 01:09:14,200
Murray wants me on the Murray Franklin show?

761
01:09:14,710 --> 01:09:16,310
Yeah. Isn't that great?

762
01:09:16,310 --> 01:09:19,370
He'd love to talk to you, maybe do some of your act.

763
01:09:20,240 --> 01:09:21,740
Does that sound good to you?

764
01:09:26,780 --> 01:09:28,370
Yeah, that's sounds great.

765
01:09:29,040 --> 01:09:30,940
Can we set up a date right now?

766
01:09:31,010 --> 01:09:32,970
Are you available next Thursday?

767
01:10:27,610 --> 01:10:30,100
Man. Sorry about that, my man.

768
01:10:30,310 --> 01:10:32,670
All our records that are 10 years or older are stored in the basement

769
01:10:32,670 --> 01:10:35,370
and you're talking about something' 30 years ago, so.

770
01:10:37,010 --> 01:10:39,040
Can I ask you a question?

771
01:10:39,210 --> 01:10:40,040
Sure.

772
01:10:41,040 --> 01:10:44,540
How does someone wind up in here?

773
01:10:45,810 --> 01:10:46,900
Have they all---

774
01:10:47,280 --> 01:10:49,600
all the people committed crimes?

775
01:10:50,240 --> 01:10:51,670
Yeah. Some have.

776
01:10:51,880 --> 01:10:57,040
You know. Some are just crazy and pose a danger to themselves or others.

777
01:10:57,480 --> 01:10:59,040
Some just got nowhere else to go.

778
01:10:59,580 --> 01:11:01,070
Don't know what to do, you know?

779
01:11:01,540 --> 01:11:04,440
Yeah, I hear you, brother.

780
01:11:05,340 --> 01:11:07,900
Sometimes, I don't know what to do.

781
01:11:09,580 --> 01:11:12,400
Last time I ended up taking it out on some people.

782
01:11:13,740 --> 01:11:17,170
I thought it was gonna bother me but it really hasn't.

783
01:11:18,870 --> 01:11:19,700
What's that?

784
01:11:21,210 --> 01:11:22,470
I fucked up.

785
01:11:23,210 --> 01:11:25,000
I've done some bad shit.

786
01:11:28,370 --> 01:11:29,540
You know what I'm talking about.

787
01:11:29,540 --> 01:11:31,870
It's so hard just to try and be...

788
01:11:33,370 --> 01:11:35,540
happy all the time.

789
01:11:37,910 --> 01:11:38,830
Listen, man...

790
01:11:39,980 --> 01:11:41,670
I'm just an administor assistant.

791
01:11:41,670 --> 01:11:42,870
Like a clerk, you know.

792
01:11:42,870 --> 01:11:44,570
All I do is file paperwork,

793
01:11:45,780 --> 01:11:47,170
I don't know what to tell you,

794
01:11:47,640 --> 01:11:49,100
but you should see somebody.

795
01:11:49,580 --> 01:11:52,940
They have programs, city services, stuff like that.

796
01:11:53,710 --> 01:11:55,070
Oh, yeah.

797
01:11:55,110 --> 01:11:56,870
They cut all those.

798
01:12:01,670 --> 01:12:03,240
All right. Here it is.

799
01:12:03,440 --> 01:12:06,200
Fleck. Penny Fleck. I see.

800
01:12:06,610 --> 01:12:10,470
Diagnosed by Dr. Benjamin Stoner...

801
01:12:11,910 --> 01:12:16,070
The patient suffers from delusional psychosis

802
01:12:16,080 --> 01:12:18,830
and narcissistic personality disorder...

803
01:12:20,110 --> 01:12:20,940
Was found guilty

804
01:12:20,940 --> 01:12:25,400
of endangering the welfare of her own child--

805
01:12:33,610 --> 01:12:34,540
What?

806
01:12:38,040 --> 01:12:39,540
You said she's your mother?

807
01:12:45,780 --> 01:12:46,610
I'm sorry, man.

808
01:12:46,610 --> 01:12:49,270
Like I said, I can't release these records, you know,

809
01:12:49,370 --> 01:12:51,710
without the proper forms.

810
01:12:51,710 --> 01:12:52,940
I--I could get in trouble.

811
01:12:54,110 --> 01:12:56,210
Look, if you wanna bring your mom in here to sign,

812
01:12:56,210 --> 01:12:57,040
that would be much easier,

813
01:12:57,040 --> 01:13:00,100
but, I can't-- I can't let this go without a signature, okay?

814
01:13:00,670 --> 01:13:01,500
I'm sorry.

815
01:13:05,710 --> 01:13:06,900
No, man!

816
01:13:08,610 --> 01:13:10,970
Come on, man! Give it to me!

817
01:14:11,840 --> 01:14:13,270
We went over this, Penny.

818
01:14:13,940 --> 01:14:15,240
You adopted him.

819
01:14:15,640 --> 01:14:17,370
We have all the paperwork right here.

820
01:14:17,980 --> 01:14:19,500
That's not true.

821
01:14:20,480 --> 01:14:22,570
Thomas had them all made up,

822
01:14:22,980 --> 01:14:25,040
so it stayed our secret.

823
01:14:27,480 --> 01:14:28,940
You also stood by

824
01:14:30,370 --> 01:14:33,570
as one of your boyfriends repeatedly abused

825
01:14:34,040 --> 01:14:35,600
your adopted son

826
01:14:36,910 --> 01:14:38,200
and battered you.

827
01:14:57,440 --> 01:14:58,370
Penny,

828
01:14:59,610 --> 01:15:03,040
your son was found tied to a radiator

829
01:15:03,540 --> 01:15:05,370
in your filthy apartment,

830
01:15:05,940 --> 01:15:08,810
malnourished, with multiple bruises across his body

831
01:15:08,810 --> 01:15:10,940
and severe trauma to his head.

832
01:15:12,780 --> 01:15:14,600
I never heard him crying.

833
01:15:15,640 --> 01:15:18,940
He's always been such a happy little boy.

834
01:17:19,940 --> 01:17:21,170
It's time for bed.

835
01:17:25,280 --> 01:17:26,240
Oh, my god!

836
01:17:26,870 --> 01:17:28,170
What are you doing in here?

837
01:17:31,040 --> 01:17:32,400
You're in the wrong apartment.

838
01:17:39,580 --> 01:17:40,970
Your name is Arthur, right?

839
01:17:42,040 --> 01:17:43,100
You live down the hall.

840
01:17:46,240 --> 01:17:48,240
I really need you to leave.

841
01:17:52,440 --> 01:17:54,770
My little girl is sleeping in the other room.

842
01:18:00,540 --> 01:18:01,570
Please.

843
01:18:04,280 --> 01:18:06,200
I've had a bad day.

844
01:18:09,440 --> 01:18:11,570
Can I call someone? Is your mother home?

845
01:19:39,000 --> 01:19:40,060
Shut up!

846
01:19:59,140 --> 01:20:00,330
Hi, Penny.

847
01:20:03,110 --> 01:20:04,830
Penny Fleck.

848
01:20:12,580 --> 01:20:14,200
I always hated that name.

849
01:20:17,940 --> 01:20:19,440
You know, you used to tell me

850
01:20:22,010 --> 01:20:24,940
that my laugh was a condition,

851
01:20:26,140 --> 01:20:28,200
that there are something wrong with me.

852
01:20:31,280 --> 01:20:32,300
There isn't.

853
01:20:35,370 --> 01:20:36,870
That's the real me.

854
01:20:37,780 --> 01:20:39,330
Ha--appy

855
01:20:41,310 --> 01:20:42,470
"Happy".

856
01:20:42,980 --> 01:20:43,900
Funny.

857
01:20:47,040 --> 01:20:48,540
I haven't been happy...

858
01:20:49,810 --> 01:20:52,600
one minute of my entire fucking life.

859
01:20:59,140 --> 01:21:00,330
You know what's funny?

860
01:21:03,310 --> 01:21:05,000
You know what really makes me laugh?

861
01:21:07,280 --> 01:21:10,330
I used to think that my life was a tragedy,

862
01:21:11,740 --> 01:21:15,300
but now I realize it's a fucking comedy.

863
01:22:26,010 --> 01:22:27,270
A very fine actor.

864
01:22:27,280 --> 01:22:30,310
He's got a new movie called 'American Playboy',

865
01:22:30,310 --> 01:22:32,370
opening this week across the country.

866
01:22:32,370 --> 01:22:34,610
Will you please welcome a good friend of the show,

867
01:22:34,610 --> 01:22:36,470
Mr. Ethan Chase.

868
01:22:56,280 --> 01:22:58,240
Good to see you, Ethan. You looking great.

869
01:22:58,440 --> 01:23:00,370
Thank you very much. You look good yourself.

870
01:23:00,370 --> 01:23:01,400
Can't complain.

871
01:23:01,610 --> 01:23:04,100
Hi, Murray, Thank so much for having---

872
01:23:05,210 --> 01:23:06,130
Hey, Murray.

873
01:23:06,440 --> 01:23:08,570
Thank you so much for having me on the show.

874
01:23:08,980 --> 01:23:10,940
It's been a lifetime dream of mine.

875
01:23:13,440 --> 01:23:14,770
I'm nervous right now.

876
01:23:16,610 --> 01:23:17,670
- You are? - I am.

877
01:23:18,740 --> 01:23:20,240
Hey, Murray. It's been a ---

878
01:23:33,480 --> 01:23:34,800
I'm sorry, what's that?

879
01:23:36,440 --> 01:23:38,100
That's very funny, Murray.

880
01:23:39,310 --> 01:23:41,130
You know, I'm also a comedian.

881
01:23:41,610 --> 01:23:43,130
Would you like to hear a joke?

882
01:23:44,240 --> 01:23:46,300
Yeah? All of you?

883
01:23:47,240 --> 01:23:48,170
Okay.

884
01:23:50,980 --> 01:23:53,400
Knock. Knock- knock.

885
01:24:07,240 --> 01:24:08,370
Knock- knock.

886
01:26:05,810 --> 01:26:06,670
Coming!

887
01:26:17,910 --> 01:26:19,200
Hey, Arthur.

888
01:26:19,710 --> 01:26:20,670
How's it going?

889
01:26:21,580 --> 01:26:22,700
Oh, hi, guys.

890
01:26:23,340 --> 01:26:24,370
Come on in.

891
01:26:25,110 --> 01:26:26,740
Did you, get a new gig?

892
01:26:26,910 --> 01:26:27,770
No.

893
01:26:28,610 --> 01:26:31,300
You must be going down to that rally at City Hall.

894
01:26:31,580 --> 01:26:33,370
I hear It's gonna be nuts.

895
01:26:33,710 --> 01:26:34,830
Is it today?

896
01:26:36,140 --> 01:26:36,970
Yeah.

897
01:26:38,080 --> 01:26:39,630
What's with the make-up, then?

898
01:26:40,810 --> 01:26:41,940
My mom died.

899
01:26:42,540 --> 01:26:43,540
I'm celebrating.

900
01:26:44,580 --> 01:26:45,740
Right. We heard.

901
01:26:45,740 --> 01:26:47,800
That's-- that's why we came by. Figured...

902
01:26:48,340 --> 01:26:49,800
you could use some cheering up.

903
01:26:50,410 --> 01:26:51,540
That's sweet.

904
01:26:52,010 --> 01:26:53,630
But, no.

905
01:26:53,870 --> 01:26:55,070
I feel good.

906
01:26:55,710 --> 01:26:57,500
I stopped taking my medication.

907
01:26:57,740 --> 01:26:59,270
I feel lot better now.

908
01:27:02,110 --> 01:27:03,940
Okay. Well, good for you.

909
01:27:05,970 --> 01:27:09,260
So, hey, listen. Uh, I don't know if you're heard, but..

910
01:27:09,260 --> 01:27:11,680
the cops had been calling around the shop

911
01:27:12,130 --> 01:27:14,090
talking all the guys about

912
01:27:14,550 --> 01:27:16,240
those subway murders.

913
01:27:16,930 --> 01:27:18,360
They didn't talk to me.

914
01:27:20,000 --> 01:27:22,770
That's because the suspect was a regular sized person.

915
01:27:23,090 --> 01:27:25,760
If it was a fucking midget you'd be in jail right now.

916
01:27:31,360 --> 01:27:32,420
Anyway, um...

917
01:27:33,100 --> 01:27:34,810
Hoyt said that, um...

918
01:27:35,040 --> 01:27:36,720
they talked to you and

919
01:27:36,980 --> 01:27:38,460
now they're looking for me---

920
01:27:38,460 --> 01:27:40,160
I just want to know what you said.

921
01:27:40,160 --> 01:27:41,820
Make sure our stories line up,

922
01:27:41,820 --> 01:27:43,040
seeing as, um--

923
01:27:43,040 --> 01:27:45,080
you're my boy and,

924
01:27:45,080 --> 01:27:46,540
- It makes lot of sense. - you know what I mean?

925
01:27:46,540 --> 01:27:48,440
Thank you, Randall. Thank you so much.

926
01:27:48,440 --> 01:27:50,570
- I just wanna-- - Fuck!

927
01:27:54,310 --> 01:27:55,860
Oh, god!

928
01:27:55,970 --> 01:27:57,030
No!

929
01:27:58,630 --> 01:28:00,110
What?

930
01:28:00,950 --> 01:28:02,130
No!

931
01:28:09,840 --> 01:28:12,060
Why would you do that, Arthur?

932
01:28:32,960 --> 01:28:34,680
Do you watch Murray Franklin show?

933
01:28:35,660 --> 01:28:36,590
Yeah.

934
01:28:37,930 --> 01:28:39,430
I'll be on it tonight.

935
01:28:44,120 --> 01:28:45,860
It's fucking crazy isn't it?

936
01:28:45,950 --> 01:28:47,470
Me on a telly.

937
01:28:49,720 --> 01:28:51,590
What the fuck, Arthur?

938
01:28:51,870 --> 01:28:52,850
What?

939
01:28:53,200 --> 01:28:54,120
What?

940
01:28:59,070 --> 01:29:00,570
It's okay, Garry.

941
01:29:00,730 --> 01:29:01,730
You can go.

942
01:29:04,370 --> 01:29:05,950
I'm not gonna hurt you.

943
01:29:10,650 --> 01:29:13,140
Don't look. Just go.

944
01:29:25,300 --> 01:29:26,470
Fuck.

945
01:29:31,690 --> 01:29:34,020
- H-hey Arthur? - Yeah?

946
01:29:35,110 --> 01:29:38,050
Arthur, can you get... the lock?

947
01:29:40,780 --> 01:29:41,750
Shit.

948
01:29:42,110 --> 01:29:43,600
It's alright, Garry.

949
01:29:54,910 --> 01:29:56,740
- Garry? - Yeah?

950
01:29:59,360 --> 01:30:01,680
You're the only one that's ever been nice to me.

951
01:30:04,160 --> 01:30:05,320
Get out of here.

952
01:31:32,590 --> 01:31:35,700
Hey, Arthur! We need to talk!

953
01:31:37,910 --> 01:31:39,330
Hey, stop, Arthur!

954
01:31:44,250 --> 01:31:45,360
Arthur!

955
01:31:47,710 --> 01:31:49,760
- You fucking-- - Hey, out of the way!

956
01:31:52,770 --> 01:31:53,680
Move!

957
01:31:55,920 --> 01:31:57,300
Arthur!

958
01:32:09,550 --> 01:32:11,070
Arthur, stop!

959
01:32:16,160 --> 01:32:17,050
Go! Go!

960
01:32:19,310 --> 01:32:21,760
...now get out.

961
01:32:23,180 --> 01:32:25,140
Stand clear of the closing doors.

962
01:32:34,420 --> 01:32:36,010
Hold that train!

963
01:32:36,010 --> 01:32:37,090
Hold it!

964
01:32:38,900 --> 01:32:40,150
Get out! Get out!

965
01:32:41,420 --> 01:32:42,470
Next stop --

966
01:32:57,340 --> 01:32:59,030
Hey, asshole! Better watch it!

967
01:33:00,700 --> 01:33:02,840
Stand down! Now!

968
01:33:11,490 --> 01:33:13,300
Police! Stand down!

969
01:33:14,190 --> 01:33:15,590
Stand down!

970
01:33:19,720 --> 01:33:21,020
Hey, what the fuck?

971
01:33:24,170 --> 01:33:25,700
Beating there!

972
01:33:32,050 --> 01:33:34,980
Stop fighting! Police! Police!

973
01:33:38,010 --> 01:33:40,730
Get down! Get the fuck down!

974
01:33:41,140 --> 01:33:45,060
Police, get down! Get the fuck down!

975
01:33:49,100 --> 01:33:51,080
What the fuck...!

976
01:33:55,200 --> 01:33:56,270
What the--?

977
01:33:59,460 --> 01:34:00,950
Arthur!

978
01:34:03,740 --> 01:34:05,140
God, no!

979
01:34:54,860 --> 01:34:56,090
Two officer on the train

980
01:34:56,090 --> 01:34:58,390
were violently confronted by the crowd tonight

981
01:34:58,400 --> 01:34:59,310
and they're in serious

982
01:34:59,320 --> 01:35:02,240
but stable condition at Gotham Metropolitan.

983
01:35:02,380 --> 01:35:05,020
We're going live now to co-anchor Courtney Weathers

984
01:35:05,020 --> 01:35:07,270
who's standing by outside the Bedford park station

985
01:35:07,270 --> 01:35:09,160
near where the shooting took place.

986
01:35:09,160 --> 01:35:11,230
Courtney, what's the scene there?

987
01:35:16,460 --> 01:35:17,520
Murray!

988
01:35:17,790 --> 01:35:20,360
- It's "Mr. Franklin!". - Oh, come on, Gene.

989
01:35:20,360 --> 01:35:22,010
That's all bullshit.

990
01:35:22,790 --> 01:35:23,970
Thank you, Murray.

991
01:35:24,980 --> 01:35:26,670
I feel like I know you.

992
01:35:27,220 --> 01:35:29,090
I've been watching you forever.

993
01:35:29,400 --> 01:35:30,400
Thank you.

994
01:35:30,620 --> 01:35:32,060
What's with the face?

995
01:35:32,060 --> 01:35:33,540
That mean that you are part of the protest?

996
01:35:34,280 --> 01:35:35,110
No.

997
01:35:35,330 --> 01:35:37,440
No, I don't believe in any of that.

998
01:35:37,850 --> 01:35:39,400
I don't believe in anything.

999
01:35:40,000 --> 01:35:41,670
I just thought it would be good for my act.

1000
01:35:41,670 --> 01:35:43,960
For your act? Didn't you hear what happened on the subway?

1001
01:35:43,960 --> 01:35:46,470
- Some clown got kills. - He's aware of that, yeah.

1002
01:35:46,470 --> 01:35:47,920
No, I haven't heard.

1003
01:35:48,240 --> 01:35:49,830
- Yeah? - You see ,this is what I'm telling you.

1004
01:35:49,830 --> 01:35:51,900
the audience is gonna go crazy if you put this guy on.

1005
01:35:51,900 --> 01:35:54,310
Maybe, maybe for a bit, but not a whole segment.

1006
01:35:54,310 --> 01:35:57,030
Gene, It's gonna work. It's gonna work.

1007
01:35:57,330 --> 01:35:58,650
We're gonna go with it.

1008
01:35:59,730 --> 01:36:01,080
Thank you, Murray.

1009
01:36:01,080 --> 01:36:02,400
Couple of rules, though:

1010
01:36:02,400 --> 01:36:04,320
No cursing, no off-color material,

1011
01:36:04,320 --> 01:36:07,260
we do a clean show, okay?

1012
01:36:07,370 --> 01:36:08,960
You go on right after Dr. Sally.

1013
01:36:08,960 --> 01:36:11,040
- I love Dr. Sally. - Good! Good, good.

1014
01:36:11,040 --> 01:36:13,390
- Well, someone will come and get you, okay? - Okay.

1015
01:36:13,390 --> 01:36:14,560
Perfect.

1016
01:36:14,560 --> 01:36:15,710
- Good luck. - Thanks, Murray.

1017
01:36:15,710 --> 01:36:16,570
Okay.

1018
01:36:17,000 --> 01:36:19,590
Hey, Murray...one small thing.

1019
01:36:19,780 --> 01:36:22,150
- Yeah? - When you bring me out

1020
01:36:22,430 --> 01:36:24,700
can you introduce me as "Joker"?

1021
01:36:24,700 --> 01:36:26,230
What's wrong with your real name?

1022
01:36:26,850 --> 01:36:29,230
That's what you called me on the show.

1023
01:36:29,230 --> 01:36:30,540
A Joker.

1024
01:36:30,690 --> 01:36:31,830
Do you remember?

1025
01:36:31,990 --> 01:36:34,070
- Did I? - Yeah, I don't know.

1026
01:36:34,070 --> 01:36:36,610
Well, if you say so, kid, you know, joker it is.

1027
01:36:36,610 --> 01:36:39,060
- It's good. - Thanks, Murray.

1028
01:37:00,780 --> 01:37:01,790
I would try it, you know,

1029
01:37:01,790 --> 01:37:04,160
but I'm not sure my wife would let me do it.

1030
01:37:05,430 --> 01:37:07,020
Maybe my next wife.

1031
01:37:10,590 --> 01:37:12,330
You gotta see our next guest for yourself.

1032
01:37:12,340 --> 01:37:14,670
I'm pretty sure this guy can use a doctor.

1033
01:37:15,680 --> 01:37:17,410
Does he have a sexual problem?

1034
01:37:17,410 --> 01:37:19,890
He looks like he's got a lot of problems.

1035
01:37:21,020 --> 01:37:23,660
Alright, Let's show that clip one last time.

1036
01:37:30,190 --> 01:37:34,250
I hated school as a kid.

1037
01:37:34,640 --> 01:37:37,360
But my mother would always say,

1038
01:37:37,860 --> 01:37:39,500
"You should enjoy it.

1039
01:37:39,500 --> 01:37:42,160
One day you'll have to work for a living."

1040
01:37:42,590 --> 01:37:46,020
"No I won't, Ma. I'm gonna be a comedian!"

1041
01:37:52,050 --> 01:37:53,090
Okay,

1042
01:37:55,790 --> 01:37:59,190
you may have seen that clip of our next guest.

1043
01:37:59,190 --> 01:38:01,780
Now, before he comes out, I just want to say

1044
01:38:01,790 --> 01:38:05,470
that we're all heartbroken about what's going on in the city tonight.

1045
01:38:05,470 --> 01:38:07,940
But, this is how he wanted to come out.

1046
01:38:07,940 --> 01:38:11,280
And, honestly, I think we could all use a good laugh.

1047
01:38:11,280 --> 01:38:13,850
So, please welcome "Joker".

1048
01:38:56,300 --> 01:38:57,910
Are you alright, doctor?

1049
01:39:01,350 --> 01:39:03,870
Well, that was... quite an entrance.

1050
01:39:10,600 --> 01:39:11,610
You okay?

1051
01:39:14,080 --> 01:39:14,950
Oh, yeah.

1052
01:39:15,830 --> 01:39:18,770
This is exactly how I imagined it.

1053
01:39:20,450 --> 01:39:22,130
Well, that makes one of us.

1054
01:39:29,140 --> 01:39:31,660
So, can you tell us about this look?

1055
01:39:31,660 --> 01:39:33,210
When we spoke earlier, you mentioned

1056
01:39:33,210 --> 01:39:36,110
that this look is not a political statement, is that right?

1057
01:39:36,110 --> 01:39:38,180
That's right, Murray. I'm not political.

1058
01:39:38,180 --> 01:39:40,530
I'm just trying to make people laugh.

1059
01:39:40,780 --> 01:39:42,220
And how's that goin' for ya?

1060
01:39:49,900 --> 01:39:52,710
It's alright. It's alright. So, I know you're a comedian.

1061
01:39:52,950 --> 01:39:54,720
Have you been working on any new material?

1062
01:39:54,720 --> 01:39:56,230
You want to tell us a joke?

1063
01:40:01,550 --> 01:40:02,440
Yeah?

1064
01:40:04,760 --> 01:40:05,630
Okay.

1065
01:40:11,740 --> 01:40:13,080
He's got a book.

1066
01:40:14,270 --> 01:40:16,100
A book of jokes.

1067
01:40:25,590 --> 01:40:27,170
Take your time. We got all night.

1068
01:40:33,010 --> 01:40:35,660
Okay. Okay. Here's one.

1069
01:40:38,470 --> 01:40:40,250
Knock-knock.

1070
01:40:41,280 --> 01:40:42,900
And you had to look that up?

1071
01:40:49,490 --> 01:40:50,920
I wanted to get it right.

1072
01:40:53,120 --> 01:40:54,610
Knock-knock.

1073
01:40:54,860 --> 01:40:56,240
Who's there?

1074
01:40:57,720 --> 01:40:59,340
It's the police, ma'am.

1075
01:40:59,350 --> 01:41:01,450
Your son has been hit by a drunk driver.

1076
01:41:01,450 --> 01:41:02,660
He's dead.

1077
01:41:05,740 --> 01:41:07,410
Oh, no, no, no!

1078
01:41:07,420 --> 01:41:09,470
No, you cannot joke about that.

1079
01:41:09,470 --> 01:41:11,510
Yeah, that's not funny, Arthur.

1080
01:41:11,510 --> 01:41:14,290
That's not the kind of humor we do on this show.

1081
01:41:14,460 --> 01:41:16,970
Okay, I'm s... Yeah, I'm sorry.

1082
01:41:16,970 --> 01:41:18,470
It's just, you know,

1083
01:41:18,930 --> 01:41:21,790
it's been a rough few weeks, Murray.

1084
01:41:22,960 --> 01:41:24,620
Ever since I

1085
01:41:27,260 --> 01:41:29,860
killed those three Wall Street guys.

1086
01:41:36,010 --> 01:41:38,020
Okay. I'm waiting for the punchline.

1087
01:41:39,420 --> 01:41:40,980
There is no punchline.

1088
01:41:42,670 --> 01:41:44,020
It's not a joke.

1089
01:41:49,200 --> 01:41:50,190
You're serious, aren't you?

1090
01:41:50,190 --> 01:41:53,080
You're telling us you killed those three young men on the subway?

1091
01:41:53,960 --> 01:41:55,840
And why should we believe you?

1092
01:41:55,840 --> 01:41:57,860
I've got nothing left to lose.

1093
01:41:59,860 --> 01:42:01,630
Nothing can hurt me anymore.

1094
01:42:05,000 --> 01:42:08,050
My life is nothing but a comedy.

1095
01:42:11,300 --> 01:42:12,150
Let me get this straight,

1096
01:42:12,150 --> 01:42:15,080
you think that killing those guys is funny?

1097
01:42:15,650 --> 01:42:16,640
I do.

1098
01:42:17,140 --> 01:42:19,840
And I'm tired of pretending it's not.

1099
01:42:19,990 --> 01:42:22,300
Comedy is subjective, Murray.

1100
01:42:22,300 --> 01:42:23,700
Isn't that what they say?

1101
01:42:24,180 --> 01:42:25,620
All of you,

1102
01:42:26,050 --> 01:42:28,880
the system that knows so much,

1103
01:42:28,880 --> 01:42:31,850
you decide what's right or wrong

1104
01:42:31,860 --> 01:42:36,090
the same way that you decide what's funny...

1105
01:42:36,090 --> 01:42:37,550
or not.

1106
01:42:38,420 --> 01:42:39,720
Get him off!

1107
01:42:40,080 --> 01:42:43,880
Well, okay, I--I think I might understand that you

1108
01:42:44,060 --> 01:42:45,690
did this to start a movement,

1109
01:42:45,690 --> 01:42:48,160
to become a symbol.

1110
01:42:48,210 --> 01:42:49,940
Come on, Murray,

1111
01:42:49,940 --> 01:42:52,630
do I look like the kind of a clown that could start a movement?

1112
01:42:53,060 --> 01:42:55,770
I killed those guys because they were awful.

1113
01:42:56,200 --> 01:42:58,830
Everybody's awful these days.

1114
01:42:58,830 --> 01:43:01,070
It's enough to make anyone crazy.

1115
01:43:01,070 --> 01:43:03,760
Okay. So that's it, you're crazy. That's your defense

1116
01:43:03,760 --> 01:43:05,490
for killing three young men?

1117
01:43:06,060 --> 01:43:07,060
Nah.

1118
01:43:07,690 --> 01:43:11,660
They couldn't carry a tune to save their lives.

1119
01:43:13,400 --> 01:43:16,520
Why is everybody so upset about these guys?

1120
01:43:17,060 --> 01:43:20,560
If it was me dying on the side-walk, you'd walk right over me.

1121
01:43:20,560 --> 01:43:23,560
I pass you everyday and you don't notice me! But these guys,

1122
01:43:23,560 --> 01:43:27,090
what, because Thomas Wayne went and cried about them on TV?

1123
01:43:27,090 --> 01:43:29,090
Well, you have a problem with Thomas Wayne,too?

1124
01:43:29,090 --> 01:43:30,760
Yes, I do.

1125
01:43:31,460 --> 01:43:34,820
Have you seen what it's like out there, Murray?

1126
01:43:34,930 --> 01:43:37,520
Do you ever actually leave the studio?

1127
01:43:38,290 --> 01:43:42,020
Everybody just yells and screams at each other.

1128
01:43:42,030 --> 01:43:43,930
Nobody's civil anymore!

1129
01:43:44,260 --> 01:43:47,590
Nobody thinks what it's like to be the other guy.

1130
01:43:48,730 --> 01:43:50,660
You think men like Thomas Wayne

1131
01:43:50,660 --> 01:43:53,630
ever think what it's like to be someone like me?

1132
01:43:53,690 --> 01:43:56,560
To be somebody but themselves? They don't.

1133
01:43:56,620 --> 01:43:59,620
They think that we'll just sit there and take it

1134
01:43:59,620 --> 01:44:01,460
like good little boys!

1135
01:44:01,460 --> 01:44:03,960
That we won't werewolf and go wild.

1136
01:44:03,960 --> 01:44:05,130
You finished?

1137
01:44:05,460 --> 01:44:07,990
I mean, there is so much self-pity, Arthur.

1138
01:44:07,990 --> 01:44:11,290
You sound like you're making excuses for killing those young men.

1139
01:44:11,290 --> 01:44:14,690
Not everybody-- and I'll tell you this-- not everyone is awful.

1140
01:44:16,790 --> 01:44:19,260
- But you're awful, Murray. - Me?

1141
01:44:19,390 --> 01:44:21,990
I'm awful? Oh, yeah? How am I awful?

1142
01:44:24,160 --> 01:44:25,790
Playing my video,

1143
01:44:27,090 --> 01:44:28,890
inviting me on the show---

1144
01:44:30,160 --> 01:44:32,860
You just wanted to make fun of me.

1145
01:44:33,460 --> 01:44:35,490
You're just like the rest of 'em.

1146
01:44:35,590 --> 01:44:37,760
You don't know the first thing about me, pal.

1147
01:44:37,760 --> 01:44:40,620
Look what happened because of what you did, what it led to.

1148
01:44:40,620 --> 01:44:42,320
There are riots out there.

1149
01:44:42,320 --> 01:44:45,060
Two policemen are in critical condition and you're laughing.

1150
01:44:45,060 --> 01:44:47,590
You're laughing. Someone was killed today

1151
01:44:47,590 --> 01:44:49,160
because of what you did.

1152
01:44:49,160 --> 01:44:50,190
I know.

1153
01:44:53,230 --> 01:44:54,620
How about a another joke, Murray?

1154
01:44:54,620 --> 01:44:56,490
No, I think we got enough of your jokes.

1155
01:44:56,490 --> 01:44:57,920
- What do you get... - I don't think so.

1156
01:44:57,930 --> 01:45:01,820
when you cross a mentally-ill loner with a society

1157
01:45:01,820 --> 01:45:04,090
that abandons him and treats him like trash?

1158
01:45:04,090 --> 01:45:05,020
Call the police, Gene.

1159
01:45:05,030 --> 01:45:06,660
- I'll tell you what you get. - Call the police!

1160
01:45:06,660 --> 01:45:08,790
You get what you fucking deserve!

1161
01:45:45,120 --> 01:45:47,990
Good night. And always remember.

1162
01:45:47,990 --> 01:45:48,820
That's--

1163
01:45:53,760 --> 01:45:55,090
Breaking news.

1164
01:45:55,090 --> 01:45:57,560
Popular TV talk show host Murray Franklin

1165
01:45:57,560 --> 01:45:59,920
was shot dead tonight on the live telecast

1166
01:45:59,930 --> 01:46:02,390
...the man who was introduced by Franklin

1167
01:45:59,930 --> 01:46:02,230
of his program by one of his guests.

1168
01:46:02,390 --> 01:46:05,260
as "Joker" is currently under arrest--

1169
01:46:05,260 --> 01:46:08,520
The police led the suspect handcuffed out of the studio--

1170
01:46:08,620 --> 01:46:09,960
...when asking him what he did..

1171
01:46:09,960 --> 01:46:12,760
...merely just a punchline to a joke...

1172
01:46:12,760 --> 01:46:13,900
You get what you fucking deserve!

1173
01:46:15,040 --> 01:46:17,090
I think we got enough of your jokes.

1174
01:46:17,090 --> 01:46:21,230
...with the society that abandons him and treats him like trash.

1175
01:46:21,930 --> 01:46:23,860
...Murray Franklin, dead tonight...

1176
01:46:25,230 --> 01:46:28,820
If it was me dying on the side-walk, you'd walk right over me!

1177
01:46:28,930 --> 01:46:31,490
To all of those who have been ignored by the system--

1178
01:46:31,490 --> 01:46:34,090
...and as you can see, Gotham is burning--

1179
01:47:29,260 --> 01:47:31,560
Stop laughing you freak. This isn't funny.

1180
01:47:31,860 --> 01:47:34,660
We have the whole fucking city's on fire because of what you did.

1181
01:47:35,430 --> 01:47:37,740
All units, fire reported. North of Ally.

1182
01:47:39,790 --> 01:47:40,890
I know.

1183
01:47:42,730 --> 01:47:44,460
Isn't it beautiful?

1184
01:49:27,430 --> 01:49:28,490
Let's go over there.

1185
01:49:46,560 --> 01:49:47,630
Hey, Wayne.

1186
01:49:48,660 --> 01:49:50,520
You get what you fucking deserve.

1187
01:49:50,660 --> 01:49:51,760
No, pal!

1188
01:50:32,820 --> 01:50:34,690
Joker!

1189
01:50:35,390 --> 01:50:37,130
Get up!

1190
01:53:15,890 --> 01:53:17,190
What's so funny?

1191
01:53:19,590 --> 01:53:20,890
I just think--

1192
01:53:21,890 --> 01:53:23,720
just thinking of this joke.

1193
01:53:42,790 --> 01:53:44,260
You wanna tell it to me?

1194
01:53:50,890 --> 01:53:52,430
You wouldn't get it.

1195
01:54:04,790 --> 01:54:10,960
That's Life - Frank Sinatra

1196
01:54:04,790 --> 01:54:06,040
♪ That's life. ♪

1197
01:54:06,040 --> 01:54:08,060
♪ That's life. ♪

1198
01:54:08,060 --> 01:54:10,960
♪ and as funny as it may seem ♪

1199
01:54:12,090 --> 01:54:14,690
♪ Some people get their kicks ♪

1200
01:54:15,090 --> 01:54:17,460
♪ Stompin' on a dream ♪

1201
01:54:18,490 --> 01:54:22,320
♪ But I don't let it, let it get me down ♪

1202
01:54:24,230 --> 01:54:26,520
♪ 'Cause this fine old world ♪

1203
01:54:26,560 --> 01:54:29,390
♪ it keeps spinnin' around ♪

1204
01:54:29,860 --> 01:54:33,120
♪ I've been a puppet, a pauper, a pirate ♪

1205
01:54:33,120 --> 01:54:36,690
♪ A poet, a pawn and a king ♪

1206
01:54:36,690 --> 01:54:40,160
♪ I've been up and down and over and out ♪

1207
01:54:40,690 --> 01:54:42,790
♪ And I know one thing ♪

1208
01:54:43,060 --> 01:54:46,220
♪ Each time I find myself ♪

1209
01:54:46,230 --> 01:54:48,800
♪ laying flat on my face ♪

1210
01:54:49,320 --> 01:54:51,820
♪ I just pick myself up ♪

1211
01:54:52,060 --> 01:54:55,920
♪ and get back in the race ♪

1212
01:54:55,930 --> 01:54:57,060
♪ That's life ♪

1213
01:54:57,060 --> 01:54:58,320
♪ That's life ♪

1214
01:54:58,320 --> 01:55:02,590
♪ That's life and I tell ya, I can't deny it ♪

1215
01:55:03,020 --> 01:55:06,020
♪ Many times I thought of cuttin' out♪

1216
01:55:06,020 --> 01:55:08,430
♪ but my heart won't buy it ♪

1217
01:55:08,790 --> 01:55:13,690
♪ But if there's nothing shakin' come here this July ♪

1218
01:55:16,230 --> 01:55:19,190
♪ I'm gonna roll myself up ♪

1219
01:55:19,660 --> 01:55:27,560
♪ in a big ball and die ♪

1220
01:55:30,790 --> 01:55:37,060
♪ My, my ♪

