[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.7
; http://www.aegisub.net
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-01-08 21:32:18
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:花咲くいろは
Original Script:澄空学园&华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00000000,&H503D3D3D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,1,2,30,30,15,1
Style: Default2,@方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00000000,&H503D3D3D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,2,3,1,2,40,40,15,1
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H1E000000,&HA0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,1,8,10,10,15,1
Style: TITLE,@方正稚艺_GBK,45,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,2,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正稚艺_GBK,45,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFPMinchoP-W5,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,2,8,10,10,20,1
Style: OPCN,方正小标宋_GBK,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,2,2,2,2,10,10,18,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00000000,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,0,2,25,25,15,1
Style: INCN,方正小标宋_GBK,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,2,2,2,8,10,10,60,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------STAFF----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.00,0:03:00.00,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,Banner;6;0;35,本話製作人員　翻譯: 月々姫 涼子　校對: 高町米牙口　歌詞協力: tjx 豆奶　計時: Lantis　後期: HySauce　繁化: 阿爽　製作: 澄空學園 × 華盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------TITLE----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.24,0:02:15.74,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(510,360)}在夜晚呼喊
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------NEXT-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.90,0:23:41.40,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(510,360)}再見
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPJP-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.88,0:00:12.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)}{\be5}涙の雨が頬をたたくたびに美しく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.25,0:00:23.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}くだらないルールから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}はみ出せずに泣いていた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.57,0:00:30.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ぼやけすぎた未来地図
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.80,0:00:36.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,50)}{\be5}すり減ったココロを埋めたくて集めた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:40.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,200)}{\be5}要らないモノばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.53,0:00:46.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}バイバイ　あの愛しき日々は
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.21,0:00:51.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}戻りはしないから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:57.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}開いてゆく　小さく閉じたココロが
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.86,0:01:01.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}夜の隅で静かに
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:04.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}色付いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.28,0:01:12.70,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}もっと深く優しく朝の光を受けて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.94,0:01:25.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}{\be5}涙の雨が頬をたたくたびに美しく
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPCN-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.88,0:00:12.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)}{\be5}淚雨敲打著我的面頰　我卻變得越來越美麗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.25,0:00:23.39,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}無法逃離那世俗的規則
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}我只能默默哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.57,0:00:30.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}看著模糊不清的未來地圖
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.80,0:00:36.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,50)}{\be5}為了填補空虛的心靈而收集來的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:40.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,200)}{\be5}盡是些無聊的事物
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.53,0:00:46.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}Bye-bye　我那些一去不復返的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.21,0:00:51.07,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}珍愛時光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:57.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}打開那扇緊閉的小小心窗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.86,0:01:01.64,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}在那夜深人靜的角落裡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:04.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}漸漸染上色彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.28,0:01:12.70,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}感受更深沉安詳的朝陽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.94,0:01:25.48,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}{\be5}淚雨敲打著我的面頰　我卻變得越來越美麗
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------EDJP-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.76,0:22:06.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}時間が後ろへ流されてく
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.71,0:22:12.37,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}手を振る間もなく流されてく
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.86,0:22:18.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}あの子の匂いが薄れてゆく
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.56,0:22:25.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}赤い目をこすった　まだ眠りたくない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.57,0:22:31.28,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}夢を見るたびオトナになる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.86,0:22:37.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}大事なものから零れてくの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.45,0:22:44.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}もしも明日目が覚める頃
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.70,0:22:51.49,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}すべた忘れてしまうとしても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.04,0:22:57.23,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}爪で掻いた傷跡も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.23,0:23:04.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}いつかは消えてしまうとしても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.55,0:23:09.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}ぼくの細胞のヒトツが
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.70,0:23:16.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)\be5}ずっと覚えてるから
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------EDCN-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.76,0:22:06.39,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}時間正在慢慢向後流逝
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.71,0:22:12.37,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}在彈指一揮間就已經逝去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.86,0:22:18.75,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}那些孩子們生活的氣息也都漸漸淡去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.56,0:22:25.32,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}眨著赤紅的雙眼  但卻無法入眠
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.57,0:22:31.28,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}隨著每次墜入夢鄉漸漸成長
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.86,0:22:37.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}重要的事物也都一一零落失去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.45,0:22:44.84,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}哪怕明天一覺醒來
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.70,0:22:51.49,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}一切已被忘卻
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.04,0:22:57.23,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}就算指甲留下的傷痕
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.23,0:23:04.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}不經意間癒合消失
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.55,0:23:09.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}在我的一個細胞裡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.70,0:23:16.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)\be5}種種卻早已悄然珍藏
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------TEXT-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.23,0:01:34.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了  這個這個
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.44,0:01:39.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真  真讓人心跳加速呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.70,0:01:40.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.21,0:01:44.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗚嗚  果然還是不敢看
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.26,0:01:45.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民拜託你了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.95,0:01:47.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼要我來
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.18,0:01:51.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為收到過好評  所以我想應該不要緊…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.00,0:01:55.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過萬一上面寫了些負面消息的話該怎麼辦…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.24,0:01:55.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.59,0:02:02.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滿分…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.44,0:02:07.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五…五…五分滿分…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.98,0:02:08.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.93,0:02:12.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滿分十分裡面…打五分
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.67,0:02:13.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.66,0:02:19.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,崇子小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.72,0:02:21.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必須得跟崇子小姐聯繫才行
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.84,0:02:22.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,崇子小姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.96,0:02:27.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖說可以稱之為懷古風格
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.27,0:02:29.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但和時代脫節這一點卻無法否認
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.50,0:02:32.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餐點也千篇一律非常單調
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.85,0:02:35.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住宿的舒適度也並不理想…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.15,0:02:35.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開什麼玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.25,0:02:39.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蓮先生他總是追求著更美味的料理…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.36,0:02:42.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  這讓人太不甘心了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.44,0:02:46.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  而且那天我們的招待應該是很完美的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.32,0:02:49.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這件事就到此為止
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.56,0:02:51.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眾人快各自歸位
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.98,0:02:52.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.09,0:02:54.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都沒聽見嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.75,0:02:56.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一句話我可不說兩遍
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.38,0:03:12.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了  請幫我轉接那篇報導的責編
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.21,0:03:13.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有辦法接受…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.72,0:03:14.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託您了！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.09,0:03:17.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  等等…請等一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.87,0:03:18.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.68,0:03:25.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是豆丁老爺呀
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.26,0:03:26.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.80,0:03:27.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福屋
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.38,0:03:34.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湯乃鷺的旅館獲得的評分都不高
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.30,0:03:36.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是個很嚴重的事態
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.93,0:03:39.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在湯乃鷺的咽喉處
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.28,0:03:41.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在這個正在建造中
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.60,0:03:43.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一夜八千元嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.67,0:03:45.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想住一晚試試
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.61,0:03:47.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,優哉游哉地說些什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.22,0:03:48.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個要是建好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.40,0:03:50.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湯乃鷺可就要受到重創了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.27,0:03:52.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要攀比的並不是那方面
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.94,0:03:54.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都在於質…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.16,0:03:56.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在的問題就是我們的質量受到考驗了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.87,0:03:59.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了  現在就別窩裡鬥了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.20,0:04:02.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在是湯乃鷺最應該團結一致…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.61,0:04:04.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在幹什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.14,0:04:10.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  拉你來幫我忙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.82,0:04:13.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是要在雪洞祭上用的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.37,0:04:15.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  真是煩死了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.74,0:04:18.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是外婆神經繃得緊緊的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.17,0:04:20.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣子誰還敢反抗她
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.52,0:04:21.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.83,0:04:23.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都登出那樣的報導了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.44,0:04:25.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且這裡竟然還要造高級賓館
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.26,0:04:29.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過  總感覺很棒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.26,0:04:31.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結名貌似也想在那裡住住看了～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.76,0:04:36.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結名同學  要是你真住了我會罵你毛蛋哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.99,0:04:43.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是這樣的  結名同學又沒有錯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.34,0:04:45.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.31,0:04:46.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是了！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.87,0:04:48.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管結名同學有什麼感想
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.59,0:04:50.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都要雪願到底！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.40,0:04:51.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪願？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.45,0:04:53.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛閃現的一個詞！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.71,0:04:57.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花真的好有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.11,0:05:04.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說想請假？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.77,0:05:09.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我想去雜誌社問他們評分的含義
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.35,0:05:10.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.60,0:05:13.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這週末客人也少  數都數得過來
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.55,0:05:14.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而打電話的話根本就沒結果…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.71,0:05:16.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別去做些沒意義的事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.04,0:05:20.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做出評價的人不是自己  全是由別人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.82,0:05:21.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.68,0:05:25.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算無法接受評價的結果
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.69,0:05:29.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也要以此勉勵自己  然後爭取做到更好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.05,0:05:34.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…可這實在是太奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.78,0:05:36.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.10,0:05:39.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為…比起其他任何一家旅館
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.54,0:05:43.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜翠莊絕對…絕對都要更好才對！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.72,0:05:47.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個結果
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.14,0:05:50.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我絕對…我絕對不會承認
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.22,0:05:59.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花居然去尋釁？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.27,0:06:01.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她留了留言…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.02,0:06:03.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.22,0:06:08.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去和給喜翠莊做出如此糟糕評價的犯人戰鬥了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.67,0:06:10.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要拼命雪願
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.38,0:06:12.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意義不明
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.06,0:06:14.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不光是喜翠莊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.54,0:06:17.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花的語文水平大概也是五分吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.74,0:06:22.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您好  這裡是喜翠莊…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.69,0:06:27.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  咦…  我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.77,0:06:29.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您好  這裡是喜翠莊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.65,0:06:31.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.04,0:06:34.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘  預訂好入住的客人好像要取消了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.04,0:06:35.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.13,0:06:38.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…這邊這位也要取消…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.68,0:06:43.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雜誌評分的結果已經…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.43,0:06:44.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.69,0:06:46.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.02,0:06:56.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}（雪願  ->  雪洞祭上許的願  ->  為了實現願望而自己努力的意思）
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.28,0:06:58.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪願
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.45,0:07:02.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs38}（來電：小菜）
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.88,0:07:08.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起  現在我不能接
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.01,0:07:10.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪願
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.18,0:07:17.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了守護喜翠莊  我要雪願！！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.68,0:07:23.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀…就算你這麼說
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.05,0:07:27.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個是撰稿公司的人寫的報導
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.70,0:07:29.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我們一點都沒有關係…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.36,0:07:32.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你們就刊登這種沒有關係的報導嗎！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.07,0:07:35.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們就那麼不負責任嗎！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.08,0:07:37.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道正如坊間傳言  傳媒都是漆黑一片的嗎！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.52,0:07:39.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有…真傷腦筋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.83,0:07:41.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請你告訴我！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.13,0:07:44.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什麼地方的什麼人寫出這種傷人的報導
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.39,0:07:46.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太近  靠太近了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.84,0:07:49.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起  拜託您了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.16,0:07:51.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請告訴我吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.66,0:07:55.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.80,0:07:56.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是負責人的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.40,0:07:58.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是那邪惡之源…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.80,0:08:03.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花～～
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.34,0:08:05.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還好嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.61,0:08:11.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種溫暖的感覺好久沒有體驗到了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.47,0:08:14.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼了  不好嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.20,0:08:19.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有誰被親人賣了還能過得好好的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.03,0:08:20.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是想見識看看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.98,0:08:24.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒  你怎麼突然間淨說這些難懂的話
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.79,0:08:25.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子餓不餓？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.91,0:08:30.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後我很快和那傢伙拜拜了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.05,0:08:34.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是工作更有意思
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.12,0:08:37.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,於是就我一個人回到這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.35,0:08:40.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的想夜逃一次看看的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.73,0:08:46.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回想起來是那時候  和那個人的感情處於最高峰呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.40,0:08:48.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.05,0:08:51.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼能說自己家的壞話
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.47,0:08:52.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明明沒有來過喜翠莊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.47,0:09:04.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種排行榜的背後都會牽扯到很多複雜的事情啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.20,0:09:09.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有某位大人物想給喜翠莊抹黑
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.80,0:09:11.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我只是順著他的意思編輯了一下而已
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.60,0:09:18.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明不清楚現在的喜翠莊的情況
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.43,0:09:20.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你卻寫出了那種報導？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.56,0:09:22.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啦  先冷靜一點
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.76,0:09:25.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶汁烤菜涼了就不好吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.31,0:09:26.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要敷衍我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.70,0:09:27.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽你總是這樣子…！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.86,0:09:31.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一點都不會考慮我的感受
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.24,0:09:33.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不和我商量
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.87,0:09:35.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就自說自話地決定一切…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.87,0:09:38.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這份報導也是  夜逃也是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.97,0:09:40.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小學兩年級搬家也是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.56,0:09:42.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五年級的聖誕禮物也是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.46,0:09:46.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我根本就沒想要過布偶熊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.52,0:09:48.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要的是貼紙簿
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.72,0:09:50.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明前一個月都已經說好了的！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.36,0:09:54.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虧你還記得這麼久的事情呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.66,0:09:57.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我很傷心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.44,0:10:01.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過那時候沒有收到貼紙簿 也沒見你說什麼嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.63,0:10:03.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我在忍耐啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.72,0:10:06.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊…我一直一直都在忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.56,0:10:10.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽晚上出去玩的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.08,0:10:12.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然很黑  雖然我自己一個人很害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.63,0:10:14.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但即便如此我依然在忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.02,0:10:17.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,參觀聽課也是  動物園也是  游泳池也是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.96,0:10:21.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次你爽約的時候我都在忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.33,0:10:25.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶  話題是不是轉變成對我個人的意見了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.70,0:10:28.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽總是說是因為工作
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.02,0:10:33.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因為是工作…所以我才一直忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.91,0:10:39.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…為了這種會傷害到別人的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.24,0:10:45.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直忍耐到今天  一直…一直忍耐過來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.48,0:10:47.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就為了這種工作嗎！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.21,0:10:48.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.77,0:10:54.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直以來從事的就是這份工作
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.77,0:10:57.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是靠這份工作把你養大的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.83,0:11:04.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以為只有那些讓人引以為傲的崇高工作才算是工作嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.44,0:11:10.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你看來是這樣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.46,0:11:12.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.61,0:11:16.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在母親眼裡看來  我的工作或許很無聊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.66,0:11:19.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但就是如此  我還是這麼一路拼命走來了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.43,0:11:20.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.92,0:11:21.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.01,0:11:22.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.90,0:11:25.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我知道…但請你修改它
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.45,0:11:27.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都說了  要修改報導什麼的辦不到
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.89,0:11:29.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用你在書面上做道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.43,0:11:32.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你來一趟喜翠莊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.20,0:11:34.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把媽媽你看到的  感受到的喜翠莊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.85,0:11:36.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣原原本本地寫下來
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.45,0:11:38.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些不登上雜誌也不要緊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.45,0:11:41.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要媽媽你明白喜翠莊是多麼棒的一家旅館…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.05,0:11:44.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可不成  我非常忙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.52,0:11:45.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,修改它…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.36,0:11:46.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辦不到
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.67,0:11:49.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會死心的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.41,0:11:52.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你答應修改前我決不會死心
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.63,0:11:54.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對會讓你寫的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.31,0:11:55.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…緒花！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.52,0:12:04.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻煩續杯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.24,0:12:10.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝惠顧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.18,0:12:16.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也知道  媽媽作為敵人來說
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.57,0:12:19.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是個非常強大的對手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.67,0:12:24.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從出生起  一直都在敗給她
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.32,0:12:25.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.15,0:12:29.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}（你不覺得刺激才是人生嗎？現在就邂逅完全免費的刺激人生！點擊這裡註冊）
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.79,0:12:34.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣  真的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.38,0:12:35.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,騙人啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.17,0:12:39.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來東京這事還沒和阿孝說過呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.61,0:12:44.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次可不是為那種事來的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.71,0:12:53.22,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\be3}阿孝\N我是緒花\N今天在做什麼呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.21,0:12:58.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再把這部分修改一下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.78,0:13:00.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.23,0:13:03.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皋月小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.50,0:13:03.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.69,0:13:05.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看那個
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.52,0:13:12.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}松前皋月  取回做人的良心吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.52,0:13:12.53,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(120,340)}不允許虛假報導！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.52,0:13:12.53,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(1110,340)}釋放你的靈魂！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.52,0:13:12.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(510,240)}醒醒吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.52,0:13:12.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(850,320)}不可原諒！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.91,0:13:12.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.92,0:13:15.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我記得…是你女兒吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.60,0:13:17.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.36,0:13:20.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓她去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.76,0:13:22.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放著不管她就會放棄嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.77,0:13:23.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.80,0:13:26.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子絕對不會放棄的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.48,0:13:27.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.25,0:13:32.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可原諒…嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.74,0:13:35.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.14,0:13:37.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要生氣到什麼時候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.23,0:13:40.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒辦法呀  都已經既成事實了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.26,0:13:42.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  不能原諒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.13,0:13:46.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作沒辦法  放過我吧～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.34,0:13:48.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這一輩子都不會原諒的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.26,0:13:52.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你說的話什麼意思嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.37,0:13:53.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.08,0:13:58.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越來越不能被原諒了呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.67,0:14:01.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  工作工作
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.87,0:14:08.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會輸的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.47,0:14:11.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無論如何都要讓媽媽去喜翠莊…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.92,0:14:16.67,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\be3}喲\N今天在打工
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.29,0:14:18.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打工…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.18,0:14:21.18,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\be3}打工？\N還在快遞公司嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.36,0:14:29.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得好久沒有這樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.76,0:14:33.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這片景色也好  和阿孝互發郵件也好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.41,0:14:37.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自從分開還不到半年的說
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.20,0:14:41.82,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\be3}今天在池袋的大書店
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.46,0:14:47.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰讓他就在鄰站呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.05,0:14:53.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且現在的標語也有些缺乏迫力
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.14,0:14:55.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是讀些深奧的書
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.24,0:14:58.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學些深奧的語言比較好…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.51,0:15:03.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孝一君
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.75,0:15:06.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些該放在哪裡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.71,0:15:07.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.93,0:15:08.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.38,0:15:09.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.88,0:15:11.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搞不清楚呀
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.82,0:15:12.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說你呀
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.88,0:15:15.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們兩個  工作中不要卿卿我我的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.26,0:15:18.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.39,0:15:21.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.46,0:15:22.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.95,0:15:29.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs38\fad(0,200)}（醒醒吧！）
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.42,0:15:26.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.74,0:15:29.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的  你認錯人了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.47,0:15:31.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.28,0:15:32.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.50,0:15:35.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼你會在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.53,0:15:39.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…有點事…剛好在附近…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.33,0:15:40.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來東京？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.82,0:15:41.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.10,0:15:42.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.87,0:15:50.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  打擾你們了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.03,0:15:54.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作加油  再見
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.47,0:15:55.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.47,0:16:11.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花  差不多該認輸了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.03,0:16:13.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了  老太婆
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.97,0:16:15.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔  迎來了第一次的反抗期
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.67,0:16:19.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我一起去喜翠莊  老太婆
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.73,0:16:21.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.53,0:16:25.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老太婆…老太婆…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.53,0:16:36.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對不能接受敵人的施捨
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.42,0:16:38.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.05,0:16:42.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.55,0:16:48.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.87,0:16:52.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是超搞笑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.97,0:16:58.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作不要緊嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.22,0:16:59.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.74,0:17:03.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有努力工作嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.75,0:17:04.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.31,0:17:08.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…這種評價要是沒有結果的話
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.51,0:17:12.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能判斷你是不是努力的只能是客人  而不是自己
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.25,0:17:13.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.42,0:17:21.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是有點裝模作樣了…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.24,0:17:26.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我突然來到這裡惹阿孝生氣了？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.23,0:17:29.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明有好多話想說
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.74,0:17:33.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝  長高了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.47,0:17:38.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝  和剛才那個女孩關係有多好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.16,0:17:41.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝  是不是還對我…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.27,0:17:47.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去續杯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.24,0:17:53.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了  我不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.80,0:17:57.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是為什麼而來東京的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.13,0:18:02.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心情…好混亂
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.37,0:18:04.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好混亂…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.23,0:18:13.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼還這種喝法
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.46,0:18:16.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一半冰茶一半可樂
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.50,0:18:18.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然想喝可樂
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.99,0:18:20.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但又受不了碳酸
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.78,0:18:22.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝下去嘴裡好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.99,0:18:27.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別輸給可樂呀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.44,0:18:28.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.18,0:18:36.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那份打工什麼時候開始的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.63,0:18:39.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2個月之前吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.90,0:18:42.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店員們似乎都很要好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.54,0:18:44.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  年齡也相近
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.99,0:18:48.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有可愛的女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.74,0:18:51.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.69,0:18:53.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.40,0:18:59.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個人似乎喜歡阿孝呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.92,0:19:00.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.97,0:19:05.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「嗯」是被告白過了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.52,0:19:06.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.93,0:19:09.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.46,0:19:12.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我說了沒有那種意思
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.88,0:19:13.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.50,0:19:15.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她說會等的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.56,0:19:17.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得有些曖昧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.19,0:19:21.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好好回答的話很失禮的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.49,0:19:22.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.76,0:19:30.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好好回答的話會很失禮
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.13,0:19:33.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是說我自己…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.30,0:19:36.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告白回答得那麼含糊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.52,0:19:40.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我對阿孝做的事…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.09,0:19:48.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  要走了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.75,0:19:49.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.35,0:19:52.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帳單我去付
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.24,0:19:53.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了  我來…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.97,0:19:58.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.67,0:20:01.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.73,0:20:10.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的背影…之前也有見過
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.06,0:20:19.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雨又下大了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.72,0:20:21.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等著  我去買傘…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.32,0:20:25.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的  我會自己買的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.19,0:20:26.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.54,0:20:27.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.53,0:20:41.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想再看到阿孝的背影了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.22,0:20:48.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊的小妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.31,0:20:50.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全身濕透了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.94,0:20:52.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濕了濕了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.82,0:20:53.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.35,0:20:56.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等啊  小妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.78,0:20:58.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會感冒的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.32,0:21:13.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.52,0:21:17.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.89,0:21:32.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.76,0:21:34.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救救我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.04,0:21:35.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救救我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.79,0:21:38.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.56,0:21:40.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.18,0:21:47.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.10,0:21:50.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花  沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.08,0:21:55.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在這種地方做什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.35,0:22:03.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…為什麼要哭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.87,0:22:07.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不明白  不明白啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.53,0:22:11.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.59,0:22:15.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但唯獨這點我很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.57,0:22:21.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心情如此變動的一天
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.85,0:22:22.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是第一次…

Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回預告
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.02,0:23:34.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生有女朋友嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.28,0:23:36.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1}喂  緒花  現在在哪裡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.58,0:23:37.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3}好像在約會一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.03,0:23:38.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1}注定是壞人了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.66,0:23:39.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3}緒花  要回來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.85,0:23:41.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見
