[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.7
; http://www.aegisub.net
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2011-08-25 10:39:52
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:花咲くいろは
Original Script:澄空学园&华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00000000,&H503D3D3D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,1,2,30,30,15,1
Style: Default2,@方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00000000,&H503D3D3D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,2,3,1,2,40,40,15,1
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H1E000000,&HA0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,1,8,10,10,15,1
Style: TITLE,@方正稚艺_GBK,45,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,2,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正稚艺_GBK,45,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFPMinchoP-W5,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,2,8,10,10,20,1
Style: OPCN,方正小标宋_GBK,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,2,2,2,2,10,10,18,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00000000,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,0,2,25,25,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------STAFF----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.00,0:03:00.00,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,Banner;6;0;35,本話製作人員　翻譯: 月々姫 涼子　校對: 高町米牙口　歌詞協力: tjx　計時: Lantis　後期: HySauce　繁化: 阿爽　製作: 澄空學園 × 華盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------TITLE----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.80,0:22:01.30,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(510,360)}青鷺狂想曲
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------NEXT-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.90,0:23:41.40,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(510,360)}流淚的廚師之戀
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPJP-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.88,0:00:12.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)}{\be5}涙の雨が頬をたたくたびに美しく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.25,0:00:23.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}くだらないルールから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}はみ出せずに泣いていた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.57,0:00:30.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ぼやけすぎた未来地図
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.80,0:00:36.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,50)}{\be5}すり減ったココロを埋めたくて集めた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:40.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,200)}{\be5}要らないモノばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.53,0:00:46.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}バイバイ　あの愛しき日々は
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.21,0:00:51.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}戻りはしないから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:57.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}開いてゆく　小さく閉じたココロが
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.86,0:01:01.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}夜の隅で静かに
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:04.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}色付いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.28,0:01:12.70,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}もっと深く優しく朝の光を受けて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.94,0:01:25.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}{\be5}涙の雨が頬をたたくたびに美しく
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPCN-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.88,0:00:12.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)}{\be5}淚雨敲打著我的面頰　我卻變得越來越美麗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.25,0:00:23.39,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}無法逃離那世俗的規則
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}我只能默默哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.57,0:00:30.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}看著模糊不清的未來地圖
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.80,0:00:36.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,50)}{\be5}為了填補空虛的心靈而收集來的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:40.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,200)}{\be5}盡是些無聊的事物
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.53,0:00:46.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}Bye-bye　我那些一去不復返的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.21,0:00:51.07,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}珍愛時光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:57.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}打開那扇緊閉的小小心窗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.86,0:01:01.64,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}在那夜深人靜的角落裡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:04.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}漸漸染上色彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.28,0:01:12.70,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}感受更深沉安詳的朝陽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.94,0:01:25.48,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}{\be5}淚雨敲打著我的面頰　我卻變得越來越美麗
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------EDJP-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.80,0:22:19.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}夢を見る少し手前で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.19,0:22:23.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}置いてきたものはなんだっけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.02,0:22:29.59,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}忘れてしまいたくはないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.77,0:22:31.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}時折ふっと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.20,0:22:35.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}記憶の隅に浮かぶのは
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.58,0:22:39.26,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ふんわりぼやけたセピア色
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.32,0:22:46.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}目の前を塞ぐ日々の向こう　少しずつ遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.12,0:22:55.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}大体なんで息を切らして走ってるんだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.30,0:23:01.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}スピード上げてゆくほど
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.06,0:23:05.25,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}立ち止まることが怖くて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.35,0:23:12.18,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}早くなる鼓動に触れココに居ると確かめた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.59,0:23:20.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ココロの奥の小さな声に耳を澄ましたら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.31,0:23:29.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}{\be5}包み込む世界が晴れ広がるよ明日へ
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------EDCN-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.80,0:22:19.88,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}就要墜入夢鄉之前
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.19,0:22:23.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}把什麼放在了手邊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.02,0:22:29.59,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}明明不想忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.77,0:22:31.75,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}卻又無法想起
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.20,0:22:35.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}時而浮現在記憶角落裡的往日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.58,0:22:39.26,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}輕輕染上歲月的痕跡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.32,0:22:46.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}一縱即逝　漸行漸離
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.12,0:22:55.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}氣喘吁吁地奔跑又是為何
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.30,0:23:01.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}愈是加快步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.06,0:23:05.25,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}就愈是畏懼停下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.35,0:23:12.18,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}撫摸加速的心跳確認了自己的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.59,0:23:20.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}側耳傾聽　那微弱的心聲
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.31,0:23:29.95,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}{\be5}卻發現　天高海闊　直至未來
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------TEXT-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.00,0:01:36.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身體也好內心也好全都仔細打磨  將愛給…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.31,0:01:40.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎先生  這裡結束了的話後院也拜託你咯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.84,0:01:41.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了  少爺
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.67,0:01:43.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.40,0:01:48.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是了  今天起就是新學期了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.71,0:01:51.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很合身哦  緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.37,0:01:56.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯  制服還真是能把少女的清爽魅力徹底展現出來的東西呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.03,0:01:57.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎先生
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.71,0:02:01.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去打掃後院了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.71,0:02:06.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那人是不是最好也打掃一下自己骯髒的慾望呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.83,0:02:08.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是出於興趣和利益啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.84,0:02:15.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子  差不多該出發了  民子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.19,0:02:19.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬆鬆垮垮  簡直就像小學生的COSPLAY一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.39,0:02:21.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  徹
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.27,0:02:25.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說你新定的那份菜單呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.30,0:02:27.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  您能幫我審閱一下嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.66,0:02:37.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在幹什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.98,0:02:42.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗚嗚  好緊張啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.26,0:02:46.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係的  反正緒花很快就會交到朋友的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.76,0:02:49.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這句話真想讓徹先生來聽聽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.44,0:02:50.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.33,0:02:51.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.28,0:02:54.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是能和你們倆分到一個班就好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.73,0:02:57.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你分在同一個班裡絕對是毛蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.25,0:03:02.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說的毛蛋在日常對話中很難用的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.32,0:03:05.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在指我呢還是在指這種狀況呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.65,0:03:07.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少囉嗦少囉嗦  毛蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.41,0:03:14.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.05,0:03:16.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那邊的車哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.84,0:03:19.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福屋旅館很有名對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.25,0:03:23.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  還登在導遊手冊上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.68,0:03:25.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,強大的對手出現了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.19,0:03:29.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼出現  人家的歷史比喜翠莊還要久遠
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.64,0:03:41.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒  好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.56,0:03:43.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花好像很開心
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.43,0:03:48.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為花開得那麼多  一般來說早就被賞花的人擠得水洩不通了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.84,0:03:57.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下  等下啦  阿孝  口袋被勾住了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.43,0:03:58.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別離開我哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.94,0:04:06.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  這樣很難為情的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.33,0:04:08.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.72,0:04:22.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我這一路真的都是由阿孝保護過來的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.02,0:04:31.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花  你怎麼啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.56,0:04:33.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.16,0:04:38.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我該怎麼回覆他呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.44,0:04:47.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來就沒事了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.83,0:04:49.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你  菜子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.84,0:04:50.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再見
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.37,0:05:03.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望能分在一個班級  希望能分在一個班級
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.61,0:05:07.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望能分在一個班級  希望能分在一個班級
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.08,0:05:09.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望能分在一個班級…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.04,0:05:06.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}討厭…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.22,0:05:14.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是松前？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.52,0:05:15.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.37,0:05:21.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.66,0:05:24.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松前緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.28,0:05:27.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.53,0:05:36.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂  新學期才剛開始  你們至少給我乖乖坐在座位上啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.58,0:05:41.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  是你們期待的轉學生哦  大家注意了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.18,0:05:46.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來  轉學生  打個招呼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.71,0:05:51.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那個
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.57,0:05:56.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫松前緒花  是從東京過來的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.53,0:05:58.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害  是東京人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.13,0:06:01.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個髮夾  我也在雜誌上看到過
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.56,0:06:03.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我在三百元平價店裡買的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.22,0:06:04.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頭髮燙得好洋氣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.37,0:06:07.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只不過是天然捲而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.05,0:06:09.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裙子的長度也穿得剛剛好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.75,0:06:14.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那都是託了剛才被徹先生嘲笑的福
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.92,0:06:22.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.06,0:06:26.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶吶  你是東京哪一塊過來的？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.29,0:06:28.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新宿？  原宿？  涉谷？  御台場？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.58,0:06:30.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些地方又沒有人住
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.65,0:06:31.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…是有人住的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.29,0:06:33.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有男朋友嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.50,0:06:34.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男朋友？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.12,0:06:42.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝他不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.97,0:06:56.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和松前同學都在旅館裡打工是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.52,0:06:57.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鶴來同學
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.89,0:06:59.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是說民子嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.26,0:06:59.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.39,0:07:02.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  在一個房間裡…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.48,0:07:03.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦哦  真的？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.53,0:07:07.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託你告訴我  民子公主她平日裡的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.05,0:07:09.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民  民子公主？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.31,0:07:13.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  怎麼說呢  民子公主呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.47,0:07:17.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就仿若那和純白連衣裙相稱的高原少女
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.86,0:07:22.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然有點尖刻又沒有一絲破綻  但這更像是一朵高嶺之花
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.50,0:07:27.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她平時穿運動衫  而且單純就是個不擅交流的人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.56,0:07:32.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  拜託幫我把平時的民子公主偷拍下來吧  我出三千元
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.28,0:07:35.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出浴瞬間的話那我出三千五百元
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.18,0:07:39.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你小子…居然從這麼骯髒的視角來看民子公主
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.73,0:07:40.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我上屋頂一趟
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.61,0:07:44.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別—吵—了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.11,0:07:47.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結名
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.28,0:07:53.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  真是的  緒花都很為難了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.63,0:08:01.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啦  下次自習啦  家政課什麼的 都一起上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.24,0:08:05.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走啦走啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.00,0:08:10.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子公主和結名公主  居然和兩大人氣公主在同一教室
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.17,0:08:14.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說不定把一生的運氣都在這裡花完了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.30,0:08:17.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那個
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.62,0:08:20.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  抱歉 一直把你拖到這裡來
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.56,0:08:22.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都囉囉嗦嗦的  很吃不消吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.55,0:08:24.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過他們都沒有惡意  你就原諒他們吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.06,0:08:29.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她原來是來替我解圍的啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.34,0:08:31.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.58,0:08:35.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結名同學也不是這裡人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.31,0:08:38.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？  你是說我這口音？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.34,0:08:41.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我正好有心情來說幾句三腳貓的關西話
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.08,0:08:46.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪不得我覺得有點…不…是相當的奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.77,0:08:49.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是喜翠莊的外孫女吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.56,0:08:52.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是個外孫女
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.53,0:08:54.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和倉結名
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.30,0:08:59.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是福屋旅館的繼承人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.56,0:09:02.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那個高級旅館的？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.37,0:09:05.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  只是年代久遠點而已啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.75,0:09:09.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了繼承旅館  果然還是得每天用功學習嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.43,0:09:12.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…其實我也沒怎麼用功呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.40,0:09:13.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然阿婆非常煩人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.02,0:09:16.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你就不想繼承了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.56,0:09:19.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒…我倒是無所謂啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.54,0:09:22.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要開心的話繼不繼承都無所謂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.02,0:09:29.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結名同學好帥氣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.70,0:09:34.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜翠莊也有吧  帥氣的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.88,0:09:37.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們這邊？ 帥氣的人？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.77,0:09:38.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是誰呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.82,0:09:40.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是說次郎丸先生嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.43,0:09:43.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過他很色的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.46,0:09:44.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.43,0:09:51.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民超級受歡迎的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.17,0:09:55.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的鞋箱裡總是塞滿了情書
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.20,0:09:58.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒  她的確是很漂亮啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.67,0:10:00.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.26,0:10:04.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  說曹操曹操到
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.88,0:10:05.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.59,0:10:06.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.74,0:10:10.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都喜歡鶴來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.52,0:10:12.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.18,0:10:13.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我不喜歡你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.83,0:10:15.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.66,0:10:16.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好冷漠
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.45,0:10:17.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}等一等
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.04,0:10:19.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  他開始死纏爛打了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.73,0:10:22.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那麼你喜歡怎樣的男性？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.51,0:10:24.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有義務回答你嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.92,0:10:26.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是很認真的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.13,0:10:31.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒法那麼輕易放棄  我希望能接近鶴來你心目中的理想
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.13,0:10:31.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.15,0:10:35.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說話很毒
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.24,0:10:37.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但實際上卻很體貼人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.12,0:10:40.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總會搶在別人先頭行動起來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.10,0:10:41.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對工作也傾盡全力
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.60,0:10:44.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頭髮長短大概到這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.73,0:10:46.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼角有點往上吊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.50,0:10:49.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真是有夠具體
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.97,0:10:53.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民喜歡的人是…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.61,0:10:55.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是個很優秀的人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.66,0:10:57.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和徹根本就是天上地下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.57,0:10:59.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.64,0:11:07.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼高原少女啊  哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.43,0:11:10.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼校舍裡的告白 哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.15,0:11:12.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這青青澀澀的算什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.55,0:11:15.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我這邊根本就沒有男人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.03,0:11:18.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天就只有工作和自己相伴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.99,0:11:22.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此我就偷拍平日裡的民子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.24,0:11:25.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把高中男生的妄想打得粉碎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.31,0:11:31.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.93,0:11:36.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又在搞什麼啊笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.87,0:11:41.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  竹籤要這樣插  要這樣轉一轉的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.13,0:11:44.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噗嗤一下  一口氣插進去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.18,0:11:49.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴小姐  請你清醒一些
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.25,0:11:53.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了  緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.78,0:11:55.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那麼遊刃有餘嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.66,0:11:57.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來你…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.02,0:12:00.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有男人了吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.58,0:12:03.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都說了  阿孝…不是那樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.30,0:12:05.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.51,0:12:07.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人的名字嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.44,0:12:08.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然是男人的名字…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.94,0:12:11.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.07,0:12:15.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這個叛徒～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.86,0:12:27.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}（阿孝: 沒去送你對不起  緒花  加油！！）
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.53,0:12:33.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}（我有努力哦  阿孝那邊如何？）
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.12,0:12:36.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種把表白的事當沒發生過一樣的回信
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.12,0:12:39.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得自己有點狡猾
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.86,0:12:40.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刪除…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.99,0:12:47.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先 關於之前您說的那些難能可貴的話
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.99,0:12:50.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,託了您的福 我最近過得很好…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.51,0:12:56.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刪除！我不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.45,0:12:57.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花…？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.57,0:13:09.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伸展身體後…兔子跳
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.57,0:13:12.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是驚訝
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.29,0:13:18.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花也有不知道該如何交談的時候呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.60,0:13:20.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是因為我是個笨蛋而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.93,0:13:22.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有那樣的事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.31,0:13:25.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很羨慕你可以把想說的事直接說出來
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.37,0:13:28.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.46,0:13:30.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.57,0:13:37.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.74,0:13:41.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它就棲息在這附近的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.90,0:13:42.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,青鷺
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.81,0:13:49.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這種地方不要緊嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.54,0:13:51.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種不是應該在動物園嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.29,0:13:55.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這裡  緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.48,0:13:58.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自治會的通知嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.07,0:14:01.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻…麻煩您了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.73,0:14:04.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是寬敞的大廳呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.66,0:14:05.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.79,0:14:07.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜翠莊的人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.95,0:14:11.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.16,0:14:18.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得…好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.86,0:14:22.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花能陪我一起來真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.75,0:14:24.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菜子  這個…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.72,0:14:26.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個人真是好害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.98,0:14:28.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個就不害怕嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.80,0:14:31.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能稍微繞一下路嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.16,0:14:33.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…可以…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.19,0:14:40.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我從小就很內向
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.76,0:14:42.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要改變那樣的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.85,0:14:45.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才開始了旅館的打工
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.85,0:14:48.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎  好強的行動力
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.32,0:14:50.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不怎麼順利
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.17,0:14:54.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我經常在這裡祭拜神靈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.86,0:14:55.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神靈？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.45,0:15:00.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一個與狐狸相依為伴的小女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.26,0:15:05.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以老是迷路
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.62,0:15:07.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神靈會迷路？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.40,0:15:11.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  所以在十月會有雪洞祭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.89,0:15:13.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪洞祭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.60,0:15:18.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日本的神靈們每年十月回到出雲的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.65,0:15:22.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都裝飾上紙燈  當作路標
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.19,0:15:29.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指引神靈們的前進道路  祈禱他們不會迷失方向
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.83,0:15:31.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前進的道路…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.47,0:15:52.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好美妙…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.09,0:15:59.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真是個很美妙的祭典呢  小菜
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.58,0:16:01.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小菜？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.43,0:16:03.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.31,0:16:04.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為民子是「小民」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.10,0:16:07.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以菜子就叫小菜吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.47,0:16:09.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不喜歡嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.48,0:16:10.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.62,0:16:14.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太高興了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.42,0:16:17.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能被用暱稱稱呼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.03,0:16:18.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.15,0:16:24.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直想和朋友用暱稱互相稱呼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.81,0:16:26.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但總是不怎麼順利
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.80,0:16:33.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子醬…民醬…民民…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.93,0:16:35.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.63,0:16:48.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小…小民…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.68,0:16:51.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居……居然卡殼了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.40,0:16:54.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民什麼的  這麼難聽的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.35,0:16:56.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼難聽的稱呼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.66,0:16:58.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事  菜子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.49,0:17:06.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個啊  明天霧之間的早餐…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.40,0:17:08.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎  那真是厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.70,0:17:09.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀～
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.47,0:17:13.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼說來民子說的那個毛蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.60,0:17:17.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊的人思考事情時都會記筆記嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.43,0:17:20.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是深思熟慮呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.51,0:17:23.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼  對了  小菜
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.39,0:17:24.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也給我想個暱稱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.67,0:17:27.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會考慮的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.30,0:17:28.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好期待
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.95,0:17:34.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻花樹葉的香味真是不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.16,0:17:37.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  是徹他做的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.18,0:17:40.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那小夥子也變得很能幹了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.56,0:17:49.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  餐前準備完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.78,0:17:50.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  那麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.95,0:17:54.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.86,0:17:56.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花  我馬上回來
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.87,0:17:57.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.42,0:18:09.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你在搞什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.52,0:18:11.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然來了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.66,0:18:13.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烤製的料理不該放那裡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.89,0:18:15.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.43,0:18:19.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易做的料理變得看上去很難吃了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.23,0:18:22.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說起來學校怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.16,0:18:26.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定沒交到什麼朋友吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.16,0:18:28.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不懂場合的你的話
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.68,0:18:31.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福屋的繼承人也在那裡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.02,0:18:32.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個高中
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.46,0:18:35.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結名同學嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.40,0:18:37.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明同齡還真是不一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.80,0:18:39.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發育的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.16,0:18:43.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在說上臂嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.89,0:18:45.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.66,0:18:49.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.64,0:18:52.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她還有別的事要做
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.90,0:18:54.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.79,0:18:55.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子  這個拜託了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.02,0:18:56.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.38,0:19:00.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為我解圍了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.88,0:19:08.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子真是個好人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.87,0:19:11.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要是也能和她好好相處該多好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.89,0:19:15.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先是從稱呼她為小民開始
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.77,0:19:32.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須說點什麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.34,0:19:35.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個…對了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.41,0:19:36.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說到女生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.64,0:19:39.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要討論共同的敵人就一定談得起來
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.84,0:19:41.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個  民子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.13,0:19:44.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才真是謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.10,0:19:47.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生真是會抱怨
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.74,0:19:53.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靈魂的邪惡通過眼神就能看出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.05,0:19:54.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有反應了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.08,0:19:57.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  趁現在叫暱稱…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.04,0:20:00.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不覺得嗎  小民…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.25,0:20:05.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這人…真是毛蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.43,0:20:08.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是毛蛋？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.15,0:20:09.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是徹的抱怨
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.94,0:20:11.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然處事嚴格
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.39,0:20:14.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那是因為他比任何人都關心我們
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.08,0:20:16.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比任何人都傾盡全力
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.58,0:20:21.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實要比任何人都要體貼人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.70,0:20:28.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然處事嚴格  但是體貼人  傾盡全力
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.40,0:20:32.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這好像在哪裡聽…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.66,0:20:38.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民喜歡的人難道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.77,0:20:43.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.41,0:20:48.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.90,0:20:51.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.19,0:20:58.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.78,0:21:04.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.83,0:21:08.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.71,0:21:12.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起  我又說了多餘的事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.89,0:21:14.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生的事…那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.87,0:21:17.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.77,0:21:23.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你現在就在說多餘的事情 你明不明白啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.63,0:21:25.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.60,0:21:33.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.64,0:21:40.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結名同學？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.47,0:21:49.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Let's  party？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.66,0:21:53.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子…
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回預告
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.07,0:23:35.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1}喜歡一個人真是不得了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.90,0:23:35.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3}那傢伙的話  不會來了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.44,0:23:36.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3}那是怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.10,0:23:37.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3}新人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.18,0:23:37.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1}昨天的晚上我看到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.62,0:23:40.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請讓我在這裡工作
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
