[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.7
; http://www.aegisub.net
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-07-13 12:10:47
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:花咲くいろは
Original Script:澄空学园&华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00000000,&H503D3D3D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,1,2,30,30,15,1
Style: Default2,@方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00000000,&H503D3D3D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,2,3,1,2,40,40,15,1
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H1E000000,&HA0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,1,8,10,10,15,1
Style: TITLE,@方正稚艺_GBK,45,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,2,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正稚艺_GBK,45,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFPMinchoP-W5,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,2,8,10,10,20,1
Style: OPCN,方正小标宋_GBK,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,2,2,2,2,10,10,18,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00000000,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,0,2,25,25,15,1
Style: INCN,方正小标宋_GBK,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,2,2,2,8,10,10,60,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------STAFF----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.00,0:04:00.00,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,Banner;6;0;35,本話製作人員　翻譯: 涼子 月々姫　校對: 高町米牙口　歌詞協力: tjx　計時: Lantis　後期: volence　繁化: 阿爽　製作: 澄空學園 × 華盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------TITLE----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.55,0:02:37.05,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(510,360)}下定決心的單相思
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------NEXT-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.90,0:23:41.40,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(510,360)}夢的終結
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPJP-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.03,0:00:22.21,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}地平線をなぞるように
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.57,0:00:27.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}空と地球を繋いでる雲が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.26,0:00:29.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}ぼくの住むこの街を
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.47,0:00:35.81,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}ぐるりと囲った夢うつつの昼下がりに
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.38,0:00:40.81,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}綿菓子みたいなそれを千切り
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.96,0:00:45.38,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}微かに空いた穴の向こう側
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.51,0:00:53.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}目を凝らせば小さな夏の入り口がほら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.09,0:00:59.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}注ぐ蝉時雨
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:03.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}追いかけてたカブトムシ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.36,0:01:08.30,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}溶けたアイスキャンディ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.34,0:01:13.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}巻き戻る記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.50,0:01:17.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}二度と戻ることはない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.63,0:01:23.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)\be5}でも消えない模様
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPCN-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.03,0:00:22.21,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}沿著地平線
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.57,0:00:27.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}連接著天空和地球的雲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.26,0:00:29.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}團團圍住我所在的小鎮
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.47,0:00:35.81,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}在一個半夢半醒慵懶的午後
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.38,0:00:40.81,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}撕開棉花糖般的雲朵
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.96,0:00:45.38,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}在雲彩對面朦朧可見
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.51,0:00:53.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}凝眸遠眺　看啊　那裡有著通往夏天的小小入口
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.09,0:00:59.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}蟬鳴如雨點般響個不停
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:03.96,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}拼命追逐著的獨角仙
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.36,0:01:08.30,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}融掉的冰棒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.34,0:01:13.01,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}回溯的記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.50,0:01:17.60,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}再也回不到的過去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.63,0:01:23.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)\be5}卻是永不磨滅的回憶
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------EDJP-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.27,0:18:41.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}時計のいらない朝に2人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.27,0:18:41.60,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}在一個不需要鬧鐘的早晨
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.20,0:18:49.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}白い雲に包まれて笑う
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.20,0:18:49.62,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}兩個人包裹在白雲中歡笑
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.36,0:18:57.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}わずかな隙から漏れる光
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.36,0:18:57.53,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}從細小的縫隙中漏出的光
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.17,0:19:05.79,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}窓の向こう自由に歌う鳥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.17,0:19:05.79,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}窗外鳥兒在自由歌唱
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.11,0:19:13.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}その手を繋げば時は延びて
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.11,0:19:13.62,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}牽起你的手時間就變得漫長
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.17,0:19:21.79,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}短い永遠に変わる
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.17,0:19:21.79,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}這瞬間凝縮成短暫的永恆
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.57,0:19:32.27,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}奇跡なんて信じていないけど　今なら
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.57,0:19:32.27,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}雖然不相信什麼奇跡　但是現在
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.33,0:19:39.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}なんでも出来る気がしてる
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.33,0:19:39.10,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}卻感到自己無所不能
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.65,0:19:48.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}強くなんてないけどたしかにこの手で
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.65,0:19:48.15,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}雖然並不堅強　但堅信能用這雙手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.23,0:19:57.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)\be5}きみを守れる気がしてる
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.23,0:19:57.29,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)\be5}保護好你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.25,0:20:09.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}空を飛びたいと願うぼくを
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.25,0:20:09.83,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}看著夢想在天空飛翔的我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.37,0:20:17.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}子供みたいだときみが笑う
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.37,0:20:17.50,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}你微笑著說我像個孩子一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.34,0:20:25.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}ふざけてそっぽ向いた背中に
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.34,0:20:25.56,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}開玩笑似的偷偷在你的背後
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.27,0:20:34.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}指で小さく羽根の絵を書く
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.27,0:20:34.77,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}用手指畫上了小小的翅膀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.48,0:20:57.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}奇跡なんて信じていないけど　今なら
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.48,0:20:57.33,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}雖然不相信什麼奇跡　但是現在
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.33,0:21:03.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}空さえ飛べる気がしてる
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.33,0:21:03.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}就算天空 也好似能自由翱翔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.08,0:21:11.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}飛び疲れて2人はまた夢に堕ちても
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.08,0:21:11.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}就算飛累了兩個人再次墜入夢鄉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.90,0:21:18.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}繋いだ手と手は離さぬまま
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.90,0:21:18.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}牽著的雙手卻依然緊握不放
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.48,0:21:29.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,2000)\be5}奇跡なんて信じていないけど　今なら
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.48,0:21:29.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,2000)\be5}雖然不相信什麼奇跡　但是現在
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.03,0:21:44.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,2000)\be5}強くなんてないけどたしかにこの手で
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.03,0:21:44.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,2000)\be5}雖然並不堅強　但堅信能用這雙手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.79,0:21:55.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}奇跡なんて信じていないけど　今なら
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.79,0:21:55.55,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be5}雖然不相信什麼奇跡　但是現在
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.58,0:22:04.28,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)\be5}きみを守れる気がしてる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.58,0:22:04.28,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)\be5}卻覺得能夠保護好你
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------TEXT-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.05,0:01:39.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Good morning everyone
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.67,0:01:41.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多麼美妙的早晨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.70,0:01:47.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒  崇子小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.70,0:01:53.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒  這不才四點嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.70,0:01:56.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,The early bird catches the worm
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.66,0:01:59.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們身負喜翠莊的日常業務
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.47,0:02:02.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接著還要準備我們的婚禮
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.13,0:02:05.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了完成這繁重的任務
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.61,0:02:09.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就只能從削減年輕人的睡眠時間開始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.15,0:02:14.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總而言之  接下來要和anything開一場會
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.99,0:02:17.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出發去員工食堂  Here we go
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.66,0:02:25.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事啊  崇子小姐突然好有幹勁
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.10,0:02:41.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Good moring Miss巴
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.30,0:02:44.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始這美妙的一天吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.45,0:02:47.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.75,0:02:49.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.73,0:02:51.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來來  Miss巴請就座吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.87,0:02:53.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來開始會議
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.70,0:02:54.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家要拿出幹勁來
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.08,0:02:56.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Are you ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.55,0:03:03.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃  芥川龍之介寫這部《羅生門》的經過是這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.98,0:03:09.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時芥川和他的青梅竹馬  吉田彌生的婚約告吹
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.67,0:03:12.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂——
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.19,0:03:13.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對  對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.90,0:03:16.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為它很少會響的所以就…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.22,0:03:17.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喲  男朋友怎麼說？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.56,0:03:22.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請不要說男女朋友什麼的…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.64,0:03:29.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.64,0:03:33.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在想什麼呀  真難以置信
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.48,0:03:35.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然在上課的時候打電話來
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.19,0:03:36.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.86,0:03:40.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我總覺得你是不是一直都在幹活啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.42,0:03:41.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了對了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.32,0:03:42.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還是個女高中生呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.07,0:03:43.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.80,0:03:45.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你有什麼事？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.69,0:03:48.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  我收到了張請帖
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.72,0:03:50.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緣他要結婚了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.37,0:03:51.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.55,0:03:53.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定會參加吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.94,0:03:55.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒那麼容易吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.41,0:03:57.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒  工作很忙嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.58,0:03:59.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  各種原因吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.18,0:04:00.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,賀電的話我會發一個的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.57,0:04:03.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過話說回來緣結婚了啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.99,0:04:06.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被他超前了呢  媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.22,0:04:08.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.52,0:04:13.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶  媽媽你一直在換男朋友吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.61,0:04:15.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.93,0:04:18.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟別人交往到底是種什麼感覺？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.13,0:04:22.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？  你又把上其他男人了？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.32,0:04:24.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.26,0:04:30.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒準還對你爸爸單相思吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.65,0:04:31.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.68,0:04:33.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,單相思？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.19,0:04:37.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這算什麼口氣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.87,0:04:39.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家還以為說了一句不錯的話呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.30,0:04:41.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是單相思這個詞
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.60,0:04:46.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我根本想不到會從放蕩的媽媽嘴裡說出來
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.78,0:04:47.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.04,0:04:50.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因為忘不了喜歡的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.49,0:04:52.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才摸索其他戀情的不是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.92,0:04:54.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰讓這份感情又得不到回報
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.43,0:04:59.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過那人去世至今也有十五年了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.83,0:05:02.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近我會開始這麼想
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.56,0:05:04.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實也沒有必要得到回報了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.03,0:05:05.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.27,0:05:10.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很少能遇到讓自己喜歡到這種地步的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.86,0:05:13.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光是遇到  就已經足夠幸運了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.14,0:05:16.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧  緒花？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.74,0:05:18.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.62,0:05:31.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我居然為媽媽的單相思心跳加速
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.50,0:05:32.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.10,0:05:35.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  單相思…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.46,0:05:47.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼…為什麼我會想要放棄阿孝呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.86,0:05:53.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就連小民都能那麼認真地對徹先生…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.41,0:06:05.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼我會想不到這是單相思呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.34,0:06:14.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好咧  完成了！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.26,0:06:15.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.38,0:06:19.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一個外行而言做得挺不錯了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.30,0:06:22.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來就是試穿  再做做微調了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.97,0:06:24.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結名同學穿穿看嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.32,0:06:26.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒  不要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.38,0:06:29.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有種說法是穿上婚紗婚期就會延後
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.84,0:06:33.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我穿的話  下擺肯定要拖地的…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.26,0:06:49.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感覺之前貌似也有過一次這種情況
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.55,0:06:51.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一種怪討厭的既視感
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.11,0:06:54.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已  已經可以了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.33,0:06:55.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.12,0:06:59.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴小姐正在努力地做我們那份工作
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.99,0:07:02.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼讓鶴來同學穿穿看啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.48,0:07:05.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然那邊沒準還不如崇子小姐有料
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.03,0:07:08.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過沒胸反而方便試穿不是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.85,0:07:12.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之沒胸走遍天下都不怕  對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.47,0:07:15.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.60,0:07:18.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來你就要開始試做宴會料理了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.91,0:07:19.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.17,0:07:21.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過我基本上都有點底了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.10,0:07:24.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.87,0:07:28.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  那個…我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.09,0:07:30.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說過用不著幫忙了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.13,0:07:35.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.92,0:07:38.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題  我已經放棄胡蘿蔔政策了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.10,0:07:39.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.27,0:07:43.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果沒有嚴苛的環境  人是無法擺脫低潮的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.90,0:07:45.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我終於想通了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.62,0:07:47.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要像當時冷酷無情的蓮先生那樣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.36,0:07:52.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷酷…無情？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.51,0:07:55.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民好遲呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.09,0:08:00.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.48,0:08:04.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是大家一起做的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.90,0:08:06.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但最後的調整還…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.70,0:08:07.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不穿
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.55,0:08:10.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種輕飄飄的衣服我絕對不穿
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.14,0:08:13.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可  可是…小民…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.68,0:08:14.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少囉嗦！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.16,0:08:23.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一等  小民！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.15,0:08:28.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看我不爽這沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.06,0:08:32.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那件婚紗是我和小菜還有結名同學
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.81,0:08:34.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了少爺和崇子小姐才做的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.29,0:08:37.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們做得非常用心！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.52,0:08:38.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你卻把那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.70,0:08:39.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少囉嗦！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.61,0:08:41.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說你非常用心的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.16,0:08:42.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道徹先生就不是了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.33,0:08:47.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你踐踏了非常用心的徹先生的心意！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.60,0:08:50.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹  徹先生？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.62,0:08:52.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我決定了！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.07,0:08:55.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要單戀阿孝！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.76,0:08:58.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像小民這樣直接
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.66,0:08:59.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.29,0:09:02.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少胡說八道了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.91,0:09:04.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.77,0:09:06.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少給我去搞什麼單相思
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.84,0:09:07.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去跟徹先生交往啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.12,0:09:09.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死  去死  去死
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.86,0:09:12.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  要是死了就沒法交往了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.85,0:09:18.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  我已經決定要單戀阿孝了！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.68,0:09:19.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.76,0:09:21.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝什麼的那種傻瓜！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.17,0:09:22.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.12,0:09:24.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民你又沒見過他！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.58,0:09:28.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟徹先生相比  男人全都是傻瓜！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.51,0:09:28.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}小民
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.63,0:09:30.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生他那麼有型！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.83,0:09:32.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他那麼出色！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.29,0:09:33.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別再吵了！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.50,0:09:41.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子…你…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.56,0:09:47.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民  等一等…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.46,0:10:19.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是白癡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.06,0:10:24.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我嘛…那啥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.49,0:10:27.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確實對緒花有點意思
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.02,0:10:32.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說不定…真是有點喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.82,0:10:35.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也不是說我就要怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.82,0:10:38.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是看到她時會有些興奮而已
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.41,0:10:42.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會去猜測她接下來又會做些什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.25,0:10:49.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但看到你時我會放不下心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.73,0:10:55.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我剛說了什麼過分的話了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.36,0:10:58.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  不是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.36,0:11:00.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好開心…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.40,0:11:06.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算徹先生並不喜歡我…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.49,0:11:09.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也一樣會關注我…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.74,0:11:18.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是個白癡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.82,0:11:26.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  基本都弄乾淨了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.02,0:11:27.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.47,0:11:30.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.89,0:11:33.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.49,0:11:34.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太感動了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.04,0:11:40.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我還沒談過戀愛什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.02,0:11:43.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我覺得這一定很美妙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.08,0:11:45.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美妙…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.61,0:11:48.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  一直單相思下去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.84,0:11:51.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然吵架是不好的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.95,0:11:55.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我覺得緒花和小民都很棒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.99,0:11:59.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能像那樣思念著一個人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.55,0:12:01.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被你們感動了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.86,0:12:02.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小菜…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.84,0:12:05.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼感動啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.95,0:12:09.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.60,0:12:13.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.45,0:12:19.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常合適
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.11,0:12:25.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶吶  試著拿些白色鮮花吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.76,0:12:28.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說起來有在電視上看到過
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.31,0:12:29.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會顯得華貴一些呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.04,0:12:33.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去把樓梯旁邊的花拿過來
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.90,0:12:35.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小…小菜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.14,0:12:43.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鼻子不要緊嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.95,0:12:47.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.83,0:12:48.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會放棄的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.69,0:12:52.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會放棄的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.14,0:12:57.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的必須要和徹先生交往嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.15,0:12:59.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.00,0:13:03.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我想和徹先生交往
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.95,0:13:06.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說的是這個不會放棄
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.72,0:13:11.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要交往  所以會繼續單相思的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.94,0:13:12.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.43,0:13:15.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你說的那樣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.78,0:13:17.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直衝目標  所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.67,0:13:24.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.93,0:13:30.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花…又吵架…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.40,0:13:34.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛蛋復活祭喲～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.01,0:13:41.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之後  婚禮的準備也順利進行著
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.74,0:13:45.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不覺中我下定了決心
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.20,0:13:49.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婚禮順利結束後就去告白吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.36,0:13:56.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  挺不錯的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.80,0:13:57.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Perfect
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.14,0:14:01.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是無微不至
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.28,0:14:04.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝  多虧了大家
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.49,0:14:06.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婚禮一定會順利的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.12,0:14:08.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也這麼認為
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.73,0:14:17.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民  這邊這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.45,0:14:19.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打擾了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.79,0:14:28.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,崇子小姐  好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.81,0:14:30.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那當然了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.60,0:14:35.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可是女人一生中最漂亮的時刻
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.64,0:14:38.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人一生中…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.97,0:14:40.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有件事想要拜託你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.22,0:14:42.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拋花團的時候一定要…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.24,0:14:44.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.97,0:14:50.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大學畢業後好久不見了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.48,0:14:52.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼時候和崇子好上的？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.14,0:14:54.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.16,0:15:02.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我們就此成為夫妻
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.62,0:15:07.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能向大家宣佈這件事情我非常感動
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.48,0:15:10.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在大家面前發誓   從今天開始
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.00,0:15:13.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們夫妻將互相幫助  互相分享
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.86,0:15:17.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,營造一個幸福的家庭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.97,0:15:37.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.82,0:15:42.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到手了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.76,0:15:51.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開場結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.49,0:15:52.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來就是和時間賽跑
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.21,0:15:53.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.98,0:16:03.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.73,0:16:05.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,司儀什麼的  好緊張
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.44,0:16:07.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶吶  押水同學
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.07,0:16:09.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結名的頭髮沒問題嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.96,0:16:10.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不奇怪吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.50,0:16:13.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不奇怪  待會兒見
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.60,0:16:21.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戰鬥中的押水同學  真新鮮
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.95,0:16:23.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,廚房如戰場  開工了！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.29,0:16:24.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.31,0:16:25.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.20,0:16:27.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹  發號施令吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.96,0:16:31.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天你是這裡的主廚
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.33,0:16:32.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.19,0:16:33.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼  蓮先生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.33,0:16:35.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那裡的蔬菜處理一下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.88,0:16:37.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再把鯉魚的鱗片刮了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.12,0:16:37.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有把天婦羅油炸了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.02,0:16:40.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後把黃瓜雕花
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.08,0:16:43.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真…真過分啊你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.27,0:16:47.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在此由我誦讀一下賀電
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.38,0:16:52.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是新郎的姐姐  松前皋月發來的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.65,0:16:55.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俗話說雨後土固
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.65,0:16:55.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}註：形容經歷挫折之後現狀會變得更好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.79,0:16:58.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖說不知今天天氣如何
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.90,0:17:01.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之堅固是件好事  緣
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.39,0:17:03.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對男人來說
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.53,0:17:05.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.50,0:17:08.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一道料理呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.26,0:17:11.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才就是最後一道了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.72,0:17:14.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  各位辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.52,0:17:16.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請柬？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.91,0:17:20.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這場婚禮  我們也被邀請了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.68,0:17:25.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,崇子好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.44,0:17:26.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.41,0:17:31.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都好美味
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.53,0:17:35.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  還是第一次好好品嚐徹先生的料理
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.10,0:17:37.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.31,0:17:42.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我沒能阻止…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.86,0:17:45.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  下一個節目
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.48,0:17:48.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪裡～
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.42,0:17:53.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  我的命中注定的那個人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.66,0:17:56.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來在那裡嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.86,0:17:59.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親愛的  崇子小姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.09,0:18:05.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那邊在搞什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.12,0:18:08.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧  愛的Baiser
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.12,0:18:08.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}（Baiser：法語  接吻）
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.56,0:18:10.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.45,0:18:11.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.15,0:18:16.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噓  有反應就輸了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.58,0:19:27.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的婚禮  我完全沒有插手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.69,0:19:29.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使如此  這裡的兩人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.97,0:19:33.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及喜翠莊工作的年輕人們
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.40,0:19:35.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舉辦了如此成功的婚禮
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.68,0:19:38.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提下我的往事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.60,0:19:42.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,40年前  我和已逝的丈夫
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.96,0:19:44.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有在這裡的電六
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.65,0:19:49.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  和電六先生三人一起建起了喜翠莊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.00,0:19:52.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年輕就是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.39,0:19:55.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕受挫  迷惑
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.54,0:19:58.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也會毫不畏懼挑戰未知
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.80,0:20:02.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,創造新的事物
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.93,0:20:07.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩位以及大家一起創造的新的未來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.98,0:20:15.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就滿懷期待  在遠處喝著粗茶守望吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.66,0:20:20.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家的未來？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.45,0:20:22.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,守望？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.22,0:22:17.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順利…結束了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.85,0:22:19.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.19,0:22:22.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快收拾完了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.25,0:22:25.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.35,0:22:30.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才老闆娘所說的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.78,0:22:31.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.99,0:22:41.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓大家都聚在這裡不為別的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.33,0:22:47.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前電六先生和我談過
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.55,0:22:49.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.05,0:22:51.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,電六先生他說了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.52,0:22:55.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,40年間不曾間斷記錄著的工作日記
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.77,0:22:57.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該讓誰來繼承了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.71,0:23:03.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豆丁老爺  就是說要離開喜翠莊了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.90,0:23:06.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼  豆丁老爺
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.85,0:23:11.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這份工作日記就是喜翠莊的歷史本身
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.77,0:23:15.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼淚和歡笑全都記錄於此
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.73,0:23:18.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變得如此破爛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.65,0:23:25.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜翠莊將在這次的雪洞祭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.11,0:23:28.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與日記一同結束
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回預告
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.06,0:23:32.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1}要去見他嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.26,0:23:34.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3}單相思的那個人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.36,0:23:38.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耐心的等待也是男人的職責
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.67,0:23:41.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花 你才不是什麼沒味的咖啡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
