[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.7
; http://www.aegisub.net
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2011-12-29 17:34:41
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:花咲くいろは
Original Script:澄空学园&华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00000000,&H503D3D3D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,1,2,30,30,15,1
Style: Default2,@方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00000000,&H503D3D3D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,2,3,1,2,40,40,15,1
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H1E000000,&HA0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,1,8,10,10,15,1
Style: TITLE,@方正稚艺_GBK,45,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,2,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正稚艺_GBK,45,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFPMinchoP-W5,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,2,8,10,10,20,1
Style: OPCN,方正小标宋_GBK,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,2,2,2,2,10,10,18,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00000000,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,0,2,25,25,15,1
Style: INCN,方正小标宋_GBK,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,2,2,2,8,10,10,60,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------STAFF----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.00,0:03:00.00,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,Banner;6;0;35,本話製作人員　翻譯: 月々姫 涼子　校對: 高町米牙口　歌詞協力: tjx　計時: Lantis　後期: HySauce　繁化: 阿爽　製作: 澄空學園 × 華盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------TITLE----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.39,0:03:17.89,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(510,360)}喜翠無戰事
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------NEXT-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.90,0:23:41.40,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(510,360)}奔跑
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPJP-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.88,0:00:12.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)}{\be5}涙の雨が頬をたたくたびに美しく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.25,0:00:23.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}くだらないルールから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}はみ出せずに泣いていた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.57,0:00:30.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ぼやけすぎた未来地図
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.80,0:00:36.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,50)}{\be5}すり減ったココロを埋めたくて集めた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:40.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,200)}{\be5}要らないモノばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.53,0:00:46.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}バイバイ　あの愛しき日々は
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.21,0:00:51.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}戻りはしないから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:57.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}開いてゆく　小さく閉じたココロが
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.86,0:01:01.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}夜の隅で静かに
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:04.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}色付いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.28,0:01:12.70,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}もっと深く優しく朝の光を受けて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.94,0:01:25.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}{\be5}涙の雨が頬をたたくたびに美しく
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPCN-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.88,0:00:12.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)}{\be5}淚雨敲打著我的面頰　我卻變得越來越美麗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.25,0:00:23.39,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}無法逃離那世俗的規則
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}我只能默默哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.57,0:00:30.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}看著模糊不清的未來地圖
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.80,0:00:36.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,50)}{\be5}為了填補空虛的心靈而收集來的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:40.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,200)}{\be5}盡是些無聊的事物
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.53,0:00:46.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}Bye-bye　我那些一去不復返的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.21,0:00:51.07,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}珍愛時光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:57.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}打開那扇緊閉的小小心窗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.86,0:01:01.64,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}在那夜深人靜的角落裡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:04.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}漸漸染上色彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.28,0:01:12.70,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}感受更深沉安詳的朝陽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.94,0:01:25.48,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}{\be5}淚雨敲打著我的面頰　我卻變得越來越美麗
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------EDJP-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.80,0:22:19.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}夢を見る少し手前で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.19,0:22:23.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}置いてきたものはなんだっけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.02,0:22:29.59,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}忘れてしまいたくはないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.77,0:22:31.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}時折ふっと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.20,0:22:35.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}記憶の隅に浮かぶのは
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.58,0:22:39.26,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ふんわりぼやけたセピア色
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.32,0:22:46.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}目の前を塞ぐ日々の向こう　少しずつ遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.12,0:22:55.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}大体なんで息を切らして走ってるんだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.30,0:23:01.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}スピード上げてゆくほど
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.06,0:23:05.25,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}立ち止まることが怖くて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.35,0:23:12.18,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}早くなる鼓動に触れココに居ると確かめた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.59,0:23:20.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ココロの奥の小さな声に耳を澄ましたら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.31,0:23:29.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}{\be5}包み込む世界が晴れ広がるよ明日へ
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------EDCN-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.80,0:22:19.88,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}就要墜入夢鄉之前
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.19,0:22:23.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}把什麼放在了手邊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.02,0:22:29.59,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}明明不想忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.77,0:22:31.75,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}卻又無法想起
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.20,0:22:35.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}時而浮現在記憶角落裡的往日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.58,0:22:39.26,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}輕輕染上歲月的痕跡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.32,0:22:46.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}一縱即逝　漸行漸離
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.12,0:22:55.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}氣喘吁吁地奔跑又是為何
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.30,0:23:01.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}愈是加快步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.06,0:23:05.25,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}就愈是畏懼停下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.35,0:23:12.18,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}撫摸加速的心跳確認了自己的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.59,0:23:20.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}側耳傾聽　那微弱的心聲
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.31,0:23:29.95,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}{\be5}卻發現　天高海闊　直至未來
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------TEXT-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.17,0:01:36.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴  你下週要不要回這邊來
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.12,0:01:39.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？  一大清早的說些什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.47,0:01:42.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來相親了啊  來相親
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.34,0:01:43.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照片也寄過去了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.09,0:01:46.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你怎麼自說自話就決定了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.83,0:01:50.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一起參加聯誼的朋友裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.29,0:01:52.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒結婚的人就只剩你一個了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.76,0:01:55.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼知道那些…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.70,0:01:58.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左鄰右里的情報網  你可別小瞧它喲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.24,0:02:02.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說你看上個像是很有錢的客人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.29,0:02:04.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還說人家是個鑽石王老五
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.19,0:02:06.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但這世上哪裡還有那種客人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.57,0:02:08.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪  哪有你這麼失禮的母親
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.92,0:02:13.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是啊  你那地方事情多到連學生都要招來工作吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.60,0:02:18.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的左鄰右里情報網到底有多廣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.02,0:02:22.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總而言之  就是下週了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.12,0:02:24.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老媽我總得抱上外孫以後再入土
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.84,0:02:26.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種事我才不管呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.84,0:02:27.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣咯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.24,0:02:31.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…喂喂  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.76,0:02:42.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到…到底有多少啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.76,0:02:46.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  為了抱外孫要我結婚  結婚的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.48,0:02:53.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也明白父母總想趁著身體還健朗的時候抱上外孫
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.75,0:03:16.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣還有工作下去的意義嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.72,0:03:23.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  巴小姐  早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.74,0:03:25.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  接著要去學校了？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.19,0:03:28.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  因為工作結束得比較早
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.34,0:03:30.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天可以安安心心地上學去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.18,0:03:35.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年輕真是好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.95,0:03:39.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼話嘛  巴小姐也很年輕的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.67,0:03:45.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說出這番話還讓人覺得不是在挖苦的  大概就只有緒花你了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.09,0:03:48.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？  怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.15,0:03:49.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.98,0:03:51.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  去吧去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.85,0:03:53.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們走了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.11,0:04:08.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,青春無限好啊  前途無量
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.72,0:04:12.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,充滿了夢想和希望  還能穿迷你裙什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.86,0:04:17.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戀愛也好玩也好  想怎麼搞就怎麼搞還能有找頭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.63,0:04:21.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟她們一比  再看看我自己呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.39,0:04:25.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每一天都在重複同樣的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.34,0:04:31.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴小姐我根本沒有自己活著的實感啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.36,0:04:39.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別犯傻了  快做好迎接客人的準備
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.00,0:04:40.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.07,0:04:45.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了  說起那些客人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.18,0:04:46.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.60,0:04:51.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是那幾位哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.19,0:04:56.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是…難道說…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.21,0:05:00.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要忙碌起來咯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.80,0:05:10.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶  後天上哪兒去玩玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.72,0:05:14.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行呀  有團體預訂來喜翠莊的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.17,0:05:16.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀  是有這回事…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.87,0:05:18.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又沒得休息了嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.19,0:05:22.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總比沒客人光顧要來的強吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.24,0:05:51.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉眼確認到目標
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.61,0:05:53.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞭解  開始實施跟蹤
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.35,0:05:54.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞭解  瞭解
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.44,0:05:59.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.37,0:06:00.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是新的跟蹤狂？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.25,0:06:02.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是小菜的粉絲還是別的什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.89,0:06:04.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.76,0:06:09.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等  等一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.48,0:06:18.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根據偵察班發回的報告
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.33,0:06:21.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目標似乎是那家旅館的從業人員
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.64,0:06:23.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那正好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.44,0:06:25.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是Bravo1
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.89,0:06:27.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先來好好享受這場遊戲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.65,0:06:30.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Bravo2  瞭解
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.70,0:06:31.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞭解
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.27,0:06:33.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK  行動
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.85,0:06:45.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生存遊戲玩家？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.38,0:06:46.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什麼呀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.95,0:06:49.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩生存遊戲的人的總稱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.66,0:06:53.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是…那個…生存遊戲本身又是什麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.14,0:06:54.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,青花魚怎麼了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.47,0:07:00.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.46,0:07:02.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  我們在說生存遊戲
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.10,0:07:07.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡而言之  就是一群用玩具槍打來打去的人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.94,0:07:09.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們常來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.26,0:07:12.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然那類客人時不時就會來
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.57,0:07:14.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但大部分還是挺老實的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.94,0:07:15.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.90,0:07:16.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.23,0:07:19.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那群客人們不一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.05,0:07:22.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們是去年和前年也來過的常客
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.65,0:07:24.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之非常厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.97,0:07:27.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做的都是些幾乎就要觸及法律底線的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.57,0:07:30.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們已經做了幾乎觸及法律底線的事情了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.82,0:07:31.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對小菜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.55,0:07:36.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出生以來還是第一次那麼拼命地跑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.71,0:07:38.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前也有過這種事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.39,0:07:40.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們說這是跟蹤訓練
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.28,0:07:44.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過最多也就是跟在後面而已 不會有其他的舉動的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.93,0:07:45.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.06,0:07:48.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我才不信
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.22,0:08:11.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到達指定地點
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.84,0:08:13.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨時都可以採取突入行動
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.67,0:08:15.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在支援抵達之前待命
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.62,0:08:19.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過要是錯失她在打掃男浴室的這一良機…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.47,0:08:21.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫你待命  Bravo2
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.33,0:08:21.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隊長
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.55,0:08:23.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是命令！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.43,0:08:27.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隊長！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.52,0:08:29.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們在做什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.95,0:08:34.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  等等…客人？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.46,0:08:37.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人在嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.89,0:08:41.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷…偷窺未遂？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.03,0:08:44.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年他們的偷窺僅限於更衣室
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.56,0:08:48.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到程度越來越過火了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.36,0:08:49.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.87,0:08:53.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花你是在掃除的時候進去泡澡了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.02,0:08:54.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不自覺地就…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.93,0:08:57.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那被偷窺也咎由自取呀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.24,0:08:59.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實在是非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.96,0:09:01.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.22,0:09:04.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀  辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.42,0:09:06.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.87,0:09:10.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所謂的鑽石王老五  實際上卻是個大騙子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.75,0:09:19.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}（閒人止步）
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.20,0:09:19.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對那些孩子來說擔子還是太重了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.24,0:09:23.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也不能就這樣請他們回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.95,0:09:25.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓她們兩個多安個心眼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.48,0:09:27.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.71,0:09:31.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個  老闆娘
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.39,0:09:32.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.58,0:09:34.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然這種時候提出來有些不合時宜
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.68,0:09:38.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我考慮了下自己是不是要回趟老家
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.60,0:09:39.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶薪休假嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.75,0:09:43.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  倒不是那樣…那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.34,0:09:44.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.56,0:09:47.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶薪回老家  莫非是要去相親？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.28,0:09:50.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就連巴也死了心啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.26,0:09:59.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.77,0:10:06.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.89,0:10:09.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴小姐  我已經不堪忍受了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.08,0:10:12.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們還一直追到旅館裡面來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.91,0:10:15.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那說明他們非常中意你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.53,0:10:17.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我一點都高興不起來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.37,0:10:19.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他們攆出去不好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.52,0:10:21.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對現在的我們來說
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.10,0:10:23.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常客是最要感恩的人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.74,0:10:26.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有句話叫顧客就是上帝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.29,0:10:30.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得上帝應該不會做跟蹤狂吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.49,0:10:34.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭  又來了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.25,0:10:36.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小菜  等一等
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.37,0:10:39.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請不要跟過來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.97,0:10:40.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.47,0:10:46.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也累壞了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.60,0:10:58.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菜子再這樣下去可不妙了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.71,0:11:01.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我現在辭職  那孩子沒準就撐不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.78,0:11:05.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  又是老電影
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.57,0:11:10.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隊長  我們被敵人包圍了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.79,0:11:15.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過  我也不用去關心自己辭職之後的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.74,0:11:18.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先該怎麼辭職呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.65,0:11:21.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們還有未來
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.80,0:11:25.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎麼能讓它們在這片狗娘養的戰場上白費掉！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.20,0:11:26.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隊長
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.99,0:11:30.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓前途無量的年輕人們白白送死
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.29,0:11:31.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是於心不忍啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.25,0:11:34.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK BABY！ 放馬過來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.36,0:11:35.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隊長！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.96,0:11:40.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.89,0:11:43.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK BABY！ 放馬過來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.21,0:11:45.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果就這樣丟下那些孩子一走了之
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.05,0:11:48.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我豈不真成了白白送死了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.31,0:11:57.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.42,0:11:59.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總歸是要走的話
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.92,0:12:02.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如先惹毛那群傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.04,0:12:03.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,激得他們去投訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.63,0:12:05.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽快地把我炒魷魚不是更好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.49,0:12:10.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功的話既能把他們趕走
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.84,0:12:13.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作也能輕鬆結束
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.71,0:12:15.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了她們幾個的未來
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.77,0:12:18.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後就讓我赴湯蹈火一次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.50,0:12:22.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.09,0:12:26.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴小姐  早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.25,0:12:29.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了  大清早就愁眉苦臉的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.26,0:12:32.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些生存遊戲玩家…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.33,0:12:34.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明說好要8點進餐的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.60,0:12:36.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卻完全沒有起床的跡象
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.06,0:12:37.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都不好準備了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.37,0:12:40.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.22,0:12:52.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起床了  起床了  起床了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.26,0:12:55.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站起來把內褲穿好  小姐們
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.24,0:12:58.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我的女服務員人生結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.16,0:13:01.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Yes Ma'am
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.57,0:13:02.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.72,0:13:03.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請指示
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.16,0:13:07.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊需要準備早餐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.15,0:13:10.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以請在房外等候嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.54,0:13:11.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Yes Ma'am
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.24,0:13:14.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全隊向左轉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.76,0:13:17.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑步  走
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.67,0:13:26.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害  客人們居然那麼順從
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.93,0:13:28.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是巴小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.11,0:13:35.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得巴小姐是個可靠的姐姐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.00,0:13:36.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.10,0:13:40.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常都把女服務員的前輩稱作姐姐哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.97,0:13:44.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎  但是小菜沒有喊姐姐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.90,0:13:47.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴小姐說她不是那塊料
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.35,0:13:48.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不讓我這麼叫
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.82,0:13:53.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.27,0:13:55.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.72,0:13:58.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是命中要害了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.81,0:14:01.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴小姐  不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.78,0:14:04.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民  不可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.92,0:14:05.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放開我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.12,0:14:07.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs38}到底怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.28,0:14:08.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不去說他們幾句我就嚥不下這口氣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.85,0:14:12.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們完全不碰蓮先生做的飯菜
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.17,0:14:16.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像都在吃些速食食品
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.57,0:14:19.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是他們自己帶來的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.26,0:14:21.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.79,0:14:25.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些客人都喜歡吃戰鬥糧食
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.45,0:14:26.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戰鬥？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.53,0:14:27.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糧食？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.81,0:14:30.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,軍糧啊軍糧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.56,0:14:33.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是說比起豪華的飯菜
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.28,0:14:34.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更喜歡簡樸的食物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.72,0:14:43.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飯糰嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.40,0:14:46.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我們已經有軍糧…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.55,0:14:49.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起那種全是防腐劑和合成添加劑的食物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.83,0:14:52.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飯糰可遠遠要美味健康的多
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.32,0:14:56.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.19,0:15:00.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…巴小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.79,0:15:02.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這孩子做的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.99,0:15:06.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得給諸位的飯菜還犯不著麻煩廚師
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.65,0:15:07.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.90,0:15:10.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的…真的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.89,0:15:13.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這位小姐做的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.94,0:15:17.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點  民子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.24,0:15:23.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  不過我還不是正式廚師…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.09,0:15:26.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就稍微試吃一點…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.93,0:15:35.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.24,0:15:39.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和母親做給我的飯糰一樣的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.80,0:15:40.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隊長～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.62,0:15:43.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活著真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.37,0:15:44.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.84,0:15:46.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請再給我一些！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.18,0:15:48.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.68,0:15:51.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.49,0:15:55.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴小姐好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.76,0:15:58.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明其他飯菜一點都不吃的說
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.59,0:16:02.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次看到小民那樣的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.12,0:16:04.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.54,0:16:12.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然這樣只能不擇手段了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.71,0:16:16.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}打掃中
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.91,0:16:21.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次大意了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.36,0:16:23.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但已經沒有退路了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.27,0:16:24.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隊長
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.35,0:16:28.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我軍的存亡就賭在這場戰鬥上了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.33,0:16:30.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了也不會有人來收屍
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.32,0:16:34.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們願意把性命交給我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.21,0:16:41.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  確認情況！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.59,0:16:44.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右方確認完畢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.15,0:16:45.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左方確認完畢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.31,0:16:47.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,衝鋒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.94,0:17:07.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  今天要鼓起幹勁掃除了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.76,0:17:08.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是巴小姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.77,0:17:10.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個水管和平時的…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.10,0:17:13.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有責任由我來承擔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.27,0:17:15.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK BABY！ 放馬過來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.46,0:17:17.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,攻擊開…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.84,0:17:22.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣一來就結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.88,0:17:27.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡  撤退
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.05,0:17:28.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撤退！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.03,0:17:31.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃跑的人是生存遊戲玩家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.20,0:17:34.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不逃跑的人是訓練有素的生存遊戲玩家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.03,0:17:34.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\an8}出自電影《全金屬外殼》台詞  「逃跑的是越共，不逃跑的是訓練有素的越共」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.16,0:17:37.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像很開心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.26,0:17:41.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴小姐  很閃耀哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.35,0:17:42.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說啥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.86,0:17:46.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在～閃～耀～哦～
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.88,0:17:53.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡～
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.89,0:17:55.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.47,0:18:01.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在閃耀嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.64,0:18:05.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎麼說還是挺開心的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.75,0:18:06.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.35,0:18:10.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是這樣就結束了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.97,0:18:22.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.77,0:18:25.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.04,0:18:28.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次的事全是我的責任
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.49,0:18:30.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.33,0:18:33.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是你嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.17,0:18:39.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘  這個旅館有個非常棒的現場指揮官
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.15,0:18:39.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.62,0:18:43.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感謝您的誇獎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.98,0:18:46.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感謝你們認真配合我們的演習
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.71,0:18:50.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這段時間過得非常愉快
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.87,0:18:52.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才真是精彩的迎擊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.04,0:18:54.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們輸得心服口服
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.38,0:18:57.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還會再來的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.71,0:19:02.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到時候一定會突破你引以為豪的防線
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.23,0:19:04.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  到時候也將由現場指揮官及其下屬
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.85,0:19:08.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全力接待各位
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.46,0:19:14.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向指揮官閣下 敬禮
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.80,0:19:24.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭候再次光臨
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.10,0:19:27.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴小姐  我真是太感動了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.72,0:19:29.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接客的方法原來也是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.89,0:19:32.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根據不同的客人有不同的方法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.99,0:19:35.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差…差不多吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.42,0:19:37.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘經常說
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.12,0:19:39.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旅館是提供非日常生活的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.87,0:19:41.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來是這個意思呀
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.88,0:19:44.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個可不好說呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.51,0:19:48.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們也覺得自己還遠遠不足
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.43,0:19:50.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今後也要多多指教了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.08,0:19:55.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.17,0:19:57.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花好狡猾
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.83,0:20:00.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也可以這麼稱呼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.75,0:20:02.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴姐姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.13,0:20:08.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可愛！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.91,0:20:12.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔  叫吧叫吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.45,0:20:14.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儘管叫
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.09,0:20:15.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  巴姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.91,0:20:17.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.50,0:20:18.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.52,0:20:19.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.90,0:20:22.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  果然還是別加姐姐了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.99,0:20:24.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.74,0:20:27.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看過照片了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.41,0:20:28.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是些好男人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.76,0:20:29.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就定在下週了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.34,0:20:32.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照片都寄回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.77,0:20:35.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.33,0:20:40.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然最初也覺得辭掉工作回老家也不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.01,0:20:42.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也覺得？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.96,0:20:45.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是想繼續工作
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.15,0:20:47.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後輩也很可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.38,0:20:50.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我發現了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.56,0:20:52.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己真的很適合這個工作
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.76,0:20:55.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遇到各種不同的客人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.30,0:20:57.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得很有幹勁
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.49,0:20:59.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算什麼呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.79,0:21:02.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做著這份工作
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.41,0:21:04.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然超級累人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.48,0:21:07.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但卻也有著相應的充實感
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.21,0:21:08.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.08,0:21:12.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過累的時候的確累得要死就是了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.68,0:21:15.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很開心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.68,0:21:20.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  肯定會在媽媽你走前讓你看到外孫的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.44,0:21:21.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以再等等吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.03,0:21:26.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了  我也不說什麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.30,0:21:30.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼  要注意身體啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.52,0:21:32.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  真抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.67,0:21:35.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶爾也要回來露個臉哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.42,0:21:38.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  不過可能有點麻煩
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.68,0:21:40.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是做領班的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.84,0:21:41.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.90,0:21:42.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.95,0:21:47.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.50,0:21:49.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.25,0:21:51.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  今天也要鼓足勁幹活哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.30,0:21:52.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.00,0:23:34.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是沒用
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.55,0:23:35.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1}救護車
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.31,0:23:36.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.74,0:23:37.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3}媽媽  外婆她…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.42,0:23:41.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在的我所能做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
