[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.7
; http://www.aegisub.net
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2011-08-22 20:46:33
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:花咲くいろは
Original Script:澄空学园&华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00000000,&H503D3D3D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,1,2,30,30,15,1
Style: Default2,@方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00000000,&H503D3D3D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,2,3,1,2,40,40,15,1
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H1E000000,&HA0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,1,8,10,10,15,1
Style: TITLE,@方正稚艺_GBK,45,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,2,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正稚艺_GBK,45,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFPMinchoP-W5,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,2,8,10,10,20,1
Style: OPCN,方正小标宋_GBK,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,2,2,2,2,10,10,18,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00000000,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,0,2,25,25,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------STAFF----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.00,0:03:00.00,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,Banner;6;0;35,本話製作人員　翻譯: 月々姫　校對: 高町米牙口　歌詞協力: tjx　計時: Lantis　後期: HySauce　繁化: 阿爽　製作: 澄空學園 × 華盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------TITLE----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.45,0:02:49.95,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(510,360)}毛蛋
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------NEXT-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.90,0:23:41.40,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(510,360)}青鷺狂想曲
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPJP-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.88,0:00:12.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)}{\be5}涙の雨が頬をたたくたびに美しく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.25,0:00:23.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}くだらないルールから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}はみ出せずに泣いていた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.57,0:00:30.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ぼやけすぎた未来地図
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.80,0:00:36.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,50)}{\be5}すり減ったココロを埋めたくて集めた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:40.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,200)}{\be5}要らないモノばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.53,0:00:46.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}バイバイ　あの愛しき日々は
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.21,0:00:51.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}戻りはしないから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:57.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}開いてゆく　小さく閉じたココロが
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.86,0:01:01.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}夜の隅で静かに
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:04.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}色付いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.28,0:01:12.70,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}もっと深く優しく朝の光を受けて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.94,0:01:25.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}{\be5}涙の雨が頬をたたくたびに美しく
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPCN-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.88,0:00:12.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)}{\be5}淚雨敲打著我的面頰　我卻變得越來越美麗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.25,0:00:23.39,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}無法逃離那世俗的規則
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}我只能默默哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.57,0:00:30.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}看著模糊不清的未來地圖
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.80,0:00:36.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,50)}{\be5}為了填補空虛的心靈而收集來的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:40.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,200)}{\be5}盡是些無聊的事物
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.53,0:00:46.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}Bye-bye　我那些一去不復返的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.21,0:00:51.07,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}珍愛時光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:57.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}打開那扇緊閉的小小心窗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.86,0:01:01.64,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}在那夜深人靜的角落裡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:04.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}漸漸染上色彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.28,0:01:12.70,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}感受更深沉安詳的朝陽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.94,0:01:25.48,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}{\be5}淚雨敲打著我的面頰　我卻變得越來越美麗
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------EDJP-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.80,0:22:19.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}夢を見る少し手前で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.19,0:22:23.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}置いてきたものはなんだっけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.02,0:22:29.59,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}忘れてしまいたくはないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.77,0:22:31.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}時折ふっと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.20,0:22:35.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}記憶の隅に浮かぶのは
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.58,0:22:39.26,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ふんわりぼやけたセピア色
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.32,0:22:46.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}目の前を塞ぐ日々の向こう　少しずつ遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.12,0:22:55.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}大体なんで息を切らして走ってるんだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.30,0:23:01.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}スピード上げてゆくほど
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.06,0:23:05.25,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}立ち止まることが怖くて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.35,0:23:12.18,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}早くなる鼓動に触れココに居ると確かめた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.59,0:23:20.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ココロの奥の小さな声に耳を澄ましたら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.31,0:23:29.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}{\be5}包み込む世界が晴れ広がるよ明日へ
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------EDCN-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.80,0:22:19.88,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}就要墜入夢鄉之前
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.19,0:22:23.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}把什麼放在了手邊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.02,0:22:29.59,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}明明不想忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.77,0:22:31.75,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}卻又無法想起
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.20,0:22:35.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}時而浮現在記憶角落裡的往日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.58,0:22:39.26,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}輕輕染上歲月的痕跡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.32,0:22:46.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}一縱即逝　漸行漸離
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.12,0:22:55.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}氣喘吁吁地奔跑又是為何
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.30,0:23:01.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}愈是加快步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.06,0:23:05.25,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}就愈是畏懼停下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.35,0:23:12.18,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}撫摸加速的心跳確認了自己的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.59,0:23:20.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}側耳傾聽　那微弱的心聲
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.31,0:23:29.95,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}{\be5}卻發現　天高海闊　直至未來
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------TEXT-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.13,0:01:32.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,煩死了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.21,0:01:35.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明個子那麼小聲音卻好大
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.13,0:01:36.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要說「去死」什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.57,0:01:37.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.09,0:01:39.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開什麼玩笑  去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.60,0:01:42.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.03,0:01:44.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在嘀咕些什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.40,0:01:47.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦…沒什麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.28,0:01:58.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波之間的客人好像不要早餐了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.66,0:02:02.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個小說家  弄得好像全是這邊的錯一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.69,0:02:07.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶  我們吃掉吧  那傢伙的早餐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.46,0:02:10.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不先空著肚子的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.15,0:02:13.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.57,0:02:16.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心…心理準備
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.30,0:02:20.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.04,0:02:22.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.16,0:02:25.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,復仇的工作餐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.51,0:02:28.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是不止是芋艿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.17,0:02:30.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還放了蜥蜴什麼的該怎麼辦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.64,0:02:33.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.13,0:02:35.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃蜥蜴？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.97,0:02:37.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也會吃的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.65,0:02:39.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果討厭她的話
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.73,0:02:42.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會…並不是討厭她
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.47,0:02:45.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是她說話的時候不僅直直地盯著你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.26,0:02:47.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且聲音也大…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.39,0:02:49.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有點可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.23,0:02:55.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.28,0:03:08.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙居然背叛我們
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.63,0:03:15.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明明沒做工作餐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.74,0:03:16.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可原諒
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.17,0:03:19.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要被徹先生責罵…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.09,0:03:26.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼多…芋艿
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.82,0:03:28.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菠菜
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.92,0:03:33.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼  她人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.67,0:03:37.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.73,0:03:43.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個時候在我身上發生了不得了的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.20,0:04:06.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs36}「捆綁百選」
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.70,0:04:04.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡？還是穿過這裡？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.14,0:04:06.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.61,0:04:12.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要綁成龜甲縛卻又綁不起來
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.11,0:04:14.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.01,0:04:22.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先從這邊…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.83,0:04:25.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣嗎  謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.99,0:04:32.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然反被監禁的少女教…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.07,0:04:37.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.71,0:04:44.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的  我不會大叫的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.75,0:04:46.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.87,0:04:48.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.92,0:04:52.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼需要把我綁起來還塞住嘴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.97,0:04:59.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到了吧  那篇小說
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.87,0:05:03.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「溫泉女服務員  滿身泡沫的新人研修」
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.62,0:05:04.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.74,0:05:08.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我啊  其實不是什麼人氣小說家
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.55,0:05:11.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.89,0:05:17.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無論如何就是寫不出來
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.53,0:05:18.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎麼做都寫不出來
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.87,0:05:20.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是不能讓人共鳴
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.03,0:05:23.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本以為把自己關在旅館裡
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.88,0:05:25.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能想出什麼好題材
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.97,0:05:32.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後獲獎  想要一舉逆轉這個狀況
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.71,0:05:34.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就要滿身泡沫
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.81,0:05:39.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了償還眼前拖欠的住宿費
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.06,0:05:41.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以這次才想起寫工口小說的說
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.66,0:05:42.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工口…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.85,0:05:44.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但連工口卻都寫不出
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.31,0:05:47.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有那個才能啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.52,0:05:49.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.89,0:05:51.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別這麼灰心…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.26,0:05:57.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有沒有才能這不是自己能判斷的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.03,0:06:04.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼…能拜託你一件事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.41,0:06:05.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.72,0:06:07.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.91,0:06:33.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不在大廳
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.22,0:06:35.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豆丁老爺  你那邊怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.50,0:06:40.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然在做料理的中途消失
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.33,0:06:46.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這和那個小說家的原稿的消失有關係吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.32,0:06:49.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罪犯在這個旅館裡嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.16,0:06:51.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}果然還是報警吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.17,0:06:53.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是討厭我們了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.62,0:06:54.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}報警嗎  說的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.56,0:06:57.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們做了對緒花很過分的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.04,0:06:57.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}聯絡警察來調查吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.84,0:06:59.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}好  我去打電話
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.46,0:07:00.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回東京去了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.47,0:07:00.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}明白了  那麼拜託了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.02,0:07:02.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那趁這段時間再…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.70,0:07:06.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此為止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.38,0:07:09.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也沒什麼客人了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.63,0:07:12.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進行全館大掃除
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.24,0:07:14.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是老闆娘…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.41,0:07:15.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了  菜子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.53,0:07:18.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.50,0:07:23.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用忍耐哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.07,0:07:27.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不光是這個旅館的事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.46,0:07:31.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他的我會全部好好教給你的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.71,0:07:36.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平時聲音那麼大
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.23,0:07:38.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連這種時候也那麼大嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.03,0:07:40.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別…別再說了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.12,0:07:44.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…有才能嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.34,0:07:49.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聲音就那麼大嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.42,0:07:52.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個…不能算小吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.13,0:07:57.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是為什麼要寫我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.93,0:08:01.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那當然是在觀察你…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.33,0:08:05.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  沒有偷看洗澡哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.56,0:08:07.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對沒有  真的  我發誓
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.86,0:08:17.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然不行呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.01,0:08:19.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一點都不有趣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.74,0:08:22.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有趣什麼的  我還沒…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.72,0:08:29.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想變得閃耀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.91,0:08:34.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的  好好摩擦這裡的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.55,0:08:36.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會閃耀的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.81,0:08:38.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種地方…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.60,0:08:41.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要閃耀是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.67,0:08:49.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身體有點疲憊了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.33,0:08:52.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎丸先生  這是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.90,0:08:59.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…今天需要打掃嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.76,0:09:02.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了  今天就算了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.42,0:09:03.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.00,0:09:07.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有…我來查看下電燈…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.68,0:09:08.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真囉嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.35,0:09:11.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因為老在意這種事  原稿才會丟的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.43,0:09:13.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.63,0:09:15.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是讓人無語啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.56,0:09:17.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.33,0:09:20.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,垃圾旅館果然只有垃圾女服務員嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.25,0:09:21.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才沒有那種事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.60,0:09:27.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  為什麼你出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.48,0:09:29.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為你說過頭了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.75,0:09:30.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.69,0:09:33.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒辦法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.55,0:09:34.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然這樣就把你也…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.54,0:09:39.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.80,0:09:40.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.64,0:09:43.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然這樣連這個老頭也龜甲縛了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.00,0:09:47.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.56,0:09:48.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.20,0:09:55.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能不可能不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.86,0:09:59.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要綁這麼多人是不可能的！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.69,0:10:01.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請等一下  次郎丸先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.33,0:10:08.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.43,0:10:12.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都是謊言嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.96,0:10:14.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.65,0:10:15.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還以為他很有名氣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.01,0:10:18.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才對那些性騷擾睜一隻眼閉一隻眼的說
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.13,0:10:22.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙總是對料理挑三揀四的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.22,0:10:23.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘這次一定要報警…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.55,0:10:24.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}報警…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.91,0:10:24.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是就是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.40,0:10:25.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.97,0:10:30.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒聽客人親口承認之前還不好判斷
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.05,0:10:33.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘不相信我說的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.86,0:10:34.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.65,0:10:41.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是啊  在那之前我們不能去懷疑客人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.41,0:10:46.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼懷疑…我們都親眼看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.38,0:10:49.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豆丁老爺正要被龜甲縛的瞬間
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.82,0:10:53.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之這件事情…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.85,0:10:57.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  是我們的車
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.73,0:10:59.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是誰在駕駛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.70,0:11:18.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.63,0:11:35.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因為在這種時候也不能打破常規
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.51,0:11:36.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才那麼無能
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.35,0:11:39.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能破殼而出…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.42,0:11:44.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你快給我開門
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.60,0:11:49.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.34,0:11:54.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.22,0:11:56.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…蓮先生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.47,0:12:01.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上啊上啊  蓮先生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.25,0:12:04.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瀝水豆腐皮
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.50,0:12:05.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.64,0:12:08.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為下個月的菜單如何  老闆娘
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.03,0:12:12.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不錯  試著做一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.76,0:12:13.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.18,0:12:23.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎沒什麼緊張感呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.00,0:12:25.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是呀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.14,0:12:30.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.99,0:12:33.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.26,0:12:35.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.59,0:12:38.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來了來了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.84,0:12:45.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到哪裡去了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.78,0:12:46.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.70,0:12:48.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.20,0:13:02.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在車裡
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.19,0:13:03.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.03,0:13:07.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那裡！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.94,0:13:17.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.82,0:13:19.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很危險啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.37,0:13:20.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}別過來！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.01,0:13:22.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請不要過來！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.78,0:13:26.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我總是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.95,0:13:30.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在大家面前裝模作樣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.25,0:13:33.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打算欺騙大家
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.20,0:13:39.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那種事…早就被老闆娘看穿了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.17,0:13:42.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己真是沒用
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.06,0:13:45.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浪費別人的善意
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.95,0:13:48.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然我還是消失…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.21,0:13:49.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那才不是善意
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.76,0:13:50.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.62,0:13:53.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘說是因為工作才那樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.98,0:13:57.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘才不會那麼好心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.44,0:14:00.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…等等  我說你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.44,0:14:03.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家好不容易進入狀態
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.67,0:14:07.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉  客人  事實就是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.74,0:14:12.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.95,0:14:15.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使注意到客人的真實情況
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.54,0:14:18.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不能對其懷疑
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.01,0:14:23.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再說如果你獲獎了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.22,0:14:27.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們也能收到付款  這樣反而爽快
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.69,0:14:31.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未來的事誰也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.52,0:14:33.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要獲獎…不
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.24,0:14:35.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要不放棄要獲獎的決心
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.00,0:14:37.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能性就永遠存在
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.17,0:14:40.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人還是客人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.41,0:14:44.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真…真是太威風了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.09,0:14:46.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.76,0:14:48.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.65,0:14:49.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行不行不行不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.00,0:14:51.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有那個才能
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.15,0:14:55.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,獲獎什麼的絕對不可能！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.38,0:15:00.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎丸先生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.90,0:15:06.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還不想死
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.39,0:15:07.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.15,0:15:08.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  快去救他
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.64,0:15:13.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花  幫我拿著
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.35,0:15:14.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菜子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.19,0:15:16.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  快住…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.81,0:15:28.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.95,0:15:30.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要緊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.16,0:15:31.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.96,0:15:34.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個孩子小時候的綽號是小河童
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.57,0:15:36.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,河…？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.11,0:15:40.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三歲起就在游泳學校學習了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.66,0:15:42.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  去接菜子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.78,0:15:52.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菜子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.67,0:15:53.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菜子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.01,0:15:56.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很威風哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.25,0:15:58.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧  菜子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.87,0:16:00.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.64,0:16:01.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.37,0:16:03.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去拿毛巾
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.24,0:16:06.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菜子…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.61,0:16:13.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想死都死不成  我…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.03,0:16:16.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼還在說那種話
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.13,0:16:19.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.85,0:16:26.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎丸先生有才能的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.56,0:16:30.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「我想變得閃耀」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.16,0:16:33.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然說些什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.54,0:16:36.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是次郎丸先生寫的小說的台詞
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.24,0:16:40.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有我和民子和菜子登場
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.53,0:16:42.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.93,0:16:45.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們在浴室用拖布
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.10,0:16:48.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清洗奇怪的地方…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.86,0:16:50.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.58,0:16:53.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那篇小說  雖然工口…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.98,0:17:00.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但卻讓我注意到了…連我自己都沒注意到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.83,0:17:04.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明明不是想工作
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.98,0:17:07.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但卻不甘心  想做點什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.92,0:17:11.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是為什麼會這樣想 連我自己也不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.85,0:17:14.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是次郎丸先生卻告訴了我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.39,0:17:17.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來我是想變得閃耀
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.13,0:17:20.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.65,0:17:24.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我雖然不怎麼瞭解小說
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.49,0:17:27.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那一定是需要觀察力的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.41,0:17:33.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴了我不明白的事的次郎丸先生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.05,0:17:35.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的…是真正的小說家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.81,0:17:45.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.51,0:17:49.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎丸先生也開始在旅館工作
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.30,0:17:55.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一邊償還住宿費一邊執筆爭取獲獎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.53,0:18:04.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然在海邊吃飯比較豪華
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.54,0:18:06.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒好哦  少爺
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.21,0:18:08.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不夠意思
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.61,0:18:09.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菜子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.66,0:18:12.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是大活躍呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.68,0:18:14.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游泳的樣子  很威風哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.82,0:18:18.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來教你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.32,0:18:23.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起  那個沒必要吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.24,0:18:24.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游泳什麼的…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.09,0:18:27.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不啊  沒有那種事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.01,0:18:32.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒能好好教你女服務員的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.52,0:18:35.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是游泳的話
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.14,0:18:37.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還是有點自信的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.22,0:18:38.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.31,0:18:41.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  飯做好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.31,0:18:43.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.72,0:18:44.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.55,0:18:47.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好香
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.96,0:18:49.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儘管吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.99,0:18:50.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菠菜
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.54,0:18:54.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和小魚比較搭配
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.49,0:18:58.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來幫你盛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.98,0:19:03.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.16,0:19:06.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請用
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.94,0:19:14.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.23,0:19:14.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.97,0:19:17.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}吃下去了吃下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.63,0:19:17.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的搞不懂她
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.84,0:19:20.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.41,0:19:21.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}毛蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.58,0:19:27.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛蛋？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.44,0:19:36.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老伴  那孩子真的和皋月一個樣哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.22,0:19:41.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了  次郎丸先生換好地方了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.45,0:19:46.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖說原本是放被褥的房間
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.18,0:19:48.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過那點程度還是讓他忍忍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.05,0:19:51.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,電六  怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.86,0:19:53.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你早就知道了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.04,0:19:55.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.69,0:19:59.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花她會做好一切的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.28,0:20:06.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋只要適得其所也能派上用場
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.61,0:20:14.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}「日本的旅館  服務員教程 初級  時刻為客人著想」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.12,0:20:16.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好難
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.72,0:20:19.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休息休息
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.77,0:20:32.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還在練習削皮嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.14,0:20:40.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs36}除「去死」以外的話
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.14,0:20:40.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs36}不爽→有點太普通…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.39,0:20:43.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs36}別過來→傷害還不夠…嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.14,0:20:46.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs36}hobiron→ho=真是  bi=讓人詫異到  ron=不可理喻
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.23,0:20:51.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.30,0:20:55.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛蛋…胚胎已經死亡的禽蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.04,0:20:57.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可食用
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.28,0:20:58.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起來噁心
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.67,0:21:03.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從生理上難以接受 意思也對的上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.81,0:21:13.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這份努力  好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.18,0:21:20.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被這麼拼命地討厭  總覺得有點神清氣爽…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.13,0:21:24.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是媽媽的不分場合的郵件
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.91,0:21:28.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不分場合的習慣是媽媽遺傳的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.92,0:21:32.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.40,0:21:34.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs36}阿孝：\N沒去送你對不起  緒花  加油！！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.31,0:21:36.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好神奇
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.14,0:21:40.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在東京的時候總覺得這麼交流是理所當然的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.51,0:21:44.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收到阿孝的郵件居然會這麼高興
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.40,0:21:47.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「加油」…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.25,0:21:54.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我會加油的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.71,0:21:59.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這裡  加油到變得閃耀
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.01,0:23:35.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子非常受歡迎哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.11,0:23:35.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1}是最任性的人！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.72,0:23:37.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3}誰是「高原的少女」啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.72,0:23:40.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別—吵—了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
