[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.7
; http://www.aegisub.net
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2011-08-26 13:24:43
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:花咲くいろは
Original Script:澄空学园&华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00000000,&H503D3D3D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,1,2,30,30,15,1
Style: Default2,@方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00000000,&H503D3D3D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,2,3,1,2,40,40,15,1
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H1E000000,&HA0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,1,8,10,10,15,1
Style: TITLE,@方正稚艺_GBK,45,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,2,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正稚艺_GBK,45,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFPMinchoP-W5,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,2,8,10,10,20,1
Style: OPCN,方正小标宋_GBK,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,2,2,2,2,10,10,18,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00000000,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,0,2,25,25,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------STAFF----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.00,0:03:00.00,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,Banner;6;0;35,本話製作人員　翻譯: 月々姫 涼子　校對: 高町米牙口　歌詞協力: tjx　計時: Lantis　後期: HySauce　繁化: 阿爽　製作: 澄空學園 × 華盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------TITLE----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.44,0:03:29.94,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(510,360)}流淚的廚師之戀
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------NEXT-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.90,0:23:41.40,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,460)}不入虎穴  焉得虎子
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPJP-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.88,0:00:12.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)}{\be5}涙の雨が頬をたたくたびに美しく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.25,0:00:23.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}くだらないルールから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}はみ出せずに泣いていた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.57,0:00:30.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ぼやけすぎた未来地図
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.80,0:00:36.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,50)}{\be5}すり減ったココロを埋めたくて集めた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:40.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,200)}{\be5}要らないモノばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.53,0:00:46.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}バイバイ　あの愛しき日々は
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.21,0:00:51.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}戻りはしないから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:57.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}開いてゆく　小さく閉じたココロが
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.86,0:01:01.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}夜の隅で静かに
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:04.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}色付いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.28,0:01:12.70,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}もっと深く優しく朝の光を受けて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.94,0:01:25.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}{\be5}涙の雨が頬をたたくたびに美しく
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPCN-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.88,0:00:12.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)}{\be5}淚雨敲打著我的面頰　我卻變得越來越美麗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.25,0:00:23.39,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}無法逃離那世俗的規則
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}我只能默默哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.57,0:00:30.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}看著模糊不清的未來地圖
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.80,0:00:36.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,50)}{\be5}為了填補空虛的心靈而收集來的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:40.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,200)}{\be5}盡是些無聊的事物
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.53,0:00:46.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}Bye-bye　我那些一去不復返的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.21,0:00:51.07,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}珍愛時光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:57.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}打開那扇緊閉的小小心窗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.86,0:01:01.64,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}在那夜深人靜的角落裡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:04.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}漸漸染上色彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.28,0:01:12.70,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}感受更深沉安詳的朝陽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.94,0:01:25.48,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}{\be5}淚雨敲打著我的面頰　我卻變得越來越美麗
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------EDJP-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.80,0:22:19.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}夢を見る少し手前で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.19,0:22:23.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}置いてきたものはなんだっけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.02,0:22:29.59,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}忘れてしまいたくはないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.77,0:22:31.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}時折ふっと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.20,0:22:35.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}記憶の隅に浮かぶのは
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.58,0:22:39.26,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ふんわりぼやけたセピア色
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.32,0:22:46.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}目の前を塞ぐ日々の向こう　少しずつ遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.12,0:22:55.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}大体なんで息を切らして走ってるんだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.30,0:23:01.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}スピード上げてゆくほど
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.06,0:23:05.25,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}立ち止まることが怖くて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.35,0:23:12.18,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}早くなる鼓動に触れココに居ると確かめた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.59,0:23:20.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ココロの奥の小さな声に耳を澄ましたら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.31,0:23:29.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}{\be5}包み込む世界が晴れ広がるよ明日へ
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------EDCN-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.80,0:22:19.88,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}就要墜入夢鄉之前
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.19,0:22:23.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}把什麼放在了手邊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.02,0:22:29.59,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}明明不想忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.77,0:22:31.75,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}卻又無法想起
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.20,0:22:35.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}時而浮現在記憶角落裡的往日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.58,0:22:39.26,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}輕輕染上歲月的痕跡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.32,0:22:46.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}一縱即逝　漸行漸離
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.12,0:22:55.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}氣喘吁吁地奔跑又是為何
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.30,0:23:01.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}愈是加快步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.06,0:23:05.25,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}就愈是畏懼停下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.35,0:23:12.18,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}撫摸加速的心跳確認了自己的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.59,0:23:20.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}側耳傾聽　那微弱的心聲
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.31,0:23:29.95,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}{\be5}卻發現　天高海闊　直至未來
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------TEXT-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.38,0:01:49.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目睹了非常震撼的一幕
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.69,0:01:56.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個  大概就是所謂的修羅場吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.35,0:02:02.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.00,0:02:06.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.39,0:02:09.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  那個
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.99,0:02:10.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不許說話
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.43,0:02:13.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不許跟我搭訕也不許呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會死人的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.66,0:02:20.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.54,0:02:23.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.62,0:02:25.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.05,0:02:28.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發生什麼事了  緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.21,0:02:31.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.12,0:02:36.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.74,0:02:42.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生他？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.05,0:02:44.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會從福屋出來
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.86,0:02:46.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎麼回事…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.56,0:02:47.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那件事…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.69,0:02:51.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能告訴我詳情呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.42,0:03:07.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.55,0:03:10.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從倉庫裡拿把刨刀過來
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.70,0:03:11.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.71,0:03:17.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個  徹先生…今天好遲呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.25,0:03:19.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙的話  不會來了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.53,0:03:21.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是怎麼回事…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.79,0:03:23.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刨刀  快點拿過來
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.96,0:03:26.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.50,0:03:35.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挖牆腳？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.16,0:03:40.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從我收集到的情報來做推測的話
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.25,0:03:41.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕是了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.47,0:03:42.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情報是？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.41,0:03:47.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從前我就認為相較情色文學我更適合當一名社會派作家
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.40,0:03:52.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了以這個破落的溫泉街為背景寫小說
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.10,0:03:53.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我接觸了各種各樣的人間冷暖
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.57,0:03:56.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就各種各樣的內幕做了取材
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.05,0:03:58.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦  社會派
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.87,0:04:00.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種事都無所謂了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.58,0:04:02.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快說徹被挖角的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.54,0:04:03.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都無所謂？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.47,0:04:05.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也罷
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.16,0:04:07.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家也都知道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.22,0:04:10.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這兒的老闆娘和福屋的老闆娘
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.05,0:04:13.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她們自很早起就是競爭對手
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.52,0:04:19.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傳聞倒是有聽說過
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.83,0:04:22.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,認為必須將喜翠莊打壓下去的福屋
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.18,0:04:24.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將其魔手伸向了徹君
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.39,0:04:27.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去一位才華橫溢的廚師
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.78,0:04:30.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對喜翠莊而言是很大的損失
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.69,0:04:33.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼  那次是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.46,0:04:37.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天晚上我看到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.15,0:04:42.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的可以嗎  蓮先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.00,0:04:46.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算我不在了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.06,0:04:50.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你不在了  這裡也有我來頂著
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.88,0:04:52.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.69,0:05:02.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不是他去找蓮先生商量了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.96,0:05:04.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有關挖牆腳的事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.56,0:05:06.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福屋是超一流的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.22,0:05:10.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和經營並不興隆的這邊相較之下前途要更為光明
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.57,0:05:11.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說得太過分了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.88,0:05:14.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蓮先生為了前途有望的徹君
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.05,0:05:17.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給他指了一條坦蕩的明路
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.65,0:05:19.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概就是這麼一回事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.27,0:05:21.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼那麼突然
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.85,0:05:23.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒開離別會呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.00,0:05:26.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過徹君還真有一手呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.47,0:05:29.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到那麼快就和福屋的繼承人打得火熱…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.65,0:05:30.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才沒這回事！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.89,0:05:32.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.73,0:05:36.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然他話裡帶刺  看起來很冷漠
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.93,0:05:41.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他實際上比誰都更加鍾愛喜翠莊的人和工作！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.01,0:05:44.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生怎麼可能同意那種事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.27,0:05:46.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刨刀殺人事件
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.78,0:05:48.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我們去問當事人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.86,0:05:54.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生他…那個…今天
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.83,0:05:55.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不在嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.98,0:05:58.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚了一步嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.72,0:06:00.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已經走了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.04,0:06:03.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我們給丟下…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.37,0:06:09.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.88,0:06:18.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白姑魚順利蒸好了  花椒葉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.56,0:06:19.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬上就能做好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.61,0:06:26.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問…徹先生為什麼要去福屋
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.82,0:06:30.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是真心希望成為一名廚師的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.61,0:06:32.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.64,0:06:34.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你總有一天會明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.21,0:06:35.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.83,0:06:39.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰讓你走神了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.11,0:06:40.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起  花椒葉馬上就…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.14,0:06:41.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混帳東西
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.21,0:06:45.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就想用這手指頭去碰給客人下口的東西嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.14,0:06:47.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.99,0:06:52.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.11,0:06:55.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀  她已經是重症病人了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.35,0:07:00.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這也沒辦法  因為恩人不在了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.29,0:07:01.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩人？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.54,0:07:07.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓民子能在這裡工作的人  其實是徹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.03,0:07:11.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子本來連現在讀的學校都不去上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.59,0:07:13.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一心想當一名廚師
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.21,0:07:16.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但卻遭到了父母的反對
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.07,0:07:18.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她卻沒有死心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.01,0:07:21.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直在找能帶她鍛鍊的廚師
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.21,0:07:25.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了  請讓我在這裡工作吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.67,0:07:27.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你這麼懇求…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.85,0:07:30.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你父母不是反對嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.31,0:07:32.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.32,0:07:35.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,廚師可沒你想得那麼輕鬆
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.61,0:07:38.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你辦得好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.41,0:07:40.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辦得好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.90,0:07:45.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使給我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.48,0:08:03.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.31,0:08:09.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很厚呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.48,0:08:10.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太厚了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.67,0:08:13.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這點手藝還虧你想當廚師呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.99,0:08:19.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還差得很遠呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.53,0:08:22.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘  蓮先生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.54,0:08:27.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這傢伙成器之前  能不能先暫時留在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.85,0:08:32.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然她的手藝還差得遠  但她這份心意不像是假的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.78,0:08:37.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦  蓮先生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.78,0:08:41.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可要從頭把她教起
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.74,0:08:42.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.04,0:08:44.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧你這副呆頭呆腦的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.47,0:08:47.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,廚師的早晨可是很早的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.54,0:08:48.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你個新人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.13,0:08:51.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太  太感謝您了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.22,0:08:54.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來是這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.57,0:08:57.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去探望探望她吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.57,0:09:04.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的工作就交給我和菜子處理
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.20,0:09:05.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.66,0:09:27.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.88,0:09:32.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  那個  民子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.30,0:09:35.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己的工作呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.33,0:09:38.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…我有些擔心你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.19,0:09:40.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多管閒事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.95,0:09:47.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去不去得了福屋呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.08,0:09:49.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.47,0:09:50.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就我這手藝
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.44,0:09:56.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題的！  徹先生一定會推薦你的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.82,0:09:58.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你到這裡來一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.80,0:10:00.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  你哪裡聽來的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.85,0:10:04.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想啊  民子你在的話  徹先生一定也會方便一些…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.85,0:10:06.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這個…毛蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.45,0:10:09.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎麼可能會想去福屋那地方
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.86,0:10:13.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是多虧的徹先生才能在喜翠莊工作起來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.89,0:10:16.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生  還有老闆娘  還有蓮先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.99,0:10:19.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我欠著喜翠莊一筆還不清的恩情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.99,0:10:22.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過剛才你說想去福屋…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.75,0:10:25.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是那個意思…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.22,0:10:27.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子好厲害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.60,0:10:31.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作  戀愛  還有自己的事情  全都在努力著
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.38,0:10:36.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想為民子鼓勁
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.31,0:10:38.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你應該去追隨他
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.69,0:10:40.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可  可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.35,0:10:44.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為民子  要是沒有徹先生在身邊你就一事無成吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.00,0:10:47.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出去…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.02,0:10:50.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快出去  毛蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.84,0:10:50.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}民子…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.76,0:10:54.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被趕出來了…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.34,0:11:01.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子真的喜歡他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.14,0:11:07.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡一個人真是不得了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.84,0:11:12.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個  阿孝也是一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.28,0:11:11.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs38}（沒能去送你真對不起  緒花  要加油啊！！）
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.56,0:11:14.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.09,0:11:19.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得你可不能期待過頭哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.46,0:11:21.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為你想啊  當地的祭典…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.39,0:11:26.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  我也沒說沒用啊  崇子小姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.21,0:11:30.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼沸點那麼低啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.10,0:11:32.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它在哪兒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.45,0:11:37.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  你在這裡偷什麼懶啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.69,0:11:38.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  有點點…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.92,0:11:41.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了  你來幫個忙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.19,0:11:42.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.40,0:11:48.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到紙燈的話就告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.65,0:11:50.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,箱子你隨便翻就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.98,0:11:51.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.91,0:11:57.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道哪個是紙燈吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.87,0:12:05.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說不定我根本什麼都不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.81,0:12:11.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  就是那個  紙燈
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.75,0:12:14.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是雪洞祭用的紙燈？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.82,0:12:15.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道呀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.66,0:12:18.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.15,0:12:22.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.04,0:12:25.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔  那個是祈願牌
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.64,0:12:27.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祈願牌？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.14,0:12:39.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說把寫著願望的祈願牌掛在紙燈下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.76,0:12:41.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為指引道路的回禮
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.19,0:12:45.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神靈們就會把它帶到出雲將願望實現
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.86,0:12:53.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是能實現願望的人只有那些真正努力的人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.84,0:12:56.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像緒花這樣工作偷懶的人是沒戲的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.44,0:12:59.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,努力的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.03,0:13:05.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  光把紙燈換成現代風格
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.34,0:13:07.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人真的會增加嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.90,0:13:11.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖說還是會按照崇子小姐的意思去做
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.39,0:13:14.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正努力的人的願望會實現的對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.96,0:13:15.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.69,0:13:17.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個借用一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.17,0:13:18.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.75,0:13:22.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛蛋  毛蛋  毛蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.99,0:13:24.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本什麼都不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.86,0:13:25.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.69,0:13:36.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.12,0:13:39.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去帶徹先生回來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.34,0:13:41.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.19,0:13:43.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生說話很毒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.44,0:13:44.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作卻比任何人都傾盡全力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.92,0:13:46.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比任何人都要體貼人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.89,0:13:49.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然看上去很粗魯很無情
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.46,0:13:53.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他實際上比誰都更加鍾愛喜翠莊的人和工作
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.56,0:13:55.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頭髮長短大概到這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.80,0:13:57.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼角有點往上吊是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.36,0:14:00.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的人不在了可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.79,0:14:01.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.41,0:14:04.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本什麼都不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.61,0:14:08.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生是因為手藝得到了肯定才去的福屋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.57,0:14:12.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那是多麼了不起的事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.09,0:14:12.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.18,0:14:14.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.77,0:14:18.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要為徹先生加油
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.87,0:14:19.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.14,0:14:21.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想妨礙徹先生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.08,0:14:24.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子真是毛蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.54,0:14:25.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.40,0:14:27.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜歡徹先生沒錯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.98,0:14:29.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.95,0:14:31.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一個人去福屋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.14,0:14:34.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  你去了又有什麼用
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.79,0:14:37.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想為拼命努力的民子做點什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.44,0:14:42.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此一來我也似乎能努力去做點什麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.78,0:14:45.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  肯定沒用的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.95,0:14:47.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼能帶的回來
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.94,0:14:48.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個時候…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.51,0:14:51.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就向神靈祈願！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.69,0:14:54.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我去了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.02,0:14:58.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…你等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.69,0:15:19.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.33,0:15:28.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是毛蛋…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.48,0:15:43.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人嗎！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.65,0:15:47.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿～婆～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.25,0:15:51.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說過讓你喊老闆娘的吧  結名
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.40,0:15:54.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉～阿婆～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.55,0:15:56.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.39,0:16:02.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像～正門那邊有點吵～
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.04,0:16:04.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點出來  老闆娘！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.57,0:16:06.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  別胡鬧了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.61,0:16:08.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事啊  吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.08,0:16:10.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.91,0:16:11.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出現了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.95,0:16:14.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…四十萬那裡的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.51,0:16:15.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是她的外孫女
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.69,0:16:17.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一個請求
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.39,0:16:19.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請把徹先生還回來
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.76,0:16:20.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.78,0:16:22.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說到底福屋也太過分了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.36,0:16:26.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,房子也大  車又多
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.50,0:16:28.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外孫女又那麼漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.63,0:16:31.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不挖牆腳也沒問題啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.74,0:16:35.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這孩子到底在說什麼呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.83,0:16:39.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜翠莊需要徹先生  所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.43,0:16:40.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生的話  已經回去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.74,0:16:42.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回哪兒了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.37,0:16:44.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜翠莊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.90,0:16:47.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回喜翠莊…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.61,0:16:50.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.77,0:16:55.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幫手？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.17,0:16:59.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的廚師只有一個人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.21,0:17:01.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為感冒倒下了  讓我們很苦惱
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.28,0:17:05.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜翠莊的主廚就把徹先生借給我們了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.96,0:17:09.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天嘗試了一下三腳貓的博多腔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.58,0:17:11.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽明白了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.40,0:17:16.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.64,0:17:20.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那結名和徹先生是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.28,0:17:22.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.20,0:17:24.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個早上兩人一起坐著摩托…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.02,0:17:28.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想坐一下就拜託他載我了一程
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.70,0:17:29.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.27,0:17:31.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  對了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.73,0:17:33.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頭盔怎麼辦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.44,0:17:35.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生又不過來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.57,0:17:36.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花需要嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.95,0:17:38.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然有點花哨
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.39,0:17:39.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但以後你就可以坐摩托車了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.63,0:17:46.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到時候請務必相借…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.88,0:17:51.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,累死了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.97,0:17:53.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.01,0:17:56.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花  徹先生回來了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.60,0:17:59.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挖牆腳？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.02,0:18:01.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這話怎麼跳出來的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.01,0:18:05.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.62,0:18:10.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這作家有時間說閒話不如快去寫工口小說去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.17,0:18:14.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蓮先生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.52,0:18:19.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果…如果我真的被挖走了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.45,0:18:21.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.20,0:18:25.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次絕對會阻止你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.51,0:18:27.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又沒有問你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.20,0:18:29.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.57,0:18:33.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民子  去確認蔬菜的存貨
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.89,0:18:34.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.76,0:18:36.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後再整理一下真空包裝的食材
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.73,0:18:41.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  民子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.17,0:18:43.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.84,0:18:51.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓開
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.02,0:18:54.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這樣我騎不了摩托吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.18,0:18:55.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.39,0:18:59.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明沒什麼突出  卻到處搗亂
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.05,0:19:03.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  我讓開了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.13,0:19:07.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點回去啊  辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.01,0:19:10.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明來帶我回去又這個態度
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.41,0:19:12.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送別會要什麼時候搞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.31,0:19:14.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.57,0:19:19.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果挽留我的人只有你一個嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.92,0:19:24.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過  總比沒的好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.45,0:19:27.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.89,0:19:30.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我鼻子很纖細的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.34,0:19:34.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要讓蓮先生來挽留我  我還差得遠呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.72,0:19:46.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生回去了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.68,0:19:48.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.36,0:19:50.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我果然不擅長對付那個人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.19,0:19:58.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹他得到了一次不錯的經驗呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.84,0:20:01.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣一來我不管什麼時候去了也沒問題了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.99,0:20:02.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老闆娘
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.71,0:20:03.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開個玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.57,0:20:07.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緣  待會兒打個道歉的電話
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.79,0:20:10.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給茂子那邊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.70,0:20:12.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福屋嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.40,0:20:17.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得這一天好辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.71,0:20:20.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到處在跑呢  緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.24,0:20:22.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了呢  民子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.20,0:20:24.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有被挖牆腳
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.69,0:20:27.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不明擺著的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.36,0:20:32.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今後也一直都和徹先生在一起呢  民子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.00,0:20:34.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.85,0:20:37.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.84,0:20:38.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為交換
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.51,0:20:42.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也寫上喜歡的暱稱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.18,0:20:43.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會那麼稱呼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.07,0:20:45.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直希望給自己取個的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.73,0:20:47.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽菜子說了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.32,0:20:48.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你寫在祈願牌上的話
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.21,0:20:50.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就那麼稱呼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.04,0:20:52.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.53,0:20:56.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就收下了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.22,0:20:58.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過  還真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.74,0:21:04.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到需要自己來想
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.51,0:21:07.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然有了小菜和小民
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.37,0:21:09.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就是小緒？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.95,0:21:12.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過好像是小花比較好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.13,0:21:15.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不過那樣聽起來像鼻血了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.13,0:21:15.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}（註: 日語中鼻血與小花音相近）
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.32,0:21:16.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那還是…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.79,0:21:19.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.71,0:21:21.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時間到
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.82,0:21:23.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒  怎麼能這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.55,0:21:25.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪你太磨蹭了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.71,0:21:27.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我馬上就想好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.71,0:21:28.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來一次
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.51,0:21:29.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.82,0:21:32.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民  小民  拜託了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.60,0:21:33.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.05,0:21:38.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝  你好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.71,0:21:39.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.76,0:21:43.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝  我呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.08,0:21:45.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於有點努力了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.69,0:21:52.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是多虧阿孝發郵件讓我加油
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.98,0:21:58.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你  阿孝
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.01,0:23:34.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明明不想挑戰的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.87,0:23:34.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3}你在看什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.74,0:23:36.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1}打起精神
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.75,0:23:38.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  沒用的旅館
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.83,0:23:41.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  沒用的旅館的傭人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
