[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.7
; http://www.aegisub.net
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-01-07 12:48:36
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:花咲くいろは
Original Script:澄空学园&华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00000000,&H503D3D3D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,1,2,30,30,15,1
Style: Default2,@方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00000000,&H503D3D3D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,2,3,1,2,40,40,15,1
Style: STAFF,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H1E000000,&HA0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,3,1,8,10,10,15,1
Style: TITLE,@方正稚艺_GBK,45,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,2,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正稚艺_GBK,45,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFPMinchoP-W5,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,2,8,10,10,20,1
Style: OPCN,方正小标宋_GBK,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,2,2,2,2,10,10,18,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00000000,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,2,2,0,2,25,25,15,1
Style: INCN,方正小标宋_GBK,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,2,2,2,8,10,10,60,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------STAFF----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.00,0:03:00.00,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,Banner;6;0;35,本話製作人員　翻譯: 月々姫　校對: 高町米牙口　歌詞協力: tjx　計時: Lantis　後期: HySauce　繁化: 阿爽　製作: 澄空學園 × 華盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------TITLE----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.60,0:02:00.10,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(510,360)}再見
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------NEXT-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.90,0:23:41.40,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(480,360)}四十萬之女
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.90,0:23:41.40,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(420,450)\fs36\b0}～傷心mix～
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPJP-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.88,0:00:12.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)}{\be5}涙の雨が頬をたたくたびに美しく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.25,0:00:23.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}くだらないルールから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}はみ出せずに泣いていた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.57,0:00:30.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ぼやけすぎた未来地図
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.80,0:00:36.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,50)}{\be5}すり減ったココロを埋めたくて集めた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:40.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,200)}{\be5}要らないモノばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.53,0:00:46.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}バイバイ　あの愛しき日々は
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.21,0:00:51.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}戻りはしないから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:57.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}開いてゆく　小さく閉じたココロが
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.86,0:01:01.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}夜の隅で静かに
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:04.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}色付いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.28,0:01:12.70,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}もっと深く優しく朝の光を受けて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.94,0:01:25.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}{\be5}涙の雨が頬をたたくたびに美しく
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPCN-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.88,0:00:12.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)}{\be5}淚雨敲打著我的面頰　我卻變得越來越美麗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.25,0:00:23.39,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}無法逃離那世俗的規則
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}我只能默默哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.57,0:00:30.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}看著模糊不清的未來地圖
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.80,0:00:36.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,50)}{\be5}為了填補空虛的心靈而收集來的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:40.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,200)}{\be5}盡是些無聊的事物
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.53,0:00:46.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}Bye-bye　我那些一去不復返的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.21,0:00:51.07,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}珍愛時光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:57.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}打開那扇緊閉的小小心窗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.86,0:01:01.64,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}在那夜深人靜的角落裡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:04.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}漸漸染上色彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.28,0:01:12.70,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}感受更深沉安詳的朝陽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.94,0:01:25.48,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}{\be5}淚雨敲打著我的面頰　我卻變得越來越美麗
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------EDJP-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.80,0:22:19.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}夢を見る少し手前で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.19,0:22:23.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}置いてきたものはなんだっけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.02,0:22:29.59,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}忘れてしまいたくはないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.77,0:22:31.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}時折ふっと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.20,0:22:35.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}記憶の隅に浮かぶのは
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.58,0:22:39.26,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ふんわりぼやけたセピア色
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.32,0:22:46.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}目の前を塞ぐ日々の向こう　少しずつ遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.12,0:22:55.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}大体なんで息を切らして走ってるんだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.30,0:23:01.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}スピード上げてゆくほど
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.06,0:23:05.25,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}立ち止まることが怖くて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.35,0:23:12.18,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}早くなる鼓動に触れココに居ると確かめた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.59,0:23:20.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}ココロの奥の小さな声に耳を澄ましたら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.31,0:23:29.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}{\be5}包み込む世界が晴れ広がるよ明日へ
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------EDCN-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.80,0:22:19.88,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}就要墜入夢鄉之前
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.19,0:22:23.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}把什麼放在了手邊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.02,0:22:29.59,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}明明不想忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.77,0:22:31.75,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}卻又無法想起
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.20,0:22:35.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}時而浮現在記憶角落裡的往日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.58,0:22:39.26,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}輕輕染上歲月的痕跡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.32,0:22:46.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}一縱即逝　漸行漸離
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.12,0:22:55.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}氣喘吁吁地奔跑又是為何
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.30,0:23:01.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}愈是加快步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.06,0:23:05.25,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}就愈是畏懼停下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.35,0:23:12.18,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}撫摸加速的心跳確認了自己的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.59,0:23:20.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}側耳傾聽　那微弱的心聲
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.31,0:23:29.95,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}{\be5}卻發現　天高海闊　直至未來
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------TEXT-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.80,0:01:37.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣嗎  你的母親…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.35,0:01:39.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.01,0:01:41.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是你的錯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.82,0:01:42.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.37,0:01:43.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少自以為是了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.99,0:01:46.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湯乃鷺全體的危機
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.81,0:01:49.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼可能是你這樣一個小鬼的責任
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.78,0:01:51.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掂掂自己份量吧  呆子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.55,0:01:53.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.72,0:01:56.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起…
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.14,0:02:16.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡不著嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.08,0:02:23.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生才是  果然椅子不能消除疲勞吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.31,0:02:25.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就代替我去床上…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.13,0:02:28.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就和小民兩個人了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.34,0:02:32.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但小民可能也不討厭那樣…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.27,0:02:32.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.61,0:02:34.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.44,0:02:35.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的  沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.84,0:02:38.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡說不定能睡得很舒適
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.06,0:02:50.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生有女朋友嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.84,0:02:55.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之…現在還沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.16,0:02:57.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.45,0:03:02.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然不是很擅長和女性相處
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.11,0:03:05.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我覺得你是個好人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.02,0:03:08.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以請相信自己  雪願吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.00,0:03:09.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.77,0:03:19.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊  還以為你是因為伯母的事才沮喪的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.63,0:03:21.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來根本原因是男朋友的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.78,0:03:24.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.49,0:03:27.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖說我要是回應得正確的話
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.22,0:03:29.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在說不定已經是我男朋友了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.49,0:03:30.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.46,0:03:32.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜中了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.45,0:03:35.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都說不是了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.26,0:03:37.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼就是不相信呀
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.42,0:03:40.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你雖然嘴上很會說
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.82,0:03:43.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你那張臉表達得更多
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.02,0:03:46.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去睡了  晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.63,0:04:03.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要誘拐松前皋月
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.64,0:04:04.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.26,0:04:08.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松前皋月不打算去喜翠莊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.40,0:04:11.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以決定用武力綁她回去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.69,0:04:12.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.59,0:04:13.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請看這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.09,0:04:18.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡就是松前皋月工作的大樓
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.74,0:04:20.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從車站這條路線考慮的話
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.68,0:04:22.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這個小巷裡埋伏
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.25,0:04:24.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將她一口氣帶走
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.39,0:04:25.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,運送車輛也有了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.42,0:04:26.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊也有三個人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.07,0:04:30.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也應該能封住松前皋月的蠻力了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.47,0:04:31.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位覺得如何
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.89,0:04:33.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼如何…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.16,0:04:34.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.45,0:04:38.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝  徹先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.40,0:04:39.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以是可以  但有條件
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.35,0:04:40.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.02,0:04:44.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個叫孝一的人也一起帶去喜翠莊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.96,0:04:45.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.32,0:04:47.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.93,0:04:50.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是讓我們參加誘拐的條件
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.45,0:04:52.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.50,0:04:53.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  民子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.93,0:04:55.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在緒花把孝一帶來之前
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.80,0:04:58.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我們先去觀光東京吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.68,0:05:00.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是早餐…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.91,0:05:02.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別再吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.93,0:05:05.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了這種紙片一樣的麵包也毫無意義
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.58,0:05:08.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,東京可是存在著許多被稱為名店的館子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.97,0:05:11.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為客人  用舌頭去記憶也是很重要的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.30,0:05:13.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.55,0:05:23.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您撥打的電話不在服務區…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.45,0:05:28.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是生氣了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.03,0:05:30.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天的事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.19,0:05:32.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶阿孝一起走什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.66,0:05:36.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道該用什麼表情去見他啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.04,0:05:40.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是一個人又誘拐不了媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.44,0:05:44.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？為什麼交換條件是阿孝啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.31,0:05:47.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔細想想…不
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.42,0:05:49.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算不仔細想也很奇怪呀
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.88,0:05:59.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聯繫不上誒
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.92,0:06:01.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也去過打工的地方了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.62,0:06:04.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然不在也沒辦法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.68,0:06:07.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是  就是嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.13,0:06:09.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該做的都做了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.72,0:06:11.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生也會原諒我的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.99,0:06:14.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是緒花…小姐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.70,0:06:21.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果沒有那個意思的話
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.27,0:06:24.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把他解放吧  解放孝一君
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.05,0:06:25.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解放？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.53,0:06:28.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯  解放
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.20,0:06:32.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這說得真是難聽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.64,0:06:34.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又沒把阿孝…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.18,0:06:37.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖說是打算誘拐一下…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.97,0:06:40.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在嘀嘀咕咕說什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.08,0:06:41.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很噁心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.06,0:06:45.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說的解放是指心理上的解放
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.52,0:06:50.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順帶一提  我們現在所坐著的長椅
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.76,0:06:54.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡就是我向孝一君告白的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.91,0:06:56.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.89,0:06:59.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.88,0:07:02.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經有喜歡的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.39,0:07:05.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是在交往了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.12,0:07:08.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  暫時還沒有給我答覆
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.86,0:07:11.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒  那算什麼  太過分了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.77,0:07:15.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…我覺得她大概是沒有那個意思吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.45,0:07:19.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許是我擅自在等她
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.32,0:07:20.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.15,0:07:20.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.95,0:07:24.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正我也習慣等待了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.76,0:07:31.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且要是我不照顧著她  那傢伙總是讓人不放心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.31,0:07:36.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太狡猾了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.32,0:07:39.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在玩弄孝一君的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.76,0:07:42.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也喜歡的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.79,0:07:44.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也對阿孝…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.92,0:07:46.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是作為異性
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.34,0:07:48.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是作為人類…什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.16,0:07:50.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算說這些打發人的話嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.69,0:07:51.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.87,0:07:54.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是如何喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.41,0:07:57.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個…那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.04,0:08:01.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為人…作為一個生物喜歡！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.28,0:08:02.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.55,0:08:10.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個人…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.69,0:08:13.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.95,0:08:16.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.32,0:08:19.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十嵐小姐  你在做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.19,0:08:20.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休息已經結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.58,0:08:23.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  馬上就來
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.43,0:08:26.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的你就自己判斷吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.22,0:08:31.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你再踐踏孝一君的溫柔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.72,0:08:34.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會原諒你的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.96,0:08:43.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一彎  就前面往右轉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.84,0:08:44.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.34,0:08:49.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像約會一樣…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.63,0:08:54.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.22,0:08:56.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我開動了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.73,0:09:00.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快  吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.21,0:09:01.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.00,0:09:07.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別剩下一粒飯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.13,0:09:13.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才的燒烤
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.39,0:09:15.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是通過五分熟的火候來強調口感的變化嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.56,0:09:19.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是考慮到上菜的時機和餘熱的時間…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.91,0:09:19.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}好難受
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.45,0:09:22.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吐了  就算吐了還得吃
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.77,0:09:24.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易來了東京
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.08,0:09:27.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名店的味道必須一一記住
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.73,0:09:31.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花的事只是順便  順便
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.05,0:09:40.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我所居住的  阿孝也在的城市
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.55,0:09:44.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾經很討厭的無聊的城市
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.17,0:09:49.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個女生…是個好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.02,0:09:54.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像那樣認真  直爽的說出來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.29,0:09:56.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也能直視著對方
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.41,0:10:00.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但要到旅館裡去生活  感覺突然很有戲劇性了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.16,0:10:04.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果說有我們出演的電視劇的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.33,0:10:06.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反面角色
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.54,0:10:08.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許就是我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.51,0:10:13.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（來電：阿孝）
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.43,0:10:20.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}一號線電車車門即將關閉 請注意
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.44,0:10:21.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.88,0:10:22.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.11,0:10:25.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  害你打了這麼多次電話
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.73,0:10:26.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直在睡覺
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.94,0:10:29.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛  那就好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.48,0:10:32.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打工的人聯繫過我了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.12,0:10:36.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說你來過書店了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.95,0:10:40.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…怎麼說呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.72,0:10:42.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碰巧？不知不覺就…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.62,0:10:48.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呀…就和那時的我一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.24,0:10:50.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時的？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.57,0:10:51.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.95,0:10:54.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在之前放假的時候  去你那邊了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.17,0:10:56.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那邊…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.74,0:11:00.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去找人而闖入婚禮現場的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.76,0:11:10.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本想去一趟喜翠莊的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.73,0:11:13.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是看你挺忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.38,0:11:15.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.12,0:11:17.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花？能聽見嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.24,0:11:21.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反面角色…就是我了…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.68,0:11:25.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.75,0:11:28.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須要帶媽媽回喜翠莊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.08,0:11:32.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為此必須把阿孝也帶回去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.22,0:11:33.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？那算什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.14,0:11:35.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不明白你的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.19,0:11:37.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就給阿孝打了電話
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.13,0:11:41.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個時候明明已經被阿孝所救
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.68,0:11:44.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可這次又想讓阿孝來救我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.61,0:11:47.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想著加油吧  雪願吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.76,0:11:51.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直只想著自己的事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.46,0:11:54.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些照顧著自己
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.58,0:11:56.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為自己加油的人的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.65,0:11:57.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從沒有想過
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.41,0:12:00.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我大概是最差勁的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.94,0:12:03.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你不用來的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.38,0:12:07.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然不太明白
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.42,0:12:10.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.56,0:12:11.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會去的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.45,0:12:13.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.61,0:12:14.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次見
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.01,0:12:15.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.00,0:12:28.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝一直都照顧著最差勁的我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.04,0:12:31.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儘管如此  那個時候也是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.13,0:12:33.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個時候也是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.66,0:12:36.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明說了下次見
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.78,0:12:39.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他卻沒有回答下次見
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.04,0:12:42.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是沒有下次了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.87,0:12:47.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能哭
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.64,0:12:50.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最想哭的不是我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.45,0:12:53.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.42,0:13:08.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪洞…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.00,0:13:16.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全吐了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.61,0:13:17.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.05,0:13:19.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來是壽司
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.20,0:13:20.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.42,0:13:30.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.16,0:13:32.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…壽司呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.54,0:13:34.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿著
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.57,0:13:38.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來抓個什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.60,0:13:43.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷靜不下來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.66,0:13:47.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花她和其他男性見面
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.91,0:13:54.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明離開還不到半年
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.58,0:13:56.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卻覺得是那麼的懷念
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.22,0:13:58.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最討厭的城市
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.43,0:14:00.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.30,0:14:02.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯獨喜歡這個時間
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.23,0:14:04.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像雪洞一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.97,0:14:07.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎一直通向未來的燈光
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.90,0:14:09.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不光是我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.72,0:14:11.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各種人都有自己的願望
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.74,0:14:15.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝也有  媽媽也有
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.64,0:14:17.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定有他們的願望
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.87,0:14:20.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我傷害了阿孝
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.61,0:14:24.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝為了我而雪願
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.76,0:14:27.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被媽媽傷害了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.58,0:14:31.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是媽媽也一定是在雪願
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.66,0:14:35.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都懷著自己的想法努力著
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.99,0:14:37.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要閃耀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.45,0:14:39.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上啊  上啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.97,0:14:42.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次一定要抓到
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.84,0:14:45.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯  輕輕地
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.26,0:14:48.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住那個的繩子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.12,0:14:49.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想問他
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.80,0:14:53.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生抓到那個娃娃的話
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.80,0:14:57.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  慢慢來  慢慢來
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.66,0:14:58.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓到的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.18,0:15:00.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生的心情…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.12,0:15:06.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.00,0:15:07.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.59,0:15:09.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.43,0:15:11.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花  怎麼樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.36,0:15:14.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…孝一呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.55,0:15:15.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.51,0:15:17.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？不幹了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.59,0:15:20.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不能把阿孝帶走
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.37,0:15:24.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我也完全沒考慮過媽媽的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.81,0:15:25.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.65,0:15:25.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}喂  我說你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.49,0:15:27.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在在哪兒
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.83,0:15:31.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行李呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.87,0:15:32.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這些
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.78,0:15:36.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害  快能開店了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.22,0:15:38.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是用來當作手信的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.70,0:15:41.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.93,0:15:44.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擅自做了決定
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.24,0:15:45.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去伯母那裡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.29,0:15:46.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.73,0:15:49.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算不打算誘拐了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.54,0:15:51.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也贊同過了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.53,0:15:54.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不把喜翠莊的事好好和伯母說一說
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.01,0:15:56.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們也不能消氣
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.60,0:16:03.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又自以為是地雪願了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.47,0:16:07.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.07,0:16:09.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來帶路
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.69,0:16:22.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.64,0:16:23.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那棟大樓
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.17,0:16:27.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.01,0:16:30.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天怎麼那麼晚
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.56,0:16:35.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這行李是怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.19,0:16:38.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  難道是喜翠莊的人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.53,0:16:41.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然還接送  真走運
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.93,0:16:43.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是說了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.37,0:16:45.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要帶我回去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.77,0:16:47.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然請到假了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.62,0:16:49.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心想就去泡泡溫泉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.32,0:17:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的興趣不錯嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.10,0:17:03.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們公司能搞到演唱會的門票哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.25,0:17:04.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.97,0:17:06.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.11,0:17:08.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都那麼拜託了還拒絕了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.49,0:17:11.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以啊  請到假了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.83,0:17:14.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湯乃鷺那邊正好可以避暑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.43,0:17:16.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫什麼來著  那個新建的旅館
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.72,0:17:18.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湯乃鷺Cirrus嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.49,0:17:21.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對  那邊已經是大人氣
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.21,0:17:23.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不預約就不能入住了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.08,0:17:26.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜翠莊的話永遠都是可以臨時入住的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.95,0:17:27.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.89,0:17:31.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道說是能從湯乃鷺Cirrus拿到錢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.83,0:17:32.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才寫了那樣的報導…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.88,0:17:34.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了…別在意那麼多
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.65,0:17:35.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在意啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.92,0:17:38.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是說要好好說一說嗎  徹先生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.25,0:17:42.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都要來喜翠莊了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.03,0:17:44.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之後再慢慢…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.83,0:17:45.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.00,0:17:47.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起好好喝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.00,0:17:48.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹君
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.48,0:17:53.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說不定是喜歡年長的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.02,0:17:55.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是說…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.37,0:17:57.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是喜歡這個家族的…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.15,0:18:00.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說來啊  緒花
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.52,0:18:02.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見到阿孝了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.86,0:18:05.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿孝是指孝一嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.73,0:18:08.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對  是緒花的男朋友哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.72,0:18:10.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.70,0:18:14.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  這首也喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.77,0:18:24.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小民
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.58,0:18:26.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.51,0:18:29.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為謝禮  這個給你…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.35,0:18:30.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.77,0:18:33.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是徹先生的努力
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.07,0:18:39.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生比預想的要好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.18,0:18:40.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.23,0:18:42.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更正！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.23,0:18:44.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然努力了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.74,0:18:46.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就那樣而已
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.21,0:18:54.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要來一支嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.10,0:18:57.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是廚師  不能抽煙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.08,0:18:59.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真認真
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.10,0:19:03.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…為什麼改變主意了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.04,0:19:04.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要來喜翠莊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.96,0:19:06.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才不是說過了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.28,0:19:07.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是真話吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.30,0:19:13.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就比緒花大沒幾歲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.30,0:19:15.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹君真成熟
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.11,0:19:18.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.56,0:19:21.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被緒花猛猛地訓了一頓
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.98,0:19:24.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像想起來了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.10,0:19:28.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也和緒花  說過一樣的話
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.54,0:19:32.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽你什麼都不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.89,0:19:34.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽總是工作
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.96,0:19:37.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都忍耐著
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.39,0:19:41.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能吵架
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.59,0:19:48.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  比起我的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.92,0:19:51.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我母親的工作更偉大些
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.68,0:19:54.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是用什麼樣的心情去寫的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.50,0:19:58.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貶低自家的報導
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.55,0:20:03.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寫報導時候沒有瞎編亂造
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.19,0:20:07.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那旅館10年如一日
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.69,0:20:10.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光憑想像能寫嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.69,0:20:12.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正肯定是沒變化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.87,0:20:15.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…追求新穎並不是唯一…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.97,0:20:16.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.50,0:20:19.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外表不管怎麼裝飾
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.73,0:20:21.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的還是本質
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.15,0:20:24.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對客人的照料
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.06,0:20:26.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,招待的細緻程度
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.93,0:20:28.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,並沒有錯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.56,0:20:32.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯  媽媽總是做得正確
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.06,0:20:36.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過我覺得緒花也是挺幸運的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.21,0:20:40.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有個不總是做得正確的媽媽不也挺好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.02,0:20:41.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.12,0:20:43.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹先生
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.16,0:20:48.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔  差不多出發吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.47,0:20:49.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.17,0:20:54.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是話說回來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.19,0:20:56.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花她真是奇怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.77,0:20:59.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開口就是為喜翠莊的事生氣
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.29,0:21:02.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是覺得還有更應該生氣的事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.55,0:21:08.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼不去夜逃回到東京卻不聯繫她呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.38,0:21:11.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.14,0:21:13.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然一直搬來搬去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.96,0:21:16.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但最近終於安穩下來了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.25,0:21:19.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心想該聯繫了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.77,0:21:21.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花卻先自己過來了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.74,0:21:24.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緒花要回來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.22,0:21:26.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在睡覺吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.81,0:21:28.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才說的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.01,0:21:38.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼我一直沒想過要回東京呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.06,0:21:41.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明東京有阿孝在
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.03,0:21:46.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是就算回東京
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.72,0:21:49.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也已經不能和阿孝回到以前那樣的關係了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.61,0:21:51.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回不到了…
Comment: 0,0:00:00.05,0:00:00.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.11,0:23:34.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要在這種時候才擺出母親的架勢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.09,0:23:36.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1}讓我好好看看這家旅館的優點吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.96,0:23:36.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3}媽媽也有雪願！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.88,0:23:38.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了一個夢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.07,0:23:41.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽還真是輕啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
